<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...93W</bibcode>
			<title>The California Planet Survey. III. A Possible 2:1 Resonance in the Exoplanetary Triple System HD 37124</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Isaacson, H.; Fischer, D. A.; Spronck, J.; Anderson, J.; Valenti, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. 93 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...93W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...16J</bibcode>
			<title>Retired a Stars and Their Companions. VI. A Pair of Interacting Exoplanet Pairs Around the Subgiants 24 Sextanis and HD 200964</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Payne, Matthew; Howard, Andrew W.; Clubb, Kelsey I.; Ford, Eric B.; Bowler, Brendan P.; Henry, Gregory W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Brewer, John M.; Schwab, Christian; Reffert, Sabine; Lowe, Thomas B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 1, article id. 16 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...16J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..396B</bibcode>
			<title>Retired A Stars and Their Companions. III. Comparing the Mass-Period Distributions of Planets Around A-Type Stars and Sun-Like Stars</title>
			<authors>Bowler, Brendan P.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Henry, Gregory W.; Peek, Kathryn M. G.; Fischer, Debra A.; Clubb, Kelsey I.; Liu, Michael C.; Reffert, Sabine; Schwab, Christian; Lowe, Thomas B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 396-410 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..396B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AJ....135..209M</bibcode>
			<title>Rotational and Radial Velocities for a Sample of 761 HIPPARCOS Giants and the Role of Binarity</title>
			<authors>Massarotti, Alessandro; Latham, David W.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Fogel, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 135, Issue 1, pp. 209-231 (2008).</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AJ....135..209M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;AS..114..269D</bibcode>
			<title>Vitesses radiales. Catalogue WEB: Wilson Evans Batten. Subtittle: Radial velocities: The Wilson-Evans-Batten catalogue.</title>
			<authors>Duflot, M.; Figon, P.; Meyssonnier, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.114, p.269</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26AS..114..269D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990BICDS..38...13B</bibcode>
			<title>Flamsteed stars not contained in the Yale "Catalogue of Bright Stars"</title>
			<authors>Bidelman, W. P.</authors>
			<journal>Bull. Inf. Centre Donnees Stellaires, Vol. 38, p.13</journal>
			<date>12/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990BICDS..38...13B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986PASP...98..423E</bibcode>
			<title>Hyades and Sirius supercluster members brighter than magnitude (V) 7.1. II - Right ascension six to twelve hours</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 98, April 1986, p. 423-441.</journal>
			<date>4/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986PASP...98..423E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1974AJ.....79..682H</bibcode>
			<title>MK classification for F- and G-type stars. III.</title>
			<authors>Harlan, E. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astron. J., Vol. 79, p. 682 - 686 = Lick Obs. Bull., No. 655</journal>
			<date>6/1974</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1974AJ.....79..682H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1970ApJS...19..387A</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of Indidual Radial Velocities, 0h-12h, Measured by Astronomers of the Mount Wilson Observatory</title>
			<authors>Abt, Helmut A.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement, vol. 19, p.387 (1970)</journal>
			<date>1/1970</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1970ApJS...19..387A</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
