<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..195....3F</bibcode>
			<title>The Spitzer Infrared Spectrograph Survey of T Tauri Stars in Taurus</title>
			<authors>Furlan, E.; Luhman, K. L.; Espaillat, C.; D'Alessio, P.; Adame, L.; Manoj, P.; Kim, K. H.; Watson, Dan M.; Forrest, W. J.; McClure, M. K.; Calvet, N.; Sargent, B. A.; Green, J. D.; Fischer, W. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 195, Issue 1, article id. 3 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..195....3F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..29R</bibcode>
			<title>The Ultra Cool Brown Dwarf Companion of WD 0806-661B: Age, Mass, and Formation Mechanism</title>
			<authors>Rodriguez, David R.; Zuckerman, B.; Melis, Carl; Song, Inseok</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..29R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...39B</bibcode>
			<title>A Keck LGS AO Search for Brown Dwarf and Planetary Mass Companions to Upper Scorpius Brown Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Biller, Beth; Allers, Katelyn; Liu, Michael; Close, Laird M.; Dupuy, Trent</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. 39 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...39B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726L...3A</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Spectroscopy of the Circumprimary Disk in the Binary Brown Dwarf 2MASS J04414489+2301513</title>
			<authors>Adame, Luc&#237;a; Calvet, Nuria; Luhman, K. L.; D'Alessio, Paola; Furlan, Elise; McClure, M. K.; Hartmann, Lee; Forrest, William J.; Watson, Dan M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id. L3 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726L...3A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721L.177C</bibcode>
			<title>High-contrast 3.8 mum Imaging of the Brown Dwarf/Planet-mass Companion to GJ 758</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Bailey, Vanessa; Fabrycky, Daniel; Murray-Clay, Ruth; Rodigas, Timothy; Hinz, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. L177-L181 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...721L.177C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714L..84T</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Planetary-mass Companion to a Brown Dwarf in Taurus</title>
			<authors>Todorov, K.; Luhman, K. L.; McLeod, K. K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. L84-L88 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714L..84T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..186..111L</bibcode>
			<title>The Disk Population of the Taurus Star-Forming Region</title>
			<authors>Luhman, K. L.; Allen, P. R.; Espaillat, C.; Hartmann, L.; Calvet, N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 186, Issue 1, pp. 111-174 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..186..111L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704..531K</bibcode>
			<title>The Coevality of Young Binary Systems</title>
			<authors>Kraus, Adam L.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 1, pp. 531-547 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704..531K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..399L</bibcode>
			<title>An Infrared/X-Ray Survey for New Members of the Taurus Star-Forming Region</title>
			<authors>Luhman, K. L.; Mamajek, E. E.; Allen, P. R.; Cruz, K. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 399-419 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662..413K</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Mass and Environment in Multiple-Star Formation: A 2MASS Survey of Wide Multiplicity in Three Young Associations</title>
			<authors>Kraus, Adam L.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 1, pp. 413-430.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662..413K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...645..676L</bibcode>
			<title>The Spatial Distribution of Brown Dwarfs in Taurus</title>
			<authors>Luhman, K. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 645, Issue 1, pp. 676-687.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...645..676L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
