<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..72L</bibcode>
			<title>Sparse aperture masking at the VLT. I. Faint companion detection limits for the two debris disk stars HD 92945 and HD 141569</title>
			<authors>Lacour, S.; Tuthill, P.; Amico, P.; Ireland, M.; Ehrenreich, D.; Huelamo, N.; Lagrange, A.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A72</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..72L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528L..15B</bibcode>
			<title>High angular resolution detection of beta Pictoris b at 2.18 mum</title>
			<authors>Bonnefoy, M.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Boccaletti, A.; Chauvin, G.; Apai, D.; Allard, F.; Ehrenreich, D.; Girard, J. H. V.; Mouillet, D.; Rouan, D.; Gratadour, D.; Kasper, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.L15</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528L..15B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729..139W</bibcode>
			<title>The Gemini NICI Planet-finding Campaign: Discovery of a Substellar L Dwarf Companion to the Nearby Young M Dwarf CD-35 2722</title>
			<authors>Wahhaj, Zahed; Liu, Michael C.; Biller, Beth A.; Clarke, Fraser; Nielsen, Eric L.; Close, Laird M.; Hayward, Thomas L.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Cushing, Michael; Dupuy, Trent; Tecza, Matthias; Thatte, Niranjan; Chun, Mark; Ftaclas, Christ; Hartung, Markus; Reid, I. Neill; Shkolnik, Evgenya L.; Alencar, Silvia H. P.; Artymowicz, Pawel; Boss, Alan; de Gouveia Dal Pino, Elisabethe; Gregorio-Hetem, Jane; Ida, Shigeru; Kuchner, Marc; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Toomey, Douglas W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 139 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729..139W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729..128C</bibcode>
			<title>A Combined Subaru/VLT/MMT 1-5 mum Study of Planets Orbiting HR 8799: Implications for Atmospheric Properties, Masses, and Formation</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Burrows, Adam; Itoh, Yoichi; Matsumura, Soko; Fukagawa, Misato; Apai, Daniel; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Hinz, Philip M.; Rodigas, T. J.; Kasper, Markus; Pyo, T.-S.; Ogino, Satoshi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 128 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729..128C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.468.1080M</bibcode>
			<title>Images of a fourth planet orbiting HR 8799</title>
			<authors>Marois, Christian; Zuckerman, B.; Konopacky, Quinn M.; Macintosh, Bruce; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 468, Issue 7327, pp. 1080-1083 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Natur.468.1080M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1405B</bibcode>
			<title>Clouds in the Coldest Brown Dwarfs: Fire Spectroscopy of Ross 458C</title>
			<authors>Burgasser, Adam J.; Simcoe, Robert A.; Bochanski, John J.; Saumon, Didier; Mamajek, Eric E.; Cushing, Michael C.; Marley, Mark S.; McMurtry, Craig; Pipher, Judith L.; Forrest, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1405-1420 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1405B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724....1S</bibcode>
			<title>The Search for Planetary Mass Companions to Field Brown Dwarfs with HST/NICMOS</title>
			<authors>