<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..131D</bibcode>
			<title>Transitional Disks as Signposts of Young, Multiplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Salyk, Colette</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 131 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..131D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..33C</bibcode>
			<title>A 5 mum Image of beta Pictoris b at a Sub-Jupiter Projected Separation: Evidence for a Misalignment Between the Planet and the Inner, Warped Disk</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Thalmann, Christian; Matsumura, Soko; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Burrows, Adam; Kuchner, Marc</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L33 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..33C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..32Q</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for Gas Giant Planets on Solar System Scales: VLT NACO/APP Observations of the Debris Disk Host Stars HD172555 and HD115892</title>
			<authors>Quanz, Sascha P.; Kenworthy, Matthew A.; Meyer, Michael R.; Girard, Julien H. V.; Kasper, Markus</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L32 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..32Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...89J</bibcode>
			<title>High-contrast Imaging Search for Planets and Brown Dwarfs around the Most Massive Stars in the Solar Neighborhood</title>
			<authors>Janson, Markus; Bonavita, Mariangela; Klahr, Hubert; Lafreni&#232;re, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; Zinnecker, Hans</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. 89 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...89J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..79S</bibcode>
			<title>Defining and cataloging exoplanets: the exoplanet.eu database</title>
			<authors>Schneider, J.; Dedieu, C.; Le Sidaner, P.; Savalle, R.; Zolotukhin, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A79</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..79S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..72L</bibcode>
			<title>Sparse aperture masking at the VLT. I. Faint companion detection limits for the two debris disk stars HD 92945 and HD 141569</title>
			<authors>Lacour, S.; Tuthill, P.; Amico, P.; Ireland, M.; Ehrenreich, D.; Huelamo, N.; Lagrange, A.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A72</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..72L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A...6S</bibcode>
			<title>Estimation of the XUV radiation onto close planets and their evaporation</title>
			<authors>Sanz-Forcada, J.; Micela, G.; Ribas, I.; Pollock, A. M. T.; Eiroa, C.; Velasco, A.; Solano, E.; Garc&#237;a-&#193;lvarez, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A6</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A...6S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...30G</bibcode>
			<title>Hubble and Spitzer Space Telescope Observations of the Debris Disk around the nearby K Dwarf HD 92945</title>
			<authors>Golimowski, D. A.; Krist, J. E.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Chen, C. H.; Ardila, D. R.; Bryden, G.; Clampin, M.; Ford, H. C.; Illingworth, G. D.; Plavchan, P.; Rieke, G. H.; Su, K. Y. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 1, article id. 30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142...30G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733..126C</bibcode>
			<title>Estimates of the Planet Yield from Ground-based High-contrast Imaging Observations as a Function of Stellar Mass</title>
			<authors>Crepp, Justin R.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. 126 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733..126C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...65B</bibcode>
			<title>Clouds and Chemistry in the Atmosphere of Extrasolar Planet HR8799b</title>
			<authors>Barman, Travis S.; Macintosh, Bruce; Konopacky, Quinn M.; Marois, Christian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 65 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..29R</bibcode>
			<title>The Ultra Cool Brown Dwarf Companion of WD 0806-661B: Age, Mass, and Formation Mechanism</title>
			<authors>Rodriguez, David R.; Zuckerman, B.; Melis, Carl; Song, Inseok</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..29R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732..107S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence Against an Edge-on Disk Around the Extrasolar Planet, 2MASS 1207 b and a New Thick-cloud Explanation for Its Underluminosity</title>
			<authors>Skemer, Andrew J.; Close, Laird M.; Szucs, L&#225;szl&#243;; Apai, D&#225;niel; Pascucci, Ilaria; Biller, Beth A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. 107 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732..107S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528L..15B</bibcode>
			<title>High angular resolution detection of beta Pictoris b at 2.18 mum</title>
			<authors>Bonnefoy, M.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Boccaletti, A.; Chauvin, G.; Apai, D.; Allard, F.; Ehrenreich, D.; Girard, J. H. V.; Mouillet, D.; Rouan, D.; Gratadour, D.; Kasper, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.L15</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528L..15B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A.134B</bibcode>
			<title>VLT/NACO astrometry of the HR 8799 planetary system. L'-band observations of the three outer planets</title>
			<authors>Bergfors, C.; Brandner, W.; Janson, M.; K&#246;hler, R.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A134</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A.134B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...42L</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of an ~23 M Jup Brown Dwarf Orbiting ~700 AU from the Massive Star HIP 78530 in Upper Scorpius</title>
			<authors>Lafreni&#232;re, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; Janson, Markus; Helling, Christiane; Witte, Soeren; Hauschildt, Peter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. 42 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...42L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.468.1080M</bibcode>
			<title>Images of a fourth planet orbiting HR 8799</title>
			<authors>Marois, Christian; Zuckerman, B.; Konopacky, Quinn M.; Macintosh, Bruce; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 468, Issue 7327, pp. 1080-1083 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Natur.468.1080M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724....1S</bibcode>
			<title>The Search for Planetary Mass Companions to Field Brown Dwarfs with HST/NICMOS</title>
			<authors>Stumpf, M. B.; Brandner, W.; Joergens, V.; Henning, Th.; Bouy, H.; K&#246; hler, R.; Kasper, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. 1-11 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724....1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523L...1M</bibcode>
			<title>Direct detection of a substellar companion to the young nearby star PZ Telescopii</title>
			<authors>Mugrauer, M.; Vogt, N.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Schmidt, T. O. B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.L1</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523L...1M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722L..49Q</bibcode>
			<title>First Results from Very Large Telescope NACO Apodizing Phase Plate: 4 mum Images of The Exoplanet beta Pictoris b</title>
			<authors>Quanz, Sascha P.; Meyer, Michael R.; Kenworthy, Matthew A.; Girard, Julien H. V.; Kasper, Markus; Lagrange, Anne-Marie; Apai, Daniel; Boccaletti, Anthony; Bonnefoy, Micka&#235;l; Chauvin, Gael; Hinz, Philip M.; Lenzen, Rainer</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. L49-L53 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722L..49Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407...71V</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric characterization of exoplanets using angular and spectral differential imaging</title>
			<authors>Vigan, A.; Moutou, C.; Langlois, M.; Allard, F.; Boccaletti, A.; Carbillet, M.; Mouillet, D.; Smith, I.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 1, pp. 71-82.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407...71V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...329...57L</bibcode>
			<title>A Giant Planet Imaged in the Disk of the Young Star beta Pictoris</title>
			<authors>Lagrange, A.-M.; Bonnefoy, M.; Chauvin, G.; Apai, D.; Ehrenreich, D.; Boccaletti, A.; Gratadour, D.; Rouan, D.; Mouillet, D.; Lacour, S.; Kasper, M.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 329, Issue 5987, pp. 57- (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...329...57L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;ARv..18..317A</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and evolution of planetary systems: the impact of high-angular resolution optical techniques</title>
			<authors>Absil, Olivier; Mawet, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomy and Astrophysics Review, Volume 18, Issue 3, pp.317-382</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26ARv..18..317A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..52B</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared integral-field spectra of the planet/brown dwarf companion AB Pictoris b</title>
			<authors>Bonnefoy, M.; Chauvin, G.; Rojo, P.; Allard, F.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Homeier, D.; Dumas, C.; Beuzit, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A52</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..52B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010RAA....10..189D</bibcode>
			<title>High-contrast coronagraph for ground-based imaging of Jupiter-like planets</title>
			<authors>Dou, Jiang-Pei; Ren, De-Qing; Zhu, Yong-Tian</authors>
			<journal>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 10, Issue 2, pp. 189-198 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010RAA....10..189D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401.2587C</bibcode>
			<title>The effects of opacity on gravitational stability in protoplanetary discs</title>
			<authors>Cossins, Peter; Lodato, Giuseppe; Clarke, Cathie</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 4, pp. 2587-2598.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401.2587C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...511L...8S</bibcode>
			<title>A scenario of planet erosion by coronal radiation</title>
			<authors>Sanz-Forcada, J.; Ribas, I.; Micela, G.; Pollock, A. M. T.; Garc&#237;a-&#193; lvarez, D.; Solano, E.; Eiroa, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 511, id.L8</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...511L...8S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..396B</bibcode>
			<title>Retired A Stars and Their Companions. III. Comparing the Mass-Period Distributions of Planets Around A-Type Stars and Sun-Like Stars</title>
			<authors>Bowler, Brendan P.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Henry, Gregory W.; Peek, Kathryn M. G.; Fischer, Debra A.; Clubb, Kelsey I.; Liu, Michael C.; Reffert, Sabine; Schwab, Christian; Lowe, Thomas B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 396-410 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..396B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A..52C</bibcode>
			<title>Deep imaging survey of young, nearby austral stars . VLT/NACO near-infrared Lyot-coronographic observations</title>
			<authors>Chauvin, G.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Bonavita, M.; Zuckerman, B.; Dumas, C.; Bessell, M. S.; Beuzit, J.-L.; Bonnefoy, M.; Desidera, S.; Farihi, J.; Lowrance, P.; Mouillet, D.; Song, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A52</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A..52C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706L..41F</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Constraints on the beta Pic Inner Planet Candidate with Keck Adaptive Optics</title>
			<authors>Fitzgerald, Michael P.; Kalas, Paul G.; Graham, James R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. L41-L45 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706L..41F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..927L</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining the orbit of the possible companion to beta Pictoris. New deep imaging observations</title>
			<authors>Lagrange, A.-M.; Kasper, M.; Boccaletti, A.; Chauvin, G.; Gratadour, D.; Fusco, T.; Ehrenreich, D.; Apai, D.; Mouillet, D.; Rouan, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 2, 2009, pp.927-934</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..927L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.399..377J</bibcode>
			<title>Imaging search for the unseen companion to &amp;epsil Ind A - improving the detection limits with 4 mum observations</title>
			<authors>Janson, M.; Apai, D.; Zechmeister, M.; Brandner, W.; K&#252;rster, M.; Kasper, M.; Reffert, S.; Endl, M.; Lafreni&#232;re, D.; Gei&#223;ler, K.; Hippler, S.; Henning, Th.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 399, Issue 1, pp. 377-384.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.399..377J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Msngr.137....8K</bibcode>
			<title>Direct Imaging of Exoplanets and Brown Dwarfs with the VLT: NACO Pupil-stabilised Lyot Coronagraphy at 4 &#181;m</title>
			<authors>Kasper, Markus; Amico, Paola; Pompei, Emanuela; Ageorges, Nancy; Apai, Daniel; Argomedo, Javier; Kornweibel, Nick; Lidman, Chris</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 137, p. 8-13</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Msngr.137....8K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121..309J</bibcode>
			<title>International Year of Astronomy Invited Review on Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 878, pp.309-315</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121..309J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...497..557L</bibcode>
			<title>Is beta Pictoris b the transiting planet of November 1981?</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 497, Issue 2, 2009, pp.557-562</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...497..557L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1279S</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-Radius Relationships for Solid Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Seager, S.; Kuchner, M.; Hier-Majumder, C. A.; Militzer, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1279-1297.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1279S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AAS...205.1125M</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Substellar Companions of the Debris Disk Star &amp;epsil  Eridani with the Spitzer Space Telescope</title>
			<authors>Marengo, M.; Megeath, T.; Fazio, G.; Backman, D.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Warner, M.; Beichman, C.; Su, K.; Stansberry, J.; Rieke, G.; Hines, D.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society Meeting 205, #11.25; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 36, p.1356</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AAS...205.1125M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...600..804M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Flux of Extrasolar Dust in Earth's Atmosphere</title>
			<authors>Murray, N.; Weingartner, Joseph C.; Capobianco, C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 600, Issue 2, pp. 804-827.</journal>
			<date>1/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...600..804M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...584L..27W</bibcode>
			<title>The Inner Rings of beta Pictoris</title>
			<authors>Wahhaj, Z.; Koerner, D. W.; Ressler, M. E.; Werner, M. W.; Backman, D. E.; Sargent, A. I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 584, Issue 1, pp. L27-L31.</journal>
			<date>2/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...584L..27W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.333L..26N</bibcode>
			<title>Possible commensurabilities among pairs of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Nelson, Richard P.; Papaloizou, John C. B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 333, Issue 2, pp. L26-L30.</journal>
			<date>6/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.333L..26N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...553..410K</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Encounters with the beta Pictoris Planetesimal System</title>
			<authors>Kalas, Paul; Deltorn, Jean-Marc; Larwood, John</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 553, Issue 1, pp. 410-420.</journal>
			<date>5/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...553..410K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997MNRAS.292..896M</bibcode>
			<title>A planet on an inclined orbit as an explanation of the warp in the Beta Pictoris disc</title>
			<authors>Mouillet, D.; Larwood, J. D.; Papaloizou, J. C. B.; Lagrange, A. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, vol. 292, p. 896</journal>
			<date>12/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997MNRAS.292..896M</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar />
</planet>
