<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745..174S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectral and Photometric Diagnostics of Giant Planet Formation Scenarios</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 2, article id. 174 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745..174S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745....5K</bibcode>
			<title>LkCa 15: A Young Exoplanet Caught at Formation?</title>
			<authors>Kraus, Adam L.; Ireland, Michael J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 5 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745....5K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743L..17D</bibcode>
			<title>On the Misalignment of the Directly Imaged Planet beta Pictoris b with the System's Warped Inner Disk</title>
			<authors>Dawson, Rebekah I.; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. L17 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743L..17D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..148B</bibcode>
			<title>A Disk around the Planetary-mass Companion GSC 06214-00210 b: Clues about the Formation of Gas Giants on Wide Orbits</title>
			<authors>Bowler, Brendan P.; Liu, Michael C.; Kraus, Adam L.; Mann, Andrew W.; Ireland, Michael J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 148 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..148B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..131D</bibcode>
			<title>Transitional Disks as Signposts of Young, Multiplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Salyk, Colette</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 131 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..131D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..33C</bibcode>
			<title>A 5 mum Image of beta Pictoris b at a Sub-Jupiter Projected Separation: Evidence for a Misalignment Between the Planet and the Inner, Warped Disk</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Thalmann, Christian; Matsumura, Soko; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Burrows, Adam; Kuchner, Marc</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L33 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..33C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..32Q</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for Gas Giant Planets on Solar System Scales: VLT NACO/APP Observations of the Debris Disk Host Stars HD172555 and HD115892</title>
			<authors>Quanz, Sascha P.; Kenworthy, Matthew A.; Meyer, Michael R.; Girard, Julien H. V.; Kasper, Markus</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L32 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..32Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...89J</bibcode>
			<title>High-contrast Imaging Search for Planets and Brown Dwarfs around the Most Massive Stars in the Solar Neighborhood</title>
			<authors>