<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...753..142B</bibcode>
			<title>Planets around Low-mass Stars (PALMS). I. A Substellar Companion to the Young M Dwarf 1RXS J235133.3+312720</title>
			<authors>Bowler, Brendan P.; Liu, Michael C.; Shkolnik, Evgenya L.; Dupuy, Trent J.; Cieza, Lucas A.; Kraus, Adam L.; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 753, Issue 2, article id. 142 (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...753..142B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...56F</bibcode>
			<title>The Brown Dwarf Kinematics Project (BDKP). III. Parallaxes for 70 Ultracool Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Faherty, Jacqueline K.; Burgasser, Adam J.; Walter, Frederick M.; Van der Bliek, Nicole; Shara, Michael M.; Cruz, Kelle L.; West, Andrew A.; Vrba, Frederick J.; Anglada-Escud, Guillem</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 56 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...56F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143..134M</bibcode>
			<title>The Sizes of the Nearest Young Stars</title>
			<authors>McCarthy, Kyle; White, Russel J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 6, article id. 134 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143..134M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729..139W</bibcode>
			<title>The Gemini NICI Planet-finding Campaign: Discovery of a Substellar L Dwarf Companion to the Nearby Young M Dwarf CD-35 2722</title>
			<authors>Wahhaj, Zahed; Liu, Michael C.; Biller, Beth A.; Clarke, Fraser; Nielsen, Eric L.; Close, Laird M.; Hayward, Thomas L.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Cushing, Michael; Dupuy, Trent; Tecza, Matthias; Thatte, Niranjan; Chun, Mark; Ftaclas, Christ; Hartung, Markus; Reid, I. Neill; Shkolnik, Evgenya L.; Alencar, Silvia H. P.; Artymowicz, Pawel; Boss, Alan; de Gouveia Dal Pino, Elisabethe; Gregorio-Hetem, Jane; Ida, Shigeru; Kuchner, Marc; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Toomey, Douglas W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 139 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729..139W</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143..134M</bibcode>
			<title>The Sizes of the Nearest Young Stars</title>
			<authors>McCarthy, Kyle; White, Russel J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 6, article id. 134 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143..134M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750...53N</bibcode>
			<title>The Gemini NICI Planet-Finding Campaign: Discovery of a Multiple System Orbiting the Young A Star HD 1160</title>
			<authors>Nielsen, Eric L.; Liu, Michael C.; Wahhaj, Zahed; Biller, Beth A.; Hayward, Thomas L.; Boss, Alan; Bowler, Brendan; Kraus, Adam; Shkolnik, Evgenya L.; Tecza, Matthias; Chun, Mark; Clarke, Fraser; Close, Laird M.; Ftaclas, Christ; Hartung, Markus; Males, Jared R.; Reid, I. Neill; Skemer, Andrew J.; Alencar, Silvia H. P.; Burrows, Adam; de Gouveia Dal Pino, Elisabethe; Gregorio-Hetem, Jane; Kuchner, Marc; Thatte, Niranjan; Toomey, Douglas W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 1, article id. 53 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750...53N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.419.1701R</bibcode>
			<title>Possible planet-forming regions on submillimetre images</title>
			<authors>Regly, Zs.; Juhsz, A.; Sndor, Zs.; Dullemond, C. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 419, Issue 2, pp. 1701-1712.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.419.1701R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..10M</bibcode>
			<title>RACE-OC project: rotation and variability in the &amp;epsil Chamaeleontis, Octans, and Argus stellar associations</title>
			<authors>Messina, S.; Desidera, S.; Lanzafame, A. C.; Turatto, M.; Guinan, E. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A10</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..10M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...61Z</bibcode>
			<title>The Tucana/Horologium, Columba, AB Doradus, and Argus Associations: New Members and Dusty Debris Disks</title>
			<authors>Zuckerman, B.; Rhee, Joseph H.; Song, Inseok; Bessell, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. 61 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...61Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729..139W</bibcode>
			<title>The Gemini NICI Planet-finding Campaign: Discovery of a Substellar L Dwarf Companion to the Nearby Young M Dwarf CD-35 2722</title>
			<authors>Wahhaj, Zahed; Liu, Michael C.; Biller, Beth A.; Clarke, Fraser; Nielsen, Eric L.; Close, Laird M.; Hayward, Thomas L.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Cushing, Michael; Dupuy, Trent; Tecza, Matthias; Thatte, Niranjan; Chun, Mark; Ftaclas, Christ; Hartung, Markus; Reid, I. Neill; Shkolnik, Evgenya L.; Alencar, Silvia H. P.; Artymowicz, Pawel; Boss, Alan; de Gouveia Dal Pino, Elisabethe; Gregorio-Hetem, Jane; Ida, Shigeru; Kuchner, Marc; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Toomey, Douglas W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 139 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729..139W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..15M</bibcode>
			<title>RACE-OC project: Rotation and variability of young stellar associations within 100 pc</title>
			<authors>Messina, S.; Desidera, S.; Turatto, M.; Lanzafame, A. C.; Guinan, E. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A15</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..15M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508..833D</bibcode>
			<title>Search for associations containing young stars (SACY). III. Ages and Li abundances</title>
			<authors>da Silva, L.; Torres, C. A. O.; de La Reza, R.; Quast, G. R.; Melo, C. H. F.; Sterzik, M. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 2, 2009, pp.833-839</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508..833D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..184..138H</bibcode>
			<title>XID II: Statistical Cross-Association of ROSAT Bright Source Catalog X-ray Sources with 2MASS Point Source Catalog Near-Infrared Sources</title>
			<authors>Haakonsen, Christian Bernt; Rutledge, Robert E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 184, Issue 1, pp. 138-151 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..184..138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460..695T</bibcode>
			<title>Search for associations containing young stars (SACY). I. Sample and searching method</title>
			<authors>Torres, C. A. O.; Quast, G. R.; da Silva, L.; de La Reza, R.; Melo, C. H. F.; Sterzik, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 3, December IV 2006, pp.695-708</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460..695T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....132..866R</bibcode>
			<title>Identification of New M Dwarfs in the Solar Neighborhood</title>
			<authors>Riaz, Basmah; Gizis, John E.; Harvin, James</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 132, Issue 2, pp. 866-872.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....132..866R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...486..179P</bibcode>
			<title>Faint Sources in the EUVE Survey: Identification of White Dwarfs, Active Late-Type Stars, and Galactic Nuclei</title>
			<authors>Polomski, Elisha; Vennes, Stephane; Thorstensen, John R.; Mathioudakis, Mihalis; Falco, Emilio E.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.486, p.179</journal>
			<date>9/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...486..179P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997AJ....114..244C</bibcode>
			<title>Extreme Ultraviolet Explorer Optical Identification Campaign.III. A Southern Hemisphere Sample of Active Late-Type Stars and White Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Craig, Nahide; Christian, Damian J.; Dupuis, Jean; Roberts, Bryce A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.114, p. 244-257 (1997)</journal>
			<date>7/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997AJ....114..244C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJS..108..545L</bibcode>
			<title>An All-Sky Catalog of Faint Extreme Ultraviolet Sources</title>
			<authors>Lampton, M.; Lieu, R.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Bowyer, S.; Voges, W.; Lewis, J.; Wu, X.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement v.108, p.545</journal>
			<date>2/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJS..108..545L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
