<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..122Z</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based Detections of Thermal Emission from CoRoT-1b and WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Zhao, Ming; Monnier, John D.; Swain, Mark R.; Barman, Travis; Hinkley, Sasha</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 122 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744..122Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...72N</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Distributions of Close-in Planets and Distant Planets Formed by Scattering and Dynamical Tides</title>
			<authors>Nagasawa, M.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 72 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...72N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740...61K</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Phase Variations of the 55 Cancri System</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.; Ciardi, David R.; Dragomir, Diana; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 740, Issue 2, article id. 61 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740...61K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A.113M</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-orbit inclinations of the exoplanetary systems HAT-P-8b, HAT-P-9b, HAT-P-16b, and HAT-P-23b</title>
			<authors>Moutou, C.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Udry, S.; H&#233;brard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Santerne, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Martinez, P.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Toublanc, D.; Troncin, J. P.; Vanhuysse, M.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A113</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A.113M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735L..12D</bibcode>
			<title>The High Albedo of the Hot Jupiter Kepler-7 b</title>
			<authors>Demory, Brice-Olivier; Seager, Sara; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Kjeldsen, Hans; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Gillon, Micha&#235;l; Rowe, Jason F.; Welsh, William F.; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Dupree, Andrea; McCarthy, Don; Kulesa, Craig; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 735, Issue 1, article id. L12 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735L..12D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...74G</bibcode>
			<title>Consequences of the Ejection and Disruption of Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Guillochon, James; Ramirez-Ruiz, Enrico; Lin, Douglas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...74G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..41L</bibcode>
			<title>Distorted, nonspherical transiting planets: impact on the transit depth and on the radius determination</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Lai, D.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A41</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..41L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...50K</bibcode>
			<title>An Independent Analysis of Kepler-4b Through Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. 50 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...50K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...74K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Inclination Dependence of Exoplanet Phase Signatures</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...74K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527L..11H</bibcode>
			<title>The retrograde orbit of the HAT-P-6b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Ehrenreich, D.; Bouchy, F.; Delfosse, X.; Moutou, C.; Arnold, L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.L11</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527L..11H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411L..46V</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for detection of exoplanet magnetic fields through bow-shock observations during transits</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. L46-L50.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411L..46V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...74V</bibcode>
			<title>Quantifying the Challenges of Detecting Unseen Planetary Companions with Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Payne, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...74V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62L..61N</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect of the Transiting Exoplanet XO-4b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.6, pp.L61--L65</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62L..61N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARep...54.1105A</bibcode>
			<title>Light curve analysis for eclipsing systems with exoplanets. The system HD 209458</title>
			<authors>Abubekerov, M. K.; Gostev, N. Yu.; Cherepashchuk, A. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Reports, Volume 54, Issue 12, pp.1105-1124</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARep...54.1105A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..818K</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Phase Variations of Long-period Eccentric Planets</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. 818-826 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..818K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A.110C</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission . XIII. CoRoT-13b: a dense hot Jupiter in transit around a star with solar metallicity and super-solar lithium content</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Bruntt, H.; Ollivier, M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; von Paris, P.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Titz-Weider, R.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A110</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...522A.110C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722L.168V</bibcode>
			<title>Early UV Ingress in WASP-12b: Measuring Planetary Magnetic Fields</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 722, Issue 2, pp. L168-L172 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722L.168V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..920C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from TrES-3b: A Ks-band Detection and an H-band Upper Limit on the Depth of the Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Lafreni&#232;re, David; Albert, Loic</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 920-927 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..920C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717.1084C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Thermal Emission from the Hot Jupiter TrES-2b: Ground-based Detection of the Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Lafreniere, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. 1084-1091 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717.1084C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518L.153G</bibcode>
			<title>Possible detection of phase changes from the non-transiting planet HD 46375b by CoRoT</title>
			<authors>Gaulme, P.; Vannier, M.; Guillot, T.; Mosser, B.; Mary, D.; Weiss, W. W.; Schmider, F.-X.; Bourguignon, S.; Deeg, H. J.; R&#233;gulo, C.; Aigrain, S.; Schneider, J.; Bruntt, H.; Deheuvels, S.; Donati, J.-F.; Appourchaux, T.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Baudin, F.; Catala, C.; Michel, E.; Samadi, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.L153</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518L.153G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.404L.114G</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based detection of thermal emission from the exoplanet WASP-19b</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Aigrain, S.; Pollacco, D. L.; Barros, S. C. C.; Hebb, L.; Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; West, R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 404, Issue 1, pp. L114-L118.</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.404L.114G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...513A..76S</bibcode>
			<title>Bright optical day-side emission from extrasolar planet CoRoT-2b</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.; de Mooij, E. J. W.; Burrows, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 513, id.A76</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...513A..76S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..14F</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. IX. CoRoT-6b: a transiting ``hot Jupiter'' planet in an 8.9d orbit around a low-metallicity star</title>
			<authors>Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Alonso, R.; Deleuil, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Bruntt, H.; Alapini, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Guillot, T.; Lammer, H.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Guenther, E.; Gondoin, P.; den Hartog, R.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..14F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...510A..94C</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing analysis of CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Csizmadia, Sz.; Renner, S.; Barge, P.; Agol, E.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Almenara, J.-M.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Guenther, E. W.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#225;zaro, C.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Wuchterl, G.; Gandolfi, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 510, id.A94</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...510A..94C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....139...53R</bibcode>
			<title>Pre-Discovery Observations of CoRoT-1b and CoRoT-2b with the BEST Survey</title>
			<authors>Rauer, H.; Erikson, A.; Kabath, P.; Hedelt, P.; Boer, M.; Carone, L.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Eigm&#252;ller, P.; Paris, P. v.; Renner, S.; Tournois, G.; Titz, R.; Voss, H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 139, Issue 1, pp. 53-58 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....139...53R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707.1707R</bibcode>
			<title>Ks-Band Detection of Thermal Emission and Color Constraints to CoRoT-1b: A Low-Albedo Planet with Inefficient Atmospheric Energy Redistribution and a Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Rogers, Justin C.; Apai, D&#225;niel; L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Sing, David K.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 2, article id. 1707-1716 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707.1707R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..569K</bibcode>
			<title>Periodic variable stars in CoRoT field LRa02 observed with BEST II</title>
			<authors>Kabath, P.; Erikson, A.; Rauer, H.; Pasternacki, T.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Chini, R.; Lemke, R.; Murphy, M.; Fruth, T.; Titz, R.; Eigm&#252;ller, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.569-587</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..501C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in CoRoT-LRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Fridlund, M.; Ollivier, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233; , P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Hatzes, A.; Hebrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R&#233; gulo, C.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.501-517</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..501C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..491C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in Corot-IRa01 field</title>
			<authors>Carpano, S.; Cabrera, J.; Alonso, R.; Barge, P.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J.-M.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Carone, L.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fressin, F.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Janot-Pacheco, E.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; R&#233;gulo, C.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.491-500</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..491C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..391A</bibcode>
			<title>Planet formation by nucleated-instability: comparison with the two first CoRoT runs</title>
			<authors>Alibert, Y.; Pont, F.; Baraffe, I.; Reyl&#233;, C.; Mordasini, C.; Queloz, D.; Benz, W.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.391-398</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..391A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..385L</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and evolution of the first CoRoT exoplanets: probing the brown dwarf/planet overlapping mass regime</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.385-389</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..385L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..369B</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the transit times of CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Bean, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.369-375</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..369B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..359G</bibcode>
			<title>VLT transit and occultation photometry for the bloated planet CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Demory, B.-O.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Barman, T.; Hebb, L.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Deleuil, M.; Magain, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.359-367</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..359G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..353A</bibcode>
			<title>The secondary eclipse of CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Alonso, R.; Alapini, A.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Chaintreuil, S.; de La Reza, R.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; de Oliveira Fialho, F.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.353-358</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..353A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..343D</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based photometry of space-based transit detections: photometric follow-up of the CoRoT  mission</title>
			<authors>Deeg, H. J.; Gillon, M.; Shporer, A.; Rouan, D.; Stecklum, B.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Bouchy, F.; Eisl&#246; ffel, J.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Eigm&#252;ller, P.; Handler, G.; Hatzes, A.; Kabath, P.; Lendl, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rabus, M.; Tingley, B.; Titz, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.343-352</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..343D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..321M</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT initial run: resolving their nature</title>
			<authors>Moutou, C.; Pont, F.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Bruntt, H.; Deeg, H. J.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rouan, D.; Shporer, A.; Udry, S.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Carpano, S.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Rauer, H.; Schneider, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.321-336</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..321M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..281R</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. VII. The ``hot-Jupiter''-type planet CoRoT-5b</title>
			<authors>Rauer, H.; Queloz, D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; de La Reza, R.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Guenther, E.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Kabath, P.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Rabus, M.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Shporer, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.281-286</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..281R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Natur.459..543S</bibcode>
			<title>The changing phases of extrasolar planet CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Snellen, Ignas A. G.; de Mooij, Ernst J. W.; Albrecht, Simon</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 459, Issue 7246, pp. 543-545 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Natur.459..543S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690.1393S</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-9b: A Low-Density Planet Transiting a Moderately Faint F Star</title>
			<authors>Shporer, Avi; Bakos, G&#193;sp&#193;r &#193;.; Bouchy, Francois; Pont, Frederic; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Latham, Dave W.; Sip&#246;cz, Brigitta; Torres, Guillermo; Mazeh, Tsevi; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Noyes, Robert W.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J&#243;zsef; Papp, Istv&#225;n; S&#225;ri, P&#225;l; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 2, pp. 1393-1400 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690.1393S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PABei..27...14Z</bibcode>
			<title>The detection methods and statistical characteristics of exoplanet.</title>
			<authors>Zhang, N.; Ji, J.-H.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 27, 14-28 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PABei..27...14Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488L..47M</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. V. CoRoT-Exo-4b: stellar and planetary parameters</title>
			<authors>Moutou, C.; Bruntt, H.; Guillot, T.; Shporer, A.; Guenther, E.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.L47-L50</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488L..47M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488L..43A</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. IV. CoRoT-Exo-4b: a transiting planet in a 9.2 day synchronous orbit</title>
			<authors>Aigrain, S.; Collier Cameron, A.; Ollivier, M.; Pont, F.; Jorda, L.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barge, P.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deeg, H.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Paetzold, M.; Pinte, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Wuchter, G.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.L43-L46</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488L..43A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482L..21A</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. II. CoRoT-Exo-2b: a transiting planet around an active G star</title>
			<authors>Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Ollivier, M.; Moutou, C.; Rouan, D.; Deeg, H. J.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Kabath, P.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Shporer, A.; Schneider, J.; Stecklum, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 3, 2008, pp.L21-L24</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482L..21A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482L..17B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. I. CoRoT-Exo-1b: a low-density short-period planet around a G0V star</title>
			<authors>Barge, P.; Baglin, A.; Auvergne, M.; Rauer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Schneider, J.; Pont, F.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J.-M.; Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deeg, H. J.; La Reza, De; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hebrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lammer, H.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rouan, D.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 3, 2008, pp.L17-L20</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482L..17B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667L.191L</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission from Transiting Very Hot Jupiters: Prospects for Ground-based Detection at Optical Wavelengths</title>
			<authors>L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 2, pp. L191-L194.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667L.191L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..122Z</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based Detections of Thermal Emission from CoRoT-1b and WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Zhao, Ming; Monnier, John D.; Swain, Mark R.; Barman, Travis; Hinkley, Sasha</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 122 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744..122Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...11D</bibcode>
			<title>The Atmospheres of the Hot-Jupiters Kepler-5b and Kepler-6b Observed during Occultations with Warm-Spitzer and Kepler</title>
			<authors>D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Charbonneau, David; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Knutson, Heather A.; Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Deming, Drake; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 11 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...11D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A.116D</bibcode>
			<title>Prospecting transit duration variations in extrasolar planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Damiani, C.; Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A116</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...535A.116D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414..108B</bibcode>
			<title>On the use of the Virtual Observatory to select calibrators for phase-referenced astrometry of exoplanet-host stars</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonneau, D.; Mourard, D.; Lafrasse, S.; Mella, G.; Duvert, G.; Chelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. 108-115.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414..108B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63S.531H</bibcode>
			<title>A Possible Tilted Orbit of the Super-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Narita, Norio; Shporer, Avi; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.SP2, pp.531--536</journal>
			<date>3/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63S.531H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1953P</bibcode>
			<title>Reassessing the radial-velocity evidence for planets around CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Aigrain, Suzanne; Zucker, Shay</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 3, pp. 1953-1962.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1953P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...23B</bibcode>
			<title>Secondary Eclipse Photometry of WASP-4b with Warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Beerer, Ingrid M.; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Agol, Eric; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Deming, Drake; Desert, Jean-Michel; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 23 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...95D</bibcode>
			<title>Warm Spitzer Photometry of the Transiting Exoplanets CoRoT-1 and CoRoT-2 at Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather; Agol, Eric; Desert, Jean-Michel; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan; Showman, Adam P.; Lewis, Nikole K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 95 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...95D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 29, 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724.1108J</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect of Exoplanet Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Cochran, William D.; Welsh, William F.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John Asher; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Howard, Andrew W.; MacQueen, Phillip; Orosz, Jerome A.; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Allen, Christopher; Tenenbaum, Peter; Wu, Hayley; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Cote, Miles T.; McCauliff, Sean; Girouard, Forrest R.; Gunter, Jay P.; Wohler, Bill; Hall, Jennifer R.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Kamal Uddin, AKM; Wu, Michael S.; Bhavsar, Paresh A.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Pletcher, David L.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, article id. 1108-1119 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724.1108J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2625M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation in exoplanet WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Ginski, Ch.; Adam, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2625-2631.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2625M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521L..59M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of the ellipsoidal and the relativistic beaming effects in the CoRoT-3 lightcurve</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Faigler, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.L59</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521L..59M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.1867S</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit alignment of the transiting exoplanet WASP-3b from Rossiter-McLaughlin observations</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Pollacco, D.; H&#233;brard, G.; Gibson, N. P.; Barros, S. C. C.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Miller, G. R. M.; Watson, C. A.; Keenan, F. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 1867-1872.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.1867S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..421T</bibcode>
			<title>A Prograde, Low-inclination Orbit for the Very Hot Jupiter WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Tripathi, Anjali; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Halverson, Sam; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Holman, Matthew J.; de Kleer, Katherine R.; Carter, Joshua A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Cabrera, Nicole E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 421-428 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..421T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714...13A</bibcode>
			<title>Lack of Transit Timing Variations of OGLE-TR-111b: A Re-Analysis with Six New Epochs</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; L&#243;pez-Morales, M.; Elliot, J. L.; Seager, S.; Osip, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 13-24 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714...13A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...513A..76S</bibcode>
			<title>Bright optical day-side emission from extrasolar planet CoRoT-2b</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.; de Mooij, E. J. W.; Burrows, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 513, id.A76</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...513A..76S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...510A..94C</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing analysis of CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Csizmadia, Sz.; Renner, S.; Barge, P.; Agol, E.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Almenara, J.-M.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Guenther, E. W.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#225;zaro, C.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Wuchterl, G.; Gandolfi, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 510, id.A94</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...510A..94C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...510A..21S</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar limb-darkening coefficients for CoRot and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Sing, D. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 510, id.A21</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...510A..21S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A.103S</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos preliminary astrometric masses for the two close-in companions to HD 131664 and HD 43848. A brown dwarf and a low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Desidera, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A103</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A.103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707.1707R</bibcode>
			<title>Ks-Band Detection of Thermal Emission and Color Constraints to CoRoT-1b: A Low-Albedo Planet with Inefficient Atmospheric Energy Redistribution and a Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Rogers, Justin C.; Apai, D&#225;niel; L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Sing, David K.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 2, article id. 1707-1716 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707.1707R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..369B</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the transit times of CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Bean, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.369-375</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..369B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..359G</bibcode>
			<title>VLT transit and occultation photometry for the bloated planet CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Demory, B.-O.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Barman, T.; Hebb, L.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Deleuil, M.; Magain, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.359-367</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..359G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..353A</bibcode>
			<title>The secondary eclipse of CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Alonso, R.; Alapini, A.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Chaintreuil, S.; de La Reza, R.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; de Oliveira Fialho, F.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.353-358</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..353A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..343D</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based photometry of space-based transit detections: photometric follow-up of the CoRoT  mission</title>
			<authors>Deeg, H. J.; Gillon, M.; Shporer, A.; Rouan, D.; Stecklum, B.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Bouchy, F.; Eisl&#246; ffel, J.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Eigm&#252;ller, P.; Handler, G.; Hatzes, A.; Kabath, P.; Lendl, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rabus, M.; Tingley, B.; Titz, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.343-352</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..343D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..321M</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT initial run: resolving their nature</title>
			<authors>Moutou, C.; Pont, F.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Bruntt, H.; Deeg, H. J.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rouan, D.; Shporer, A.; Udry, S.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Carpano, S.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Rauer, H.; Schneider, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.321-336</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..321M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700.1078G</bibcode>
			<title>A Transit Timing Analysis of Nine Rise Light Curves of the Exoplanet System TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Barros, S.; Joshi, Y. C.; Todd, I.; Keenan, F. P.; Skillen, I.; Benn, C.; Christian, D.; Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Steele, I. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 1078-1085 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700.1078G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482L..17B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. I. CoRoT-Exo-1b: a low-density short-period planet around a G0V star</title>
			<authors>Barge, P.; Baglin, A.; Auvergne, M.; Rauer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Schneider, J.; Pont, F.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J.-M.; Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deeg, H. J.; La Reza, De; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hebrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lammer, H.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rouan, D.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 3, 2008, pp.L17-L20</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482L..17B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667L.191L</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission from Transiting Very Hot Jupiters: Prospects for Ground-based Detection at Optical Wavelengths</title>
			<authors>L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 2, pp. L191-L194.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667L.191L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
