<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...545A...6P</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XXIII. CoRoT-21b: a doomed large Jupiter around a faint subgiant star</title>
			<authors>Ptzold, M.; Endl, M.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Gandolfi, D.; Jorda, L.; Grziwa, S.; Carone, L.; Pasternacki, T.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Cavarroc, C.; Cochran, W. B.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 545, id.A6</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...545A...6P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754..137M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Detectability of Star-Planet Interaction</title>
			<authors>Miller, Brendan P.; Gallo, Elena; Wright, Jason T.; Dupree, Andrea K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 754, Issue 2, article id. 137 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754..137M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.1761A</bibcode>
			<title>The radial velocity signature of tides raised in stars hosting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Arras, Phil; Burkart, Joshua; Quataert, Eliot; Weinberg, Nevin N.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 2, pp. 1761-1766.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.1761A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..14E</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT-SRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Erikson, A.; Santerne, A.; Renner, S.; Barge, P.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; Rgulo, C.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..14E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A.145D</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XX. CoRoT-20b: A very high density, high eccentricity transiting giant planet</title>
			<authors>Deleuil, M.; Bonomo, A. S.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Erikson, A.; Bouchy, F.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J.-M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord, P.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carpano, S.; Cavarroc, C.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Damiani, C.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Fridlund, M.; Hbrard, G.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; Lger, A.; Lammer, H.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Parviainen, H.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rodrguez, A.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A145</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A.145D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..83B</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. III. KOI-423b: an 18 MJup transiting companion around an F7IV star</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Moutou, C.; Deleuil, M.; D az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H brard, G.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A83</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..83B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1365B</bibcode>
			<title>Three-dimensional simulations of internal wave breaking and the fate of planets around solar-type stars</title>
			<authors>Barker, Adrian J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1365-1378.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1365B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..97T</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XVI. CoRoT-14b: an unusually dense very hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Endl, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Alonso, R.; Mazeh, T.; Jorda, L.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord , P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carpano, S.; Carone, L.; Cochran, W. D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A97</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..97T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729L...7L</bibcode>
			<title>On the Anomalous Radii of the Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Crismani, Matteo; Adams, Fred C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. L7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729L...7L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...543A.125G</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-object spectroscopy of stars in the CoRoT fields. II. The stellar population of the CoRoT fields IRa01, LRa01, LRa02, and LRa06</title>
			<authors>Guenther, E. W.; Gandolfi, D.; Sebastian, D.; Deleuil, M.; Moutou, C.; Cusano, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 543, id.A125</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...543A.125G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..38R</bibcode>
			<title>Warm debris disks candidates in transiting planets systems</title>
			<authors>Ribas, .; Mern, B.; Ardila, D. R.; Bouy, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A38</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..38R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418L..15K</bibcode>
			<title>Debris disc candidates in systems with transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Krivov, A. V.; Reidemeister, M.; Fiedler, S.; Lhne, T.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 418, Issue 1, pp. L15-L19.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.418L..15K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..83B</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. III. KOI-423b: an 18 MJup transiting companion around an F7IV star</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Moutou, C.; Deleuil, M.; D az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H brard, G.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A83</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..83B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..97T</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XVI. CoRoT-14b: an unusually dense very hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Endl, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Alonso, R.; Mazeh, T.; Jorda, L.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord , P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carpano, S.; Carone, L.; Cochran, W. D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A97</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..97T</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
