<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...545A...6P</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XXIII. CoRoT-21b: a doomed large Jupiter around a faint subgiant star</title>
			<authors>Ptzold, M.; Endl, M.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Gandolfi, D.; Jorda, L.; Grziwa, S.; Carone, L.; Pasternacki, T.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Cavarroc, C.; Cochran, W. B.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 545, id.A6</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...545A...6P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.2024J</bibcode>
			<title>The coronal X-ray-age relation and its implications for the evaporation of exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Alan P.; Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 3, pp. 2024-2043.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.2024J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A.149O</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XXII. CoRoT-16b: a hot Jupiter with a hint of eccentricity around a faint solar-like star</title>
			<authors>Ollivier, M.; Gillon, M.; Santerne, A.; Wuchterl, G.; Havel, M.; Bruntt, H.; Bord, P.; Pasternacki, T.; Endl, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cavarroc, C.; Cochran, W. D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Diaz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Grziwa, S.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tadeu dos Santos, M.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A149</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A.149O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A.140B</bibcode>
			<title>Multiwavelength flux variations induced by stellar magnetic activity: effects on planetary transits</title>
			<authors>Ballerini, P.; Micela, G.; Lanza, A. F.; Pagano, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A140</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A.140B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..14E</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT-SRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Erikson, A.; Santerne, A.; Renner, S.; Barge, P.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; Rgulo, C.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..14E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A.112C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT LRa01 field</title>
			<authors>Carone, L.; Gandolfi, D.; Cabrera, J.; Hatzes, A. P.; Deeg, H. J.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Ptzold, M.; Weingrill, J.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deleuil, M.; Daz, R. F.; Dreizler, S.; Dvorak, R.; Eislffel, J.; Eigmller, P.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gibson, N.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Grziwa, S.; Gnther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Nortmann, L.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R gulo, C.; Renner, S.; de La Reza, R.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A112</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A.112C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A.136G</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XXI. CoRoT-19b: a low density planet orbiting an old inactive F9V-star</title>
			<authors>Guenther, E. W.; Daz, R. F.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Mazeh, T.; Rouan, D.; Gibson, N.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cavarroc, C.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Dreizler, S.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Jehin, E.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Moutou, C.; Nortmann, L.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Pasternacki, Th.; Ptzold, M.; Parviainen, H.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 537, id.A136</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...537A.136G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..97G</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XII. CoRoT-12b: a short-period low-density planet transiting a solar analog star</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Hatzes, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Fridlund, M.; Deleuil, M.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Barnes, S. I.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J. C.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Montalbn, J.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A97</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..97G</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...543A.125G</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-object spectroscopy of stars in the CoRoT fields. II. The stellar population of the CoRoT fields IRa01, LRa01, LRa02, and LRa06</title>
			<authors>Guenther, E. W.; Gandolfi, D.; Sebastian, D.; Deleuil, M.; Moutou, C.; Cusano, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 543, id.A125</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...543A.125G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.2024J</bibcode>
			<title>The coronal X-ray-age relation and its implications for the evaporation of exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Alan P.; Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 3, pp. 2024-2043.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.2024J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A.140B</bibcode>
			<title>Multiwavelength flux variations induced by stellar magnetic activity: effects on planetary transits</title>
			<authors>Ballerini, P.; Micela, G.; Lanza, A. F.; Pagano, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A140</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A.140B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A.112C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT LRa01 field</title>
			<authors>Carone, L.; Gandolfi, D.; Cabrera, J.; Hatzes, A. P.; Deeg, H. J.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Ptzold, M.; Weingrill, J.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deleuil, M.; Daz, R. F.; Dreizler, S.; Dvorak, R.; Eislffel, J.; Eigmller, P.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gibson, N.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Grziwa, S.; Gnther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Nortmann, L.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R gulo, C.; Renner, S.; de La Reza, R.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A112</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A.112C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..97G</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XII. CoRoT-12b: a short-period low-density planet transiting a solar analog star</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Hatzes, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Fridlund, M.; Deleuil, M.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Barnes, S. I.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J. C.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Montalbn, J.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A97</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..97G</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
