<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744....4G</bibcode>
			<title>A High-eccentricity Component in the Double-planet System around HD 163607 and a Planet around HD 164509</title>
			<authors>Giguere, Matthew J.; Fischer, Debra A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John A.; Henry, Gregory W.; Wright, Jason T.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard T.; Hou, Fengji; Spronck, Julien</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 1, article id. 4 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744....4G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...741...52K</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of Exoplanet Periastron Passage in the Infrared</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 741, Issue 1, article id. 52 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...741...52K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>The Heavy-element Masses of Extrasolar Giant Planets, Revealed</title>
			<authors>Miller, Neil; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1573V</bibcode>
			<title>Transit variability in bow shock-hosting planets</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1573-1582.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1573V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...74K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Inclination Dependence of Exoplanet Phase Signatures</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...74K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727L..44S</bibcode>
			<title>A Short-period Censor of Sub-Jupiter Mass Exoplanets with Low Density</title>
			<authors>Szab&#243;, Gy. M.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. L44 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727L..44S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..866K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-15b: A 10.9 Day Extrasolar Planet Transiting a Solar-type Star</title>
			<authors>Kov&#225;cs, G.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J. D.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, B. B&#233;ky J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, pp. 866-877 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744L..23C</bibcode>
			<title>Pumping the Eccentricity of Exoplanets by Tidal Effect</title>
			<authors>Correia, Alexandre C. M.; Bou&#233;, Gwena&#235;l; Laskar, Jacques</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. L23 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744L..23C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1573V</bibcode>
			<title>Transit variability in bow shock-hosting planets</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1573-1582.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1573V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63S.531H</bibcode>
			<title>A Possible Tilted Orbit of the Super-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Narita, Norio; Shporer, Avi; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.SP2, pp.531--536</journal>
			<date>3/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63S.531H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..66B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XI. CoRoT-8b: a hot and dense sub-Saturn around a K1 dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Cabrera, J.; Jorda, L.; Lovis, C.; Csizmadia, S.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Ollivier, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A66</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..66B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..501C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in CoRoT-LRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Fridlund, M.; Ollivier, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233; , P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Hatzes, A.; Hebrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R&#233; gulo, C.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.501-517</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..501C</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
