<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754...60H</bibcode>
			<title>On the Stability of Super-Earth Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Heng, Kevin; Kopparla, Pushkar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 754, Issue 1, article id. 60 (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754...60H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752....7H</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra of Terrestrial Exoplanet Surfaces</title>
			<authors>Hu, Renyu; Ehlmann, Bethany L.; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752....7H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752....1R</bibcode>
			<title>Possible Disintegrating Short-period Super-Mercury Orbiting KIC 12557548</title>
			<authors>Rappaport, S.; Levine, A.; Chiang, E.; El Mellah, I.; Jenkins, J.; Kalomeni, B.; Kite, E. S.; Kotson, M.; Nelson, L.; Rousseau-Nepton, L.; Tran, K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 1 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752....1R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..148W</bibcode>
			<title>The Effect of Population-wide Mass-to-radius Relationships on the Interpretation of Kepler and HARPS Super-Earth Occurrence Rates</title>
			<authors>Wolfgang, Angie; Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 148 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750..148W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A.103W</bibcode>
			<title>Rocky super-Earth interiors. Structure and internal dynamics of CoRoT-7b and Kepler-10b</title>
			<authors>Wagner, F. W.; Tosi, N.; Sohl, F.; Rauer, H.; Spohn, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A103</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A.103W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..34S</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-object spectroscopy of stars in the CoRoT fields. I. Early-type stars in the CoRoT-fields IRa01, LRa01, LRa02&lt;xref ref-type="fn" rid="FN1"&gt;&lt;xref ref-type="fn" rid="FN2"&gt;*</title>
			<authors>Sebastian, D.; Guenther, E. W.; Schaffenroth, V.; Gandolfi, D.; Geier, S.; Heber, U.; Deleuil, M.; Moutou, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A34</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..34S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..26P</bibcode>
			<title>The high-energy environment in the super-Earth system CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Poppenhaeger, K.; Czesla, S.; Schrter, S.; Lalitha, S.; Kashyap, V.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A26</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..26P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749...15G</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-20: A Sun-like Star with Three Sub-Neptune Exoplanets and Two Earth-size Candidates</title>
			<authors>Gautier, Thomas N., III; Charbonneau, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Francois; Rogers, Leslie A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ciardi, David R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Howell, Steve B.; Horch, Elliott P.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Borucki, William J.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Silverio, Kathryn; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Still, Martin; Stumpe, Martin C.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 1, article id. 15 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749...15G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A.140B</bibcode>
			<title>Multiwavelength flux variations induced by stellar magnetic activity: effects on planetary transits</title>
			<authors>Ballerini, P.; Micela, G.; Lanza, A. F.; Pagano, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A140</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A.140B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..78C</bibcode>
			<title>Elliptical instability in terrestrial planets and moons</title>
			<authors>Cebron, D.; Le Bars, M.; Moutou, C.; Le Gal, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A78</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..28G</bibcode>
			<title>Improved precision on the radius of the nearby super-Earth 55 Cnc e</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Demory, B.-O.; Benneke, B.; Valencia, D.; Deming, D.; Seager, S.; Lovis, Ch.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A28</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..28G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..14E</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT-SRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Erikson, A.; Santerne, A.; Renner, S.; Barge, P.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; Rgulo, C.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..14E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.482..195F</bibcode>
			<title>Two Earth-sized planets orbiting Kepler-20</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Rowe, Jason F.; Charbonneau, David; Rogers, Leslie A.; Ballard, Sarah; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Ciardi, David R.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Dressing, Courtney D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howard, Andrew; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Barclay, Thomas; Mullally, Fergal; Seader, Shawn E.; Still, Martin; Twicken, Joseph D.; Thompson, Susan E.; Uddin, Kamal</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 482, Issue 7384, pp. 195-198 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.482..195F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.420.1045G</bibcode>
			<title>The needle in the haystack: searching for transiting extrasolar planets in CoRoT stellar light curves</title>
			<authors>Grziwa, S.; Ptzold, M.; Carone, L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 420, Issue 2, pp. 1045-1052.</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.420.1045G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.419.2737H</bibcode>
			<title>Global models of planetary system formation in radiatively-inefficient protoplanetary discs</title>
			<authors>Hellary, Phil; Nelson, Richard P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 419, Issue 4, pp. 2737-2757.</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.419.2737H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746...45T</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the Atmospheres of Transiting Planets with a Dedicated Space Telescope</title>
			<authors>Tessenyi, M.; Ollivier, M.; Tinetti, G.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Coud du Foresto, V.; Encrenaz, T.; Micela, G.; Swinyard, B.; Ribas, I.; Aylward, A.; Tennyson, J.; Swain, M. R.; Sozzetti, A.; Vasisht, G.; Deroo, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 1, article id. 45 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...746...45T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A.112C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT LRa01 field</title>
			<authors>Carone, L.; Gandolfi, D.; Cabrera, J.; Hatzes, A. P.; Deeg, H. J.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Ptzold, M.; Weingrill, J.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deleuil, M.; Daz, R. F.; Dreizler, S.; Dvorak, R.; Eislffel, J.; Eigmller, P.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gibson, N.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Grziwa, S.; Gnther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Nortmann, L.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R gulo, C.; Renner, S.; de La Reza, R.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A112</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A.112C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A..95M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal phase curves of nontransiting terrestrial exoplanets. II. Characterizing airless planets</title>
			<authors>Maurin, A. S.; Selsis, F.; Hersant, F.; Belu, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A95</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A..95M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A...4M</bibcode>
			<title>Estimating transiting exoplanet masses from precise optical photometry</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Heller, R.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Hodgkin, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A4</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A...4M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewAR..56...19M</bibcode>
			<title>From 51 Peg to Earth-type planets</title>
			<authors>Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 56, Issue 1, p. 19-24.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012NewAR..56...19M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...81F</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Infrared Observations and Independent Validation of the Transiting Super-Earth CoRoT-7 b</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Pont, Frederic; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Mazeh, Tsevi; Aigrain, Suzanne; Fridlund, Malcolm; Henze, Christopher E.; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 81 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...81F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745....2L</bibcode>
			<title>Interaction of Close-in Planets with the Magnetosphere of Their Host Stars. II. Super-Earths as Unipolar Inductors and Their Orbital Evolution</title>
			<authors>Laine, Randy O.; Lin, Douglas N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745....2L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744...59S</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-Radius Relationships for Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Swift, D. C.; Eggert, J. H.; Hicks, D. G.; Hamel, S.; Caspersen, K.; Schwegler, E.; Collins, G. W.; Nettelmann, N.; Ackland, G. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744...59S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Sci...337..556C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-36: A pair of planets with neighboring orbits and dissimilar densities.</title>
			<authors>Carter, J. A.; Agol, E.; Chaplin, W. J.; Basu, S.; Bedding, T. R.; Buchhave, L. A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Deck, K. M.; Elsworth, Y.; Fabrycky, D. C.; Ford, E. B.; Fortney, J. J.; Hale, S. J.; Handberg, R.; Hekker, S.; Holman, M. J.; Huber, D.; Karoff, C.; Kawaler, S. D.; Kjeldsen, H.; Lissauer, J. J.; Lopez, E. D.; Lund, M. N. L.; Lundkvist, M.; Metcalfe, T. S.; Miglio, A.; Rogers, L. A.; Stello, D.; Borucki, W. J.; Bryson, S.; Christiansen, J. L.; Cochran, W. D.; Geary, J. C.; Gilliland, R. L.; Haas, M. R.; Hall, J.; Howard, A. W.; Jenkins, J. M.; Klaus, T.; Koch, D. G.; Latham, D.; MacQueen, P. J.; Sasselov, D.; Steffen, J.; Twicken, J. D.; Winn, J. N.</authors>
			<journal>Science, 337, 556-559 (2012)</journal>
			<date>0/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Sci...337..556C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.480..496C</bibcode>
			<title>A compact system of small planets around a former red-giant star</title>
			<authors>Charpinet, S.; Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.; Green, E. M.; van Grootel, V.; Randall, S. K.; Silvotti, R.; Baran, A. S.; stensen, R. H.; Kawaler, S. D.; Telting, J. H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 480, Issue 7378, pp. 496-499 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.480..496C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743L..36C</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheres of Hot Super-Earths</title>
			<authors>Castan, Thibaut; Menou, Kristen</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. L36 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743L..36C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...75H</bibcode>
			<title>The Mass of CoRoT-7b</title>
			<authors>Hatzes, Artie P.; Fridlund, Malcolm; Nachmani, Gil; Mazeh, Tsevi; Valencia, Diana; Hbrard, Guillaume; Carone, Ludmila; Ptzold, Martin; Udry, Stephane; Bouchy, Francois; Deleuil, Magali; Moutou, Claire; Barge, Pierre; Bord , Pascal; Deeg, Hans; Tingley, Brandon; Dvorak, Rudolf; Gandolfi, Davide; Ferraz-Mello, Sylvio; Wuchterl, Gnther; Guenther, Eike; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike; Erikson, Anders; Cabrera, Juan; Csizmadia, Szilard; Lger, Alain; Lammer, Helmut; Weingrill, Jrg; Queloz, Didier; Alonso, Roi; Rouan, Daniel; Schneider, Jean</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...75H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742L..19M</bibcode>
			<title>Compositions of Hot Super-earth Atmospheres: Exploring Kepler Candidates</title>
			<authors>Miguel, Y.; Kaltenegger, L.; Fegley, B.; Schaefer, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. L19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742L..19M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742..116B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-20b-HAT-P-23b: Four Massive Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Kipping, D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Shporer, A.; Bky, B.; Buchhave, L. A.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...536A..70S</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. IV. KOI-196b: a non-inflated hot Jupiter with a high albedo</title>
			<authors>Santerne, A.; Bonomo, A. S.; Hbrard, G.; Deleuil, M.; Moutou, C.; Almenara, J.-M.; Bouchy, F.; Daz, R. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 536, id.A70</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...536A..70S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....7C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-18b, c, and d: A System of Three Planets Confirmed by Transit Timing Variations, Light Curve Validation, Warm-Spitzer Photometry, and Radial Velocity Measurements</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran ois; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steve B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Borucki, William. J.; Koch, David G.; Winn, Joshua N.; Welsh, William F.; Uddin, Kamal; Tenenbaum, Peter; Still, M.; Seager, Sara; Quinn, Samuel N.; Mullally, F.; Miller, Neil; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Lucas, Phillip; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Knutson, Heather; Kinemuchi, K.; Johnson, John A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew; Horch, Elliott; Holman, Matthew J.; Henze, Christopher E.; Haas, Michael R.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Ford, Eric B.; Fischer, Debra A.; Everett, Mark; Endl, Michael; Demory, Brice-Oliver; Deming, Drake; Charbonneau, David; Caldwell, Douglas; Buchhave, Lars; Brown, Timothy M.; Batalha, Natalie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....7C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....5F</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-10 c: a 2.2 Earth Radius Transiting Planet in a Multiple System</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Franois; Torres, Guillermo; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Charbonneau, David; Batalha, Natalie M.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Allen, Christopher; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Deming, Drake; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Knutson, Heather; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Uddin, Kamal</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 5 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....5F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...741L..30R</bibcode>
			<title>The Orbital Phases and Secondary Transits of Kepler-10b. A Physical Interpretation Based on the Lava-ocean Planet Model</title>
			<authors>Rouan, D.; Deeg, H. J.; Demangeon, O.; Samuel, B.; Cavarroc, C.; Fegley, B.; Lger, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 741, Issue 2, article id. L30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...741L..30R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417L..16G</bibcode>
			<title>Potential biases in the detection of planetary systems with large transit timing variations</title>
			<authors>Garca-Melendo, E.; Lpez-Morales, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 417, Issue 1, pp. L16-L20.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417L..16G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534A..58P</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for Earth-like planets in the habitable zone. I. Very low-mass planets around HD 20794, HD 85512, and HD 192310</title>
			<authors>Pepe, F.; Lovis, C.; Sgransan, D.; Benz, W.; Bouchy, F.; Dumusque, X.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.A58</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534A..58P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534A..26V</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic characterization of the atmospheres of potentially habitable planets: GL 581 d as a model case study</title>
			<authors>von Paris, P.; Cabrera, J.; Godolt, M.; Grenfell, J. L.; Hedelt, P.; Rauer, H.; Schreier, F.; Stracke, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.A26</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534A..26V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A.136H</bibcode>
			<title>Venus transit 2004: Illustrating the capability of exoplanet transmission spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Hedelt, P.; Alonso, R.; Brown, T.; Collados Vera, M.; Rauer, H.; Schleicher, H.; Schmidt, W.; Schreier, F.; Titz, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A136</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A.136H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A.130H</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XVIII. CoRoT-18b: a massive hot Jupiter on a prograde, nearly aligned orbit</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Evans, T. M.; Alonso, R.; Fridlund, M.; Ofir, A.; Aigrain, S.; Guillot, T.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cavarroc, C.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Daz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Gandolfi, D.; Gibson, N.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Ptzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A130</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A.130H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A.114D</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a transit of the super-Earth 55 Cancri e with warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Demory, B.-O.; Gillon, M.; Deming, D.; Valencia, D.; Seager, S.; Benneke, B.; Lovis, C.; Cubillos, P.; Harrington, J.; Stevenson, K. B.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A114</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A.114D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..44L</bibcode>
			<title>Deriving the radial-velocity variations induced by stellar activity from high-precision photometry. Test on HD 189733 with simultaneous MOST/SOPHIE data</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Moutou, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A44</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..44L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.2349R</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal decay and orbital circularization in close-in two-planet systems</title>
			<authors>Rodrguez, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Michtchenko, T. A.; Beaug, C.; Miloni, O.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 3, pp. 2349-2358.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.2349R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.2275M</bibcode>
			<title>Modelling the secular evolution of migrating planet pairs</title>
			<authors>Michtchenko, T. A.; Rodrguez, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 3, pp. 2275-2292.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.2275M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737L..18W</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth Transiting a Naked-eye Star</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Dawson, Rebekah I.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Holman, Matthew J.; Kallinger, Thomas; Kuschnig, Rainer; Sasselov, Dimitar; Dragomir, Diana; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Rucinski, Slavek; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 737, Issue 1, article id. L18 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737L..18W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Broadband Transmission Spectroscopy of the Super-Earth GJ 1214b Suggests a Low Mean Molecular Weight Atmosphere</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Miller-Ricci Kempton, Eliza; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman; Neilson, Hilding</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. 78 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..58V</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric studies of habitability in the Gliese 581 system</title>
			<authors>von Paris, P.; Gebauer, S.; Godolt, M.; Rauer, H.; Stracke, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A58</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..58V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A...1S</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal phase curves of nontransiting terrestrial exoplanets. I. Characterizing atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Selsis, F.; Wordsworth, R. D.; Forget, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A1</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A...1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..15V</bibcode>
			<title>Mantle Convection, Plate Tectonics, and Volcanism on Hot Exo-Earths</title>
			<authors>van Summeren, Joost; Conrad, Clinton P.; Gaidos, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. L15 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..15V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...12B</bibcode>
			<title>The GJ1214 Super-Earth System: Stellar Variability, New Transits, and a Search for Additional Planets</title>
			<authors>Berta, Zachory K.; Charbonneau, David; Bean, Jacob; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Nutzman, Philip; Falco, Emilio E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 12 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...12B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...72G</bibcode>
			<title>Effects of Stellar Flux on Tidally Locked Terrestrial Planets: Degree-1 Mantle Convection and Local Magma Ponds</title>
			<authors>Gelman, S. E.; Elkins-Tanton, L. T.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 2, article id. 72 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735...72G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A.161F</bibcode>
			<title>On the mass determination of super-Earths orbiting active stars: the CoRoT-7 system</title>
			<authors>Ferraz-Mello, S.; Tadeu Dos Santos, M.; Beaug, C.; Michtchenko, T. A.; Rodrguez, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A161</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A.161F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A...5P</bibcode>
			<title>On the dynamics of resonant super-Earths in disks with turbulence driven by stochastic forcing</title>
			<authors>Pierens, A.; Baruteau, C.; Hersant, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A5</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A...5P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A...3H</bibcode>
			<title>The multiple planets transiting Kepler-9. I. Inferring stellar properties and planetary compositions</title>
			<authors>Havel, M.; Guillot, T.; Valencia, D.; Crida, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A3</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A...3H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1788B</bibcode>
			<title>Evaporation of Jupiter-like planets orbiting extreme horizontal branch stars</title>
			<authors>Bear, Ealeal; Soker, Noam</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1788-1792.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1788B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...35K</bibcode>
			<title>Model Spectra of the First Potentially Habitable Super-Earth---Gl581d</title>
			<authors>Kaltenegger, Lisa; Segura, Antgona; Mohanty, Subhanjoy</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 35 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...35K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733....2N</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Evolution and Structure Models of the Transiting Super-Earth GJ 1214b</title>
			<authors>Nettelmann, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Kramm, U.; Redmer, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733....2N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..24L</bibcode>
			<title>A First Comparison of Kepler Planet Candidates in Single and Multiple Systems</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Wohler, Bill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..24L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A...8R</bibcode>
			<title>Potential biosignatures in super-Earth atmospheres. I. Spectral appearance of super-Earths around M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Rauer, H.; Gebauer, S.; Paris, P. V.; Cabrera, J.; Godolt, M.; Grenfell, J. L.; Belu, A.; Selsis, F.; Hedelt, P.; Schreier, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A8</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A...8R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...731..123K</bibcode>
			<title>APOSTLE Observations of GJ 1214b: System Parameters and Evidence for Stellar Activity</title>
			<authors>Kundurthy, P.; Agol, E.; Becker, A. C.; Barnes, R.; Williams, B.; Mukadam, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 731, Issue 2, article id. 123 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...731..123K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...731...16B</bibcode>
			<title>Methane in the Atmosphere of the Transiting Hot Neptune GJ436B?</title>
			<authors>Beaulieu, J.-P.; Tinetti, G.; Kipping, D. M.; Ribas, I.; Barber, R. J.; Cho, J. Y.-K.; Polichtchouk, I.; Tennyson, J.; Yurchenko, S. N.; Griffith, C. A.; Batista, V.; Waldmann, I.; Miller, S.; Carey, S.; Mousis, O.; Fossey, S. J.; Aylward, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 731, Issue 1, article id. 16 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...731...16B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A.112L</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XXVIII. Up to seven planets orbiting HD 10180: probing the architecture of low-mass planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Lovis, C.; Sgransan, D.; Mayor, M.; Udry, S.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Bouchy, F.; Correia, A. C. M.; Laskar, J.; Lo Curto, G.; Mordasini, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A112</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A.112L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..97T</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XVI. CoRoT-14b: an unusually dense very hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Endl, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Alonso, R.; Mazeh, T.; Jorda, L.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord , P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carpano, S.; Carone, L.; Cochran, W. D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A97</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..97T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A...4B</bibcode>
			<title>Disentangling between stellar activity and planetary signals</title>
			<authors>Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Hbrard, G.; Bonfils, X.; Santos, N.; Vauclair, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A4</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A...4B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A...2B</bibcode>
			<title>The mass-period distribution of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Bentez-Llambay, P.; Masset, F.; Beaug, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A2</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A...2B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1953P</bibcode>
			<title>Reassessing the radial-velocity evidence for planets around CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Aigrain, Suzanne; Zucker, Shay</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 3, pp. 1953-1962.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1953P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1792B</bibcode>
			<title>Connecting planets around horizontal branch stars with known exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Bear, Ealeal; Soker, Noam</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 3, pp. 1792-1802.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1792B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...41M</bibcode>
			<title>High Metallicity and Non-equilibrium Chemistry in the Dayside Atmosphere of hot-Neptune GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...41M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...27B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler's First Rocky Planet: Kepler-10b</title>
			<authors>Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Ciardi, David; Dunham, Edward W.; Fressin, Francois; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Torres, Guillermo; Basri, Gibor S.; Brown, Timothy M.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie; Clarke, Bruce; Cochran, William D.; Dupree, Andrea; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fischer, Debra; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Girouard, Forrest R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Johnson, John; Isaacson, Howard; Klaus, Todd C.; Machalek, Pavel; Moorehead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Twicken, Joseph; Quinn, Samuel; VanCleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Welsh, William F.; Devore, Edna; Gould, Alan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 27 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...27B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729....6S</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Chemistry of Venus-like Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Schaefer, Laura; Fegley, Bruce, Jr.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 6 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729....6S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411L..46V</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for detection of exoplanet magnetic fields through bow-shock observations during transits</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. L46-L50.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411L..46V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..138H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-26b: A Low-density Neptune-mass Planet Transiting a K Star</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Kipping, D. M.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Quinn, S. N.; Buchhave, L. A.; Bky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 138 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728...19P</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the Atmospheres of Transiting Rocky Planets Around Late-type Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Pall, E.; Zapatero Osorio, M. R.; Garca Muoz, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728...19P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727L..44S</bibcode>
			<title>A Short-period Censor of Sub-Jupiter Mass Exoplanets with Low Density</title>
			<authors>Szab, Gy. M.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. L44 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727L..44S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...24T</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling Kepler Transit Light Curves as False Positives: Rejection of Blend Scenarios for Kepler-9, and Validation of Kepler-9 d, A Super-earth-size Planet in a Multiple System</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Franois; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David R.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Monet, David G.; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...24T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...73H</bibcode>
			<title>The NASA-UC Eta-Earth Program. II. A Planet Orbiting HD 156668 with a Minimum Mass of Four Earth Masses</title>
			<authors>Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Wright, Jason T.; Henry, Gregory W.; Isaacson, Howard; Valenti, Jeff A.; Anderson, Jay; Piskunov, Nikolai E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 73 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...73H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...70T</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Evolution and Lifetime of Intrinsic Magnetic Fields of Super-Earths in Habitable Zones</title>
			<authors>Tachinami, C.; Senshu, H.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 70 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...70T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..32G</bibcode>
			<title>An educated search for transiting habitable planets:. Targetting M dwarfs with known transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Bonfils, X.; Demory, B.-O.; Seager, S.; Deming, D.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A32</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..32G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..24G</bibcode>
			<title>Constraints on the exosphere of CoRoT-7b</title>
			<authors>Guenther, E. W.; Cabrera, J.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Lammer, H.; Mura, A.; Rauer, H.; Schneider, J.; Tulej, M.; von Paris, Ph.; Wurz, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A24</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..24G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010BASI...38..137L</bibcode>
			<title>Evaporation of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the Astronomical Soceity of India, Vol. 38, p. 137-145, 2010</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010BASI...38..137L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1341B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for a Sub-Earth-Sized Companion to GJ 436 and a Novel Method to Calibrate Warm Spitzer IRAC Observations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Seager, Sara; A'Hearn, Michael F.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 897, pp.1341-1352</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1341B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724L..53S</bibcode>
			<title>A Population of Very Hot Super-Earths in Multiple-planet Systems Should be Uncovered by Kepler</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.; Lin, D. N. C.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. L53-L58 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724L..53S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723L..60H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-29b: A Saturn-sized Transiting Exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Enoch, B.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S gransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. L60-L63 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723L..60H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.1370K</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting Volcanism on Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Kaltenegger, L.; Henning, W. G.; Sasselov, D. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 5, pp. 1370-1380 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.1370K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..26N</bibcode>
			<title>Interior structure models of GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Nettelmann, N.; Kramm, U.; Redmer, R.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A26</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..26N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A.110C</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission . XIII. CoRoT-13b: a dense hot Jupiter in transit around a star with solar metallicity and super-solar lithium content</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Bruntt, H.; Ollivier, M.; Daz, R. F.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; von Paris, P.; Ptzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Titz-Weider, R.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A110</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...522A.110C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A..23V</bibcode>
			<title>The extrasolar planet Gliese 581d: a potentially habitable planet?</title>
			<authors>von Paris, P.; Gebauer, S.; Godolt, M.; Grenfell, J. L.; Hedelt, P.; Kitzmann, D.; Patzer, A. B. C.; Rauer, H.; Stracke, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A23</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...522A..23V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2625M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation in exoplanet WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuhuser, R.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Ginski, Ch.; Adam, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2625-2631.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2625M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721.1295D</bibcode>
			<title>Habitable Climates: The Influence of Eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Dressing, Courtney D.; Spiegel, David S.; Scharf, Caleb A.; Menou, Kristen; Raymond, Sean N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. 1295-1307 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...721.1295D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..83G</bibcode>
			<title>High-resolution infrared spectroscopy as a tool to detect false positives of transit search programs</title>
			<authors>Guenther, E. W.; Tal-Or, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A83</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..83G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407..910J</bibcode>
			<title>The roles of tidal evolution and evaporative mass loss in the origin of CoRoT-7 b</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Miller, Neil; Barnes, Rory; Raymond, Sean N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 910-922.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407..910J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..97G</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XII. CoRoT-12b: a short-period low-density planet transiting a solar analog star</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Hatzes, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Fridlund, M.; Deleuil, M.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Barnes, S. I.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J. C.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Montalbn, J.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A97</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..97G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..93H</bibcode>
			<title>An investigation into the radial velocity variations of CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Hatzes, A. P.; Dvorak, R.; Wuchterl, G.; Guterman, P.; Hartmann, M.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Guenther, E.; Ptzold, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A93</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..93H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..66B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XI. CoRoT-8b: a hot and dense sub-Saturn around a K1 dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Cabrera, J.; Jorda, L.; Lovis, C.; Csizmadia, S.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Ollivier, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A66</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..66B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..53L</bibcode>
			<title>Photospheric activity, rotation, and radial velocity variations of the planet-hosting star CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Moutou, C.; Pagano, I.; Messina, S.; Leto, G.; Cutispoto, G.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Barge, P.; Deleuil, M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Collier Cameron, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A53</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A..51B</bibcode>
			<title>Improved stellar parameters of CoRoT-7. A star hosting two super Earths</title>
			<authors>Bruntt, H.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; Alonso, R.; Bouchy, F.; Hatzes, A.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A51</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A..51B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719L..45M</bibcode>
			<title>Water/Icy Super-Earths: Giant Impacts and Maximum Water Content</title>
			<authors>Marcus, Robert A.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Stewart, Sarah T.; Hernquist, Lars</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. L45-L49 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719L..45M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..596G</bibcode>
			<title>Thermodynamic Limits on Magnetodynamos in Rocky Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Gaidos, Eric; Conrad, Clinton P.; Manga, Michael; Hernlund, John</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 596-609 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..596G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;ARv..18..383J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability: from stars to cells</title>
			<authors>Javaux, Emmanuelle J.; Dehant, Vronique</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomy and Astrophysics Review, Volume 18, Issue 3, pp.383-416</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26ARv..18..383J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518A..25G</bibcode>
			<title>The Spitzer search for the transits of HARPS low-mass planets. I. No transit for the super-Earth HD 40307b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Deming, D.; Demory, B.-O.; Lovis, C.; Seager, S.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Delmelle, S.; Magain, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.A25</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518A..25G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405..573P</bibcode>
			<title>On the dynamics of multiple systems of hot super-Earths and Neptunes: tidal circularization, resonance and the HD 40307 system</title>
			<authors>Papaloizou, John C. B.; Terquem, Caroline</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 1, pp. 573-592.</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405..573P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716L..74M</bibcode>
			<title>The Nature of the Atmosphere of the Transiting Super-Earth GJ 1214b</title>
			<authors>Miller-Ricci, Eliza; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 716, Issue 1, pp. L74-L79 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716L..74M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1208R</bibcode>
			<title>Three Possible Origins for the Gas Layer on GJ 1214b</title>
			<authors>Rogers, L. A.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1208-1216 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1208R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..866F</bibcode>
			<title>Colors of a Second Earth: Estimating the Fractional Areas of Ocean, Land, and Vegetation of Earth-like Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Fujii, Yuka; Kawahara, Hajime; Suto, Yasushi; Taruya, Atsushi; Fukuda, Satoru; Nakajima, Teruyuki; Turner, Edwin L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 2, pp. 866-880 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..866F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..82F</bibcode>
			<title>The stability of ultra-compact planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Funk, B.; Wuchterl, G.; Schwarz, R.; Pilat-Lohinger, E.; Eggl, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A82</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..82F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..20V</bibcode>
			<title>Composition and fate of short-period super-Earths. The case of CoRoT-7b</title>
			<authors>Valencia, D.; Ikoma, M.; Guillot, T.; Nettelmann, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A20</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..20V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714..462S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Apparent Orbital Inclination Change of the Extrasolar Transiting Planet TrES-2b</title>
			<authors>Scuderi, Louis J.; Dittmann, Jason A.; Males, Jared R.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Close, Laird M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 462-468 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714..462S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010JRASC.104...75S</bibcode>
			<title>Second Light: A Plethora of Planets</title>
			<authors>Sage, Leslie J.</authors>
			<journal>Journal of the Royal Society of Canada, Vol. 104, No. 2, p.75</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010JRASC.104...75S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.126B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-4b: A Hot Neptune-like Planet of a G0 Star Near Main-sequence Turnoff</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Brown, Timothy M.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Monet, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, article id. L126-L130 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.126B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..974R</bibcode>
			<title>A Framework for Quantifying the Degeneracies of Exoplanet Interior Compositions</title>
			<authors>Rogers, L. A.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 2, pp. 974-991 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..974R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.464..384D</bibcode>
			<title>A transiting giant planet with a temperature between 250K and 430K</title>
			<authors>Deeg, H. J.; Moutou, C.; Erikson, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Tingley, B.; Barge, P.; Bruntt, H.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Ciardi, D.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hartog, R. Den; Hatzes, A.; Hidas, M.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Lister, T.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Street, R.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 464, Issue 7287, pp. 384-387 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Natur.464..384D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..14F</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. IX. CoRoT-6b: a transiting ``hot Jupiter'' planet in an 8.9d orbit around a low-metallicity star</title>
			<authors>Fridlund, M.; Hbrard, G.; Alonso, R.; Deleuil, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Bruntt, H.; Alapini, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Guillot, T.; Lammer, H.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Guenther, E.; Gondoin, P.; den Hartog, R.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..14F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1724B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-11b: A Super-Neptune Planet Transiting a Bright K Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Pl, A.; Hartman, J.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Isaacson, H.; Howard, A.; Vogt, S.; Kovcs, Gbor; Fernandez, J.; Mor, A.; Stefanik, R. P.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1724-1745 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709L..95B</bibcode>
			<title>CoRoT-7b: Super-Earth or Super-Io?</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Rory; Raymond, Sean N.; Greenberg, Richard; Jackson, Brian; Kaib, Nathan A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 709, Issue 2, pp. L95-L98 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709L..95B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..149S</bibcode>
			<title>Models of Neptune-Mass Exoplanets: Emergent Fluxes and Albedos</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent; Hubeny, Ivan; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 149-158 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..149S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708.1492R</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth Orbiting the Nearby Sun-like Star HD 1461</title>
			<authors>Rivera, Eugenio J.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Laughlin, Gregory; Henry, Gregory W.; Meschiari, Stefano</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 2, pp. 1492-1499 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...708.1492R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708.1162K</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting Planetary Geochemical Cycles on Exoplanets: Atmospheric Signatures and the Case of SO2</title>
			<authors>Kaltenegger, L.; Sasselov, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 2, pp. 1162-1167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...708.1162K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PABei..28...53J</bibcode>
			<title>Proper motions and the frontier of studies on the Galaxy.</title>
			<authors>Jin, W.-J.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 28, 53-71 (2010)</journal>
			<date>0/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PABei..28...53J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Natur.462..891C</bibcode>
			<title>A super-Earth transiting a nearby low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Berta, Zachory K.; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; Nutzman, Philip; Buchhave, Lars A.; Lovis, Christophe; Bonfils, Xavier; Latham, David W.; Udry, Stphane; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Falco, Emilio E.; Winn, Joshua N.; Queloz, Didier; Pepe, Francesco; Mayor, Michel; Delfosse, Xavier; Forveille, Thierry</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 462, Issue 7275, pp. 891-894 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Natur.462..891C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508.1509H</bibcode>
			<title>Transit detections of extrasolar planets around main-sequence stars. I. Sky maps for hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Heller, R.; Mislis, D.; Antoniadis, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1509-1516</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508.1509H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..785H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-12b: A Low-Density Sub-Saturn Mass Planet Transiting a Metal-Poor K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Pl, A.; Latham, D. W.; Sipocz, B.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kovcs, Gbor; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 785-796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..785H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703L.113S</bibcode>
			<title>Chemistry of Silicate Atmospheres of Evaporating Super-Earths</title>
			<authors>Schaefer, Laura; Fegley, Bruce</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. L113-L117 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703L.113S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..501C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in CoRoT-LRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Fridlund, M.; Ollivier, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord , P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Hatzes, A.; Hebrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R gulo, C.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.501-517</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..501C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..445O</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for transiting circumbinary planets in CoRoT and ground-based data using CB-BLS</title>
			<authors>Ofir, A.; Deeg, H. J.; Lacy, C. H. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.445-453</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..445O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..431M</bibcode>
			<title>Removing systematics from the CoRoT light curves. I. Magnitude-dependent zero point</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Guterman, P.; Aigrain, S.; Zucker, S.; Grinberg, N.; Alapini, A.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deeg, H.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Sabo, R.; Schneider, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.431-434</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..431M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..385L</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and evolution of the first CoRoT exoplanets: probing the brown dwarf/planet overlapping mass regime</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.385-389</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..385L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..343D</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based photometry of space-based transit detections: photometric follow-up of the CoRoT  mission</title>
			<authors>Deeg, H. J.; Gillon, M.; Shporer, A.; Rouan, D.; Stecklum, B.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Bouchy, F.; Eisl ffel, J.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Eigmller, P.; Handler, G.; Hatzes, A.; Kabath, P.; Lendl, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rabus, M.; Tingley, B.; Titz, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.343-352</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..343D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..337A</bibcode>
			<title>Rate and nature of false positives in the CoRoT exoplanet search</title>
			<authors>Almenara, J. M.; Deeg, H. J.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Catala, C.; Csizmadia, Sz.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rgulo, C.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.337-341</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..337A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..303Q</bibcode>
			<title>The CoRoT-7 planetary system: two orbiting super-Earths</title>
			<authors>Queloz, D.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Jorda, L.; Hartmann, M.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.303-319</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..303Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..287L</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. VIII. CoRoT-7b: the first super-Earth with measured radius</title>
			<authors>Lger, A.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Barge, P.; Fridlund, M.; Samuel, B.; Ollivier, M.; Guenther, E.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Auvergne, M.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J. M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Bruntt, H.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Catala, C.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Foing, B.; Fressin, F.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, Ph.; Grasset, O.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ptzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Renner, S.; Samadi, R.; Shporer, A.; Sotin, Ch.; Tingley, B.; Wuchterl, G.; Adda, M.; Agogu, P.; Appourchaux, T.; Ballans, H.; Baron, P.; Beaufort, T.; Bellenger, R.; Berlin, R.; Bernardi, P.; Blouin, D.; Baudin, F.; Bodin, P.; Boisnard, L.; Boit, L.; Bonneau, F.; Borzeix, S.; Briet, R.; Buey, J.-T.; Butler, B.; Cailleau, D.; Cautain, R.; Chabaud, P.-Y.; Chaintreuil, S.; Chiavassa, F.; Costes, V.; Cuna Parrho, V.; de Oliveira Fialho, F.; Decaudin, M.; Defise, J.-M.; Djalal, S.; Epstein, G.; Exil, G.-E.; Faur, C.; Fenouillet, T.; Gaboriaud, A.; Gallic, A.; Gamet, P.; Gavalda, P.; Grolleau, E.; Gruneisen, R.; Gueguen, L.; Guis, V.; Guivarc'h, V.; Guterman, P.; Hallouard, D.; Hasiba, J.; Heuripeau, F.; Huntzinger, G.; Hustaix, H.; Imad, C.; Imbert, C.; Johlander, B.; Jouret, M.; Journoud, P.; Karioty, F.; Kerjean, L.; Lafaille, V.; Lafond, L.; Lam-Trong, T.; Landiech, P.; Lapeyrere, V.; Larqu, T.; Laudet, P.; Lautier, N.; Lecann, H.; Lefevre, L.; Leruyet, B.; Levacher, P.; Magnan, A.; Mazy, E.; Mertens, F.; Mesnager, J.-M.; Meunier, J.-C.; Michel, J.-P.; Monjoin, W.; Naudet, D.; Nguyen-Kim, K.; Orcesi, J.-L.; Ottacher, H.; Perez, R.; Peter, G.; Plasson, P.; Plesseria, J.-Y.; Pontet, B.; Pradines, A.; Quentin, C.; Reynaud, J.-L.; Rolland, G.; Rollenhagen, F.; Romagnan, R.; Russ, N.; Schmidt, R.; Schwartz, N.; Sebbag, I.; Sedes, G.; Smit, H.; Steller, M. B.; Sunter, W.; Surace, C.; Tello, M.; Tiphne, D.; Toulouse, P.; Ulmer, B.; Vandermarcq, O.; Vergnault, E.; Vuillemin, A.; Zanatta, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.287-302</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..287L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702..779V</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Window Functions in Planet Transit Surveys</title>
			<authors>von Braun, Kaspar; Kane, Stephen R.; Ciardi, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 1, pp. 779-790 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702..779V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700.1732K</bibcode>
			<title>Geodynamics and Rate of Volcanism on Massive Earth-like Planets</title>
			<authors>Kite, E. S.; Manga, M.; Gaidos, E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 1732-1749 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700.1732K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700L..30B</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Limits to Planetary Habitability</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Rory; Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Raymond, Sean N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. L30-L33 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700L..30B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699L..48D</bibcode>
			<title>Follow-up Observations of the Neptune Mass Transiting Extrasolar Planet HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, Jason A.; Close, Laird M.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Scuderi, Louis J.; Males, Jared R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. L48-L51 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699L..48D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698..519K</bibcode>
			<title>Transits of Earth-like Planets</title>
			<authors>Kaltenegger, Lisa; Traub, Wesley A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 1, pp. 519-527 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698..519K</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..172M</bibcode>
			<title>A New Multi-band Radial Velocity Technique for Detecting Exoplanets around Active Stars</title>
			<authors>Ma, Bo; Ge, Jian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 172 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750..172M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A.103W</bibcode>
			<title>Rocky super-Earth interiors. Structure and internal dynamics of CoRoT-7b and Kepler-10b</title>
			<authors>Wagner, F. W.; Tosi, N.; Sohl, F.; Rauer, H.; Spohn, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A103</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A.103W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..26P</bibcode>
			<title>The high-energy environment in the super-Earth system CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Poppenhaeger, K.; Czesla, S.; Schrter, S.; Lalitha, S.; Kashyap, V.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A26</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..26P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749..134H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-17b,c: A Transiting, Eccentric, Hot Saturn and a Long-period, Cold Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Howard, A. W.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Mazeh, T.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Bky, B.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 2, article id. 134 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749..134H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749...15G</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-20: A Sun-like Star with Three Sub-Neptune Exoplanets and Two Earth-size Candidates</title>
			<authors>Gautier, Thomas N., III; Charbonneau, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Francois; Rogers, Leslie A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ciardi, David R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Howell, Steve B.; Horch, Elliott P.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Borucki, William J.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Silverio, Kathryn; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Still, Martin; Stumpe, Martin C.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 1, article id. 15 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749...15G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A.140B</bibcode>
			<title>Multiwavelength flux variations induced by stellar magnetic activity: effects on planetary transits</title>
			<authors>Ballerini, P.; Micela, G.; Lanza, A. F.; Pagano, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A140</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A.140B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..28G</bibcode>
			<title>Improved precision on the radius of the nearby super-Earth 55 Cnc e</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Demory, B.-O.; Benneke, B.; Valencia, D.; Deming, D.; Seager, S.; Lovis, Ch.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A28</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..28G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.420.1045G</bibcode>
			<title>The needle in the haystack: searching for transiting extrasolar planets in CoRoT stellar light curves</title>
			<authors>Grziwa, S.; Ptzold, M.; Carone, L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 420, Issue 2, pp. 1045-1052.</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.420.1045G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A.112C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT LRa01 field</title>
			<authors>Carone, L.; Gandolfi, D.; Cabrera, J.; Hatzes, A. P.; Deeg, H. J.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Ptzold, M.; Weingrill, J.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deleuil, M.; Daz, R. F.; Dreizler, S.; Dvorak, R.; Eislffel, J.; Eigmller, P.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gibson, N.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Grziwa, S.; Gnther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Nortmann, L.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R gulo, C.; Renner, S.; de La Reza, R.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A112</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A.112C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewAR..56...19M</bibcode>
			<title>From 51 Peg to Earth-type planets</title>
			<authors>Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 56, Issue 1, p. 19-24.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012NewAR..56...19M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...81F</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Infrared Observations and Independent Validation of the Transiting Super-Earth CoRoT-7 b</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Pont, Frederic; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Mazeh, Tsevi; Aigrain, Suzanne; Fridlund, Malcolm; Henze, Christopher E.; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 81 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...81F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..189A</bibcode>
			<title>A High Stellar Obliquity in the WASP-7 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Albrecht, Simon; Winn, Joshua N.; Butler, R. Paul; Crane, Jeffrey D.; Shectman, Stephen A.; Thompson, Ian B.; Hirano, Teruyuki; Wittenmyer, Robert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 189 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744..189A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744...59S</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-Radius Relationships for Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Swift, D. C.; Eggert, J. H.; Hicks, D. G.; Hamel, S.; Caspersen, K.; Schwegler, E.; Collins, G. W.; Nettelmann, N.; Ackland, G. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744...59S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143....4H</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Cycle 1 Observations of Low-mass Stars: New Eclipsing Binaries, Single Star Rotation Rates, and the Nature and Frequency of Starspots</title>
			<authors>Harrison, T. E.; Coughlin, J. L.; Ule, N. M.; Lpez-Morales, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 1, article id. 4 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143....4H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A.147H</bibcode>
			<title>Optimizing exoplanet transit searches around low-mass stars with inclination constraints</title>
			<authors>Herrero, E.; Ribas, I.; Jordi, C.; Guinan, E. F.; Engle, S. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 537, id.A147</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...537A.147H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418.1039M</bibcode>
			<title>UBV(RI)C photometry of transiting planet hosting stars</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Koen, C.; Smalley, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 418, Issue 2, pp. 1039-1042.</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.418.1039M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...75H</bibcode>
			<title>The Mass of CoRoT-7b</title>
			<authors>Hatzes, Artie P.; Fridlund, Malcolm; Nachmani, Gil; Mazeh, Tsevi; Valencia, Diana; Hbrard, Guillaume; Carone, Ludmila; Ptzold, Martin; Udry, Stephane; Bouchy, Francois; Deleuil, Magali; Moutou, Claire; Barge, Pierre; Bord , Pascal; Deeg, Hans; Tingley, Brandon; Dvorak, Rudolf; Gandolfi, Davide; Ferraz-Mello, Sylvio; Wuchterl, Gnther; Guenther, Eike; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike; Erikson, Anders; Cabrera, Juan; Csizmadia, Szilard; Lger, Alain; Lammer, Helmut; Weingrill, Jrg; Queloz, Didier; Alonso, Roi; Rouan, Daniel; Schneider, Jean</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...75H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...41K</bibcode>
			<title>Climate Instability on Tidally Locked Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Kite, Edwin S.; Gaidos, Eric; Manga, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...41K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..44L</bibcode>
			<title>Deriving the radial-velocity variations induced by stellar activity from high-precision photometry. Test on HD 189733 with simultaneous MOST/SOPHIE data</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Moutou, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A44</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..44L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.2349R</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal decay and orbital circularization in close-in two-planet systems</title>
			<authors>Rodrguez, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Michtchenko, T. A.; Beaug, C.; Miloni, O.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 3, pp. 2349-2358.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.2349R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.2275M</bibcode>
			<title>Modelling the secular evolution of migrating planet pairs</title>
			<authors>Michtchenko, T. A.; Rodrguez, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 3, pp. 2275-2292.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.2275M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..79S</bibcode>
			<title>Defining and cataloging exoplanets: the exoplanet.eu database</title>
			<authors>Schneider, J.; Dedieu, C.; Le Sidaner, P.; Savalle, R.; Zolotukhin, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A79</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..79S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...12B</bibcode>
			<title>The GJ1214 Super-Earth System: Stellar Variability, New Transits, and a Search for Additional Planets</title>
			<authors>Berta, Zachory K.; Charbonneau, David; Bean, Jacob; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Nutzman, Philip; Falco, Emilio E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 12 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...12B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...72G</bibcode>
			<title>Effects of Stellar Flux on Tidally Locked Terrestrial Planets: Degree-1 Mantle Convection and Local Magma Ponds</title>
			<authors>Gelman, S. E.; Elkins-Tanton, L. T.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 2, article id. 72 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735...72G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A.161F</bibcode>
			<title>On the mass determination of super-Earths orbiting active stars: the CoRoT-7 system</title>
			<authors>Ferraz-Mello, S.; Tadeu Dos Santos, M.; Beaug, C.; Michtchenko, T. A.; Rodrguez, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A161</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A.161F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414..108B</bibcode>
			<title>On the use of the Virtual Observatory to select calibrators for phase-referenced astrometry of exoplanet-host stars</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonneau, D.; Mourard, D.; Lafrasse, S.; Mella, G.; Duvert, G.; Chelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. 108-115.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414..108B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733....8G</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of a Secularly Interacting Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Greenberg, Richard; Van Laerhoven, Christa</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 8 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733....8G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733....2N</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Evolution and Structure Models of the Transiting Super-Earth GJ 1214b</title>
			<authors>Nettelmann, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Kramm, U.; Redmer, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733....2N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..24L</bibcode>
			<title>A First Comparison of Kepler Planet Candidates in Single and Multiple Systems</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Wohler, Bill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..24L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...731..123K</bibcode>
			<title>APOSTLE Observations of GJ 1214b: System Parameters and Evidence for Stellar Activity</title>
			<authors>Kundurthy, P.; Agol, E.; Becker, A. C.; Barnes, R.; Williams, B.; Mukadam, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 731, Issue 2, article id. 123 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...731..123K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A.112L</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XXVIII. Up to seven planets orbiting HD 10180: probing the architecture of low-mass planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Lovis, C.; Sgransan, D.; Mayor, M.; Udry, S.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Bouchy, F.; Correia, A. C. M.; Laskar, J.; Lo Curto, G.; Mordasini, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A112</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A.112L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A...4B</bibcode>
			<title>Disentangling between stellar activity and planetary signals</title>
			<authors>Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Hbrard, G.; Bonfils, X.; Santos, N.; Vauclair, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A4</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A...4B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A...2B</bibcode>
			<title>The mass-period distribution of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Bentez-Llambay, P.; Masset, F.; Beaug, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A2</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A...2B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1953P</bibcode>
			<title>Reassessing the radial-velocity evidence for planets around CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Aigrain, Suzanne; Zucker, Shay</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 3, pp. 1953-1962.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1953P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...98P</bibcode>
			<title>An Analysis of Jitter and Transit Timing Variations in the HAT-P-13 System</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 98 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...98P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...74V</bibcode>
			<title>Quantifying the Challenges of Detecting Unseen Planetary Companions with Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Payne, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...74V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...73H</bibcode>
			<title>The NASA-UC Eta-Earth Program. II. A Planet Orbiting HD 156668 with a Minimum Mass of Four Earth Masses</title>
			<authors>Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Wright, Jason T.; Henry, Gregory W.; Isaacson, Howard; Valenti, Jeff A.; Anderson, Jay; Piskunov, Nikolai E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 73 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...73H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..65P</bibcode>
			<title>The barycentric motion of exoplanet host stars. Tests of solar spin-orbit coupling</title>
			<authors>Perryman, M. A. C.; Schulze-Hartung, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A65</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..65P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..14L</bibcode>
			<title>Photospheric activity, rotation, and star-planet interaction of the planet-hosting star CoRoT-6</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Pagano, I.; Leto, G.; Messina, S.; Cutispoto, G.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Barge, P.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; Silva-Valio, A.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Collier Cameron, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A14</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..14L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 29, 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724L..53S</bibcode>
			<title>A Population of Very Hot Super-Earths in Multiple-planet Systems Should be Uncovered by Kepler</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.; Lin, D. N. C.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. L53-L58 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724L..53S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..954V</bibcode>
			<title>The Lick-Carnegie Exoplanet Survey: A 3.1 M &amp;oplus; Planet in the Habitable Zone of the Nearby M3V Star Gliese 581</title>
			<authors>Vogt, Steven S.; Butler, R. Paul; Rivera, E. J.; Haghighipour, N.; Henry, Gregory W.; Williamson, Michael H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 954-965 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..954V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..84S</bibcode>
			<title>A multi-site campaign to detect the transit of the second planet in HAT-P-13</title>
			<authors>Szab, Gy. M.; Kiss, L. L.; Benko, J. M.; Mezo, Gy.; Nuspl, J.; Regly, Zs.; Srneczky, K.; Simon, A. E.; Leto, G.; Zanmar Sanchez, R.; Ngeow, C.-C.; Kovri, Zs.; Szab, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A84</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..84S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407..910J</bibcode>
			<title>The roles of tidal evolution and evaporative mass loss in the origin of CoRoT-7 b</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Miller, Neil; Barnes, Rory; Raymond, Sean N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 910-922.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407..910J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1290G</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Parameters and Metallicities of Stars Hosting Jovian and Neptunian Mass Planets: A Possible Dependence of Planetary Mass on Metallicity</title>
			<authors>Ghezzi, L.; Cunha, K.; Smith, V. V.; de Arajo, F. X.; Schuler, S. C.; de la Reza, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1290-1302 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1290G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..93H</bibcode>
			<title>An investigation into the radial velocity variations of CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Hatzes, A. P.; Dvorak, R.; Wuchterl, G.; Guterman, P.; Hartmann, M.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Guenther, E.; Ptzold, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A93</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..93H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..66B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XI. CoRoT-8b: a hot and dense sub-Saturn around a K1 dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Cabrera, J.; Jorda, L.; Lovis, C.; Csizmadia, S.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Ollivier, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A66</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..66B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..53L</bibcode>
			<title>Photospheric activity, rotation, and radial velocity variations of the planet-hosting star CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Moutou, C.; Pagano, I.; Messina, S.; Leto, G.; Cutispoto, G.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Barge, P.; Deleuil, M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Collier Cameron, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A53</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A..51B</bibcode>
			<title>Improved stellar parameters of CoRoT-7. A star hosting two super Earths</title>
			<authors>Bruntt, H.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; Alonso, R.; Bouchy, F.; Hatzes, A.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A51</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A..51B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..596G</bibcode>
			<title>Thermodynamic Limits on Magnetodynamos in Rocky Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Gaidos, Eric; Conrad, Clinton P.; Manga, Michael; Hernlund, John</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 596-609 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..596G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..575W</bibcode>
			<title>The HAT-P-13 Exoplanetary System: Evidence for Spin-Orbit Alignment and a Third Companion</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Bakos, Gspr .; Hartman, Joel; Torres, Guillermo; Albrecht, Simon; Narita, Norio</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 1, pp. 575-582 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..575W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..20V</bibcode>
			<title>Composition and fate of short-period super-Earths. The case of CoRoT-7b</title>
			<authors>Valencia, D.; Ikoma, M.; Guillot, T.; Nettelmann, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A20</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..20V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..421T</bibcode>
			<title>A Prograde, Low-inclination Orbit for the Very Hot Jupiter WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Tripathi, Anjali; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Halverson, Sam; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Holman, Matthew J.; de Kleer, Katherine R.; Carter, Joshua A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Cabrera, Nicole E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 421-428 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..421T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..974R</bibcode>
			<title>A Framework for Quantifying the Degeneracies of Exoplanet Interior Compositions</title>
			<authors>Rogers, L. A.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 2, pp. 974-991 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..974R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712L..86P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Variations for Inclined and Retrograde Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.; Veras, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. L86-L92 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712L..86P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..46H</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XX. Planets around the active star BD -082823</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Udry, S.; Lo Curto, G.; Robichon, N.; Naef, D.; Ehrenreich, D.; Benz, W.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A46</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..46H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709L..95B</bibcode>
			<title>CoRoT-7b: Super-Earth or Super-Io?</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Rory; Raymond, Sean N.; Greenberg, Richard; Jackson, Brian; Kaib, Nathan A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 709, Issue 2, pp. L95-L98 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709L..95B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...510A..21S</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar limb-darkening coefficients for CoRot and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Sing, D. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 510, id.A21</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...510A..21S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708..224H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-19b: The Shortest Period Transiting Exoplanet Yet Discovered</title>
			<authors>Hebb, L.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Hellier, C.; Anderson, D. R.; Pollacco, D.; Gillon, M.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Horne, K.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 1, pp. 224-231 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...708..224H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PABei..28...53J</bibcode>
			<title>Proper motions and the frontier of studies on the Galaxy.</title>
			<authors>Jin, W.-J.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 28, 53-71 (2010)</journal>
			<date>0/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PABei..28...53J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..431M</bibcode>
			<title>Removing systematics from the CoRoT light curves. I. Magnitude-dependent zero point</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Guterman, P.; Aigrain, S.; Zucker, S.; Grinberg, N.; Alapini, A.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deeg, H.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Sabo, R.; Schneider, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.431-434</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..431M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..343D</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based photometry of space-based transit detections: photometric follow-up of the CoRoT  mission</title>
			<authors>Deeg, H. J.; Gillon, M.; Shporer, A.; Rouan, D.; Stecklum, B.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Bouchy, F.; Eisl ffel, J.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Eigmller, P.; Handler, G.; Hatzes, A.; Kabath, P.; Lendl, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rabus, M.; Tingley, B.; Titz, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.343-352</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..343D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..303Q</bibcode>
			<title>The CoRoT-7 planetary system: two orbiting super-Earths</title>
			<authors>Queloz, D.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Jorda, L.; Hartmann, M.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.303-319</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..303Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..287L</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. VIII. CoRoT-7b: the first super-Earth with measured radius</title>
			<authors>Lger, A.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Barge, P.; Fridlund, M.; Samuel, B.; Ollivier, M.; Guenther, E.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Auvergne, M.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J. M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Bruntt, H.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Catala, C.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Foing, B.; Fressin, F.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, Ph.; Grasset, O.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ptzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Renner, S.; Samadi, R.; Shporer, A.; Sotin, Ch.; Tingley, B.; Wuchterl, G.; Adda, M.; Agogu, P.; Appourchaux, T.; Ballans, H.; Baron, P.; Beaufort, T.; Bellenger, R.; Berlin, R.; Bernardi, P.; Blouin, D.; Baudin, F.; Bodin, P.; Boisnard, L.; Boit, L.; Bonneau, F.; Borzeix, S.; Briet, R.; Buey, J.-T.; Butler, B.; Cailleau, D.; Cautain, R.; Chabaud, P.-Y.; Chaintreuil, S.; Chiavassa, F.; Costes, V.; Cuna Parrho, V.; de Oliveira Fialho, F.; Decaudin, M.; Defise, J.-M.; Djalal, S.; Epstein, G.; Exil, G.-E.; Faur, C.; Fenouillet, T.; Gaboriaud, A.; Gallic, A.; Gamet, P.; Gavalda, P.; Grolleau, E.; Gruneisen, R.; Gueguen, L.; Guis, V.; Guivarc'h, V.; Guterman, P.; Hallouard, D.; Hasiba, J.; Heuripeau, F.; Huntzinger, G.; Hustaix, H.; Imad, C.; Imbert, C.; Johlander, B.; Jouret, M.; Journoud, P.; Karioty, F.; Kerjean, L.; Lafaille, V.; Lafond, L.; Lam-Trong, T.; Landiech, P.; Lapeyrere, V.; Larqu, T.; Laudet, P.; Lautier, N.; Lecann, H.; Lefevre, L.; Leruyet, B.; Levacher, P.; Magnan, A.; Mazy, E.; Mertens, F.; Mesnager, J.-M.; Meunier, J.-C.; Michel, J.-P.; Monjoin, W.; Naudet, D.; Nguyen-Kim, K.; Orcesi, J.-L.; Ottacher, H.; Perez, R.; Peter, G.; Plasson, P.; Plesseria, J.-Y.; Pontet, B.; Pradines, A.; Quentin, C.; Reynaud, J.-L.; Rolland, G.; Rollenhagen, F.; Romagnan, R.; Russ, N.; Schmidt, R.; Schwartz, N.; Sebbag, I.; Sedes, G.; Smit, H.; Steller, M. B.; Sunter, W.; Surace, C.; Tello, M.; Tiphne, D.; Toulouse, P.; Ulmer, B.; Vandermarcq, O.; Vergnault, E.; Vuillemin, A.; Zanatta, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.287-302</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..287L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
