<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..26P</bibcode>
			<title>The high-energy environment in the super-Earth system CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Poppenhaeger, K.; Czesla, S.; Schrter, S.; Lalitha, S.; Kashyap, V.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A26</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..26P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A.112C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT LRa01 field</title>
			<authors>Carone, L.; Gandolfi, D.; Cabrera, J.; Hatzes, A. P.; Deeg, H. J.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Ptzold, M.; Weingrill, J.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deleuil, M.; Daz, R. F.; Dreizler, S.; Dvorak, R.; Eislffel, J.; Eigmller, P.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gibson, N.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Grziwa, S.; Gnther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Nortmann, L.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R gulo, C.; Renner, S.; de La Reza, R.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A112</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A.112C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...75H</bibcode>
			<title>The Mass of CoRoT-7b</title>
			<authors>Hatzes, Artie P.; Fridlund, Malcolm; Nachmani, Gil; Mazeh, Tsevi; Valencia, Diana; Hbrard, Guillaume; Carone, Ludmila; Ptzold, Martin; Udry, Stephane; Bouchy, Francois; Deleuil, Magali; Moutou, Claire; Barge, Pierre; Bord , Pascal; Deeg, Hans; Tingley, Brandon; Dvorak, Rudolf; Gandolfi, Davide; Ferraz-Mello, Sylvio; Wuchterl, Gnther; Guenther, Eike; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike; Erikson, Anders; Cabrera, Juan; Csizmadia, Szilard; Lger, Alain; Lammer, Helmut; Weingrill, Jrg; Queloz, Didier; Alonso, Roi; Rouan, Daniel; Schneider, Jean</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...75H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..44L</bibcode>
			<title>Deriving the radial-velocity variations induced by stellar activity from high-precision photometry. Test on HD 189733 with simultaneous MOST/SOPHIE data</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Moutou, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A44</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..44L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.2349R</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal decay and orbital circularization in close-in two-planet systems</title>
			<authors>Rodrguez, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Michtchenko, T. A.; Beaug, C.; Miloni, O.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 3, pp. 2349-2358.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.2349R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.2275M</bibcode>
			<title>Modelling the secular evolution of migrating planet pairs</title>
			<authors>Michtchenko, T. A.; Rodrguez, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 3, pp. 2275-2292.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.2275M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...12B</bibcode>
			<title>The GJ1214 Super-Earth System: Stellar Variability, New Transits, and a Search for Additional Planets</title>
			<authors>Berta, Zachory K.; Charbonneau, David; Bean, Jacob; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Nutzman, Philip; Falco, Emilio E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 12 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...12B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...72G</bibcode>
			<title>Effects of Stellar Flux on Tidally Locked Terrestrial Planets: Degree-1 Mantle Convection and Local Magma Ponds</title>
			<authors>Gelman, S. E.; Elkins-Tanton, L. T.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 2, article id. 72 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735...72G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A.161F</bibcode>
			<title>On the mass determination of super-Earths orbiting active stars: the CoRoT-7 system</title>
			<authors>Ferraz-Mello, S.; Tadeu Dos Santos, M.; Beaug, C.; Michtchenko, T. A.; Rodrguez, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A161</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A.161F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..24L</bibcode>
			<title>A First Comparison of Kepler Planet Candidates in Single and Multiple Systems</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Wohler, Bill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..24L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A...4B</bibcode>
			<title>Disentangling between stellar activity and planetary signals</title>
			<authors>Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Hbrard, G.; Bonfils, X.; Santos, N.; Vauclair, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A4</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A...4B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1953P</bibcode>
			<title>Reassessing the radial-velocity evidence for planets around CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Aigrain, Suzanne; Zucker, Shay</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 3, pp. 1953-1962.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1953P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1792B</bibcode>
			<title>Connecting planets around horizontal branch stars with known exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Bear, Ealeal; Soker, Noam</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 3, pp. 1792-1802.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1792B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..24G</bibcode>
			<title>Constraints on the exosphere of CoRoT-7b</title>
			<authors>Guenther, E. W.; Cabrera, J.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Lammer, H.; Mura, A.; Rauer, H.; Schneider, J.; Tulej, M.; von Paris, Ph.; Wurz, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A24</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..24G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407..910J</bibcode>
			<title>The roles of tidal evolution and evaporative mass loss in the origin of CoRoT-7 b</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Miller, Neil; Barnes, Rory; Raymond, Sean N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 910-922.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407..910J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..93H</bibcode>
			<title>An investigation into the radial velocity variations of CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Hatzes, A. P.; Dvorak, R.; Wuchterl, G.; Guterman, P.; Hartmann, M.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Guenther, E.; Ptzold, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A93</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..93H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..53L</bibcode>
			<title>Photospheric activity, rotation, and radial velocity variations of the planet-hosting star CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Moutou, C.; Pagano, I.; Messina, S.; Leto, G.; Cutispoto, G.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Barge, P.; Deleuil, M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Collier Cameron, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A53</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..82F</bibcode>
			<title>The stability of ultra-compact planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Funk, B.; Wuchterl, G.; Schwarz, R.; Pilat-Lohinger, E.; Eggl, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A82</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..82F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709L..95B</bibcode>
			<title>CoRoT-7b: Super-Earth or Super-Io?</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Rory; Raymond, Sean N.; Greenberg, Richard; Jackson, Brian; Kaib, Nathan A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 709, Issue 2, pp. L95-L98 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709L..95B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..303Q</bibcode>
			<title>The CoRoT-7 planetary system: two orbiting super-Earths</title>
			<authors>Queloz, D.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Jorda, L.; Hartmann, M.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.303-319</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..303Q</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..172M</bibcode>
			<title>A New Multi-band Radial Velocity Technique for Detecting Exoplanets around Active Stars</title>
			<authors>Ma, Bo; Ge, Jian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 172 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750..172M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..26P</bibcode>
			<title>The high-energy environment in the super-Earth system CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Poppenhaeger, K.; Czesla, S.; Schrter, S.; Lalitha, S.; Kashyap, V.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A26</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..26P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749..134H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-17b,c: A Transiting, Eccentric, Hot Saturn and a Long-period, Cold Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Howard, A. W.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Mazeh, T.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Bky, B.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 2, article id. 134 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749..134H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749...15G</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-20: A Sun-like Star with Three Sub-Neptune Exoplanets and Two Earth-size Candidates</title>
			<authors>Gautier, Thomas N., III; Charbonneau, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Francois; Rogers, Leslie A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ciardi, David R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Howell, Steve B.; Horch, Elliott P.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Borucki, William J.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Silverio, Kathryn; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Still, Martin; Stumpe, Martin C.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 1, article id. 15 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749...15G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A.140B</bibcode>
			<title>Multiwavelength flux variations induced by stellar magnetic activity: effects on planetary transits</title>
			<authors>Ballerini, P.; Micela, G.; Lanza, A. F.; Pagano, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A140</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A.140B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..28G</bibcode>
			<title>Improved precision on the radius of the nearby super-Earth 55 Cnc e</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Demory, B.-O.; Benneke, B.; Valencia, D.; Deming, D.; Seager, S.; Lovis, Ch.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A28</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..28G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A.112C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT LRa01 field</title>
			<authors>Carone, L.; Gandolfi, D.; Cabrera, J.; Hatzes, A. P.; Deeg, H. J.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Ptzold, M.; Weingrill, J.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deleuil, M.; Daz, R. F.; Dreizler, S.; Dvorak, R.; Eislffel, J.; Eigmller, P.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gibson, N.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Grziwa, S.; Gnther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Nortmann, L.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R gulo, C.; Renner, S.; de La Reza, R.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A112</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A.112C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewAR..56...19M</bibcode>
			<title>From 51 Peg to Earth-type planets</title>
			<authors>Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 56, Issue 1, p. 19-24.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012NewAR..56...19M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...81F</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Infrared Observations and Independent Validation of the Transiting Super-Earth CoRoT-7 b</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Pont, Frederic; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Mazeh, Tsevi; Aigrain, Suzanne; Fridlund, Malcolm; Henze, Christopher E.; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 81 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...81F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..189A</bibcode>
			<title>A High Stellar Obliquity in the WASP-7 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Albrecht, Simon; Winn, Joshua N.; Butler, R. Paul; Crane, Jeffrey D.; Shectman, Stephen A.; Thompson, Ian B.; Hirano, Teruyuki; Wittenmyer, Robert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 189 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744..189A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744...59S</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-Radius Relationships for Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Swift, D. C.; Eggert, J. H.; Hicks, D. G.; Hamel, S.; Caspersen, K.; Schwegler, E.; Collins, G. W.; Nettelmann, N.; Ackland, G. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744...59S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143....4H</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Cycle 1 Observations of Low-mass Stars: New Eclipsing Binaries, Single Star Rotation Rates, and the Nature and Frequency of Starspots</title>
			<authors>Harrison, T. E.; Coughlin, J. L.; Ule, N. M.; Lpez-Morales, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 1, article id. 4 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143....4H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A.147H</bibcode>
			<title>Optimizing exoplanet transit searches around low-mass stars with inclination constraints</title>
			<authors>Herrero, E.; Ribas, I.; Jordi, C.; Guinan, E. F.; Engle, S. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 537, id.A147</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...537A.147H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418.1039M</bibcode>
			<title>UBV(RI)C photometry of transiting planet hosting stars</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Koen, C.; Smalley, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 418, Issue 2, pp. 1039-1042.</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.418.1039M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...75H</bibcode>
			<title>The Mass of CoRoT-7b</title>
			<authors>Hatzes, Artie P.; Fridlund, Malcolm; Nachmani, Gil; Mazeh, Tsevi; Valencia, Diana; Hbrard, Guillaume; Carone, Ludmila; Ptzold, Martin; Udry, Stephane; Bouchy, Francois; Deleuil, Magali; Moutou, Claire; Barge, Pierre; Bord , Pascal; Deeg, Hans; Tingley, Brandon; Dvorak, Rudolf; Gandolfi, Davide; Ferraz-Mello, Sylvio; Wuchterl, Gnther; Guenther, Eike; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike; Erikson, Anders; Cabrera, Juan; Csizmadia, Szilard; Lger, Alain; Lammer, Helmut; Weingrill, Jrg; Queloz, Didier; Alonso, Roi; Rouan, Daniel; Schneider, Jean</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...75H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...41K</bibcode>
			<title>Climate Instability on Tidally Locked Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Kite, Edwin S.; Gaidos, Eric; Manga, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...41K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..44L</bibcode>
			<title>Deriving the radial-velocity variations induced by stellar activity from high-precision photometry. Test on HD 189733 with simultaneous MOST/SOPHIE data</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Moutou, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A44</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..44L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.2349R</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal decay and orbital circularization in close-in two-planet systems</title>
			<authors>Rodrguez, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Michtchenko, T. A.; Beaug, C.; Miloni, O.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 3, pp. 2349-2358.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.2349R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.2275M</bibcode>
			<title>Modelling the secular evolution of migrating planet pairs</title>
			<authors>Michtchenko, T. A.; Rodrguez, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 3, pp. 2275-2292.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.2275M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..79S</bibcode>
			<title>Defining and cataloging exoplanets: the exoplanet.eu database</title>
			<authors>Schneider, J.; Dedieu, C.; Le Sidaner, P.; Savalle, R.; Zolotukhin, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A79</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..79S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...12B</bibcode>
			<title>The GJ1214 Super-Earth System: Stellar Variability, New Transits, and a Search for Additional Planets</title>
			<authors>Berta, Zachory K.; Charbonneau, David; Bean, Jacob; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Nutzman, Philip; Falco, Emilio E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 12 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...12B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...72G</bibcode>
			<title>Effects of Stellar Flux on Tidally Locked Terrestrial Planets: Degree-1 Mantle Convection and Local Magma Ponds</title>
			<authors>Gelman, S. E.; Elkins-Tanton, L. T.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 2, article id. 72 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735...72G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A.161F</bibcode>
			<title>On the mass determination of super-Earths orbiting active stars: the CoRoT-7 system</title>
			<authors>Ferraz-Mello, S.; Tadeu Dos Santos, M.; Beaug, C.; Michtchenko, T. A.; Rodrguez, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A161</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A.161F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414..108B</bibcode>
			<title>On the use of the Virtual Observatory to select calibrators for phase-referenced astrometry of exoplanet-host stars</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonneau, D.; Mourard, D.; Lafrasse, S.; Mella, G.; Duvert, G.; Chelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. 108-115.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414..108B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733....8G</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of a Secularly Interacting Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Greenberg, Richard; Van Laerhoven, Christa</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 8 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733....8G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733....2N</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Evolution and Structure Models of the Transiting Super-Earth GJ 1214b</title>
			<authors>Nettelmann, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Kramm, U.; Redmer, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733....2N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..24L</bibcode>
			<title>A First Comparison of Kepler Planet Candidates in Single and Multiple Systems</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Wohler, Bill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..24L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...731..123K</bibcode>
			<title>APOSTLE Observations of GJ 1214b: System Parameters and Evidence for Stellar Activity</title>
			<authors>Kundurthy, P.; Agol, E.; Becker, A. C.; Barnes, R.; Williams, B.; Mukadam, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 731, Issue 2, article id. 123 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...731..123K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A.112L</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XXVIII. Up to seven planets orbiting HD 10180: probing the architecture of low-mass planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Lovis, C.; Sgransan, D.; Mayor, M.; Udry, S.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Bouchy, F.; Correia, A. C. M.; Laskar, J.; Lo Curto, G.; Mordasini, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A112</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A.112L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A...4B</bibcode>
			<title>Disentangling between stellar activity and planetary signals</title>
			<authors>Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Hbrard, G.; Bonfils, X.; Santos, N.; Vauclair, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A4</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A...4B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A...2B</bibcode>
			<title>The mass-period distribution of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Bentez-Llambay, P.; Masset, F.; Beaug, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A2</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A...2B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1953P</bibcode>
			<title>Reassessing the radial-velocity evidence for planets around CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Aigrain, Suzanne; Zucker, Shay</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 3, pp. 1953-1962.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1953P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...98P</bibcode>
			<title>An Analysis of Jitter and Transit Timing Variations in the HAT-P-13 System</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 98 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...98P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...74V</bibcode>
			<title>Quantifying the Challenges of Detecting Unseen Planetary Companions with Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Payne, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...74V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...73H</bibcode>
			<title>The NASA-UC Eta-Earth Program. II. A Planet Orbiting HD 156668 with a Minimum Mass of Four Earth Masses</title>
			<authors>Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Wright, Jason T.; Henry, Gregory W.; Isaacson, Howard; Valenti, Jeff A.; Anderson, Jay; Piskunov, Nikolai E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 73 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...73H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..65P</bibcode>
			<title>The barycentric motion of exoplanet host stars. Tests of solar spin-orbit coupling</title>
			<authors>Perryman, M. A. C.; Schulze-Hartung, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A65</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..65P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..14L</bibcode>
			<title>Photospheric activity, rotation, and star-planet interaction of the planet-hosting star CoRoT-6</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Pagano, I.; Leto, G.; Messina, S.; Cutispoto, G.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Barge, P.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; Silva-Valio, A.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Collier Cameron, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A14</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..14L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 29, 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724L..53S</bibcode>
			<title>A Population of Very Hot Super-Earths in Multiple-planet Systems Should be Uncovered by Kepler</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.; Lin, D. N. C.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. L53-L58 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724L..53S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..954V</bibcode>
			<title>The Lick-Carnegie Exoplanet Survey: A 3.1 M &amp;oplus; Planet in the Habitable Zone of the Nearby M3V Star Gliese 581</title>
			<authors>Vogt, Steven S.; Butler, R. Paul; Rivera, E. J.; Haghighipour, N.; Henry, Gregory W.; Williamson, Michael H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 954-965 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..954V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..84S</bibcode>
			<title>A multi-site campaign to detect the transit of the second planet in HAT-P-13</title>
			<authors>Szab, Gy. M.; Kiss, L. L.; Benko, J. M.; Mezo, Gy.; Nuspl, J.; Regly, Zs.; Srneczky, K.; Simon, A. E.; Leto, G.; Zanmar Sanchez, R.; Ngeow, C.-C.; Kovri, Zs.; Szab, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A84</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..84S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407..910J</bibcode>
			<title>The roles of tidal evolution and evaporative mass loss in the origin of CoRoT-7 b</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Miller, Neil; Barnes, Rory; Raymond, Sean N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 910-922.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407..910J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1290G</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Parameters and Metallicities of Stars Hosting Jovian and Neptunian Mass Planets: A Possible Dependence of Planetary Mass on Metallicity</title>
			<authors>Ghezzi, L.; Cunha, K.; Smith, V. V.; de Arajo, F. X.; Schuler, S. C.; de la Reza, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1290-1302 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1290G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..93H</bibcode>
			<title>An investigation into the radial velocity variations of CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Hatzes, A. P.; Dvorak, R.; Wuchterl, G.; Guterman, P.; Hartmann, M.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Guenther, E.; Ptzold, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A93</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..93H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..66B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XI. CoRoT-8b: a hot and dense sub-Saturn around a K1 dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Cabrera, J.; Jorda, L.; Lovis, C.; Csizmadia, S.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Ollivier, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A66</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..66B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..53L</bibcode>
			<title>Photospheric activity, rotation, and radial velocity variations of the planet-hosting star CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Moutou, C.; Pagano, I.; Messina, S.; Leto, G.; Cutispoto, G.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Barge, P.; Deleuil, M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Collier Cameron, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A53</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A..51B</bibcode>
			<title>Improved stellar parameters of CoRoT-7. A star hosting two super Earths</title>
			<authors>Bruntt, H.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; Alonso, R.; Bouchy, F.; Hatzes, A.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A51</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A..51B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..596G</bibcode>
			<title>Thermodynamic Limits on Magnetodynamos in Rocky Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Gaidos, Eric; Conrad, Clinton P.; Manga, Michael; Hernlund, John</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 596-609 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..596G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..575W</bibcode>
			<title>The HAT-P-13 Exoplanetary System: Evidence for Spin-Orbit Alignment and a Third Companion</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Bakos, Gspr .; Hartman, Joel; Torres, Guillermo; Albrecht, Simon; Narita, Norio</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 1, pp. 575-582 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..575W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..20V</bibcode>
			<title>Composition and fate of short-period super-Earths. The case of CoRoT-7b</title>
			<authors>Valencia, D.; Ikoma, M.; Guillot, T.; Nettelmann, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A20</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..20V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..421T</bibcode>
			<title>A Prograde, Low-inclination Orbit for the Very Hot Jupiter WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Tripathi, Anjali; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Halverson, Sam; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Holman, Matthew J.; de Kleer, Katherine R.; Carter, Joshua A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Cabrera, Nicole E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 421-428 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..421T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..974R</bibcode>
			<title>A Framework for Quantifying the Degeneracies of Exoplanet Interior Compositions</title>
			<authors>Rogers, L. A.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 2, pp. 974-991 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..974R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712L..86P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Variations for Inclined and Retrograde Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.; Veras, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. L86-L92 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712L..86P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..46H</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XX. Planets around the active star BD -082823</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Udry, S.; Lo Curto, G.; Robichon, N.; Naef, D.; Ehrenreich, D.; Benz, W.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A46</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..46H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709L..95B</bibcode>
			<title>CoRoT-7b: Super-Earth or Super-Io?</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Rory; Raymond, Sean N.; Greenberg, Richard; Jackson, Brian; Kaib, Nathan A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 709, Issue 2, pp. L95-L98 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709L..95B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...510A..21S</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar limb-darkening coefficients for CoRot and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Sing, D. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 510, id.A21</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...510A..21S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708..224H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-19b: The Shortest Period Transiting Exoplanet Yet Discovered</title>
			<authors>Hebb, L.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Hellier, C.; Anderson, D. R.; Pollacco, D.; Gillon, M.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Horne, K.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 1, pp. 224-231 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...708..224H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PABei..28...53J</bibcode>
			<title>Proper motions and the frontier of studies on the Galaxy.</title>
			<authors>Jin, W.-J.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 28, 53-71 (2010)</journal>
			<date>0/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PABei..28...53J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..431M</bibcode>
			<title>Removing systematics from the CoRoT light curves. I. Magnitude-dependent zero point</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Guterman, P.; Aigrain, S.; Zucker, S.; Grinberg, N.; Alapini, A.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deeg, H.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Sabo, R.; Schneider, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.431-434</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..431M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..343D</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based photometry of space-based transit detections: photometric follow-up of the CoRoT  mission</title>
			<authors>Deeg, H. J.; Gillon, M.; Shporer, A.; Rouan, D.; Stecklum, B.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Bouchy, F.; Eisl ffel, J.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Eigmller, P.; Handler, G.; Hatzes, A.; Kabath, P.; Lendl, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rabus, M.; Tingley, B.; Titz, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.343-352</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..343D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..303Q</bibcode>
			<title>The CoRoT-7 planetary system: two orbiting super-Earths</title>
			<authors>Queloz, D.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Jorda, L.; Hartmann, M.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.303-319</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..303Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..287L</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. VIII. CoRoT-7b: the first super-Earth with measured radius</title>
			<authors>Lger, A.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Barge, P.; Fridlund, M.; Samuel, B.; Ollivier, M.; Guenther, E.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Auvergne, M.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J. M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Bruntt, H.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Catala, C.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Foing, B.; Fressin, F.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, Ph.; Grasset, O.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ptzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Renner, S.; Samadi, R.; Shporer, A.; Sotin, Ch.; Tingley, B.; Wuchterl, G.; Adda, M.; Agogu, P.; Appourchaux, T.; Ballans, H.; Baron, P.; Beaufort, T.; Bellenger, R.; Berlin, R.; Bernardi, P.; Blouin, D.; Baudin, F.; Bodin, P.; Boisnard, L.; Boit, L.; Bonneau, F.; Borzeix, S.; Briet, R.; Buey, J.-T.; Butler, B.; Cailleau, D.; Cautain, R.; Chabaud, P.-Y.; Chaintreuil, S.; Chiavassa, F.; Costes, V.; Cuna Parrho, V.; de Oliveira Fialho, F.; Decaudin, M.; Defise, J.-M.; Djalal, S.; Epstein, G.; Exil, G.-E.; Faur, C.; Fenouillet, T.; Gaboriaud, A.; Gallic, A.; Gamet, P.; Gavalda, P.; Grolleau, E.; Gruneisen, R.; Gueguen, L.; Guis, V.; Guivarc'h, V.; Guterman, P.; Hallouard, D.; Hasiba, J.; Heuripeau, F.; Huntzinger, G.; Hustaix, H.; Imad, C.; Imbert, C.; Johlander, B.; Jouret, M.; Journoud, P.; Karioty, F.; Kerjean, L.; Lafaille, V.; Lafond, L.; Lam-Trong, T.; Landiech, P.; Lapeyrere, V.; Larqu, T.; Laudet, P.; Lautier, N.; Lecann, H.; Lefevre, L.; Leruyet, B.; Levacher, P.; Magnan, A.; Mazy, E.; Mertens, F.; Mesnager, J.-M.; Meunier, J.-C.; Michel, J.-P.; Monjoin, W.; Naudet, D.; Nguyen-Kim, K.; Orcesi, J.-L.; Ottacher, H.; Perez, R.; Peter, G.; Plasson, P.; Plesseria, J.-Y.; Pontet, B.; Pradines, A.; Quentin, C.; Reynaud, J.-L.; Rolland, G.; Rollenhagen, F.; Romagnan, R.; Russ, N.; Schmidt, R.; Schwartz, N.; Sebbag, I.; Sedes, G.; Smit, H.; Steller, M. B.; Sunter, W.; Surace, C.; Tello, M.; Tiphne, D.; Toulouse, P.; Ulmer, B.; Vandermarcq, O.; Vergnault, E.; Vuillemin, A.; Zanatta, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.287-302</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..287L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
