<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A.149O</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XXII. CoRoT-16b: a hot Jupiter with a hint of eccentricity around a faint solar-like star</title>
			<authors>Ollivier, M.; Gillon, M.; Santerne, A.; Wuchterl, G.; Havel, M.; Bruntt, H.; Bord, P.; Pasternacki, T.; Endl, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cavarroc, C.; Cochran, W. D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Diaz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Grziwa, S.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tadeu dos Santos, M.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A149</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A.149O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..14E</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT-SRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Erikson, A.; Santerne, A.; Renner, S.; Barge, P.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; Rgulo, C.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..14E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.420.1045G</bibcode>
			<title>The needle in the haystack: searching for transiting extrasolar planets in CoRoT stellar light curves</title>
			<authors>Grziwa, S.; Ptzold, M.; Carone, L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 420, Issue 2, pp. 1045-1052.</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.420.1045G</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A.149O</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XXII. CoRoT-16b: a hot Jupiter with a hint of eccentricity around a faint solar-like star</title>
			<authors>Ollivier, M.; Gillon, M.; Santerne, A.; Wuchterl, G.; Havel, M.; Bruntt, H.; Bord, P.; Pasternacki, T.; Endl, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cavarroc, C.; Cochran, W. D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Diaz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Grziwa, S.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tadeu dos Santos, M.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A149</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A.149O</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
