<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...39C</bibcode>
			<title>A Uniform Search for Secondary Eclipses of Hot Jupiters in Kepler Q2 Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Coughlin, J. L.; L&#243;pez-Morales, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 2, article id. 39 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143...39C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744...59S</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-Radius Relationships for Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Swift, D. C.; Eggert, J. H.; Hicks, D. G.; Hamel, S.; Caspersen, K.; Schwegler, E.; Collins, G. W.; Nettelmann, N.; Ackland, G. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744...59S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742..116B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-20b-HAT-P-23b: Four Massive Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Kipping, D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Shporer, A.; B&#233;ky, B.; Buchhave, L. A.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..83B</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. III. KOI-423b: an 18 MJup transiting companion around an F7IV star</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Moutou, C.; Deleuil, M.; D&#237; az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H&#233; brard, G.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A83</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..83B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...47B</bibcode>
			<title>The Dependence of Brown Dwarf Radii on Atmospheric Metallicity and Clouds: Theory and Comparison with Observations</title>
			<authors>Burrows, Adam; Heng, Kevin; Nampaisarn, Thane</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 47 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...47B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..41C</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XVII. The hot Jupiter CoRoT-17b: a very old planet</title>
			<authors>Csizmadia, Sz.; Moutou, C.; Deleuil, M.; Cabrera, J.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cavarroc, C.; Cochran, W.; Deeg, H. J.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fruth, Th.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jehin, E.; Jorda, L.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mazeh, T.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Titz-Weider, R.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A41</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..41C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...79J</bibcode>
			<title>LHS 6343 C: A Transiting Field Brown Dwarf Discovered by the Kepler Mission</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Apps, Kevin; Gazak, J. Zachary; Crepp, Justin R.; Crossfield, Ian J.; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoff W.; Morton, Timothy D.; Chubak, Carly; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. 79 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...79J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..97T</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XVI. CoRoT-14b: an unusually dense very hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Endl, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Alonso, R.; Mazeh, T.; Jorda, L.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233; , P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carpano, S.; Carone, L.; Cochran, W. D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A97</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..97T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411L..46V</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for detection of exoplanet magnetic fields through bow-shock observations during transits</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. L46-L50.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411L..46V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727L..44S</bibcode>
			<title>A Short-period Censor of Sub-Jupiter Mass Exoplanets with Low Density</title>
			<authors>Szab&#243;, Gy. M.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. L44 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727L..44S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...57S</bibcode>
			<title>The Deuterium-burning Mass Limit for Brown Dwarfs and Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 57 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...57S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726L..19A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-30b: A 61 M Jup Brown Dwarf Transiting a V = 12, F8 Star</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Todd, I.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Barros, S. C. C.; Enoch, B.; Gillon, M.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. L19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726L..19A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..95S</bibcode>
			<title>Search for brown-dwarf companions of stars</title>
			<authors>Sahlmann, J.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Santos, N. C.; Marmier, M.; Mayor, M.; Naef, D.; Pepe, F.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A95</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..95S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..85E</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. I. Detection of the low-mass white dwarf KOI 74b</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Bouchy, F.; Perrier, C.; H&#233;brard, G.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; Arnold, L.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lovis, C.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Santos, N. C.; Santerne, A.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A85</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..85E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..68B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XV. CoRoT-15b: a brown-dwarf transiting companion</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Guillot, T.; Aigrain, S.; Carone, L.; Cochran, W. D.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Csizmadia, Sz.; de Bondt, K.; Deeg, H. J.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J. C.; Gibson, N.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; L&#233;ger, A.; Lovis, C.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A68</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..68B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1226S</bibcode>
			<title>Five Kepler Target Stars That Show Multiple Transiting Exoplanet Candidates</title>
			<authors>Steffen, Jason H.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Haas, Michael J.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Moorhead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Marcy, Geoffrey; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 1, pp. 1226-1241 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1226S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521L..59M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of the ellipsoidal and the relativistic beaming effects in the CoRoT-3 lightcurve</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Faigler, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.L59</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521L..59M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521L..54H</bibcode>
			<title>A brown dwarf companion to the intermediate-mass star HR 6037</title>
			<authors>Hu&#233;lamo, N.; N&#252;rnberger, D. E. A.; Ivanov, V. D.; Chauvin, G.; Carraro, G.; Sterzik, M. F.; Melo, C. H. F.; Bonnefoy, M.; Hartung, M.; Haubois, X.; Foellmi, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.L54</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521L..54H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1644K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Transit Potential of the Planet Orbiting Iota Draconis</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Reffert, Sabine; Henry, Gregory W.; Fischer, Debra; Schwab, Christian; Clubb, Kelsey I.; Bergmann, Christoph</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1644-1649 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1644K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..66B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XI. CoRoT-8b: a hot and dense sub-Saturn around a K1 dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Cabrera, J.; Jorda, L.; Lovis, C.; Csizmadia, S.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Ollivier, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A66</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..66B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718.1353I</bibcode>
			<title>NLTT 41135: A Field M Dwarf + Brown Dwarf Eclipsing Binary in a Triple System, Discovered by the MEarth Observatory</title>
			<authors>Irwin, Jonathan; Buchhave, Lars; Berta, Zachory K.; Charbonneau, David; Latham, David W.; Burke, Christopher J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Nutzman, Philip; Berlind, Perry; Calkins, Michael L.; Falco, Emilio E.; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John A.; Gazak, J. Zachary</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 1353-1366 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718.1353I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718.1186F</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Low-mass Companion to a Metal-rich F Star with the MARVELS Pilot Project</title>
			<authors>Fleming, Scott W.; Ge, Jian; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Lee, Brian; Eastman, Jason D.; Siverd, Robert J.; Gaudi, B. Scott; Niedzielski, Andrzej; Sivarani, Thirupathi; Stassun, Keivan G.; Wolszczan, Alex; Barnes, Rory; Gary, Bruce; Nguyen, Duy Cuong; Morehead, Robert C.; Wan, Xiaoke; Zhao, Bo; Liu, Jian; Guo, Pengcheng; Kane, Stephen R.; van Eyken, Julian C.; De Lee, Nathan M.; Crepp, Justin R.; Shelden, Alaina C.; Laws, Chris; Wisniewski, John P.; Schneider, Donald P.; Pepper, Joshua; Snedden, Stephanie A.; Pan, Kaike; Bizyaev, Dmitry; Brewington, Howard; Malanushenko, Olena; Malanushenko, Viktor; Oravetz, Daniel; Simmons, Audrey; Watters, Shannon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 1186-1199 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718.1186F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...517A..40C</bibcode>
			<title>Distribution of refractory and volatile elements in CoRoT exoplanet host stars</title>
			<authors>Chavero, C.; de La Reza, R.; Domingos, R. C.; Drake, N. A.; Pereira, C. B.; Winter, O. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 517, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...517A..40C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..14F</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. IX. CoRoT-6b: a transiting ``hot Jupiter'' planet in an 8.9d orbit around a low-metallicity star</title>
			<authors>Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Alonso, R.; Deleuil, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Bruntt, H.; Alapini, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Guillot, T.; Lammer, H.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Guenther, E.; Gondoin, P.; den Hartog, R.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..14F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A.103S</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos preliminary astrometric masses for the two close-in companions to HD 131664 and HD 43848. A brown dwarf and a low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Desidera, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A103</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A.103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507.1659G</bibcode>
			<title>A substellar component orbiting the F-star 30 Arietis B</title>
			<authors>Guenther, E. W.; Hartmann, M.; Esposito, M.; Hatzes, A. P.; Cusano, F.; Gandolfi, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1659-1665</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507.1659G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..785H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-12b: A Low-Density Sub-Saturn Mass Planet Transiting a Metal-Poor K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; P&#225;l, A.; Latham, D. W.; Sipocz, B.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 785-796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..785H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.2085S</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamics of possible Trojan planets in binary systems</title>
			<authors>Schwarz, R.; S&#252;li, &#193;.; Dvorak, R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 2085-2090.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.2085S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704.1107L</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Transiting Planet and Eight Eclipsing Binaries in HATNet Field G205</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Torres, Guillermo; Stefanik, Robert P.; Noyes, Robert W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Butler, R. Paul; Sipocz, Brigitta; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Vogt, Steven S.; Hartman, Joel D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; L&#225;z&#225;r, J&#243;zsef; Papp, Istv&#225;n; S&#225;ri, P&#225;l</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 2, pp. 1107-1119 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704.1107L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..501C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in CoRoT-LRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Fridlund, M.; Ollivier, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233; , P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Hatzes, A.; Hebrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R&#233; gulo, C.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.501-517</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..501C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..391A</bibcode>
			<title>Planet formation by nucleated-instability: comparison with the two first CoRoT runs</title>
			<authors>Alibert, Y.; Pont, F.; Baraffe, I.; Reyl&#233;, C.; Mordasini, C.; Queloz, D.; Benz, W.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.391-398</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..391A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..385L</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and evolution of the first CoRoT exoplanets: probing the brown dwarf/planet overlapping mass regime</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.385-389</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..385L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..377T</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin effect of CoRoT-3b and HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Queloz, D.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Collier Cameron, A.; Claret, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Deleuil, M.; Guillot, T.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lecavelier Des &#201;tangs, A.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.377-384</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..377T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..343D</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based photometry of space-based transit detections: photometric follow-up of the CoRoT  mission</title>
			<authors>Deeg, H. J.; Gillon, M.; Shporer, A.; Rouan, D.; Stecklum, B.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Bouchy, F.; Eisl&#246; ffel, J.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Eigm&#252;ller, P.; Handler, G.; Hatzes, A.; Kabath, P.; Lendl, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rabus, M.; Tingley, B.; Titz, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.343-352</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..343D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..153M</bibcode>
			<title>Accuracy of stellar parameters of exoplanet-host stars determined from asteroseismology</title>
			<authors>Mulet-Marquis, C.; Baraffe, I.; Aigrain, S.; Pont, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.153-158</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..153M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...505..853B</bibcode>
			<title>The SOPHIE search for northern extrasolar planets . I. A companion around HD 16760 with mass close to the planet/brown-dwarf transition</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; H&#233;brard, G.; Udry, S.; Delfosse, X.; Boisse, I.; Desort, M.; Bonfils, X.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A. M.; Le Coroller, H.; Lovis, C.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 505, Issue 2, 2009, pp.853-858</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...505..853B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..671S</bibcode>
			<title>A Substellar Companion in a 1.3 yr Nearly Circular Orbit of HD 16760</title>
			<authors>Sato, Bun'ei; Fischer, Debra A.; Ida, Shigeru; Harakawa, Hiroki; Omiya, Masashi; Johnson, John A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Toyota, Eri; Hori, Yasunori; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew W.; Peek, Kathryn M. G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 671-674 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..671S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.395.2299R</bibcode>
			<title>The mass ratio and the orbital parameters of the sdOB binary AA Doradus</title>
			<authors>Rucinski, Slavek M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 395, Issue 4, pp. 2299-2303.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.395.2299R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394L..93M</bibcode>
			<title>On the various origins of close-in extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.; Ortolani, S.; Nagasawa, M.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. L93-L96.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394L..93M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AJ....137.3529W</bibcode>
			<title>HD 91669B: A New Brown Dwarf Candidate from the McDonald Observatory Planet Search</title>
			<authors>Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Ram&#237;rez, Ivan; Reffert, Sabine; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Shetrone, Matthew</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 137, Issue 3, pp. 3529-3532 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AJ....137.3529W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692..290K</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Low-Mass Companion to the Solar-Type Star TYC 2534-698-1</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Cochran, William D.; Street, Rachel A.; Sivarani, Thirupathi; Henry, Gregory W.; Williamson, Michael H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. 290-297 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692..290K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...491..889D</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission . VI. CoRoT-Exo-3b: the first secure inhabitant of the brown-dwarf desert</title>
			<authors>Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Alonso, R.; Bouchy, F.; Rouan, D.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bruntt, H.; Bord&#233;, P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 491, Issue 3, 2008, pp.889-897</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...491..889D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488L..43A</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. IV. CoRoT-Exo-4b: a transiting planet in a 9.2 day synchronous orbit</title>
			<authors>Aigrain, S.; Collier Cameron, A.; Ollivier, M.; Pont, F.; Jorda, L.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barge, P.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deeg, H.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Paetzold, M.; Pinte, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Wuchter, G.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.L43-L46</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488L..43A</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534L...6T</bibcode>
			<title>The time dependence of hot Jupiters' orbital inclinations</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.L6</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534L...6T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..83B</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. III. KOI-423b: an 18 MJup transiting companion around an F7IV star</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Moutou, C.; Deleuil, M.; D&#237; az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H&#233; brard, G.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A83</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..83B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...47B</bibcode>
			<title>The Dependence of Brown Dwarf Radii on Atmospheric Metallicity and Clouds: Theory and Comparison with Observations</title>
			<authors>Burrows, Adam; Heng, Kevin; Nampaisarn, Thane</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 47 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...47B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414..108B</bibcode>
			<title>On the use of the Virtual Observatory to select calibrators for phase-referenced astrometry of exoplanet-host stars</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonneau, D.; Mourard, D.; Lafrasse, S.; Mella, G.; Duvert, G.; Chelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. 108-115.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414..108B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..139C</bibcode>
			<title>A Third Hot White Dwarf Companion Detected by Kepler</title>
			<authors>Carter, Joshua A.; Rappaport, Saul; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 139 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..139C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..85E</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. I. Detection of the low-mass white dwarf KOI 74b</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Bouchy, F.; Perrier, C.; H&#233;brard, G.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; Arnold, L.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lovis, C.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Santos, N. C.; Santerne, A.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A85</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..85E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725L.200S</bibcode>
			<title>A Ground-based Measurement of the Relativistic Beaming Effect in a Detached Double White Dwarf Binary</title>
			<authors>Shporer, Avi; Kaplan, David L.; Steinfadt, Justin D. R.; Bildsten, Lars; Howell, Steve B.; Mazeh, Tsevi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. L200-L204 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725L.200S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521L..59M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of the ellipsoidal and the relativistic beaming effects in the CoRoT-3 lightcurve</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Faigler, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.L59</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521L..59M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718.1353I</bibcode>
			<title>NLTT 41135: A Field M Dwarf + Brown Dwarf Eclipsing Binary in a Triple System, Discovered by the MEarth Observatory</title>
			<authors>Irwin, Jonathan; Buchhave, Lars; Berta, Zachory K.; Charbonneau, David; Latham, David W.; Burke, Christopher J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Nutzman, Philip; Berlind, Perry; Calkins, Michael L.; Falco, Emilio E.; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John A.; Gazak, J. Zachary</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 1353-1366 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718.1353I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...517A..40C</bibcode>
			<title>Distribution of refractory and volatile elements in CoRoT exoplanet host stars</title>
			<authors>Chavero, C.; de La Reza, R.; Domingos, R. C.; Drake, N. A.; Pereira, C. B.; Winter, O. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 517, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...517A..40C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..64L</bibcode>
			<title>Is tidal heating sufficient to explain bloated exoplanets? Consistent calculations accounting for finite initial eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Chabrier, G.; Baraffe, I.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A64</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..64L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...510A..21S</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar limb-darkening coefficients for CoRot and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Sing, D. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 510, id.A21</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...510A..21S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A.103S</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos preliminary astrometric masses for the two close-in companions to HD 131664 and HD 43848. A brown dwarf and a low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Desidera, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A103</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A.103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705..683B</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Lightcurves of Extrasolar Planets Orbiting Rapidly Rotating Stars</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 705, Issue 1, pp. 683-692 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705..683B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.2085S</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamics of possible Trojan planets in binary systems</title>
			<authors>Schwarz, R.; S&#252;li, &#193;.; Dvorak, R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 2085-2090.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.2085S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..501C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in CoRoT-LRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Fridlund, M.; Ollivier, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233; , P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Hatzes, A.; Hebrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R&#233; gulo, C.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.501-517</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..501C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..377T</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin effect of CoRoT-3b and HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Queloz, D.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Collier Cameron, A.; Claret, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Deleuil, M.; Guillot, T.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lecavelier Des &#201;tangs, A.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.377-384</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..377T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692..290K</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Low-Mass Companion to the Solar-Type Star TYC 2534-698-1</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Cochran, William D.; Street, Rachel A.; Sivarani, Thirupathi; Henry, Gregory W.; Williamson, Michael H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. 290-297 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692..290K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...491..889D</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission . VI. CoRoT-Exo-3b: the first secure inhabitant of the brown-dwarf desert</title>
			<authors>Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Alonso, R.; Bouchy, F.; Rouan, D.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bruntt, H.; Bord&#233;, P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 491, Issue 3, 2008, pp.889-897</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...491..889D</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
