<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.2007M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-22 b: A Transiting "Hot Jupiter" Planet in a Hierarchical Triple System</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Cegla, H.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 2007-2012 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.2007M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Cameron, A. C.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..14F</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. IX. CoRoT-6b: a transiting ``hot Jupiter'' planet in an 8.9d orbit around a low-metallicity star</title>
			<authors>Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Alonso, R.; Deleuil, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Bruntt, H.; Alapini, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Guillot, T.; Lammer, H.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Guenther, E.; Gondoin, P.; den Hartog, R.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..14F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..501C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in CoRoT-LRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Fridlund, M.; Ollivier, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233; , P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Hatzes, A.; Hebrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R&#233; gulo, C.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.501-517</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..501C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..343D</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based photometry of space-based transit detections: photometric follow-up of the CoRoT  mission</title>
			<authors>Deeg, H. J.; Gillon, M.; Shporer, A.; Rouan, D.; Stecklum, B.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Bouchy, F.; Eisl&#246; ffel, J.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Eigm&#252;ller, P.; Handler, G.; Hatzes, A.; Kabath, P.; Lendl, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rabus, M.; Tingley, B.; Titz, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.343-352</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..343D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..281R</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. VII. The ``hot-Jupiter''-type planet CoRoT-5b</title>
			<authors>Rauer, H.; Queloz, D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; de La Reza, R.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Guenther, E.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Kabath, P.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Rabus, M.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Shporer, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.281-286</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..281R</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...517A..40C</bibcode>
			<title>Distribution of refractory and volatile elements in CoRoT exoplanet host stars</title>
			<authors>Chavero, C.; de La Reza, R.; Domingos, R. C.; Drake, N. A.; Pereira, C. B.; Winter, O. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 517, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...517A..40C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...510A..21S</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar limb-darkening coefficients for CoRot and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Sing, D. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 510, id.A21</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...510A..21S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..281R</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. VII. The ``hot-Jupiter''-type planet CoRoT-5b</title>
			<authors>Rauer, H.; Queloz, D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; de La Reza, R.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Guenther, E.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Kabath, P.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Rabus, M.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Shporer, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.281-286</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..281R</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
