<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...545A...6P</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XXIII. CoRoT-21b: a doomed large Jupiter around a faint subgiant star</title>
			<authors>Ptzold, M.; Endl, M.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Gandolfi, D.; Jorda, L.; Grziwa, S.; Carone, L.; Pasternacki, T.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Cavarroc, C.; Cochran, W. B.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 545, id.A6</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...545A...6P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.2024J</bibcode>
			<title>The coronal X-ray-age relation and its implications for the evaporation of exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Alan P.; Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 3, pp. 2024-2043.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.2024J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..14E</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT-SRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Erikson, A.; Santerne, A.; Renner, S.; Barge, P.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; Rgulo, C.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..14E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A.112C</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT LRa01 field</title>
			<authors>Carone, L.; Gandolfi, D.; Cabrera, J.; Hatzes, A. P.; Deeg, H. J.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Ptzold, M.; Weingrill, J.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deleuil, M.; Daz, R. F.; Dreizler, S.; Dvorak, R.; Eislffel, J.; Eigmller, P.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gibson, N.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Grziwa, S.; Gnther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hartmann, M.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Nortmann, L.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; R gulo, C.; Renner, S.; de La Reza, R.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A112</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A.112C</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...545A...6P</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XXIII. CoRoT-21b: a doomed large Jupiter around a faint subgiant star</title>
			<authors>Ptzold, M.; Endl, M.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Gandolfi, D.; Jorda, L.; Grziwa, S.; Carone, L.; Pasternacki, T.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Cavarroc, C.; Cochran, W. B.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Parviainen, H.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 545, id.A6</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...545A...6P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...543A.125G</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-object spectroscopy of stars in the CoRoT fields. II. The stellar population of the CoRoT fields IRa01, LRa01, LRa02, and LRa06</title>
			<authors>Guenther, E. W.; Gandolfi, D.; Sebastian, D.; Deleuil, M.; Moutou, C.; Cusano, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 543, id.A125</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...543A.125G</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
