<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746..165H</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Significant Magnetic Cataclysmic Variable Population in the Limiting Window</title>
			<authors>Hong, JaeSub; van den Berg, Maureen; Grindlay, Jonathan E.; Servillat, Mathieu; Zhao, Ping</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 2, article id. 165 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...746..165H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AN....333...53T</bibcode>
			<title>Where do the progenitors of millisecond pulsars come from?</title>
			<authors>Taani, A.; Zhang, C. M.; Al-Wardat, M.; Zhao, Y. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, vol. 333, issue 1, pp. 53-59</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AN....333...53T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416L..11H</bibcode>
			<title>A dynamical analysis of the proposed HU Aquarii planetary system</title>
			<authors>Horner, J.; Marshall, J. P.; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Tinney, C. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 416, Issue 1, pp. L11-L15.</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.416L..11H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737...51M</bibcode>
			<title>X-Ray and Optical Observations of the Unique Binary System HD 49798/RX J0648.0-4418</title>
			<authors>Mereghetti, S.; La Palombara, N.; Tiengo, A.; Pizzolato, F.; Esposito, P.; Woudt, P. A.; Israel, G. L.; Stella, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 737, Issue 2, article id. 51 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737...51M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414L..16Q</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a planetary system orbiting the eclipsing polar HU Aqr</title>
			<authors>Qian, S.-B.; Liu, L.; Liao, W.-P.; Li, L.-J.; Zhu, L.-Y.; Dai, Z.-B.; He, J.-J.; Zhao, E.-G.; Zhang, J.; Li, K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. L16-L20.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414L..16Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A..53B</bibcode>
			<title>The giant planet orbiting the cataclysmic binary DP Leonis</title>
			<authors>