<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..184..138H</bibcode>
			<title>XID II: Statistical Cross-Association of ROSAT Bright Source Catalog X-ray Sources with 2MASS Point Source Catalog Near-Infrared Sources</title>
			<authors>Haakonsen, Christian Bernt; Rutledge, Robert E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 184, Issue 1, pp. 138-151 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..184..138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493..339W</bibcode>
			<title>The XMM-Newton serendipitous survey. V. The Second XMM-Newton serendipitous source catalogue</title>
			<authors>Watson, M. G.; Schr&#246;der, A. C.; Fyfe, D.; Page, C. G.; Lamer, G.; Mateos, S.; Pye, J.; Sakano, M.; Rosen, S.; Ballet, J.; Barcons, X.; Barret, D.; Boller, T.; Brunner, H.; Brusa, M.; Caccianiga, A.; Carrera, F. J.; Ceballos, M.; Della Ceca, R.; Denby, M.; Denkinson, G.; Dupuy, S.; Farrell, S.; Fraschetti, F.; Freyberg, M. J.; Guillout, P.; Hambaryan, V.; Maccacaro, T.; Mathiesen, B.; McMahon, R.; Michel, L.; Motch, C.; Osborne, J. P.; Page, M.; Pakull, M. W.; Pietsch, W.; Saxton, R.; Schwope, A.; Severgnini, P.; Simpson, M.; Sironi, G.; Stewart, G.; Stewart, I. M.; Stobbart, A.-M.; Tedds, J.; Warwick, R.; Webb, N.; West, R.; Worrall, D.; Yuan, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 1, 2009, pp.339-373</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493..339W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...403..247F</bibcode>
			<title>A systematic study of X-ray variability in the ROSAT all-sky survey</title>
			<authors>Fuhrmeister, B.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.403, p.247-260 (2003)</journal>
			<date>5/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...403..247F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...349..389V</bibcode>
			<title>The ROSAT all-sky survey bright source catalogue</title>
			<authors>Voges, W.; Aschenbach, B.; Boller, Th.; Br&#228;uninger, H.; Briel, U.; Burkert, W.; Dennerl, K.; Englhauser, J.; Gruber, R.; Haberl, F.; Hartner, G.; Hasinger, G.; K&#252;rster, M.; Pfeffermann, E.; Pietsch, W.; Predehl, P.; Rosso, C.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Tr&#252;mper, J.; Zimmermann, H. U.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.349, p.389-405 (1999)</journal>
			<date>9/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...349..389V</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
