<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..46D</bibcode>
			<title>Protoplanetary disks of T Tauri binary systems in the Orion nebula cluster</title>
			<authors>Daemgen, S.; Correia, S.; Petr-Gotzens, M. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A46</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..46D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A...8B</bibcode>
			<title>The quest for companions to post-common envelope binaries. II. NSVS14256825 and HS0705+6700</title>
			<authors>Beuermann, K.; Breitenstein, P.; Bski, B. De.; Diese, J.; Dubovsky, P. A.; Dreizler, S.; Hessman, F. V.; Hornoch, K.; Husser, T.-O.; Pojmanski, G.; Wolf, M.; Woz niak, P. R.; Zasche, P.; Denk, B.; Langer, M.; Wagner, C.; Wahrenberg, D.; Bollmann, T.; Habermann, F. N.; Haustovich, N.; Lauser, M.; Liebing, F.; Niederstadt, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A8</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A...8B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A.153P</bibcode>
			<title>Period changes of the long-period cataclysmic binary EX Draconis</title>
			<authors>Pilarck, L.; Wolf, M.; Dubovsk, P. A.; Hornoch, K.; Kotkov, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A153</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A.153P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.419.3258W</bibcode>
			<title>Revisiting the proposed planetary system orbiting the eclipsing polar HU Aquarii</title>
			<authors>Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Horner, J.; Marshall, J. P.; Butters, O. W.; Tinney, C. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 419, Issue 4, pp. 3258-3267.</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.419.3258W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746..165H</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Significant Magnetic Cataclysmic Variable Population in the Limiting Window</title>
			<authors>Hong, JaeSub; van den Berg, Maureen; Grindlay, Jonathan E.; Servillat, Mathieu; Zhao, Ping</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 2, article id. 165 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...746..165H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A..84B</bibcode>
			<title>The quest for companions to post-common envelope binaries. I. Searching a sample of stars from the CSS and SDSS</title>
			<authors>Backhaus, U.; Bauer, S.; Beuermann, K.; Diese, J.; Dreizler, S.; Hessman, F. V.; Husser, T.-O.; Klapdohr, K.-H.; Mllmanns, J.; Schnecke, R.; Dette, J.; Dubbert, J.; Miosga, T.; Rochus Vogel, A. L.; Simons, S.; Biriuk, S.; Debrah, M.; Griemens, M.; Hahn, A.; Mller, T.; Pawlowski, M.; Schweizer, M.; Speck, A.-L.; Zapros, C.; Bollmann, T.; Habermann, F. N.; Haustovich, N.; Lauser, M.; Liebing, F.; Niederstadt, F.; Hoppen, K.; Kindermann, D.; Kppers, F.; Rauch, B.; Althoff, F.; Horstmann, M.; Kellerman, J. N.; Kietz, R.; Nienaber, T.; Sauer, M.; Secci, A.; Wllner, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A84</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A..84B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AN....333...53T</bibcode>
			<title>Where do the progenitors of millisecond pulsars come from?</title>
			<authors>Taani, A.; Zhang, C. M.; Al-Wardat, M.; Zhao, Y. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.333, Issue 1, p.53</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AN....333...53T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2104V</bibcode>
			<title>The great escape: how exoplanets and smaller bodies desert dying stars</title>
			<authors>Veras, Dimitri; Wyatt, Mark C.; Mustill, Alexander J.; Bonsor, Amy; Eldridge, John J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2104-2123.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2104V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416L..11H</bibcode>
			<title>A dynamical analysis of the proposed HU Aquarii planetary system</title>
			<authors>Horner, J.; Marshall, J. P.; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Tinney, C. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 416, Issue 1, pp. L11-L15.</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.416L..11H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416.2202P</bibcode>
			<title>Possible detection of two giant extrasolar planets orbiting the eclipsing polar UZ Fornacis</title>
			<authors>Potter, Stephen B.; Romero-Colmenero, Encarni; Ramsay, Gavin; Crawford, Steven; Gulbis, Amanda; Barway, Sudhanshu; Zietsman, Ewald; Kotze, Marissa; Buckley, David A. H.; O'Donoghue, Darragh; Siegmund, O. H. W.; McPhate, J.; Welsh, B. Y.; Vallerga, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 416, Issue 3, pp. 2202-2211.</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.416.2202P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737...51M</bibcode>
			<title>X-Ray and Optical Observations of the Unique Binary System HD 49798/RX J0648.0-4418</title>
			<authors>Mereghetti, S.; La Palombara, N.; Tiengo, A.; Pizzolato, F.; Esposito, P.; Woudt, P. A.; Israel, G. L.; Stella, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 737, Issue 2, article id. 51 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737...51M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414L..16Q</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a planetary system orbiting the eclipsing polar HU Aqr</title>
			<authors>Qian, S.-B.; Liu, L.; Liao, W.-P.; Li, L.-J.; Zhu, L.-Y.; Dai, Z.-B.; He, J.-J.; Zhao, E.-G.; Zhang, J.; Li, K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. L16-L20.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414L..16Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A..53B</bibcode>
			<title>The giant planet orbiting the cataclysmic binary DP Leonis</title>
			<authors>Beuermann, K.; Buhlmann, J.; Diese, J.; Dreizler, S.; Hessman, F. V.; Husser, T.-O.; Miller, G. F.; Nickol, N.; Pons, R.; Ruhr, D.; Schmlling, H.; Schwope, A. D.; Sorge, T.; Ulrichs, L.; Winget, D. E.; Winget, K. I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A53</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A..53B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405..657S</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting circumbinary planets using eclipse timing of binary stars - numerical simulations</title>
			<authors>Sybilski, P.; Konacki, M.; Kozlowski, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 1, pp. 657-665.</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405..657S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AN....331..489S</bibcode>
			<title>Pulsations and planets: The asteroseismology-extrasolar-planet connection</title>
			<authors>Schuh, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.331, Issue 5, p.489</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AN....331..489S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708L..66Q</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a Giant Extrasolar Planet Orbiting the Eclipsing Polar DP Leo</title>
			<authors>Qian, S.-B.; Liao, W.-P.; Zhu, L.-Y.; Dai, Z.-B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 708, Issue 1, pp. L66-L68 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...708L..66Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..385B</bibcode>
			<title>A long-term optical and X-ray ephemeris of the polar EK Ursae Majoris</title>
			<authors>Beuermann, K.; Diese, J.; Paik, S.; Ploch, A.; Zachmann, J.; Schwope, A. D.; Hessman, F. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.385-388</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..385B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..184..138H</bibcode>
			<title>XID II: Statistical Cross-Association of ROSAT Bright Source Catalog X-ray Sources with 2MASS Point Source Catalog Near-Infrared Sources</title>
			<authors>Haakonsen, Christian Bernt; Rutledge, Robert E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 184, Issue 1, pp. 138-151 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..184..138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.1091G</bibcode>
			<title>A Far Ultraviolet Spectroscopic Explorer Survey of High-Declination Dwarf Novae</title>
			<authors>Godon, Patrick; Sion, Edward M.; Barrett, Paul E.; Szkody, Paula</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 1091-1115 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.1091G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693.1007T</bibcode>
			<title>Cataclysmic Variable Primary Effective Temperatures: Constraints on Binary Angular Momentum Loss</title>
			<authors>Townsley, Dean M.; Gnsicke, Boris T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 1007-1021 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693.1007T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...496..833S</bibcode>
			<title>Hunting high and low: XMM monitoring of the eclipsing polar HU Aquarii</title>
			<authors>Schwarz, R.; Schwope, A. D.; Vogel, J.; Dhillon, V. S.; Marsh, T. R.; Copperwheat, C.; Littlefair, S. P.; Kanbach, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 496, Issue 3, 2009, pp.833-840</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...496..833S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493..339W</bibcode>
			<title>The XMM-Newton serendipitous survey. V. The Second XMM-Newton serendipitous source catalogue</title>
			<authors>Watson, M. G.; Schrder, A. C.; Fyfe, D.; Page, C. G.; Lamer, G.; Mateos, S.; Pye, J.; Sakano, M.; Rosen, S.; Ballet, J.; Barcons, X.; Barret, D.; Boller, T.; Brunner, H.; Brusa, M.; Caccianiga, A.; Carrera, F. J.; Ceballos, M.; Della Ceca, R.; Denby, M.; Denkinson, G.; Dupuy, S.; Farrell, S.; Fraschetti, F.; Freyberg, M. J.; Guillout, P.; Hambaryan, V.; Maccacaro, T.; Mathiesen, B.; McMahon, R.; Michel, L.; Motch, C.; Osborne, J. P.; Page, M.; Pakull, M. W.; Pietsch, W.; Saxton, R.; Schwope, A.; Severgnini, P.; Simpson, M.; Sironi, G.; Stewart, G.; Stewart, I. M.; Stobbart, A.-M.; Tedds, J.; Warwick, R.; Webb, N.; West, R.; Worrall, D.; Yuan, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 1, 2009, pp.339-373</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493..339W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475.1011K</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of polarized emission from the long period intermediate polar RX J2133.7+5107</title>
			<authors>Katajainen, S.; Butters, O. W.; Norton, A. J.; Lehto, H. J.; Piirola, V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 3, December I 2007, pp.1011-1018</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475.1011K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007Ap.....50..351V</bibcode>
			<title>White dwarf + red dwarf binary systems and the period gap of cataclysmic variables</title>
			<authors>Vojkhanskaja, N. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics, Volume 50, Issue 3, pp.351-361</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007Ap.....50..351V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.373.1416B</bibcode>
			<title>The nature of the close magnetic white dwarf + probable brown dwarf binary SDSSJ121209.31+013627.7</title>
			<authors>Burleigh, M. R.; Marsh, T. R.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Goad, M. R.; Dhillon, V. S.; Littlefair, S. P.; Wells, M.; Bannister, N. P.; Hurkett, C. P.; Martindale, A.; Dobbie, P. D.; Casewell, S. L.; Baker, D. E. A.; Duke, J.; Farihi, J.; Irwin, M. J.; Hewett, P. C.; Roche, P.; Lewis, F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 373, Issue 4, pp. 1416-1422.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.373.1416B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.369..581W</bibcode>
			<title>The properties of cataclysmic variables in photometric Halpha surveys</title>
			<authors>Witham, A. R.; Knigge, C.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Aungwerojwit, A.; Corradi, R. L. M.; Drew, J. E.; Greimel, R.; Groot, P. J.; Morales-Rueda, L.; Rodriguez-Flores, E. R.; Rodriguez-Gil, P.; Steeghs, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 369, Issue 2, pp. 581-597.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.369..581W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622..589A</bibcode>
			<title>Far-Ultraviolet Spectroscopy of Magnetic Cataclysmic Variables</title>
			<authors>Araujo-Betancor, Sofia; Gnsicke, Boris T.; Long, Knox S.; Beuermann, Klaus; de Martino, Domitilla; Sion, Edward M.; Szkody, Paula</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 1, pp. 589-601.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622..589A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...616.1284M</bibcode>
			<title>Automated Classification of ROSAT Sources Using Heterogeneous Multiwavelength Source Catalogs</title>
			<authors>McGlynn, T. A.; Suchkov, A. A.; Winter, E. L.; Hanisch, R. J.; White, R. L.; Ochsenbein, F.; Derriere, S.; Voges, W.; Corcoran, M. F.; Drake, S. A.; Donahue, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 616, Issue 2, pp. 1284-1300.</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...616.1284M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...424..727P</bibcode>
			<title>SB9: The ninth catalogue of spectroscopic binary orbits</title>
			<authors>Pourbaix, D.; Tokovinin, A. A.; Batten, A. H.; Fekel, F. C.; Hartkopf, W. I.; Levato, H.; Morrell, N. I.; Torres, G.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.424, p.727-732 (2004)</journal>
			<date>9/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...424..727P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.351.1099C</bibcode>
			<title>Timing analysis of the isolated neutron star RX J0720.4-3125 revisited</title>
			<authors>Cropper, Mark; Haberl, Frank; Zane, Silvia; Zavlin, Vyacheslav E.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 351, Issue 3, pp. 1099-1108.</journal>
			<date>7/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.351.1099C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.350.1373R</bibcode>
			<title>XMM-Newton observations of polars in low accretion states</title>
			<authors>Ramsay, Gavin; Cropper, Mark; Wu, Kinwah; Mason, K. O.; Crdova, F. A.; Priedhorsky, W.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 350, Issue 4, pp. 1373-1384.</journal>
			<date>6/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.350.1373R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...419.1045M</bibcode>
			<title>A possible new dipping X-ray source in the field of M 31</title>
			<authors>Mangano, V.; Israel, G. L.; Stella, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.419, p.1045-1056 (2004)</journal>
			<date>6/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...419.1045M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.347..497R</bibcode>
			<title>The energy balance of polars revisited</title>
			<authors>Ramsay, Gavin; Cropper, Mark</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 347, Issue 2, pp. 497-507.</journal>
			<date>1/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.347..497R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.347...95R</bibcode>
			<title>XMM-Newton observations of three short-period polars: V347 Pav, GG Leo and EU UMa</title>
			<authors>Ramsay, Gavin; Cropper, Mark; Mason, K. O.; Crdova, F. A.; Priedhorsky, W.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 347, Issue 1, pp. 95-100.</journal>
			<date>1/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.347...95R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...406..535Z</bibcode>
			<title>The Hamburg/RASS Catalogue of optical identifications. Northern high-galactic latitude ROSAT Bright Source  Catalogue X-ray sources</title>
			<authors>Zickgraf, F.-J.; Engels, D.; Hagen, H.-J.; Reimers, D.; Voges, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.406, p.535-553 (2003)</journal>
			<date>8/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...406..535Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...403..247F</bibcode>
			<title>A systematic study of X-ray variability in the ROSAT all-sky survey</title>
			<authors>Fuhrmeister, B.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.403, p.247-260 (2003)</journal>
			<date>5/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...403..247F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003PASP..115..410W</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic Cataclysmic Variables</title>
			<authors>Warner, Brian</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 115, Issue 805, pp. 410-411.</journal>
			<date>3/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003PASP..115..410W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003MNRAS.340....1K</bibcode>
			<title>UBVRI photopolarimetry of the long-period eclipsing AM Herculis binary V1309 Ori</title>
			<authors>Katajainen, S.; Piirola, V.; Ramsay, G.; Scaltriti, F.; Lehto, H. J.; Cropper, M.; Harrop-Allin, M. K.; Anderlucci, E.; Hakala, P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notice of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 340, Issue 1, pp. 1-11.</journal>
			<date>3/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003MNRAS.340....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003MNRAS.338..219R</bibcode>
			<title>XMM-Newton observations of the polars EV UMa, RX J1002-19 and RX J1007-20</title>
			<authors>Ramsay, Gavin; Cropper, Mark</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notice of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 338, Issue 1, pp. 219-226.</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003MNRAS.338..219R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.335..918R</bibcode>
			<title>First X-ray observations of the polar CE Gru</title>
			<authors>Ramsay, Gavin; Cropper, Mark</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notice of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 335, Issue 4, pp. 918-922.</journal>
			<date>10/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.335..918R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...392..541S</bibcode>
			<title>A multiwavelength timing analysis of the eclipsing polar DP Leo</title>
			<authors>Schwope, A. D.; Hambaryan, V.; Schwarz, R.; Kanbach, G.; Gnsicke, B. T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.392, p.541-551 (2002)</journal>
			<date>9/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...392..541S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...392..505S</bibcode>
			<title>A new two-pole accretion polar: RX J1846.9+5538</title>
			<authors>Schwarz, R.; Greiner, J.; Tovmassian, G. H.; Zharikov, S. V.; Wenzel, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.392, p.505-514 (2002)</journal>
			<date>9/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...392..505S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.332..116P</bibcode>
			<title>First XMM-Newton observations of strongly magnetic cataclysmic variables - II. Timing studies of DP Leo and WW Hor</title>
			<authors>Pandel, Dirk; Cordova, France A.; Shirey, Robert E.; Ramsay, Gavin; Cropper, Mark; Mason, Keith O.; Much, Rudi; Kilkenny, Dave</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 332, Issue 1, pp. 116-126.</journal>
			<date>5/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.332..116P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...565..511H</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared Properties of Cataclysmic Variables in the 2 Micron All-Sky Survey Second Incremental Data Release</title>
			<authors>Hoard, D. W.; Wachter, S.; Clark, L. Lee; Bowers, Timothy P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 565, Issue 1, pp. 511-538.</journal>
			<date>1/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...565..511H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001MNRAS.328..112T</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray beaming caused by resonance scattering in the accretion column of magnetic cataclysmic variables</title>
			<authors>Terada, Y.; Ishida, M.; Makishima, K.; Imanari, T.; Fujimoto, R.; Matsuzaki, K.; Kaneda, H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 328, Issue 1, pp. 112-126.</journal>
			<date>11/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001MNRAS.328..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001MNRAS.326L..27R</bibcode>
			<title>First XMM-Newton observations of strongly magnetic cataclysmic variables - I. Spectral studies of DP Leo and WW Hor</title>
			<authors>Ramsay, Gavin; Cropper, Mark; Crdova, France; Mason, Keith; Much, Rudi; Pandel, Dirk; Shirey, Robert</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 326, Issue 2, pp. L27-L32.</journal>
			<date>9/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001MNRAS.326L..27R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001PASP..113..764D</bibcode>
			<title>A Catalog and Atlas of Cataclysmic Variables: The Living Edition</title>
			<authors>Downes, Ronald A.; Webbink, Ronald F.; Shara, Michael M.; Ritter, Hans; Kolb, Ulrich; Duerbeck, Hilmar W.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 113, Issue 784, pp. 764-768.</journal>
			<date>6/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001PASP..113..764D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...372..945K</bibcode>
			<title>UBVRI-polarimetry of the AM Herculis star RX J0203.8+2959</title>
			<authors>Katajainen, S.; Scaltriti, F.; Piirola, V.; Lehto, H. J.; Anderlucci, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.372, p.945-951 (2001)</journal>
			<date>6/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...372..945K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001MNRAS.322..631R</bibcode>
			<title>Multiwavelength monitoring of QS Tel</title>
			<authors>Rosen, S. R.; Rainger, J. F.; Burleigh, M. R.; Mittaz, J. P. D.; Buckley, D. A. H.; Sirk, M. M.; Lieu, R.; Howell, S. B.; de Martino, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 322, Issue 3, pp. 631-642.</journal>
			<date>4/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001MNRAS.322..631R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...548..410S</bibcode>
			<title>Time-resolved Hubble Space Telescope Spectroscopy of Four Eclipsing Magnetic Cataclysmic Variables</title>
			<authors>Schmidt, Gary D.; Stockman, H. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 548, Issue 1, pp. 410-424.</journal>
			<date>2/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...548..410S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000PASP..112..873W</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetism in Isolated and Binary White Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Wickramasinghe, D. T.; Ferrario, Lilia</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 112, Issue 773, pp. 873-924.</journal>
			<date>7/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000PASP..112..873W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...358..417M</bibcode>
			<title>Cataclysmic variables as sources of gravitational waves</title>
			<authors>Meliani, M. T.; de Araujo, J. C. N.; Aguiar, O. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.358, p.417-424 (2000)</journal>
			<date>6/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...358..417M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000NewAR..44...69W</bibcode>
			<title>Accretion and magnetic field structure in AM Herculis systems</title>
			<authors>Wickramasinghe, D. T.; Ferrario, L.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 44, Issue 1-2, p. 69-74.</journal>
			<date>4/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000NewAR..44...69W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...354..605G</bibcode>
			<title>RX J1313.2-3259, a missing link in CV evolution?</title>
			<authors>Gnsicke, B. T.; Beuermann, K.; de Martino, D.; Thomas, H.-C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.354, p.605-609 (2000)</journal>
			<date>2/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...354..605G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...349..389V</bibcode>
			<title>The ROSAT all-sky survey bright source catalogue</title>
			<authors>Voges, W.; Aschenbach, B.; Boller, Th.; Bruninger, H.; Briel, U.; Burkert, W.; Dennerl, K.; Englhauser, J.; Gruber, R.; Haberl, F.; Hartner, G.; Hasinger, G.; Krster, M.; Pfeffermann, E.; Pietsch, W.; Predehl, P.; Rosso, C.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Trmper, J.; Zimmermann, H. U.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.349, p.389-405 (1999)</journal>
			<date>9/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...349..389V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999PASP..111..532S</bibcode>
			<title>White Dwarfs in Cataclysmic Variables</title>
			<authors>Sion, E. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 111, Issue 759, pp. 532-555.</journal>
			<date>5/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999PASP..111..532S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...343..157R</bibcode>
			<title>HS 1023+3900 - a magnetic CV in the period gap with a distinct cyclotron emission line spectrum</title>
			<authors>Reimers, D.; Hagen, H.-J.; Hopp, U.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.343, p.157-162 (1999)</journal>
			<date>3/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...343..157R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...343..132C</bibcode>
			<title>Asynchronous rotation in the polars</title>
			<authors>Campbell, C. G.; Schwope, A. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.343, p.132-136 (1999)</journal>
			<date>3/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...343..132C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999MmSAI..70..547D</bibcode>
			<title>UV observations of magnetic cataclysmic variables.</title>
			<authors>de Martino, D.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societa Astronomica Italiana, 70, 547-563 (1999)</journal>
			<date>0/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999MmSAI..70..547D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998AJ....115.2587T</bibcode>
			<title>Initial Results of a Comprehensive Ultrasoft Survey of the Einstein IPC Database: Source List and Confirmation of the Selection Procedure</title>
			<authors>Thompson, R. J.; Shelton, R. G.; Arning, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 115, Issue 6, pp. 2587-2593.</journal>
			<date>6/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998AJ....115.2587T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998MNRAS.295..899B</bibcode>
			<title>Polarimetry of the eclipsing polar RX J0929.1-2404</title>
			<authors>Buckley, David A. H.; Ferrario, Lilia; Wickramasinghe, Dayal T.; Bailey, Jeremy A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 295, Issue 4, pp. 899-906.</journal>
			<date>4/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998MNRAS.295..899B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;AS..129...83R</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of cataclysmic binaries, low-mass X-ray binaries and related objects (Sixth edition)</title>
			<authors>Ritter, H.; Kolb, U.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.129, p.83-85</journal>
			<date>4/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26AS..129...83R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;A...327..602V</bibcode>
			<title>Cataclysmic variables in the ROSAT PSPC All Sky Survey.</title>
			<authors>Verbunt, F.; Bunk, W. H.; Ritter, H.; Pfeffermann, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.327, p.602-613</journal>
			<date>11/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26A...327..602V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;A...325.1070G</bibcode>
			<title>Periodic changes of the accretion geometry in the nearly-synchronous polar RX J1940.1-1025.</title>
			<authors>Geckeler, R. D.; Staubert, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.325, p.1070-1076</journal>
			<date>9/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26A...325.1070G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997PASP..109..345D</bibcode>
			<title>A Catalog and Atlas of Cataclysmic Variables-Second Edition</title>
			<authors>Downes, Ronald; Webbink, Ronald F.; Shara, Michael M.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, v.109, p.345-440</journal>
			<date>4/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997PASP..109..345D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997AN....318...25S</bibcode>
			<title>Phase-resolved spectroscopy and photometry of the eclipsing polar EP Draconis (=H1907+690)</title>
			<authors>Schwope, A. D.; Mengel, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, vol. 318, no. 1, p. 25.</journal>
			<date>0/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997AN....318...25S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996MNRAS.282..726R</bibcode>
			<title>Optical polarization and X-ray data on the AM HER star RE J1844-74</title>
			<authors>Ramsay, Gavin; Cropper, Mark; Wu, Kinwah; Potter, Stephen</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 282, Issue 3, pp. 726-734.</journal>
			<date>10/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996MNRAS.282..726R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996MNRAS.282..362S</bibcode>
			<title>The system parameters of the polars MR SER and ST LMi</title>
			<authors>Shahbaz, T.; Wood, Janet H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 282, Issue 2, pp. 362-372.</journal>
			<date>9/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996MNRAS.282..362S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996A&amp;A...312...93V</bibcode>
			<title>The systemic-velocity distribution of cataclysmic variables.</title>
			<authors>van Paradijs, J.; Augusteijn, T.; Stehle, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.312, p.93-96</journal>
			<date>8/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996A%26A...312...93V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AJ....112..289S</bibcode>
			<title>IUE Observations of Four Known/Suspected Magnetic Cataclysmic Variables</title>
			<authors>Szkody, Paula; Silber, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.112, p.289</journal>
			<date>7/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AJ....112..289S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996MNRAS.280.1121R</bibcode>
			<title>Accretion mode changes in QS Tel (RE 1938-461): EUVE, ROSAT and optical observations</title>
			<authors>Rosen, S. R.; Mittaz, J. P. D.; Buckley, D. A.; Layden, A. C.; Clayton, K. L.; McCain, C.; Wynn, G. A.; Sirk, M. M.; Osborne, J. P.; Watson, M. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 280, Issue 4, pp. 1121-1142.</journal>
			<date>6/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996MNRAS.280.1121R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996ApJ...456..777W</bibcode>
			<title>BT Monocerotis: Another Extraordinary Old Nova</title>
			<authors>White, James C., II; Schlegel, Eric M.; Honeycutt, R. Kent</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.456, p.777</journal>
			<date>1/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996ApJ...456..777W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AGAb...12...32G</bibcode>
			<title>Accretion heated magnetic white dwarfs.</title>
			<authors>Gnsicke, B. T.; Beuermann, K.; de Martino, D.; Jordan, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Gesellschaft Abstract Series, No. 12, p. 32</journal>
			<date>0/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AGAb...12...32G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJ...455..260W</bibcode>
			<title>X-Ray Emission from Magnetic Cataclysmic Variables and White Dwarf Mass Estimates</title>
			<authors>Wu, Kinwah; Chanmugam, G.; Shaviv, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.455, p.260</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJ...455..260W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;AS..114..465K</bibcode>
			<title>A ROSAT XUV pointed phase source catalogue.</title>
			<authors>Kreysing, H.-C.; Brunner, H.; Staubert, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.114, p.465</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26AS..114..465K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;AS..114..269D</bibcode>
			<title>Vitesses radiales. Catalogue WEB: Wilson Evans Batten. Subtittle: Radial velocities: The Wilson-Evans-Batten catalogue.</title>
			<authors>Duflot, M.; Figon, P.; Meyssonnier, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.114, p.269</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26AS..114..269D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995PASA...12..165W</bibcode>
			<title>On the Statistics of Am-Herculis Binaries</title>
			<authors>Wu, K.; Wickramasinghe, D. T.; Li, J.</authors>
			<journal>Proceedings of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Vol.12:2, P. 165, 1995</journal>
			<date>8/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995PASA...12..165W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJS...99..701F</bibcode>
			<title>The Einstein Extended Medium-Sensitivity Survey Second Epoch: Results for the Stars</title>
			<authors>Fleming, Thomas A.; Molendi, Silvano; Maccacaro, Tommaso; Wolter, Anna</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement v.99, p.701</journal>
			<date>8/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJS...99..701F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995PASP..107..307P</bibcode>
			<title>The Remarkable Eclipsing Asynchronous AM Herculis Binary RX J19402-1025</title>
			<authors>Patterson, Joseph; Skillman, David R.; Thorstensen, John; Hellier, Coel</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, v.107, p.307</journal>
			<date>4/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995PASP..107..307P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995PASA...12...66F</bibcode>
			<title>The Magnetic Field of 1H:1752+08</title>
			<authors>Ferrario, L.; Wickramasinghe, D. T.; Bailey, J.; Buckley, D.</authors>
			<journal>Proceedings of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Vol.12:1, P. 66, 1995</journal>
			<date>4/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995PASA...12...66F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJ...439..322S</bibcode>
			<title>Gamma-ray emission from Cataclysmic variables. 1: The Compton EGRET survey</title>
			<authors>Schlegel, Eric M.; Barrett, Paul E.; de Jager, O. C.; Chanmugam, G.; Hunter, S.; Mattox, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 439, no. 1, p. 322-329</journal>
			<date>1/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJ...439..322S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;AS..109..177W</bibcode>
			<title>Radio continuum emission from stars: a catalogue update.</title>
			<authors>Wendker, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Suppl. 109, 177-179 (1995)</journal>
			<date>1/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26AS..109..177W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994MNRAS.271..733T</bibcode>
			<title>Ww-Horologii - X-Ray and Optical Observations</title>
			<authors>Tennant, A. F.; Bailey, J.; Wickramasinghe, D. T.; Wu, K.; Ferrario, L.; Hough, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 271, NO. 3/DEC1, P. 733, 1994</journal>
			<date>12/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994MNRAS.271..733T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994ApJ...437..436R</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray variability and period determinations in the eclipsing polar DP Leonis</title>
			<authors>Robinson, Craig R.; Cordova, France A.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 437, no. 1, p. 436-448</journal>
			<date>12/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994ApJ...437..436R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994AJ....108.2207B</bibcode>
			<title>A microwave survey of magnetic cataclysmic variables</title>
			<authors>Beasley, A. J.; Bastian, T. S.; Ball, Lewis; Wu, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 108, no. 6, p. 2207-2211</journal>
			<date>12/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994AJ....108.2207B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994AAS...185.2118R</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for Magnetic Activity Induced Accretion Position Oscillations in the Eclipsing Polar DP Leo</title>
			<authors>Robinson, C. R.; Cordova, F. A.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 185th AAS Meeting, #21.18; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 26, p.1346</journal>
			<date>12/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994AAS...185.2118R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994MNRAS.270..692R</bibcode>
			<title>ROSAT Observations of An-Ursae and Mr-Serpentis - the Status of the Soft X-Ray Excess in Am-Herculis Stars</title>
			<authors>Ramsay, G.; Mason, K. O.; Cropper, M.; Watson, M. G.; Clayton, K. L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 270, NO. 3/OCT1, P. 692, 1994</journal>
			<date>10/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994MNRAS.270..692R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994MNRAS.270..650O</bibcode>
			<title>The Discovery of RE:1307+535 - the Shortest Period Am-Herculis System</title>
			<authors>Osborne, J. P.; Beardmore, A. P.; Wheatley, P. J.; Hakala, P.; Watson, M. G.; Mason, K. O.; Hassall, B. J. M.; King, A. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 270, NO. 3/OCT1, P. 650, 1994</journal>
			<date>10/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994MNRAS.270..650O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994PASAu..11..198W</bibcode>
			<title>Accretion geometry of synchronously rotating magnetic cataclysmic variables: Theories versus observations</title>
			<authors>Wu, Kinwah; Wickramasinghe, D. T.; Bailey, J.; Tennant, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of Australia, Proceedings, vol. 11, no. 2, p. 198-200</journal>
			<date>8/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994PASAu..11..198W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994MNRAS.269..779P</bibcode>
			<title>A 5-GHZ Radio Survey of Magnetic Cataclysmic Variables</title>
			<authors>Pavelin, P. E.; Spencer, R. E.; Davis, R. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 269, NO. 3/AUG1, P. 779, 1994</journal>
			<date>8/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994MNRAS.269..779P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994ApJ...430..323S</bibcode>
			<title>Eclipse mapping of the accreting magnetic white dwarf in DP Leonis with HST</title>
			<authors>Stockman, H. S.; Schmidt, Gary D.; Liebert, James; Holberg, J. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 430, no. 1, p. 323-331</journal>
			<date>7/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994ApJ...430..323S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994MNRAS.268..128F</bibcode>
			<title>The Polarization and Magnetic Field of REJ1938-461 during its Low State</title>
			<authors>Ferrario, L.; Wickramasinghe, D. T.; Bailey, J. A.; Buckley, D. A. H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 268, NO. 1/MAY1, P. 128, 1994</journal>
			<date>5/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994MNRAS.268..128F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994ApJ...424..967G</bibcode>
			<title>A broad observational study of the eclipsing magnetic cataclysmic variable RE 2107-05</title>
			<authors>Glenn, Jason; Howell, Steve B.; Schmidt, Gary D.; Liebert, James; Grauer, Albert D.; Wagner, R. Mark</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 424, no. 2, p. 967-975</journal>
			<date>4/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994ApJ...424..967G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994ApJ...424..955S</bibcode>
			<title>1H 1752 + 081: an eclipsing cataclysmic variable with a small accretion disk</title>
			<authors>Silber, Andrew D.; Remillard, Ronald A.; Horne, Keith; Bradt, Hale V.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 424, no. 2, p. 955-966</journal>
			<date>4/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994ApJ...424..955S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993AcApS..13..367F</bibcode>
			<title>Newly Statistics on the Period Distribution of Shortperiod Cataclysmic Variables</title>
			<authors>Feng, X. C.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astrophysica Sinica, Vol.13:4, P. 367, 1993</journal>
			<date>10/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993AcApS..13..367F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993AAS...183.5507R</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray Observations of the Eclipsing Polar DP Leo</title>
			<authors>Robinson, C. R.; Cordova, F. A.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 183rd AAS Meeting, #55.07; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 25, p.1379</journal>
			<date>9/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993AAS...183.5507R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993MNRAS.262..285F</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of cyclotron emission features in the infrared spectrum of ST LMi</title>
			<authors>Ferrario, Lilia; Bailey, Jeremy; Wickramasinghe, Dayal T.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 262, no. 2, p. 285-288.</journal>
			<date>5/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993MNRAS.262..285F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993MNRAS.261L..31B</bibcode>
			<title>Changes of Accretion SPOT Longitude in Eclipsing Am-Herculis Binaries</title>
			<authors>Bailey, J.; Wickramasinghe, D. T.; Ferrario, L.; Hough, J. H.; Cropper, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 261, NO.4/APR15, P. L31, 1993</journal>
			<date>4/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993MNRAS.261L..31B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993PASP..105..127D</bibcode>
			<title>A catalog and atlas of cataclysmic variables</title>
			<authors>Downes, Ronald A.; Shara, Michael M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 105, no. 684, p. 127-245.</journal>
			<date>2/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993PASP..105..127D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993MNRAS.260..696C</bibcode>
			<title>Cyclotron humps in AM HER systems. V - Two poles in DP Leo</title>
			<authors>Cropper, Mark; Wickramasinghe, D. T.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 260, no. 3, p. 696-704.</journal>
			<date>2/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993MNRAS.260..696C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993MNRAS.260..209R</bibcode>
			<title>A survey for QPOs in AM Herculis stars and a detailed study of the QPOs in an Ursae Majoris</title>
			<authors>Ramseyer, Tod F.; Robinson, Edward L.; Zhang, Erho; Wood, Janet H.; Stiening, Rae F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 260, no. 1, p. 209-220.</journal>
			<date>1/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993MNRAS.260..209R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJ...401..628S</bibcode>
			<title>A search for circular polarization in cataclysmic variables</title>
			<authors>Stockman, H. S.; Schmidt, Gary D.; Berriman, G.; Liebert, James; Moore, R. L.; Wickramasinghe, D. T.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 401, no. 2, p. 628-641.</journal>
			<date>12/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJ...401..628S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ARA&amp;A..30..143C</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic fields of degenerate stars</title>
			<authors>Chanmugam, G.</authors>
			<journal>In: Annual review of astronomy and astrophysics. Vol. 30 (A93-25826 09-90), p. 143-184.</journal>
			<date>0/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ARA%26A..30..143C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991ApJS...76..813S</bibcode>
			<title>The Einstein Observatory Extended Medium-Sensitivity Survey. II - The optical identifications</title>
			<authors>Stocke, John T.; Morris, Simon L.; Gioia, I. M.; Maccacaro, T.; Schild, R.; Wolter, A.; Fleming, Thomas A.; Henry, J. Patrick</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 76, July 1991, p. 813-874. Research supported by Smithsonian Institution and CNR.</journal>
			<date>7/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991ApJS...76..813S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991ApJ...375..600C</bibcode>
			<title>The formation and detection of strongly magnetic white dwarf binaries in globular clusters</title>
			<authors>Chanmugam, G.; Ray, A.; Singh, K. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 375, July 10, 1991, p. 600-607.</journal>
			<date>7/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991ApJ...375..600C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991MNRAS.250..152K</bibcode>
			<title>Synchronous rotation in AM Herculis systems. II - Stability</title>
			<authors>King, Andrew R.; Whitehurst, Robert</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 250, May 1, 1991, p. 152-156.</journal>
			<date>5/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991MNRAS.250..152K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991A&amp;A...244..373S</bibcode>
			<title>The orbital period of the polar MR Serpentis</title>
			<authors>Schwope, A. D.; Naundorf, C. E.; Thomas, H.-C.; Beuermann, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 244, no. 2, April 1991, p. 373-377.</journal>
			<date>4/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991A%26A...244..373S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990A&amp;AS...85.1179R</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of cataclysmic binaries, low-mass X-ray binaries and related objects (Fifth edition)</title>
			<authors>Ritter, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 85, no. 3, Nov. 1990, p. 1179-1256.</journal>
			<date>11/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990A%26AS...85.1179R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990MNRAS.245..760C</bibcode>
			<title>Cyclotron Humps in Am-Herculis Systems - Variations around the Orbit in Dp-Leonis</title>
			<authors>Cropper, M.; Mukai, K.; Mason, K. O.; Smale, A. P.; Charles, P. A.; Mittaz, J. P. D.; Machin, G.; Hassall, B. J. M.; Callanan, P. J.; Naylor, T.; van Paradijs, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 245, NO.4/AUG15, P. 760, 1990</journal>
			<date>8/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990MNRAS.245..760C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990ApJ...357..582F</bibcode>
			<title>Arc-shaped cyclotron emission regions in AM Herculis systems</title>
			<authors>Ferrario, Lilia; Wickramasinghe, D. T.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 357, July 10, 1990, p. 582-590.</journal>
			<date>7/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990ApJ...357..582F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990MNRAS.244..731K</bibcode>
			<title>Synchronous rotation in AM Herculis systems. I - Equilibrium configurations</title>
			<authors>King, A. R.; Whitehurst, R.; Frank, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 244, June 15, 1990, p. 731-737.</journal>
			<date>6/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990MNRAS.244..731K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990ApJ...356..623H</bibcode>
			<title>High galactic latitude cataclysmic variables</title>
			<authors>Howell, Steve B.; Szkody, Paula</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 356, June 20, 1990, p. 623-629. Research supported by NASA.</journal>
			<date>6/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990ApJ...356..623H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990SSRv...52..203L</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of low-resolution IUE spectra of dwarf novae and nova-like stars</title>
			<authors>La Dous, Constanze</authors>
			<journal>Space Science Reviews (ISSN 0038-6308), vol. 52, April 1990, p. 203-706.</journal>
			<date>4/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990SSRv...52..203L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990MNRAS.243..565C</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic fields in AM HER systems - A possible field for 1E1048.5 + 5241 (EK UMa) from cyclotron humps</title>
			<authors>Cropper, Mark; Mason, K. O.; Mukai, K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 243, April 15, 1990, p. 565-569. Research supported by the Royal Society.</journal>
			<date>4/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990MNRAS.243..565C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990MNRAS.243...57B</bibcode>
			<title>The masses of cataclysmic variables - A statistical approach</title>
			<authors>Bailey, Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 243, March 1, 1990, p. 57-64.</journal>
			<date>3/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990MNRAS.243...57B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990ApJS...72..567G</bibcode>
			<title>The Einstein Observatory Extended Medium-Sensitivity Survey. I - X-ray data and analysis</title>
			<authors>Gioia, I. M.; Maccacaro, T.; Schild, R. E.; Wolter, A.; Stocke, J. T.; Morris, S. L.; Henry, J. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 72, March 1990, p. 567-619. Research supported by Smithsonian Institution and CNR.</journal>
			<date>3/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990ApJS...72..567G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990AISAO..30....3V</bibcode>
			<title>Close Binary Systems of Am-Herculis - Observational Data Review</title>
			<authors>Vojkhanskaya, N. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astrofizicheskie Issledovaniia Izvestiya Spetsial'noj Astrofizicheskoj Observatorii, Vol. 30, P. 3, 1990</journal>
			<date>0/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990AISAO..30....3V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989ApJ...346..941M</bibcode>
			<title>H0538+608 - A long-period AM HER system exhibiting extreme variations in accretion geometry</title>
			<authors>Mason, Paul A.; Liebert, James; Schmidt, Gary D.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 346, Nov. 15, 1989, p. 941-949.</journal>
			<date>11/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989ApJ...346..941M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989A&amp;A...217..146L</bibcode>
			<title>Optical one second quasi-periodic oscillations in VV Puppis</title>
			<authors>Larsson, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 217, no. 1-2, June 1989, p. 146-156.</journal>
			<date>6/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989A%26A...217..146L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988PASP..100.1522G</bibcode>
			<title>Observed low states in DQ Herculis systems</title>
			<authors>Garnavich, Peter; Szkody, Paula</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 100, Dec. 1988, p. 1522-1528.</journal>
			<date>12/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988PASP..100.1522G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988A&amp;A...207...55V</bibcode>
			<title>Origin of the gamma ray bursts</title>
			<authors>Vahia, M. N.; Rao, A. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 207, no. 1, Dec. 1988, p. 55-69.</journal>
			<date>12/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988A%26A...207...55V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988MNRAS.234.1105N</bibcode>
			<title>A search for radio emission from X-ray binaries and related objects</title>
			<authors>Nelson, R. F.; Spencer, R. E.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 234, Oct. 15, 1988, p. 1105-1118.</journal>
			<date>10/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988MNRAS.234.1105N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988MNRAS.232..175M</bibcode>
			<title>Accretion streams in AM HER type systems</title>
			<authors>Mukai, Koji</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 232, May 1, 1988, p. 175-197.</journal>
			<date>5/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988MNRAS.232..175M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988MNRAS.231..597C</bibcode>
			<title>The orientations of the magnetic pole in AM HER systems - Implications for synchronous rotation and selection effects</title>
			<authors>Cropper, Mark</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 231, April 1, 1988, p. 597-608. SERC-supported research.</journal>
			<date>4/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988MNRAS.231..597C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988MmSAI..59..117O</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic cataclysmic variables seen by EXOSAT</title>
			<authors>Osborne, J. P.</authors>
			<journal>Societ Astronomica Italiana, Memorie (ISSN 0037-8720), vol. 59, no. 1-2, 1988, p. 117-145.</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988MmSAI..59..117O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988MmSAI..59...33G</bibcode>
			<title>Serendipitous sources in EXOSAT images</title>
			<authors>Giommi, P.; Tagliaferri, G.; Angelini, L.</authors>
			<journal>Societ Astronomica Italiana, Memorie (ISSN 0037-8720), vol. 59, no. 1-2, 1988, p. 33-51.</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988MmSAI..59...33G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988AcA....38..329C</bibcode>
			<title>On a polar Nova Cygni 1975 (V1500 Cyg)</title>
			<authors>Chlebowski, Tomasz; Kaluzny, Janusz</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica (ISSN 0001-5237), vol. 38, no. 4, 1988, p. 329-338. Research supported by the Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics and Smithsonian Institution.</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988AcA....38..329C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987ApJ...322L..95W</bibcode>
			<title>The period distribution and evolution of short-period cataclysmic variables</title>
			<authors>Warner, Brian; Livio, Mario</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 2 - Letters to the Editor (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 322, Nov. 15, 1987, p. L95-L98.</journal>
			<date>11/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987ApJ...322L..95W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987MNRAS.228..389C</bibcode>
			<title>Polarimetry of BL HYI (H0139-68) in high and low states</title>
			<authors>Cropper, Mark</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 228, Sept. 15, 1987, p. 389-399. Research supported by the Council for Scientific and Industrial Research and SERC.</journal>
			<date>9/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987MNRAS.228..389C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;AS...70..335R</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of cataclysmic binaries, low-mass X-ray binaries and related objects (Fourth edition)</title>
			<authors>Ritter, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 70, no. 3, Sept. 1987, p. 335-367.</journal>
			<date>9/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26AS...70..335R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987MNRAS.227..205K</bibcode>
			<title>Mass transfer rates and the soft X-ray excess in AM Herculis binaries</title>
			<authors>King, A. R.; Watson, M. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 227, July 1, 1987, p. 205-211.</journal>
			<date>7/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987MNRAS.227..205K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987ApJ...316..275H</bibcode>
			<title>The evolution of magnetic cataclysmic variables</title>
			<authors>Hameury, J. M.; King, A. R.; Lasota, J. P.; Ritter, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 316, May 1, 1987, p. 275-282.</journal>
			<date>5/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987ApJ...316..275H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987ApJS...63..685S</bibcode>
			<title>Photometry and spectroscopy of short-period cataclysmic variables</title>
			<authors>Szkody, Paula</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 63, March 1987, p. 685-699.</journal>
			<date>3/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987ApJS...63..685S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987ApJ...314..641M</bibcode>
			<title>1E 1048.5 + 5421 - A new 114 minute AM Herculis binary</title>
			<authors>Morris, Simon L.; Schmidt, Gary D.; Liebert, James; Stocke, John; Gioia, Isabella M.; Maccacaro, Tommaso</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 314, March 15, 1987, p. 641-652. SERC-NATO-supported research.</journal>
			<date>3/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987ApJ...314..641M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;A...175L...9B</bibcode>
			<title>EXO 023432-5232.3 - A new 114-minute probable AM-Herculis-type binary</title>
			<authors>Beuermann, K.; Thomas, H. C.; Giommi, P.; Tagliaferri, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 175, no. 1-2, March 1987, p. L9-L12.</journal>
			<date>3/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26A...175L...9B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;A...174..357S</bibcode>
			<title>EXOSAT observations of the magnetic binary system E1114 + 182</title>
			<authors>Schaaf, R.; Pietsch, W.; Biermann, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 174, no. 1-2, March 1987, p. 357, 358.</journal>
			<date>3/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26A...174..357S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987Ap&amp;SS.130..207O</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray observations of cataclysmic variables</title>
			<authors>Osborne, J. P.</authors>
			<journal>(IAU, DFG, and Bayerisches Staatsministerium fr Unterricht und Kultus, Colloquium on Cataclysmic Variables, Recent Multi-Frequency Observations and Theoretical Developments, 93rd, Bamberg, West Germany, June 16-19, 1986) Astrophysics and Space Science (ISSN 0004-640X), vol. 130, no. 1-2, Feb. 1987, p. 207-223.</journal>
			<date>2/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987Ap%26SS.130..207O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;AS...68...41B</bibcode>
			<title>A compilation of distances to cataclysmic variable stars</title>
			<authors>Berriman, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 68, no. 1, Feb. 1987, p. 41-50. SERC-supported research.</journal>
			<date>2/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26AS...68...41B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986IAUC.4289....2B</bibcode>
			<title>EXO 023432-5232.3</title>
			<authors>Beuermann, K.; Thomas, H.-C.; Giommi, P.; Tagliaferri, G.</authors>
			<journal>IAU Circ., 4289, 2 (1986).  Edited by Marsden, B. G.</journal>
			<date>12/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986IAUC.4289....2B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986MNRAS.219..589C</bibcode>
			<title>The attainment of synchronism in the presence of accretion in the AM Herculis binaries</title>
			<authors>Campbell, C. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 219, April 1, 1986, p. 589-596.</journal>
			<date>4/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986MNRAS.219..589C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985ApJ...293..321S</bibcode>
			<title>IUE results on the AM Herculis stars CW 1103, E1114, and PG 1550</title>
			<authors>Szkody, P.; Liebert, J.; Panek, R. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 293, June 1, 1985, p. 321-327.</journal>
			<date>6/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985ApJ...293..321S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985ApJ...293..303B</bibcode>
			<title>The new eclipsing magnetic binary system E 1114 + 182</title>
			<authors>Biermann, P.; Schmidt, G. D.; Liebert, J.; Tapia, S.; Strittmatter, P. A.; West, S.; Stockman, H. S.; Kuehr, H.; Lamb, D. Q.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 293, June 1, 1985, p. 303-320. Sponsorship: Deutsche Forschungsgemeinschaft.</journal>
			<date>6/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985ApJ...293..303B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985IBVS.2681....1K</bibcode>
			<title>The 67th Name-List of Variable Stars</title>
			<authors>Kholopov, P. N.; Samus, N. N.; Kazarovets, E. V.; Perova, N. B.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 2681, 1.</journal>
			<date>3/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985IBVS.2681....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984MNRAS.211...69C</bibcode>
			<title>Spin evolution of magnetic white dwarfs in AM Herculis binaries</title>
			<authors>Campbell, C. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 211, Nov. 1, 1984, p. 69-74.</journal>
			<date>11/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984MNRAS.211...69C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984ApJ...285..252C</bibcode>
			<title>The rotational and orbital evolution of cataclysmic binaries containing magnetic white dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Chanmugam, G.; Ray, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 285, Oct. 1, 1984, p. 252-257. Research supported by Louisiana State University.</journal>
			<date>10/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984ApJ...285..252C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984BAAS...16.1014S</bibcode>
			<title>Accretion Characteristics of the AM Her Stars CW1103+254, E1114+182 and PG 1550+191</title>
			<authors>Szkody, P.; Liebert, J.; Panek, K. J.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 16, p.1014</journal>
			<date>9/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984BAAS...16.1014S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984ApJS...54..443P</bibcode>
			<title>The evolution of cataclysmic and low-mass X-ray binaries</title>
			<authors>Patterson, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 54, April 1984, p. 443-493.</journal>
			<date>4/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984ApJS...54..443P</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
