<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..131D</bibcode>
			<title>Transitional Disks as Signposts of Young, Multiplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Salyk, Colette</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 131 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..131D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..33C</bibcode>
			<title>A 5 mum Image of beta Pictoris b at a Sub-Jupiter Projected Separation: Evidence for a Misalignment Between the Planet and the Inner, Warped Disk</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Thalmann, Christian; Matsumura, Soko; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Burrows, Adam; Kuchner, Marc</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L33 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..33C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..32Q</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for Gas Giant Planets on Solar System Scales: VLT NACO/APP Observations of the Debris Disk Host Stars HD172555 and HD115892</title>
			<authors>Quanz, Sascha P.; Kenworthy, Matthew A.; Meyer, Michael R.; Girard, Julien H. V.; Kasper, Markus</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L32 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..32Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733..126C</bibcode>
			<title>Estimates of the Planet Yield from Ground-based High-contrast Imaging Observations as a Function of Stellar Mass</title>
			<authors>Crepp, Justin R.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. 126 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733..126C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.473..187N</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters from secular planet-planet interactions</title>
			<authors>Naoz, Smadar; Farr, Will M.; Lithwick, Yoram; Rasio, Frederic A.; Teyssandier, Jean</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 473, Issue 7346, pp. 187-189 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.473..187N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...65B</bibcode>
			<title>Clouds and Chemistry in the Atmosphere of Extrasolar Planet HR8799b</title>
			<authors>Barman, Travis S.; Macintosh, Bruce; Konopacky, Quinn M.; Marois, Christian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 65 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.412.2137K</bibcode>
			<title>Collisional evolution of irregular satellite swarms: detectable dust around Solar system and extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Kennedy, G. M.; Wyatt, M. C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 412, Issue 4, pp. 2137-2153.</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.412.2137K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A.134B</bibcode>
			<title>VLT/NACO astrometry of the HR 8799 planetary system. L'-band observations of the three outer planets</title>
			<authors>Bergfors, C.; Brandner, W.; Janson, M.; K&#246;hler, R.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A134</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A.134B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...42L</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of an ~23 M Jup Brown Dwarf Orbiting ~700 AU from the Massive Star HIP 78530 in Upper Scorpius</title>
			<authors>Lafreni&#232;re, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; Janson, Markus; Helling, Christiane; Witte, Soeren; Hauschildt, Peter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. 42 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...42L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729..128C</bibcode>
			<title>A Combined Subaru/VLT/MMT 1-5 mum Study of Planets Orbiting HR 8799: Implications for Atmospheric Properties, Masses, and Formation</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Burrows, Adam; Itoh, Yoichi; Matsumura, Soko; Fukagawa, Misato; Apai, Daniel; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Hinz, Philip M.; Rodigas, T. J.; Kasper, Markus; Pyo, T.-S.; Ogino, Satoshi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 128 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729..128C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411..859M</bibcode>
			<title>The effects of fly-bys on planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Malmberg, Daniel; Davies, Melvyn B.; Heggie, Douglas C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 2, pp. 859-877.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411..859M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011NewA...16...27K</bibcode>
			<title>The outcome of the protoplanetary disk of very massive stars</title>
			<authors>Kashi, Amit; Soker, Noam</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 16, Issue 1, p. 27-32.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011NewA...16...27K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...11D</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer Infrared Spectrograph Study of Debris Disks Around Planet-host Stars</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Beichman, C. A.; Carpenter, John M.; Bryden, Geoffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 1, article id. 11 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...11D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...524L...1B</bibcode>
			<title>Dissecting the Moth: discovery of an off-centered ring in the HD 61005 debris disk with high-resolution imaging</title>
			<authors>Buenzli, E.; Thalmann, C.; Vigan, A.; Boccaletti, A.; Chauvin, G.; Augereau, J. C.; Meyer, M. R.; M&#233;nard, F.; Desidera, S.; Messina, S.; Henning, T.; Carson, J.; Montagnier, G.; Beuzit, J. L.; Bonavita, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Lagrange, A. M.; Mesa, D.; Mouillet, D.; Quanz, S. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 524, id.L1</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...524L...1B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724....1S</bibcode>
			<title>The Search for Planetary Mass Companions to Field Brown Dwarfs with HST/NICMOS</title>
			<authors>Stumpf, M. B.; Brandner, W.; Joergens, V.; Henning, Th.; Bouy, H.; K&#246; hler, R.; Kasper, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. 1-11 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724....1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..73E</bibcode>
			<title>Deep infrared imaging of close companions to austral A- and F-type stars</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Montagnier, G.; Chauvin, G.; Galland, F.; Beuzit, J.-L.; Rameau, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A73</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..73E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722L..49Q</bibcode>
			<title>First Results from Very Large Telescope NACO Apodizing Phase Plate: 4 mum Images of The Exoplanet beta Pictoris b</title>
			<authors>Quanz, Sascha P.; Meyer, Michael R.; Kenworthy, Matthew A.; Girard, Julien H. V.; Kasper, Markus; Lagrange, Anne-Marie; Apai, Daniel; Boccaletti, Anthony; Bonnefoy, Micka&#235;l; Chauvin, Gael; Hinz, Philip M.; Lenzen, Rainer</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. L49-L53 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722L..49Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407...71V</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric characterization of exoplanets using angular and spectral differential imaging</title>
			<authors>Vigan, A.; Moutou, C.; Langlois, M.; Allard, F.; Boccaletti, A.; Carbillet, M.; Mouillet, D.; Smith, I.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 1, pp. 71-82.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407...71V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122..905J</bibcode>
			<title>Giant Planet Occurrence in the Stellar Mass-Metallicity Plane</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Aller, Kimberly M.; Howard, Andrew W.; Crepp, Justin R.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 894, pp.905-915</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122..905J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.2279M</bibcode>
			<title>Exploring the conditions required to form giant planets via gravitational instability in massive protoplanetary discs</title>
			<authors>Meru, Farzana; Bate, Matthew R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 4, pp. 2279-2288.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.2279M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...329...57L</bibcode>
			<title>A Giant Planet Imaged in the Disk of the Young Star beta Pictoris</title>
			<authors>Lagrange, A.-M.; Bonnefoy, M.; Chauvin, G.; Apai, D.; Ehrenreich, D.; Boccaletti, A.; Gratadour, D.; Rouan, D.; Mouillet, D.; Lacour, S.; Kasper, M.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 329, Issue 5987, pp. 57- (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...329...57L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;ARv..18..317A</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and evolution of planetary systems: the impact of high-angular resolution optical techniques</title>
			<authors>Absil, Olivier; Mawet, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomy and Astrophysics Review, Volume 18, Issue 3, pp.317-382</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26ARv..18..317A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...515A..17J</bibcode>
			<title>NACO-SDI imaging of known companion host stars from the AAPS and Keck planet search surveys</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, J. S.; Jones, H. R. A.; Biller, B.; O'Toole, S. J.; Pinfield, D. J.; Close, L.; Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. P.; Wittenmyer, R.; Carter, B.; Day-Jones, A. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 515, id.A17</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...515A..17J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714.1570H</bibcode>
			<title>Constraints on Long-period Planets from an L'- and M-band Survey of Nearby Sun-like Stars: Modeling Results</title>
			<authors>Heinze, A. N.; Hinz, Philip M.; Kenworthy, Matthew; Meyer, Michael; Sivanandam, Suresh; Miller, Douglas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 2, pp. 1570-1581 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714.1570H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..52B</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared integral-field spectra of the planet/brown dwarf companion AB Pictoris b</title>
			<authors>Bonnefoy, M.; Chauvin, G.; Rojo, P.; Allard, F.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Homeier, D.; Dumas, C.; Beuzit, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A52</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..52B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122..162B</bibcode>
			<title>Imaging Young Giant Planets From Ground and Space</title>
			<authors>Beichman, Charles A.; Krist, John; Trauger, John T.; Greene, Tom; Oppenheimer, Ben; Sivaramakrishnan, Anand; Doyon, Ren&#233;; Boccaletti, Anthony; Barman, Travis S.; Rieke, Marcia</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, Issue 888, pp. 162-200.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122..162B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1408F</bibcode>
			<title>Stability of the Directly Imaged Multiplanet System HR 8799: Resonance and Masses</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1408-1421 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1408F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1375K</bibcode>
			<title>The Runts of the Litter: Why Planets Formed Through Gravitational Instability Can Only Be Failed Binary Stars</title>
			<authors>Kratter, Kaitlin M.; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.; Youdin, Andrew N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1375-1386 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1375K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A..52C</bibcode>
			<title>Deep imaging survey of young, nearby austral stars . VLT/NACO near-infrared Lyot-coronographic observations</title>
			<authors>Chauvin, G.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Bonavita, M.; Zuckerman, B.; Dumas, C.; Bessell, M. S.; Beuzit, J.-L.; Bonnefoy, M.; Desidera, S.; Farihi, J.; Lowrance, P.; Mouillet, D.; Song, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A52</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A..52C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707...79D</bibcode>
			<title>The Formation Mechanism of Gas Giants on Wide Orbits</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Beichman, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, pp. 79-88 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707...79D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705L.148C</bibcode>
			<title>Long Range Outward Migration of Giant Planets, with Application to Fomalhaut b</title>
			<authors>Crida, Aur&#233;lien; Masset, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Morbidelli, Alessandro</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 705, Issue 2, pp. L148-L152 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705L.148C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.399..377J</bibcode>
			<title>Imaging search for the unseen companion to &amp;epsil Ind A - improving the detection limits with 4 mum observations</title>
			<authors>Janson, M.; Apai, D.; Zechmeister, M.; Brandner, W.; K&#252;rster, M.; Kasper, M.; Reffert, S.; Endl, M.; Lafreni&#232;re, D.; Gei&#223;ler, K.; Hippler, S.; Henning, Th.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 399, Issue 1, pp. 377-384.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.399..377J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ARA&amp;A..47..253O</bibcode>
			<title>High-Contrast Observations in Optical and Infrared Astronomy</title>
			<authors>Oppenheimer, Ben R.; Hinkley, Sasha</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, vol. 47, Issue 1, pp.253-289</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ARA%26A..47..253O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702L.163N</bibcode>
			<title>Did Fomalhaut, HR 8799, and HL Tauri Form Planets Via the Gravitational Instability? Placing Limits on the Required Disk Masses</title>
			<authors>Nero, D.; Bjorkman, J. E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. L163-L167 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702L.163N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700.1647M</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer/Infrared Array Camera Limits to Planetary Companions of Fomalhaut and epsilon Eridani</title>
			<authors>Marengo, Massimo; Stapelfeldt, Karl; Werner, Michael W.; Hora, Joseph L.; Fazio, Giovanni G.; Schuster, Michael T.; Carson, Joseph C.; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 1647-1657 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700.1647M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1068P</bibcode>
			<title>New Debris Disks Around Young, Low-Mass Stars Discovered with the Spitzer Space Telescope</title>
			<authors>Plavchan, Peter; Werner, M. W.; Chen, C. H.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Su, K. Y. L.; Stauffer, J. R.; Song, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1068-1094 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1068P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...697.1928K</bibcode>
			<title>MMT/AO 5 mum Imaging Constraints on the Existence of Giant Planets Orbiting Fomalhaut at ~13-40 AU</title>
			<authors>Kenworthy, Matthew A.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Hinz, Philip M.; Meyer, Michael R.; Heinze, Aren N.; Miller, Douglas L.; Sivanandam, Suresh; Freed, Melanie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 697, Issue 2, pp. 1928-1933 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...697.1928K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498L..41L</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit alignment of the Fomalhaut planetary system probed by optical long baseline interferometry</title>
			<authors>Le Bouquin, J.-B.; Absil, O.; Benisty, M.; Massi, F.; M&#233;rand, A.; Stefl, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 3, 2009, pp.L41-L44</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498L..41L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121..309J</bibcode>
			<title>International Year of Astronomy Invited Review on Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 878, pp.309-315</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121..309J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...497..557L</bibcode>
			<title>Is beta Pictoris b the transiting planet of November 1981?</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 497, Issue 2, 2009, pp.557-562</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...497..557L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..734C</bibcode>
			<title>Fomalhaut's Debris Disk and Planet: Constraining the Mass of Fomalhaut b from disk Morphology</title>
			<authors>Chiang, E.; Kite, E.; Kalas, P.; Graham, J. R.; Clampin, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 734-749 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..734C</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar />
</planet>
