<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745..138M</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic Scaling Laws for the Atmospheres of Hot Giant Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Menou, Kristen</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 2, article id. 138 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745..138M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...78R</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Drag in the Energetics of Strongly Forced Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Rauscher, Emily; Menou, Kristen</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 78 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...78R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745....3M</bibcode>
			<title>The Atmospheric Chemistry of GJ 1214b: Photochemistry and Clouds</title>
			<authors>Miller-Ricci Kempton, Eliza; Zahnle, Kevin; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 3 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745....3M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..191M</bibcode>
			<title>Carbon-rich Giant Planets: Atmospheric Chemistry, Thermal Inversions, Spectra, and Formation Conditions</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, Nikku; Mousis, Olivier; Johnson, Torrence V.; Lunine, Jonathan I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 191 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..191M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...92B</bibcode>
			<title>The Optical and Near-infrared Transmission Spectrum of the Super-Earth GJ 1214b: Further Evidence for a Metal-rich Atmosphere</title>
			<authors>