<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725..261M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Inference of Thermal Inversions in Hot Jupiter Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 1, pp. 261-274 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725..261M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723L..60H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-29b: A Saturn-sized Transiting Exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Enoch, B.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233; gransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. L60-L63 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723L..60H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..116K</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the Thermosphere of HD209458b with UV Transit Observations</title>
			<authors>Koskinen, T. T.; Yelle, R. V.; Lavvas, P.; Lewis, N. K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 116-128 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..116K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..26N</bibcode>
			<title>Interior structure models of GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Nettelmann, N.; Kramm, U.; Redmer, R.; Neuh&#228;user, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A26</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..26N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1077D</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Transit Search for Planets around Cool Stars from the Western Italian Alps: A Site Characterization Study</title>
			<authors>Damasso, M.; Giacobbe, P.; Calcidese, P.; Sozzetti, A.; Lattanzi, M. G.; Bernagozzi, A.; Bertolini, E.; Smart, R. L.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 895, pp.1077-1091</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1077D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1020A</bibcode>
			<title>Observing Exoplanets with SOFIA</title>
			<authors>Angerhausen, D.; Krabbe, A.; Iserlohe, C.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 895, pp.1020-1029</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1020A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720..344L</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Circulation of Eccentric Hot Neptune GJ436b</title>
			<authors>Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Marley, Mark S.; Freedman, Richard S.; Lodders, Katharina</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 1, pp. 344-356 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720..344L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..66B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XI. CoRoT-8b: a hot and dense sub-Saturn around a K1 dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Cabrera, J.; Jorda, L.; Lovis, C.; Csizmadia, S.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Ollivier, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A66</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..66B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Cameron, A. C.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719L..45M</bibcode>
			<title>Water/Icy Super-Earths: Giant Impacts and Maximum Water Content</title>
			<authors>Marcus, Robert A.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Stewart, Sarah T.; Hernquist, Lars</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. L45-L49 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719L..45M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719.1796B</bibcode>
			<title>NICMOS Observations of the Transiting Hot Jupiter XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Burke, Christopher J.; McCullough, P. R.; Bergeron, L. E.; Long, Douglas; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Nelan, Edmund P.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Janes, Kenneth A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 2, pp. 1796-1806 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719.1796B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717..235D</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Observations of the WASP-10 System</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, J. A.; Close, L. M.; Scuderi, L. J.; Morris, M. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 1, pp. 235-238 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717..235D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518A..25G</bibcode>
			<title>The Spitzer search for the transits of HARPS low-mass planets. I. No transit for the super-Earth HD 40307b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Deming, D.; Demory, B.-O.; Lovis, C.; Seager, S.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Delmelle, S.; Magain, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.A25</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518A..25G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714..462S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Apparent Orbital Inclination Change of the Extrasolar Transiting Planet TrES-2b</title>
			<authors>Scuderi, Louis J.; Dittmann, Jason A.; Males, Jared R.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Close, Laird M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 462-468 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714..462S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.464.1161S</bibcode>
			<title>Possible thermochemical disequilibrium in the atmosphere of the exoplanet GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Stevenson, Kevin B.; Harrington, Joseph; Nymeyer, Sarah; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Bowman, William C.; Hardy, Ryan A.; Deming, Drake; Rauscher, Emily; Lust, Nate B.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 464, Issue 7292, pp. 1161-1164 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Natur.464.1161S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.126B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-4b: A Hot Neptune-like Planet of a G0 Star Near Main-sequence Turnoff</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Brown, Timothy M.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Monet, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L126-L130 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.126B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..974R</bibcode>
			<title>A Framework for Quantifying the Degeneracies of Exoplanet Interior Compositions</title>
			<authors>Rogers, L. A.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 2, pp. 974-991 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..974R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...327..977B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Planet-Detection Mission: Introduction and First Results</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy; Caldwell, Douglas; Caldwell, John; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kondo, Yoji; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Kjeldsen, Hans; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Morrison, David; Sasselov, Dimitar; Tarter, Jill; Boss, Alan; Brownlee, Don; Owen, Toby; Buzasi, Derek; Charbonneau, David; Doyle, Laurance; Fortney, Jonathan; Ford, Eric B.; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Rowe, Jason; Anderson, Howard; Buchhave, Lars; Ciardi, David; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Sherry, William; Horch, Elliott; Isaacson, Howard; Everett, Mark E.; Fischer, Debra; Torres, Guillermo; Johnson, John Asher; Endl, Michael; MacQueen, Phillip; Bryson, Stephen T.; Dotson, Jessie; Haas, Michael; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Allen, Christopher; Li, Jie; Wu, Haley; Tenenbaum, Peter; Verner, Ekaterina; Bruhweiler, Frederick; Barnes, Jason; Prsa, Andrej</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 327, Issue 5968, pp. 977- (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...327..977B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401.2665P</bibcode>
			<title>Refined stellar, orbital and planetary parameters of the eccentric HAT-P-2 planetary system</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Torres, Guillermo; Noyes, Robert W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Johnson, John A.; Henry, Gregory W.; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Howard, Andrew W.; Sipocz, Brigitta; Latham, David W.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 4, pp. 2665-2674.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401.2665P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1724B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-11b: A Super-Neptune Planet Transiting a Bright K Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; P&#225;l, A.; Hartman, J.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Isaacson, H.; Howard, A.; Vogt, S.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Fernandez, J.; Mo&#243;r, A.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1724-1745 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1551O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Planetary Emission from the Exoplanet Tres-2 Using Spitzer/IRAC</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Harrington, Joseph; Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1551-1556 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1551O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...511L...8S</bibcode>
			<title>A scenario of planet erosion by coronal radiation</title>
			<authors>Sanz-Forcada, J.; Ribas, I.; Micela, G.; Pollock, A. M. T.; Garc&#237;a-&#193; lvarez, D.; Solano, E.; Eiroa, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 511, id.L8</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...511L...8S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401.1691M</bibcode>
			<title>On the formation of hot Neptunes and super-Earths</title>
			<authors>McNeil, D. S.; Nelson, R. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 3, pp. 1691-1708.</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401.1691M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..186...48J</bibcode>
			<title>On the Fundamental Mass-Period Functions of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jiang, Ing-Guey; Yeh, Li-Chin; Chang, Yen-Chang; Hung, Wen-Liang</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 186, Issue 1, pp. 48-62 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..186...48J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..168A</bibcode>
			<title>How Eccentric Orbital Solutions Can Hide Planetary Systems in 2:1 Resonant Orbits</title>
			<authors>Anglada-Escud&#233;, Guillem; L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Chambers, John E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 168-178 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..168A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..149S</bibcode>
			<title>Models of Neptune-Mass Exoplanets: Emergent Fluxes and Albedos</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent; Hubeny, Ivan; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 149-158 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..149S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708.1492R</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth Orbiting the Nearby Sun-like Star HD 1461</title>
			<authors>Rivera, Eugenio J.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Laughlin, Gregory; Henry, Gregory W.; Meschiari, Stefano</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 2, pp. 1492-1499 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...708.1492R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Natur.462..891C</bibcode>
			<title>A super-Earth transiting a nearby low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Berta, Zachory K.; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; Nutzman, Philip; Buchhave, Lars A.; Lovis, Christophe; Bonfils, Xavier; Latham, David W.; Udry, St&#233;phane; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Falco, Emilio E.; Winn, Joshua N.; Queloz, Didier; Pepe, Francesco; Mayor, Michel; Delfosse, Xavier; Forveille, Thierry</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 462, Issue 7275, pp. 891-894 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Natur.462..891C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707.1000H</bibcode>
			<title>Tidally Heated Terrestrial Exoplanets: Viscoelastic Response Models</title>
			<authors>Henning, Wade G.; O'Connell, Richard J.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 2, pp. 1000-1015 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707.1000H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508.1509H</bibcode>
			<title>Transit detections of extrasolar planets around main-sequence stars. I. Sky maps for hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Heller, R.; Mislis, D.; Antoniadis, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1509-1516</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508.1509H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..785H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-12b: A Low-Density Sub-Saturn Mass Planet Transiting a Metal-Poor K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; P&#225;l, A.; Latham, D. W.; Sipocz, B.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 785-796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..785H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..481C</bibcode>
			<title>High cadence near infrared timing observations of extrasolar planets. I. GJ 436b and XO-1b</title>
			<authors>C&#225;ceres, C.; Ivanov, V. D.; Minniti, D.; Naef, D.; Melo, C.; Mason, E.; Selman, F.; Pietrzynski, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.481-486</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..481C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1096K</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Transit Constraints Based upon Secondary Eclipse Observations</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 884, pp.1096-1103</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1096K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704.1519D</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of Transiting Jupiters and Low-Mass Eclipsing Binaries in Sparsely Sampled Pan-STARRS-1 Survey Data</title>
			<authors>Dupuy, Trent J.; Liu, Michael C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 2, pp. 1519-1537 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704.1519D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704...51C</bibcode>
			<title>Parameter Estimation from Time-series Data with Correlated Errors: A Wavelet-based Method and its Application to Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Carter, Joshua A.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 1, pp. 51-67 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704...51C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...505..891S</bibcode>
			<title>Transit spectrophotometry of the exoplanet HD 189733b. I. Searching for water but finding haze with HST NICMOS</title>
			<authors>Sing, D. K.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Ballester, G. E.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; Parmentier, V.; Hebrard, G.; Henry, G. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 505, Issue 2, 2009, pp.891-899</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...505..891S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1016M</bibcode>
			<title>Systemic: A Testbed for Characterizing the Detection of Extrasolar Planets. I. The Systemic Console Package</title>
			<authors>Meschiari, Stefano; Wolf, Aaron S.; Rivera, Eugenio; Laughlin, Gregory; Vogt, Steve; Butler, Paul</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 883, pp.1016-1027</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1016M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121..952D</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Characterization of Transiting Super Earths Using an All-Sky Transit Survey and Follow-up by the James Webb Space Telescope</title>
			<authors>Deming, D.; Seager, S.; Winn, J.; Miller-Ricci, E.; Clampin, M.; Lindler, D.; Greene, T.; Charbonneau, D.; Laughlin, G.; Ricker, G.; Latham, D.; Ennico, K.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 883, pp.952-967</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121..952D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..769K</bibcode>
			<title>The 8 mum Phase Variation of the Hot Saturn HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Showman, Adam P.; Agol, Eric; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 769-784 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..769K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.1116N</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Variations for Eccentric and Inclined Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Nesvorn&#253;, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 1116-1122 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.1116N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1797K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon - II</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1797-1804.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1797K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699L..48D</bibcode>
			<title>Follow-up Observations of the Neptune Mass Transiting Extrasolar Planet HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, Jason A.; Close, Laird M.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Scuderi, Louis J.; Males, Jared R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. L48-L51 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699L..48D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..824O</bibcode>
			<title>N-Body Simulations of Planetary Accretion Around M Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Ogihara, Masahiro; Ida, Shigeru</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 824-838 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..824O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699...23B</bibcode>
			<title>A Quasi-stationary Solution to Gliese 436b's Eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Batygin, Konstantin; Laughlin, Gregory; Meschiari, Stefano; Rivera, Eugenio; Vogt, Steve; Butler, Paul</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 23-30 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...502..395W</bibcode>
			<title>The sub-Jupiter mass transiting exoplanet WASP-11b</title>
			<authors>West, R. G.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hebb, L.; Joshi, Y. C.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E.; Skillen, I.; Stempels, H. C.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D.; Anderson, D.; Bentley, S.; Bouchy, F.; Christian, D.; Enoch, B.; Gibson, N.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hellier, C.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Maxted, P.; McDonald, I.; Moutou, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 502, Issue 1, 2009, pp.395-400</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...502..395W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501.1161M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planet population synthesis. II. Statistical comparison with observations</title>
			<authors>Mordasini, C.; Alibert, Y.; Benz, W.; Naef, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1161-1184</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501.1161M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501.1139M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planet population synthesis. I. Method, formation tracks, and mass-distance distribution</title>
			<authors>Mordasini, C.; Alibert, Y.; Benz, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1139-1160</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501.1139M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501..785G</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and characterization of WASP-6b, an inflated sub-Jupiter mass planet transiting a solar-type star</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Anderson, D. R.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pollaco, D.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Parley, N.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 2, 2009, pp.785-792</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501..785G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Msngr.136...39K</bibcode>
			<title>The UVES M Dwarf Planet Search Programme</title>
			<authors>K&#252;rster, Martin; Zechmeister, Mathias; Endl, Michael; Meyer, Eva</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 136, p. 39-43</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Msngr.136...39K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1950B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-10b: A Light and Moderately Hot Jupiter Transiting A K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; P&#225;l, A.; Torres, G.; Sipocz, B.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Hartman, J.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1950-1955 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1950B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1116W</bibcode>
			<title>Nondetection of Polarized, Scattered Light from the HD 189733b Hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Wiktorowicz, Sloane J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1116-1124 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1116W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...499..615D</bibcode>
			<title>On the possibility of detecting extrasolar planets' atmospheres with the Rossiter-McLaughlin effect</title>
			<authors>Dreizler, S.; Reiners, A.; Homeier, D.; Noll, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 499, Issue 2, 2009, pp.615-621</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...499..615D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...695.1006B</bibcode>
			<title>The HD 40307 Planetary System: Super-Earths or Mini-Neptunes?</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Rory; Jackson, Brian; Raymond, Sean N.; West, Andrew A.; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 695, Issue 2, pp. 1006-1011 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...695.1006B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...695..336H</bibcode>
			<title>Deep MMT Transit Survey of the Open Cluster M37 IV: Limit on the Fraction of Stars with Planets as Small as 0.3RJ</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Gaudi, B. S.; Holman, M. J.; McLeod, B. A.; Stanek, K. Z.; Barranco, J. A.; Pinsonneault, M. H.; Meibom, S.; Kalirai, J. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 695, Issue 1, pp. 336-356 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...695..336H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694.1559S</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Follow-Up Observations of the Transiting Neptune-Mass Planet GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Shporer, Avi; Mazeh, Tsevi; Pont, Frederic; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Latham, David W.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 2, pp. 1559-1565 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694.1559S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..722G</bibcode>
			<title>A Study of the Accuracy of Mass-Radius Relationships for Silicate-Rich and Ice-Rich Planets up to 100 Earth Masses</title>
			<authors>Grasset, O.; Schneider, J.; Sotin, C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 722-733 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..722G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...496..527B</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XVII. Super-Earth and Neptune-mass planets in multiple planet systems HD 47 186 and HD 181 433</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Mayor, M.; Lovis, C.; Udry, S.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Delfosse, X.; Mordasini, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Segransan, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 496, Issue 2, 2009, pp.527-531</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...496..527B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...496..259G</bibcode>
			<title>Improved parameters for the transiting hot Jupiters WASP-4b and WASP-5b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Anderson, D. R.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 496, Issue 1, 2009, pp.259-267</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...496..259G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.393L...6P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit infrared spectroscopy of the hot Neptune around GJ 436 with the Hubble Space Telescope</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Gilliland, R. L.; Knutson, H.; Holman, M.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 393, Issue 1, pp. L6-L10.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.393L...6P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.393..229L</bibcode>
			<title>Planetpol polarimetry of the exoplanet systems 55Cnc and tauBoo</title>
			<authors>Lucas, P. W.; Hough, J. H.; Bailey, J. A.; Tamura, M.; Hirst, E.; Harrison, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 393, Issue 1, pp. 229-244.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.393..229L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392..537M</bibcode>
			<title>New methods for large dynamic range problems in planetary formation</title>
			<authors>McNeil, D. S.; Nelson, R. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 2, pp. 537-552.</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392..537M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392..181K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 1, pp. 181-189.</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392..181K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691..866K</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of A Temperature Inversion in the Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Burrows, Adam; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 1, pp. 866-874 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690.1393S</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-9b: A Low-Density Planet Transiting a Moderately Faint F Star</title>
			<authors>Shporer, Avi; Bakos, G&#193;sp&#193;r &#193;.; Bouchy, Francois; Pont, Frederic; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Latham, Dave W.; Sip&#246;cz, Brigitta; Torres, Guillermo; Mazeh, Tsevi; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Noyes, Robert W.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J&#243;zsef; Papp, Istv&#225;n; S&#225;ri, P&#225;l; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 2, pp. 1393-1400 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690.1393S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690..822K</bibcode>
			<title>Multiwavelength Constraints on the Day-Night Circulation Patterns of HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Showman, Adam P.; Agol, Eric; Henry, Gregory W.; Everett, Mark E.; Allen, Lori E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 1, pp. 822-836 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690..822K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493..671F</bibcode>
			<title>Bulk composition of the transiting hot Neptune around GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Figueira, P.; Pont, F.; Mordasini, C.; Alibert, Y.; Georgy, C.; Benz, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 2, 2009, pp.671-676</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493..671F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PABei..27...14Z</bibcode>
			<title>The detection methods and statistical characteristics of exoplanet.</title>
			<authors>Zhang, N.; Ji, J.-H.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 27, 14-28 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PABei..27...14Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689L.149C</bibcode>
			<title>New Observations and a Possible Detection of Parameter Variations in the Transits of Gliese 436b</title>
			<authors>Coughlin, Jeffrey L.; Stringfellow, Guy S.; Becker, Andrew C.; L&#243; pez-Morales, Mercedes; Mezzalira, Fabio; Krajci, Tom</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 2, pp. L149-L152.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689L.149C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689..492K</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Orbital Parameters through Planetary Transit Monitoring</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 1, pp. 492-498.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689..492K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...492..603G</bibcode>
			<title>Updated parameters for the transiting exoplanet WASP-3b using RISE, a new fast camera for the Liverpool Telescope</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Joshi, Y. C.; Todd, I.; Benn, C.; Christian, D.; Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Keenan, F. P.; Meaburn, J.; Skillen, I.; Steele, I. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 492, Issue 2, 2008, pp.603-607</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...492..603G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1191L</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Radii of Extrasolar Giant Planets: the Cases of TrES-4, XO-3b, and HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>Liu, Xin; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1191-1200.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1191L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origins of Eccentric Close-In Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Takeda, Genya; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. L29-L32.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1331B</bibcode>
			<title>XO-5b: A Transiting Jupiter-sized Planet with a 4 day Period</title>
			<authors>Burke, Christopher J.; McCullough, P. R.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Long, Doug; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Machalek, P.; Janes, Kenneth A.; Taylor, B.; Fleenor, Michael L.; Foote, C. N.; Gary, Bruce L.; Garc&#237;a-Melendo, Enrique; Gregorio, J.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1331-1340.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1331B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..621F</bibcode>
			<title>Origins of Eccentric Extrasolar Planets: Testing the Planet-Planet Scattering Model</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 621-636.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..621F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389.1383K</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting planets - light-curve analysis for eccentric orbits</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 3, pp. 1383-1390.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389.1383K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389..191P</bibcode>
			<title>Periastron precession measurements in transiting extrasolar planetary systems at the level of general relativity</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Kocsis, Bence</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 1, pp. 191-198.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389..191P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...685..543J</bibcode>
			<title>Observability of the General Relativistic Precession of Periastra in Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jord&#225;n, Andr&#233;s; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 685, Issue 1, pp. 543-552.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...685..543J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684.1427M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission of Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Burrows, Adam; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 2, pp. 1427-1432.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684.1427M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488..763H</bibcode>
			<title>Misaligned spin-orbit in the XO-3 planetary system?</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Loeillet, B.; Rabus, M.; Bonfils, X.; Moutou, C.; Boisse, I.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488..763H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1277B</bibcode>
			<title>Optical Albedo Theory of Strongly Irradiated Giant Planets: The Case of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Ibgui, L.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1277-1282.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1277B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1264K</bibcode>
			<title>Planet formation around stars of various masses: Hot Super-Earths</title>
			<authors>Kennedy, Grant M.; Kenyon, Scott J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1264-1276.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1264K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...487L..25B</bibcode>
			<title>Observational consequences of the recently proposed Super-Earth orbiting GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Bean, J. L.; Seifahrt, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 487, Issue 2, 2008, pp.L25-L28</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...487L..25B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...487L...5A</bibcode>
			<title>Limits to the planet candidate GJ 436c</title>
			<authors>Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Rabus, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Belmonte, J. A.; Almenara, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 487, Issue 1, 2008, pp.L5-L8</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...487L...5A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...486.1039B</bibcode>
			<title>A Hubble Space Telescope transit light curve for GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Bean, J. L.; Benedict, G. F.; Charbonneau, D.; Homeier, D.; Taylor, D. C.; McArthur, B.; Seifahrt, A.; Dreizler, S.; Reiners, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 486, Issue 3, 2008, pp.1039-1046</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...486.1039B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681.1631J</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 2, pp. 1631-1638.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681.1631J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...485..871G</bibcode>
			<title>Improved parameters for the transiting planet HD 17156b: a high-density giant planet with a very eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; North, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 485, Issue 3, 2008, pp.871-875</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...485..871G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.387L...4A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-5b: a dense, very hot Jupiter transiting a 12th-mag Southern-hemisphere star</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Wilson, D. M.; Collier Cameron, A.; Smalley, B.; Lister, T. A.; Bentley, S. J.; Blecha, A.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Kane, S. R.; Marmier, M.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pollacco, D. L.; Pont, F.; Ryans, R.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 387, Issue 1, pp. L4-L7.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.387L...4A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1419F</bibcode>
			<title>A Unified Theory for the Atmospheres of the Hot and Very Hot Jupiters: Two Classes of Irradiated Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Lodders, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1419-1435.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1419F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1396J</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1396-1406.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1396J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...483..317K</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on additional planetary companions to OGLE 2005-BLG-390L</title>
			<authors>Kubas, D.; Cassan, A.; Dominik, M.; Bennett, D. P.; Wambsganss, J.; Brillant, S.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Albrow, M. D.; Batista, V.; Bode, M.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Calitz, H.; Cook, K. H.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Greenhill, J.; Hill, K.; Hoffman, M.; Horne, K.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Kains, N.; Kane, S.; Marquette, J. B.; Martin, R.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Tsapras, Y.; Vinter, C.; Williams, A.; Woller, K.; Zub, M.; The PLANET/Robonet Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 483, Issue 1, 2008, pp.317-324</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...483..317K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008PASJ...60L...1N</bibcode>
			<title>A Possible Spin-Orbit Misalignment in the Transiting Eccentric Planet HD 17156b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Ohshima, Osamu; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.60, No.2, pp.L1--L5</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008PASJ...60L...1N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677L..59R</bibcode>
			<title>A ~5 M&amp;oplus; Super-Earth Orbiting GJ 436? The Power of Near-Grazing Transits</title>
			<authors>Ribas, Ignasi; Font-Ribera, Andreu; Beaulieu, Jean-Philippe</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. L59-L62.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677L..59R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677..657J</bibcode>
			<title>XO-3b: A Massive Planet in an Eccentric Orbit Transiting an F5 V Star</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Prato, L.; Bissinger, R.; Fleenor, M.; Foote, C. N.; Garcia-Melendo, E.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Mallia, F.; Masi, G.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. 657-670.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677..657J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482..315B</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and evolution of super-Earth to super-Jupiter exoplanets. I. Heavy element enrichment in the interior</title>
			<authors>Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 1, 2008, pp.315-332</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482..315B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...481..529L</bibcode>
			<title>Refined parameters and spectroscopic transit of the super-massive planet HD 147506b</title>
			<authors>Loeillet, B.; Shporer, A.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Mazeh, T.; Beuzit, J. L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; da Silva, R.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Ecuvillon, A.; Forveille, T.; Galland, F.; Gallenne, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sivan, J. P.; Santos, N. C.; Tsodikovich, Y.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 481, Issue 2, 2008, pp.529-533</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...481..529L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008PASP..120..317N</bibcode>
			<title>Design Considerations for a Ground-Based Transit Search for Habitable Planets Orbiting M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip; Charbonneau, David</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 120, issue 865, pp.317-327</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008PASP..120..317N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...675L..37W</bibcode>
			<title>Lupus-TR-3b: A Low-Mass Transiting Hot Jupiter in the Galactic Plane?</title>
			<authors>Weldrake, David T. F.; Bayliss, Daniel D. R.; Sackett, Penny D.; Tingley, Brandon W.; Gillon, Micha&#235;l; Setiawan, Johny</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 675, Issue 1, pp. L37-L40.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...675L..37W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...675.1531W</bibcode>
			<title>Five New Transits of the Super-Neptune HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Henry, Gregory W.; Torres, Guillermo; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 675, Issue 2, pp. 1531-1537.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...675.1531W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.384..663R</bibcode>
			<title>Observable consequences of planet formation models in systems with close-in terrestrial planets</title>
			<authors>Raymond, Sean N.; Barnes, Rory; Mandell, Avi M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 384, Issue 2, pp. 663-674.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.384..663R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673.1160A</bibcode>
			<title>Ocean Planet or Thick Atmosphere: On the Mass-Radius Relationship for Solid Exoplanets with Massive Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; Seager, S.; Elkins-Tanton, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 2, pp. 1160-1164.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673.1160A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...479..579P</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray induced mass loss effects on exoplanets orbiting dM stars</title>
			<authors>Penz, T.; Micela, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 479, Issue 2, February IV 2008, pp.579-584</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...479..579P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671L..65T</bibcode>
			<title>The Transiting Exoplanet Host Star GJ 436: A Test of Stellar Evolution Models in the Lower Main Sequence, and Revised Planetary Parameters</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. L65-L68.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671L..65T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671..861H</bibcode>
			<title>Two Classes of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. 861-871.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671..861H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...476L..13B</bibcode>
			<title>HD 17156b: a transiting planet with a 21.2-day period and an eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Barbieri, M.; Alonso, R.; Laughlin, G.; Almenara, J. M.; Bissinger, R.; Davies, D.; Gasparri, D.; Guido, E.; Lopresti, C.; Manzini, F.; Sostero, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 476, Issue 2, December III 2007, pp.L13-L16</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...476L..13B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475.1125D</bibcode>
			<title>Characterization of the hot Neptune GJ 436 b with Spitzer and ground-based observations</title>
			<authors>Demory, B.-O.; Gillon, M.; Barman, T.; Bonfils, X.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Bouchy, F.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Mallmann, F.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 3, December I 2007, pp.1125-1129</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475.1125D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...670..833J</bibcode>
			<title>A New Planet around an M Dwarf: Revealing a Correlation between Exoplanets and Stellar Mass</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Vogt, Steven S.; Wright, Jason T.; Peek, Kathryn M. G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 670, Issue 1, pp. 833-840.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...670..833J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1279S</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-Radius Relationships for Solid Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Seager, S.; Kuchner, M.; Hier-Majumder, C. A.; Militzer, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1279-1297.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1279S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..359G</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting low-frequency radio fluxes of known extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Grie&#223;meier, J.-M.; Zarka, P.; Spreeuw, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 1, November III 2007, pp.359-368</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..359G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.380.1488K</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of exoplanetary transits from radial velocity surveys</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 380, Issue 4, pp. 1488-1496.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.380.1488K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...668L.179E</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer Search for Water in the Transiting Exoplanet HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, David; H&#233;brard, Guillaume; Lecavelier des Etangs, Alain; Sing, David K.; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Bouchy, Fran&#231;ois; Ferlet, Roger; Vidal-Madjar, Alfred</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 668, Issue 2, pp. L179-L182.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...668L.179E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...668L.171B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectral Models of the Planet HD 209458b with a Thermal Inversion and Water Emission Bands</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Knutson, H. A.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 668, Issue 2, pp. L171-L174.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...668L.171B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667L.199D</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Transit and Secondary Eclipse Photometry of GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Harrington, Joseph; Laughlin, Gregory; Seager, Sara; Navarro, Sarah B.; Bowman, William C.; Horning, Karen</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 2, pp. L199-L202.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667L.199D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...474..293B</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. X. A m sin i = 11 M_&amp;oplus; planet around the nearby spotted M dwarf GJ 674</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Mayor, M.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Gillon, M.; Perrier, C.; Udry, S.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 474, Issue 1, October IV 2007, pp.293-299</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...474..293B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...666..475M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Planet Taxonomy: A New Statistical Approach</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 666, Issue 1, pp. 475-485.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...666..475M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...472L..13G</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of transits of the nearby hot Neptune GJ 436 b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Pont, F.; Demory, B.-O.; Mallmann, F.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Queloz, D.; Shporer, A.; Udry, S.; Vuissoz, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 472, Issue 2, September III 2007, pp.L13-L16</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...472L..13G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...471L..51G</bibcode>
			<title>Accurate Spitzer infrared radius measurement for the hot Neptune GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Demory, B.-O.; Barman, T.; Bonfils, X.; Mazeh, T.; Pont, F.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 471, Issue 3, September I 2007, pp.L51-L54</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...471L..51G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.377.1511H</bibcode>
			<title>Using long-term transit timing to detect terrestrial planets</title>
			<authors>Heyl, Jeremy S.; Gladman, Brett J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 377, Issue 4, pp. 1511-1519.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.377.1511H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...467..721M</bibcode>
			<title>A new Neptune-mass planet orbiting HD 219828</title>
			<authors>Melo, C.; Santos, N. C.; Gieren, W.; Pietrzynski, G.; Ruiz, M. T.; Sousa, S. G.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; da Silva, R.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 467, Issue 2, May IV 2007, pp.721-727</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...467..721M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ChA&amp;A..31..187J</bibcode>
			<title>A Study of Potential Earth-like Planets in the GJ 876 Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Ji, Jiang-Hui; Liu, Lin</authors>
			<journal>Chinese Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 31, Issue 2, p. 187-191.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ChA%26A..31..187J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...657..533W</bibcode>
			<title>Four New Exoplanets and Hints of Additional Substellar Companions to Exoplanet Host Stars</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Butler, R. P.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Apps, K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 657, Issue 1, pp. 533-545.</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...657..533W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASP..119...90M</bibcode>
			<title>The M Dwarf GJ 436 and its Neptune-Mass Planet</title>
			<authors>Maness, H. L.; Marcy, G. W.; Ford, E. B.; Hauschildt, P. H.; Shreve, A. T.; Basri, G. B.; Butler, R. P.; Vogt, S. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 119, Issue 851, pp. 90-101.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASP..119...90M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...461.1185L</bibcode>
			<title>A diagram to determine the evaporation status of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 461, Issue 3, January III 2007, pp.1185-1193</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...461.1185L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MmSAI..78..612M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planet taxonomy: a new statistical approach</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.; Ortolani, S.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ&#224; Astronomica Italiana, v.78, p.612 (2007)</journal>
			<date>0/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MmSAI..78..612M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653L..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Metallicities of M Dwarf Planet Hosts from Spectral Synthesis</title>
			<authors>Bean, Jacob L.; Benedict, G. Fritz; Endl, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 1, pp. L65-L68.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653L..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1506L</bibcode>
			<title>Limits to Transits of the Neptune-Mass Planet Orbiting GJ 581</title>
			<authors>L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Morrell, Nidia I.; Butler, R. Paul; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 849, pp. 1506-1509.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1506L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1010J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of Known Exoplanetary Systems Based on Measured Stellar Properties</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick; Underwood, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1019.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1010J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....132.1267S</bibcode>
			<title>No Detectable H+3 Emission from the Atmospheres of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Shkolnik, Evgenya; Gaidos, Eric; Moskovitz, Nick</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 132, Issue 3, pp. 1267-1274.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....132.1267S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.370.1379J</bibcode>
			<title>Data analysis on the extrasolar planets using robust clustering</title>
			<authors>Jiang, Ing-Guey; Yeh, Li-Chin; Hung, Wen-Liang; Yang, Miin-Shen</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 370, Issue 3, pp. 1379-1392.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.370.1379J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.369.1267D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of a binary or planetary system during encounters with a third inclined body</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 369, Issue 3, pp. 1267-1280.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.369.1267D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..505B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of Nearby Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. P.; Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Penny, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 505-522.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..505B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644L..79B</bibcode>
			<title>Rapid Formation of Super-Earths around M Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 1, pp. L79-L82.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644L..79B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644.1214T</bibcode>
			<title>Giant Planet Accretion and Migration: Surviving the Type I Regime</title>
			<authors>Thommes, Edward W.; Murray, Norman</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 2, pp. 1214-1222.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644.1214T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...447..361U</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. V. A 14 Earth-masses planet orbiting HD 4308</title>
			<authors>Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Mordasini, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Sivan, J.-P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 447, Issue 1, February III 2006, pp.361-367</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...447..361U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...443L..15B</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. VI. A Neptune-mass planet around the nearby M dwarf Gl 581</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Forveille, T.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Perrier, C.; Bouchy, F.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 443, Issue 3, December I 2005, pp.L15-L18</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...443L..15B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...441..791F</bibcode>
			<title>Oligarchic and giant impact growth of terrestrial planets in the presence of gas giant planet migration</title>
			<authors>Fogg, M. J.; Nelson, R. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 441, Issue 2, October II 2005, pp.791-806</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...441..791F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...439..367M</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. IV. Three close-in planets around HD 2638, HD 27894 and HD 63454</title>
			<authors>Moutou, C.; Mayor, M.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Udry, S.; Benz, W.; Lo Curto, G.; Naef, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sivan, J.-P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 439, Issue 1, August III 2005, pp.367-373</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...439..367M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...626.1045I</bibcode>
			<title>Toward a Deterministic Model of Planetary Formation. III. Mass Distribution of Short-Period Planets around Stars of Various Masses</title>
			<authors>Ida, S.; Lin, D. N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 626, Issue 2, pp. 1045-1060.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...626.1045I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...436L..47B</bibcode>
			<title>Hot-Jupiters and hot-Neptunes: A common origin?</title>
			<authors>Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T. S.; Selsis, F.; Allard, F.; Hauschildt, P. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 436, Issue 3, June IV 2005, pp.L47-L51</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...436L..47B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...623..472G</bibcode>
			<title>On the Period Distribution of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. Scott; Seager, S.; Mallen-Ornelas, Gabriela</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 623, Issue 1, pp. 472-481.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...623..472G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...621.1072L</bibcode>
			<title>A Comparison of Observationally Determined Radii with Theoretical Radius Predictions for Short-Period Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Wolf, Aaron; Vanmunster, Tonny; Bodenheimer, Peter; Fischer, Debra; Marcy, Geoff; Butler, Paul; Vogt, Steve</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 621, Issue 2, pp. 1072-1078.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...621.1072L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...617..580B</bibcode>
			<title>A Neptune-Mass Planet Orbiting the Nearby M Dwarf GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Wright, Jason T.; Henry, Gregory W.; Laughlin, Greg; Lissauer, Jack J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 617, Issue 1, pp. 580-588.</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...617..580B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..26N</bibcode>
			<title>Interior structure models of GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Nettelmann, N.; Kramm, U.; Redmer, R.; Neuh&#228;user, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A26</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..26N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1077D</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Transit Search for Planets around Cool Stars from the Western Italian Alps: A Site Characterization Study</title>
			<authors>Damasso, M.; Giacobbe, P.; Calcidese, P.; Sozzetti, A.; Lattanzi, M. G.; Bernagozzi, A.; Bertolini, E.; Smart, R. L.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 895, pp.1077-1091</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1077D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720L.113R</bibcode>
			<title>Metal-rich M-Dwarf Planet Hosts: Metallicities with K-band Spectra</title>
			<authors>Rojas-Ayala, B&#225;rbara; Covey, Kevin R.; Muirhead, Philip S.; Lloyd, James P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 720, Issue 1, pp. L113-L118 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720L.113R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1290G</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Parameters and Metallicities of Stars Hosting Jovian and Neptunian Mass Planets: A Possible Dependence of Planetary Mass on Metallicity</title>
			<authors>Ghezzi, L.; Cunha, K.; Smith, V. V.; de Ara&#250;jo, F. X.; Schuler, S. C.; de la Reza, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1290-1302 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1290G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720..344L</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Circulation of Eccentric Hot Neptune GJ436b</title>
			<authors>Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Marley, Mark S.; Freedman, Richard S.; Lodders, Katharina</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 1, pp. 344-356 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720..344L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A.105S</bibcode>
			<title>A physically-motivated photometric calibration of M dwarf metallicity</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, K. C.; Laughlin, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A105</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A.105S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718.1353I</bibcode>
			<title>NLTT 41135: A Field M Dwarf + Brown Dwarf Eclipsing Binary in a Triple System, Discovered by the MEarth Observatory</title>
			<authors>Irwin, Jonathan; Buchhave, Lars; Berta, Zachory K.; Charbonneau, David; Latham, David W.; Burke, Christopher J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Nutzman, Philip; Berlind, Perry; Calkins, Michael L.; Falco, Emilio E.; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John A.; Gazak, J. Zachary</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 1353-1366 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718.1353I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...515A..98P</bibcode>
			<title>Coronal properties of planet-bearing stars</title>
			<authors>Poppenhaeger, K.; Robrade, J.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 515, id.A98</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...515A..98P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..271H</bibcode>
			<title>The Lick-Carnegie Exoplanet Survey: A Saturn-Mass Planet in the Habitable Zone of the Nearby M4V Star HIP 57050</title>
			<authors>Haghighipour, Nader; Vogt, Steven S.; Butler, R. Paul; Rivera, Eugenio J.; Laughlin, Greg; Meschiari, Stefano; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 271-276 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..271H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714...13A</bibcode>
			<title>Lack of Transit Timing Variations of OGLE-TR-111b: A Re-Analysis with Six New Epochs</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; L&#243;pez-Morales, M.; Elliot, J. L.; Seager, S.; Osip, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 13-24 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714...13A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.464.1161S</bibcode>
			<title>Possible thermochemical disequilibrium in the atmosphere of the exoplanet GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Stevenson, Kevin B.; Harrington, Joseph; Nymeyer, Sarah; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Bowman, William C.; Hardy, Ryan A.; Deming, Drake; Rauscher, Emily; Lust, Nate B.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 464, Issue 7292, pp. 1161-1164 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Natur.464.1161S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..974R</bibcode>
			<title>A Framework for Quantifying the Degeneracies of Exoplanet Interior Compositions</title>
			<authors>Rogers, L. A.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 2, pp. 974-991 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..974R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010NewAR..54..178T</bibcode>
			<title>Posters from the edge of the universe</title>
			<authors>Trimble, Virginia</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 54, Issue 3-6, p. 178-180.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010NewAR..54..178T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712L..86P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Variations for Inclined and Retrograde Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.; Veras, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. L86-L92 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712L..86P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1724B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-11b: A Super-Neptune Planet Transiting a Bright K Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; P&#225;l, A.; Hartman, J.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Isaacson, H.; Howard, A.; Vogt, S.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Fernandez, J.; Mo&#243;r, A.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1724-1745 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710...97C</bibcode>
			<title>Studying the Atmosphere of the Exoplanet HAT-P-7b Via Secondary Eclipse Measurements with EPOXI, Spitzer, and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Holman, Matthew J.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Deming, Drake; A'Hearn, Michael F.; the EPOXI Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 97-104 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710...97C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....139..504B</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation and Magnetic Activity in a Sample of M-Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Browning, Matthew K.; Basri, Gibor; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; West, Andrew A.; Zhang, Jiahao</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 139, Issue 2, pp. 504-518 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....139..504B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..168A</bibcode>
			<title>How Eccentric Orbital Solutions Can Hide Planetary Systems in 2:1 Resonant Orbits</title>
			<authors>Anglada-Escud&#233;, Guillem; L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Chambers, John E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 168-178 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..168A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..149S</bibcode>
			<title>Models of Neptune-Mass Exoplanets: Emergent Fluxes and Albedos</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent; Hubeny, Ivan; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 149-158 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..149S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Natur.462..891C</bibcode>
			<title>A super-Earth transiting a nearby low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Berta, Zachory K.; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; Nutzman, Philip; Buchhave, Lars A.; Lovis, Christophe; Bonfils, Xavier; Latham, David W.; Udry, St&#233;phane; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Falco, Emilio E.; Winn, Joshua N.; Queloz, Didier; Pepe, Francesco; Mayor, Michel; Delfosse, Xavier; Forveille, Thierry</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 462, Issue 7275, pp. 891-894 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Natur.462..891C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508.1011R</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing analysis of the exoplanets TrES-1 and TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Rabus, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Alonso, R.; Belmonte, J. A.; Almenara, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 2, 2009, pp.1011-1020</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508.1011R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705.1226B</bibcode>
			<title>Planets and Debris Disks: Results from a Spitzer/MIPS Search for Infrared Excess</title>
			<authors>Bryden, G.; Beichman, C. A.; Carpenter, J. M.; Rieke, G. H.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Werner, M. W.; Tanner, A. M.; Lawler, S. M.; Wyatt, M. C.; Trilling, D. E.; Su, K. Y. L.; Blaylock, M.; Stansberry, J. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 705, Issue 2, pp. 1226-1236 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705.1226B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..487M</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XVIII. An Earth-mass planet in the GJ 581 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Mayor, M.; Bonfils, X.; Forveille, T.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Beust, H.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.487-494</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..487M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..481C</bibcode>
			<title>High cadence near infrared timing observations of extrasolar planets. I. GJ 436b and XO-1b</title>
			<authors>C&#225;ceres, C.; Ivanov, V. D.; Minniti, D.; Naef, D.; Melo, C.; Mason, E.; Selman, F.; Pietrzynski, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.481-486</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..481C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704..975J</bibcode>
			<title>Rotational Velocities for M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, J. S.; Ramsey, L. W.; Jones, H. R. A.; Pavlenko, Y.; Gallardo, J.; Barnes, J. R.; Pinfield, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 2, pp. 975-988 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704..975J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704...51C</bibcode>
			<title>Parameter Estimation from Time-series Data with Correlated Errors: A Wavelet-based Method and its Application to Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Carter, Joshua A.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 1, pp. 51-67 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704...51C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..369B</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the transit times of CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Bean, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.369-375</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..369B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..303Q</bibcode>
			<title>The CoRoT-7 planetary system: two orbiting super-Earths</title>
			<authors>Queloz, D.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Deeg, H. J.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Jorda, L.; Hartmann, M.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.303-319</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..303Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..287L</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. VIII. CoRoT-7b: the first super-Earth with measured radius</title>
			<authors>L&#233;ger, A.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Barge, P.; Fridlund, M.; Samuel, B.; Ollivier, M.; Guenther, E.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Auvergne, M.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J. M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Bruntt, H.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Catala, C.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Foing, B.; Fressin, F.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, Ph.; Grasset, O.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Renner, S.; Samadi, R.; Shporer, A.; Sotin, Ch.; Tingley, B.; Wuchterl, G.; Adda, M.; Agogu, P.; Appourchaux, T.; Ballans, H.; Baron, P.; Beaufort, T.; Bellenger, R.; Berlin, R.; Bernardi, P.; Blouin, D.; Baudin, F.; Bodin, P.; Boisnard, L.; Boit, L.; Bonneau, F.; Borzeix, S.; Briet, R.; Buey, J.-T.; Butler, B.; Cailleau, D.; Cautain, R.; Chabaud, P.-Y.; Chaintreuil, S.; Chiavassa, F.; Costes, V.; Cuna Parrho, V.; de Oliveira Fialho, F.; Decaudin, M.; Defise, J.-M.; Djalal, S.; Epstein, G.; Exil, G.-E.; Faur&#233;, C.; Fenouillet, T.; Gaboriaud, A.; Gallic, A.; Gamet, P.; Gavalda, P.; Grolleau, E.; Gruneisen, R.; Gueguen, L.; Guis, V.; Guivarc'h, V.; Guterman, P.; Hallouard, D.; Hasiba, J.; Heuripeau, F.; Huntzinger, G.; Hustaix, H.; Imad, C.; Imbert, C.; Johlander, B.; Jouret, M.; Journoud, P.; Karioty, F.; Kerjean, L.; Lafaille, V.; Lafond, L.; Lam-Trong, T.; Landiech, P.; Lapeyrere, V.; Larqu&#233;, T.; Laudet, P.; Lautier, N.; Lecann, H.; Lefevre, L.; Leruyet, B.; Levacher, P.; Magnan, A.; Mazy, E.; Mertens, F.; Mesnager, J.-M.; Meunier, J.-C.; Michel, J.-P.; Monjoin, W.; Naudet, D.; Nguyen-Kim, K.; Orcesi, J.-L.; Ottacher, H.; Perez, R.; Peter, G.; Plasson, P.; Plesseria, J.-Y.; Pontet, B.; Pradines, A.; Quentin, C.; Reynaud, J.-L.; Rolland, G.; Rollenhagen, F.; Romagnan, R.; Russ, N.; Schmidt, R.; Schwartz, N.; Sebbag, I.; Sedes, G.; Smit, H.; Steller, M. B.; Sunter, W.; Surace, C.; Tello, M.; Tiph&#232;ne, D.; Toulouse, P.; Ulmer, B.; Vandermarcq, O.; Vergnault, E.; Vuillemin, A.; Zanatta, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.287-302</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..287L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...505..859Z</bibcode>
			<title>The M dwarf planet search programme at the ESO VLT + UVES. A search for terrestrial planets in the habitable zone of M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Zechmeister, M.; K&#252;rster, M.; Endl, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 505, Issue 2, 2009, pp.859-871</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...505..859Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..769K</bibcode>
			<title>The 8 mum Phase Variation of the Hot Saturn HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Showman, Adam P.; Agol, Eric; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 769-784 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..769K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.1922B</bibcode>
			<title>Radio Interferometric Planet Search. I. First Constraints On Planetary Companions For Nearby, Low-Mass Stars From Radio Astrometry</title>
			<authors>Bower, Geoffrey C.; Bolatto, Alberto; Ford, Eric B.; Kalas, Paul</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 1922-1939 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.1922B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700L..73K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Relationship Between Debris Disks and Planets</title>
			<authors>K&#243;sp&#225;l, &#193;gnes; Ardila, David R.; Mo&#243;r, Attila; &#193;brah&#225;m, P&#233;ter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. L73-L77 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700L..73K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..965R</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Proper Motion and the Timing of Planetary Transits</title>
			<authors>Rafikov, Roman R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 965-970 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..965R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...503..301R</bibcode>
			<title>Extreme coronagraphy with an adaptive hologram. Simulations of exo-planet imaging</title>
			<authors>Ricci, D.; Le Coroller, H.; Labeyrie, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 503, Issue 1, 2009, pp.301-308</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...503..301R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..933J</bibcode>
			<title>On the Metal Richness of M Dwarfs with Planets</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Apps, Kevin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 2, pp. 933-937 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..933J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..649S</bibcode>
			<title>Identifying the Young Low-mass Stars within 25 pc. I. Spectroscopic Observations</title>
			<authors>Shkolnik, Evgenya; Liu, Michael C.; Reid, I. Neill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 649-666 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..649S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..478D</bibcode>
			<title>Search for Carbon Monoxide in the Atmosphere of the Transiting Exoplanet HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Lecavelier des Etangs, Alain; H&#233;brard, Guillaume; Sing, David K.; Ehrenreich, David; Ferlet, Roger; Vidal-Madjar, Alfred</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 478-485 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..478D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699...23B</bibcode>
			<title>A Quasi-stationary Solution to Gliese 436b's Eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Batygin, Konstantin; Laughlin, Gregory; Meschiari, Stefano; Rivera, Eugenio; Vogt, Steve; Butler, Paul</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 23-30 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Msngr.136...39K</bibcode>
			<title>The UVES M Dwarf Planet Search Programme</title>
			<authors>K&#252;rster, Martin; Zechmeister, Mathias; Endl, Michael; Meyer, Eva</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 136, p. 39-43</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Msngr.136...39K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1023S</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision photometry by telescope defocusing - I. The transiting planetary system WASP-5</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Dominik, M.; Ricci, D.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Hornstrup, A.; Wheatley, P. J.; Anguita, T.; Bozza, V.; Novati, S. Calchi; Harps&#248;e, K.; Kj&#230;rgaard, P.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Masi, G.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Scarpetta, G.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.; Th&#246; ne, C. C.; Zub, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1023-1031.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1023S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..853R</bibcode>
			<title>Activity-induced radial velocity jitter in a flaring M dwarf</title>
			<authors>Reiners, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 3, 2009, pp.853-861</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..853R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..567D</bibcode>
			<title>Binarity of transit host stars. Implications for planetary parameters</title>
			<authors>Daemgen, S.; Hormuth, F.; Brandner, W.; Bergfors, C.; Janson, M.; Hippler, S.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 2, 2009, pp.567-574</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..567D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694.1566S</bibcode>
			<title>The Stability and Dynamics of Planets in Tight Binary Systems</title>
			<authors>Saleh, Lamya A.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 2, pp. 1566-1576 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694.1566S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694.1559S</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Follow-Up Observations of the Transiting Neptune-Mass Planet GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Shporer, Avi; Mazeh, Tsevi; Pont, Frederic; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Latham, David W.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 2, pp. 1559-1565 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694.1559S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AJ....137.3487M</bibcode>
			<title>The Highly Eccentric Pre-Main-Sequence Spectroscopic Binary RX J0529.3+1210</title>
			<authors>Mace, G. N.; Prato, L.; Wasserman, L. H.; Schaefer, G. H.; Franz, O. G.; Simon, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 137, Issue 3, pp. 3487-3493 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AJ....137.3487M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...496..259G</bibcode>
			<title>Improved parameters for the transiting hot Jupiters WASP-4b and WASP-5b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Anderson, D. R.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 496, Issue 1, 2009, pp.259-267</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...496..259G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.393L...6P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit infrared spectroscopy of the hot Neptune around GJ 436 with the Hubble Space Telescope</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Gilliland, R. L.; Knutson, H.; Holman, M.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 393, Issue 1, pp. L6-L10.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.393L...6P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392.1585C</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-10b: a 3MJ, gas-giant planet transiting a late-type K star</title>
			<authors>Christian, D. J.; Gibson, N. P.; Simpson, E. K.; Street, R. A.; Skillen, I.; Pollacco, D.; Collier Cameron, A.; Joshi, Y. C.; Keenan, F. P.; Stempels, H. C.; Haswell, C. A.; Horne, K.; Anderson, D. R.; Bentley, S.; Bouchy, F.; Clarkson, W. I.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hellier, C.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Lister, T. A.; Loeillet, B.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; McDonald, I.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Todd, I.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 4, pp. 1585-1590.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392.1585C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692.1590M</bibcode>
			<title>The Use of Absorption Cells as a Wavelength Reference for Precision Radial Velocity Measurements in the Near-Infrared</title>
			<authors>Mahadevan, Suvrath; Ge, Jian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 692, Issue 2, pp. 1590-1596 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692.1590M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692..229N</bibcode>
			<title>A Precise Estimate of the Radius of the Exoplanet HD 149026b from Spitzer Photometry</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip; Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Knutson, Heather A.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Holman, Matthew J.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. 229-235 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692..229N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392..181K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 1, pp. 181-189.</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392..181K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690..743B</bibcode>
			<title>A Jupiter-Like Planet Orbiting the Nearby M dwarf GJ 832</title>
			<authors>Bailey, Jeremy; Butler, R. Paul; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, Hugh R. A.; O'Toole, Simon; Carter, Brad D.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 1, pp. 743-747 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690..743B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493..671F</bibcode>
			<title>Bulk composition of the transiting hot Neptune around GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Figueira, P.; Pont, F.; Mordasini, C.; Alibert, Y.; Georgy, C.; Benz, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 2, 2009, pp.671-676</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493..671F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493..639M</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XIII. A planetary system with 3 super-Earths (4.2, 6.9, and 9.2 M&amp;oplus;)</title>
			<authors>Mayor, M.; Udry, S.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Bouchy, F.; Mordasini, C.; Segransan, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 2, 2009, pp.639-644</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493..639M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689L.149C</bibcode>
			<title>New Observations and a Possible Detection of Parameter Variations in the Transits of Gliese 436b</title>
			<authors>Coughlin, Jeffrey L.; Stringfellow, Guy S.; Becker, Andrew C.; L&#243; pez-Morales, Mercedes; Mezzalira, Fabio; Krajci, Tom</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 2, pp. L149-L152.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689L.149C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origins of Eccentric Close-In Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Takeda, Genya; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. L29-L32.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389..191P</bibcode>
			<title>Periastron precession measurements in transiting extrasolar planetary systems at the level of general relativity</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Kocsis, Bence</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 1, pp. 191-198.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389..191P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008PASP..120..860B</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Monitoring of Ultracool Dwarfs: Prospects for Searching for Transiting Companions</title>
			<authors>Blake, Cullen H.; Bloom, Joshua S.; Latham, David W.; Szentgyorgyi, Andrew H.; Skrutskie, Michael F.; Falco, Emilio E.; Starr, Dan S.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 120, Issue 870, pp. 860-871.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008PASP..120..860B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1248S</bibcode>
			<title>BD -22 5866: A Low-Mass, Quadruple-lined Spectroscopic and Eclipsing Binary</title>
			<authors>Shkolnik, Evgenya; Liu, Michael C.; Reid, I. Neill; Hebb, Leslie; Cameron, Andrew C.; Torres, Carlos A.; Wilson, David M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1248-1255.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1248S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...487L..25B</bibcode>
			<title>Observational consequences of the recently proposed Super-Earth orbiting GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Bean, J. L.; Seifahrt, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 487, Issue 2, 2008, pp.L25-L28</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...487L..25B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...487L...5A</bibcode>
			<title>Limits to the planet candidate GJ 436c</title>
			<authors>Alonso, R.; Barbieri, M.; Rabus, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Belmonte, J. A.; Almenara, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 487, Issue 1, 2008, pp.L5-L8</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...487L...5A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...487..373S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic parameters for 451 stars in the HARPS GTO planet search program. Stellar [Fe/H] and the frequency of exo-Neptunes</title>
			<authors>Sousa, S. G.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Udry, S.; Casagrande, L.; Israelian, G.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Monteiro, M. J. P. F. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 487, Issue 1, 2008, pp.373-381</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...487..373S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...486.1039B</bibcode>
			<title>A Hubble Space Telescope transit light curve for GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Bean, J. L.; Benedict, G. F.; Charbonneau, D.; Homeier, D.; Taylor, D. C.; McArthur, B.; Seifahrt, A.; Dreizler, S.; Reiners, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 486, Issue 3, 2008, pp.1039-1046</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...486.1039B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682L..49D</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Period Variations in Extrasolar Transiting Planet OGLE-TR-111b</title>
			<authors>D&#237;az, Rodrigo F.; Rojo, Patricio; Melita, Mario; Hoyer, Sergio; Minniti, Dante; Mauas, Pablo J. D.; Ru&#237;z, Mar&#237;a Teresa</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 1, pp. L49-L52.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682L..49D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AJ....135.2194S</bibcode>
			<title>Further Constraints on the Presence of a Debris Disk in the Multiplanet System Gliese 876</title>
			<authors>Shankland, P. D.; Blank, D. L.; Boboltz, D. A.; Lazio, T. J. W.; White, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 135, Issue 6, pp. 2194-2198 (2008).</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AJ....135.2194S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008PASP..120..617V</bibcode>
			<title>Closure Phase Signatures of Planet Transit Events</title>
			<authors>van Belle, Gerard T.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 120, issue 868, pp.617-624</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008PASP..120..617V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677L..59R</bibcode>
			<title>A ~5 M&amp;oplus; Super-Earth Orbiting GJ 436? The Power of Near-Grazing Transits</title>
			<authors>Ribas, Ignasi; Font-Ribera, Andreu; Beaulieu, Jean-Philippe</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. L59-L62.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677L..59R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482..315B</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and evolution of super-Earth to super-Jupiter exoplanets. I. Heavy element enrichment in the interior</title>
			<authors>Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 1, 2008, pp.315-332</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482..315B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008PASP..120..317N</bibcode>
			<title>Design Considerations for a Ground-Based Transit Search for Habitable Planets Orbiting M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip; Charbonneau, David</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 120, issue 865, pp.317-327</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008PASP..120..317N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJS..175..191P</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Variability in the 2MASS Calibration Fields: A Search for Planetary Transit Candidates</title>
			<authors>Plavchan, Peter; Jura, M.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Cutri, Roc M.; Gallagher, S. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 175, Issue 1, pp. 191-228.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJS..175..191P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...675..790F</bibcode>
			<title>Five Planets Orbiting 55 Cancri</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Laughlin, Greg; Henry, Gregory W.; Abouav, David; Peek, Kathryn M. G.; Wright, Jason T.; Johnson, John A.; McCarthy, Chris; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 675, Issue 1, pp. 790-801.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...675..790F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.384..663R</bibcode>
			<title>Observable consequences of planet formation models in systems with close-in terrestrial planets</title>
			<authors>Raymond, Sean N.; Barnes, Rory; Mandell, Avi M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 384, Issue 2, pp. 663-674.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.384..663R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673.1165E</bibcode>
			<title>An msini = 24 M&amp;oplus; Planetary Companion to the Nearby M Dwarf GJ 176</title>
			<authors>Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 2, pp. 1165-1168.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673.1165E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673.1160A</bibcode>
			<title>Ocean Planet or Thick Atmosphere: On the Mass-Radius Relationship for Solid Exoplanets with Massive Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; Seager, S.; Elkins-Tanton, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 2, pp. 1160-1164.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673.1160A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...479..579P</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray induced mass loss effects on exoplanets orbiting dM stars</title>
			<authors>Penz, T.; Micela, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 479, Issue 2, February IV 2008, pp.579-584</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...479..579P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...478..507M</bibcode>
			<title>The effect of activity on stellar temperatures and radii</title>
			<authors>Morales, J. C.; Ribas, I.; Jordi, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 478, Issue 2, February I 2008, pp.507-512</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...478..507M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..513D</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Dynamics of Short-Period Extrasolar Gas Giant Planets. I. Dependence of Nightside Temperature on Opacity</title>
			<authors>Dobbs-Dixon, Ian; Lin, D. N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 513-525.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..513D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MmSAI..79..562R</bibcode>
			<title>Fundamental properties of low-mass stars.</title>
			<authors>Ribas, I.; Morales, J. C.; Jordi, C.; Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Gallardo, J.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ&#224; Astronomica Italiana, v.79, p.562 (2008)</journal>
			<date>0/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MmSAI..79..562R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671L.173B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-5b: A Jupiter-like Hot Jupiter Transiting a Bright Star</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Shporer, A.; P&#225;l, A.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Latham, D. W.; Mazeh, T.; Ofir, A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Esquerdo, G.; Sipocz, B.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 2, pp. L173-L176.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671L.173B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671L..65T</bibcode>
			<title>The Transiting Exoplanet Host Star GJ 436: A Test of Stellar Evolution Models in the Lower Main Sequence, and Revised Planetary Parameters</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. L65-L68.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671L..65T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671..861H</bibcode>
			<title>Two Classes of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. 861-871.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671..861H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475.1125D</bibcode>
			<title>Characterization of the hot Neptune GJ 436 b with Spitzer and ground-based observations</title>
			<authors>Demory, B.-O.; Gillon, M.; Barman, T.; Bonfils, X.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Bouchy, F.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Mallmann, F.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 3, December I 2007, pp.1125-1129</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475.1125D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...670..833J</bibcode>
			<title>A New Planet around an M Dwarf: Revealing a Correlation between Exoplanets and Stellar Mass</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Vogt, Steven S.; Wright, Jason T.; Peek, Kathryn M. G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 670, Issue 1, pp. 833-840.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...670..833J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667L.199D</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Transit and Secondary Eclipse Photometry of GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Harrington, Joseph; Laughlin, Gregory; Seager, Sara; Navarro, Sarah B.; Bowman, William C.; Horning, Karen</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 2, pp. L199-L202.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667L.199D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...474..293B</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. X. A m sin i = 11 M_&amp;oplus; planet around the nearby spotted M dwarf GJ 674</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Mayor, M.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Gillon, M.; Perrier, C.; Udry, S.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 474, Issue 1, October IV 2007, pp.293-299</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...474..293B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...666.1198B</bibcode>
			<title>Multiepoch Radial Velocity Observations of L Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Blake, Cullen H.; Charbonneau, David; White, Russel J.; Marley, Mark S.; Saumon, Didier</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 666, Issue 2, pp. 1198-1204.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...666.1198B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...472L..13G</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of transits of the nearby hot Neptune GJ 436 b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Pont, F.; Demory, B.-O.; Mallmann, F.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Queloz, D.; Shporer, A.; Udry, S.; Vuissoz, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 472, Issue 2, September III 2007, pp.L13-L16</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...472L..13G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...471L..51G</bibcode>
			<title>Accurate Spitzer infrared radius measurement for the hot Neptune GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Demory, B.-O.; Barman, T.; Bonfils, X.; Mazeh, T.; Pont, F.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 471, Issue 3, September I 2007, pp.L51-L54</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...471L..51G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.378.1418W</bibcode>
			<title>A possible stellar metallic enhancement in post-T Tauri stars by a planetesimal bombardment</title>
			<authors>Winter, O. C.; de La Reza, R.; Domingos, R. C.; Boldrin, L. A. G.; Chavero, C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 378, Issue 4, pp. 1418-1426.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.378.1418W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.377.1511H</bibcode>
			<title>Using long-term transit timing to detect terrestrial planets</title>
			<authors>Heyl, Jeremy S.; Gladman, Brett J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 377, Issue 4, pp. 1511-1519.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.377.1511H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662.1282M</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Formation Scenarios Revisited: Core-Accretion versus Disk Instability</title>
			<authors>Matsuo, T.; Shibai, H.; Ootsubo, T.; Tamura, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 2, pp. 1282-1292.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662.1282M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ChA&amp;A..31..187J</bibcode>
			<title>A Study of Potential Earth-like Planets in the GJ 876 Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Ji, Jiang-Hui; Liu, Lin</authors>
			<journal>Chinese Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 31, Issue 2, p. 187-191.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ChA%26A..31..187J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...657..533W</bibcode>
			<title>Four New Exoplanets and Hints of Additional Substellar Companions to Exoplanet Host Stars</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Butler, R. P.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Apps, K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 657, Issue 1, pp. 533-545.</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...657..533W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...657..338P</bibcode>
			<title>A Survey for Young Spectroscopic Binary K7-M4 Stars in Ophiuchus</title>
			<authors>Prato, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 657, Issue 1, pp. 338-346.</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...657..338P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJS..168..297T</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and Evolution of Nearby Stars with Planets. II. Physical Properties of ~1000 Cool Stars from the SPOCS Catalog</title>
			<authors>Takeda, Genya; Ford, Eric B.; Sills, Alison; Rasio, Frederic A.; Fischer, Debra A.; Valenti, Jeff A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 168, Issue 2, pp. 297-318.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJS..168..297T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASP..119...90M</bibcode>
			<title>The M Dwarf GJ 436 and its Neptune-Mass Planet</title>
			<authors>Maness, H. L.; Marcy, G. W.; Ford, E. B.; Hauschildt, P. H.; Shreve, A. T.; Basri, G. B.; Butler, R. P.; Vogt, S. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 119, Issue 851, pp. 90-101.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASP..119...90M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1685B</bibcode>
			<title>A Long-Period Jupiter-Mass Planet Orbiting the Nearby M Dwarf GJ 849</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. Paul; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Wright, Jason T.; Vogt, Steven S.; Fischer, Debra A.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 850, pp. 1685-1689.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1685B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653L..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Metallicities of M Dwarf Planet Hosts from Spectral Synthesis</title>
			<authors>Bean, Jacob L.; Benedict, G. Fritz; Endl, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 1, pp. L65-L68.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653L..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653..700S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Search for Transits of the Planets Orbiting Gliese 876</title>
			<authors>Shankland, P. D.; Rivera, E. J.; Laughlin, G.; Blank, D. L.; Price, A.; Gary, B.; Bissinger, R.; Ringwald, F.; White, G.; Henry, G. W.; McGee, P.; Wolf, A. S.; Carter, B.; Lee, S.; Biggs, J.; Monard, B.; Ashley, M. C. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 1, pp. 700-707.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653..700S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652.1674B</bibcode>
			<title>New Debris Disks around Nearby Main-Sequence Stars: Impact on the Direct Detection of Planets</title>
			<authors>Beichman, C. A.; Bryden, G.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Gautier, T. N.; Grogan, K.; Shao, M.; Velusamy, T.; Lawler, S. M.; Blaylock, M.; Rieke, G. H.; Lunine, J. I.; Fischer, D. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Greaves, J. S.; Wyatt, M. C.; Holland, W. S.; Dent, W. R. F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. 1674-1693.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652.1674B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460..733L</bibcode>
			<title>Search for cold debris disks around M-dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Lestrade, J.-F.; Wyatt, M. C.; Bertoldi, F.; Dent, W. R. F.; Menten, K. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 3, December IV 2006, pp.733-741</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460..733L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1506L</bibcode>
			<title>Limits to Transits of the Neptune-Mass Planet Orbiting GJ 581</title>
			<authors>L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Morrell, Nidia I.; Butler, R. Paul; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 849, pp. 1506-1509.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1506L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AstL...32..759G</bibcode>
			<title>Pulkovo Compilation of Radial Velocities for 35 495 Hipparcos stars in a common system</title>
			<authors>Gontcharov, G. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Letters, Vol. 32, Issue 11, p.759-771</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AstL...32..759G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1010J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of Known Exoplanetary Systems Based on Measured Stellar Properties</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick; Underwood, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1019.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1010J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649..436E</bibcode>
			<title>Exploring the Frequency of Close-in Jovian Planets around M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; K&#252;rster, Martin; Paulson, Diane B.; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Tull, Robert G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 1, pp. 436-443.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649..436E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....132.1267S</bibcode>
			<title>No Detectable H+3 Emission from the Atmospheres of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Shkolnik, Evgenya; Gaidos, Eric; Moskovitz, Nick</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 132, Issue 3, pp. 1267-1274.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....132.1267S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..523R</bibcode>
			<title>Two Suns in The Sky: Stellar Multiplicity in Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Raghavan, Deepak; Henry, Todd J.; Mason, Brian D.; Subasavage, John P.; Jao, Wei-Chun; Beaulieu, Thom D.; Hambly, Nigel C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 523-542.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..523R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..505B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of Nearby Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. P.; Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Penny, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 505-522.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..505B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644L..79B</bibcode>
			<title>Rapid Formation of Super-Earths around M Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 1, pp. L79-L82.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644L..79B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644.1214T</bibcode>
			<title>Giant Planet Accretion and Migration: Surviving the Type I Regime</title>
			<authors>Thommes, Edward W.; Murray, Norman</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 2, pp. 1214-1222.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644.1214T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644.1183S</bibcode>
			<title>The Gl569 Multiple System</title>
			<authors>Simon, M.; Bender, C.; Prato, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 2, pp. 1183-1192.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644.1183S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....131.3016S</bibcode>
			<title>A Large-Area Search for Low-Mass Objects in Upper Scorpius. I. The Photometric Campaign and New Brown Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Slesnick, Catherine L.; Carpenter, John M.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 131, Issue 6, pp. 3016-3027.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....131.3016S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...643..501B</bibcode>
			<title>Rapid Formation of Gas Giant Planets around M Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 643, Issue 1, pp. 501-508.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...643..501B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118..617R</bibcode>
			<title>Ca II H and K Chromospheric Emission Lines in Late-K and M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Rauscher, Emily; Marcy, Geoffrey W.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 842, pp. 617-635.</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118..617R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....131.2274S</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical Composition of the Planet-harboring Star TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Yong, David; Carney, Bruce W.; Laird, John B.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 131, Issue 4, pp. 2274-2289.</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....131.2274S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...449.1219G</bibcode>
			<title>About putative Neptune-like extrasolar planetary candidates</title>
			<authors>Gozdziewski, K.; Migaszewski, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 449, Issue 3, April III 2006, pp.1219-1232</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...449.1219G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006Msngr.123...21K</bibcode>
			<title>In Search of Terrestrial Planets in the Habitable Zone of M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Kurster, M.; Endl, M.; Rodler, F.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, volume 123, page 21</journal>
			<date>3/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006Msngr.123...21K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...446.1165J</bibcode>
			<title>Radial velocity survey for planets and brown dwarf companions to very young brown dwarfs and very low-mass stars in Chamaeleon I with UVES at the VLT</title>
			<authors>Joergens, V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 446, Issue 3, February II 2006, pp.1165-1176</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...446.1165J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AN....327....9H</bibcode>
			<title>Monitor: transiting planets and brown dwarfs in star forming regions and young open clusters</title>
			<authors>Hodgkin, S. T.; Irwin, J. M.; Aigrain, S.; Hebb, L.; Moraux, E.; Irwin, M. J.; the Monitor collaboration</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.327, Issue 1, p.9-13</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AN....327....9H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005AN....326..913A</bibcode>
			<title>M dwarfs: planet formation and long term evolution</title>
			<authors>Adams, F. C.; Bodenheimer, P.; Laughlin, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.326, Issue 10, p.913-919</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005AN....326..913A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...443L..15B</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. VI. A Neptune-mass planet around the nearby M dwarf Gl 581</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Forveille, T.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Perrier, C.; Bouchy, F.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 443, Issue 3, December I 2005, pp.L15-L18</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...443L..15B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...634..625R</bibcode>
			<title>A ~7.5 M&amp;oplus; Planet Orbiting the Nearby Star, GJ 876</title>
			<authors>Rivera, Eugenio J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Vogt, Steven S.; Fischer, Debra A.; Brown, Timothy M.; Laughlin, Gregory; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 634, Issue 1, pp. 625-640.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...634..625R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...443..609S</bibcode>
			<title>On the ages of exoplanet host stars</title>
			<authors>Saffe, C.; G&#243;mez, M.; Chavero, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 443, Issue 2, November IV 2005, pp.609-626</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...443..609S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...442..635B</bibcode>
			<title>Metallicity of M dwarfs. I. A photometric calibration and the impact on the mass-luminosity relation at the bottom of the main sequence</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.; Santos, N. C.; Forveille, T.; S&#233; gransan, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 442, Issue 2, November I 2005, pp.635-642</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...442..635B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005RMxAC..23...64E</bibcode>
			<title>The Hunt for Extrasolar Planets at McDonald Observatory</title>
			<authors>Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Hatzes, A. P.; Wittenmyer, R. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Ninth Texas-Mexico Conference on Astrophysics (Eds. S. Torres-Peimbert &amp; G. MacAlpine) Revista Mexicana de Astronom&#237;a y Astrof&#237;sica (Serie de Conferencias) Vol. 23, pp. 64-67 (2005) (http://www.astroscu.unam.mx/~rmaa/)</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005RMxAC..23...64E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...441..791F</bibcode>
			<title>Oligarchic and giant impact growth of terrestrial planets in the presence of gas giant planet migration</title>
			<authors>Fogg, M. J.; Nelson, R. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 441, Issue 2, October II 2005, pp.791-806</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...441..791F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Icar..177..264B</bibcode>
			<title>The origin and nature of Neptune-like planets orbiting close to solar type stars</title>
			<authors>Brunini, Adri&#225;n; Cionco, Rodolfo G.</authors>
			<journal>Icarus, Volume 177, Issue 1, p. 264-268.</journal>
			<date>9/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Icar..177..264B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...437.1127S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic metallicities for planet-host stars: Extending the samples</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Bento, J. P.; Almeida, P. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Ecuvillon, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 437, Issue 3, July III 2005, pp.1127-1133</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...437.1127S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...626.1045I</bibcode>
			<title>Toward a Deterministic Model of Planetary Formation. III. Mass Distribution of Short-Period Planets around Stars of Various Masses</title>
			<authors>Ida, S.; Lin, D. N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 626, Issue 2, pp. 1045-1060.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...626.1045I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...436L..47B</bibcode>
			<title>Hot-Jupiters and hot-Neptunes: A common origin?</title>
			<authors>Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T. S.; Selsis, F.; Allard, F.; Hauschildt, P. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 436, Issue 3, June IV 2005, pp.L47-L51</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...436L..47B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005PASP..117..311T</bibcode>
			<title>Astrophysics in 2004</title>
			<authors>Trimble, Virginia; Aschwanden, Markus</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 117, Issue 830, pp. 311-394.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005PASP..117..311T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...623.1171T</bibcode>
			<title>Three Low-Mass Planets from the Anglo-Australian Planet Search</title>
			<authors>Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Jones, Hugh R. A.; Penny, Alan J.; McCarthy, Chris; Carter, Brad D.; Fischer, Debra A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 623, Issue 2, pp. 1171-1179.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...623.1171T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622.1102F</bibcode>
			<title>The Planet-Metallicity Correlation</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Valenti, Jeff</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 2, pp. 1102-1117.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622.1102F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622.1091J</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for Habitable ``Earths'' in Known Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Underwood, David R.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 2, pp. 1091-1101.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622.1091J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...621.1072L</bibcode>
			<title>A Comparison of Observationally Determined Radii with Theoretical Radius Predictions for Short-Period Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Wolf, Aaron; Vanmunster, Tonny; Bodenheimer, Peter; Fischer, Debra; Marcy, Geoff; Butler, Paul; Vogt, Steve</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 621, Issue 2, pp. 1072-1078.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...621.1072L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005AJ....129.1483L</bibcode>
			<title>A Catalog of Northern Stars with Annual Proper Motions Larger than 0.15" (LSPM-NORTH Catalog)</title>
			<authors>L&#233;pine, S&#233;bastien; Shara, Michael M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 129, Issue 3, pp. 1483-1522.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005AJ....129.1483L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...620.1002N</bibcode>
			<title>Radial Velocity Detectability of Low-Mass Extrasolar Planets in Close Orbits</title>
			<authors>Narayan, Raman; Cumming, Andrew; Lin, D. N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 620, Issue 2, pp. 1002-1009.</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...620.1002N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...617..580B</bibcode>
			<title>A Neptune-Mass Planet Orbiting the Nearby M Dwarf GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Wright, Jason T.; Henry, Gregory W.; Laughlin, Greg; Lissauer, Jack J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 617, Issue 1, pp. 580-588.</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...617..580B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...426L..19S</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS survey for southern extra-solar planets. II. A 14 Earth-masses exoplanet around mu Arae</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Bouchy, F.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Lovis, C.; Bazot, M.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Lo Curto, G.; Delfosse, X.; Mordasini, C.; Naef, D.; Sivan, J.-P.; Vauclair, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.426, p.L19-L23 (2004)</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...426L..19S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AJ....128..463R</bibcode>
			<title>Meeting the Cool Neighbors. VIII. A Preliminary 20 Parsec Census from the NLTT Catalogue</title>
			<authors>Reid, I. Neill; Cruz, Kelle L.; Allen, Peter; Mungall, F.; Kilkenny, D.; Liebert, James; Hawley, Suzanne L.; Fraser, Oliver J.; Covey, Kevin R.; Lowrance, Patrick; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Burgasser, Adam J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 128, Issue 1, pp. 463-483.</journal>
			<date>7/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AJ....128..463R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJS..152..261W</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric Ca II Emission in Nearby F, G, K, and M Stars</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, S. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 152, Issue 2, pp. 261-295.</journal>
			<date>6/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJS..152..261W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003AJ....126.3099E</bibcode>
			<title>A Dedicated M Dwarf Planet Search Using The Hobby-Eberly Telescope</title>
			<authors>Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Tull, Robert G.; MacQueen, Phillip J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 126, Issue 6, pp. 3099-3107.</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003AJ....126.3099E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...582.1011S</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Astrometry and Photometry for the Luyten Catalog. II. Faint Stars and the Revised Catalog</title>
			<authors>Salim, Samir; Gould, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 582, Issue 2, pp. 1011-1031.</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...582.1011S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...397..997P</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos red stars in the HpV_T2 and V I_C systems</title>
			<authors>Platais, I.; Pourbaix, D.; Jorissen, A.; Makarov, V. V.; Berdnikov, L. N.; Samus, N. N.; Lloyd Evans, T.; Lebzelter, T.; Sperauskas, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.397, p.997-1010 (2003)</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...397..997P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002KFNT...18..535Z</bibcode>
			<title>The radii and spectra of the nearest stars</title>
			<authors>Zakhozhaj, V. A.</authors>
			<journal>Kinematika I Fizika Nebesnykh Tel, v. 18, no. 6, p. 535-552</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002KFNT...18..535Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.336..611B</bibcode>
			<title>The measurement of rotational broadening in post-common-envelope binaries</title>
			<authors>Bleach, James N.; Wood, Janet H.; Smalley, B.; Catal&#225;n, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notice of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 336, Issue 2, pp. 611-620.</journal>
			<date>10/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.336..611B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJS..141..503N</bibcode>
			<title>Radial Velocities for 889 Late-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Nidever, David L.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Fischer, Debra A.; Vogt, Steven S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 141, Issue 2, pp. 503-522.</journal>
			<date>8/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJS..141..503N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJS..141..187B</bibcode>
			<title>Revised Coordinates and Proper Motions of the Stars in the Luyten Half-Second Catalog</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Sahu, Kailash C.; N&#233;meth, P&#233;ter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 141, Issue 1, pp. 187-193.</journal>
			<date>7/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJS..141..187B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AJ....123.3356G</bibcode>
			<title>The Palomar/MSU Nearby Star Spectroscopic Survey. III. Chromospheric Activity, M Dwarf Ages, and the Local Star Formation History</title>
			<authors>Gizis, John E.; Reid, I. Neill; Hawley, Suzanne L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 123, Issue 6, pp. 3356-3369.</journal>
			<date>6/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AJ....123.3356G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...569..863P</bibcode>
			<title>The Smallest Mass Ratio Young Star Spectroscopic Binaries</title>
			<authors>Prato, L.; Simon, M.; Mazeh, T.; McLean, I. S.; Norman, D.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 569, Issue 2, pp. 863-871.</journal>
			<date>4/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...569..863P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AJ....123.2002H</bibcode>
			<title>The Solar Neighborhood. VI. New Southern Nearby Stars Identified by Optical Spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Henry, Todd J.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Barto, Todd C.; Golimowski, David A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 123, Issue 4, pp. 2002-2009.</journal>
			<date>4/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AJ....123.2002H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000PASP..112.1269T</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopy and Component Masses of the Eclipsing Dwarf Nova HS 0907+1902</title>
			<authors>Thorstensen, John R.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 112, Issue 775, pp. 1269-1276.</journal>
			<date>9/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000PASP..112.1269T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000MNRAS.317..528W</bibcode>
			<title>A TiO study of the black hole binary GRO J0422+32 in a very low state</title>
			<authors>Webb, N. A.; Naylor, T.; Ioannou, Z.; Charles, P. A.; Shahbaz, T.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 317, Issue 3, pp. 528-534.</journal>
			<date>9/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000MNRAS.317..528W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000MNRAS.314..826D</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared spectroscopy of cataclysmic variables - III. Dwarf novae below the period gap and nova-like variables</title>
			<authors>Dhillon, V. S.; Littlefair, S. P.; Howell, S. B.; Ciardi, D. R.; Harrop-Allin, M. K.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 314, Issue 4, pp. 826-838.</journal>
			<date>6/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000MNRAS.314..826D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;AS..135..319H</bibcode>
			<title>The ROSAT all-sky survey catalogue of the nearby stars</title>
			<authors>H&#252;nsch, M.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Sterzik, M. F.; Voges, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.135, p.319-338</journal>
			<date>3/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26AS..135..319H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999AJ....117..469W</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopy of Brown Dwarf Candidates in the rho Ophiuchi Molecular Core</title>
			<authors>Wilking, Bruce A.; Greene, Thomas P.; Meyer, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 117, Issue 1, pp. 469-482.</journal>
			<date>1/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999AJ....117..469W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998ApJ...509..836L</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared Colors at the Stellar/Substellar Boundary</title>
			<authors>Leggett, S. K.; Allard, F.; Hauschildt, P. H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 509, Issue 2, pp. 836-847.</journal>
			<date>12/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998ApJ...509..836L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998AJ....116.2565D</bibcode>
			<title>High Proper Motion Stars. III. Radial Velocities of 24 Late-Type Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Dawson, P. C.; De Robertis, M. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 116, Issue 5, pp. 2565-2568.</journal>
			<date>11/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998AJ....116.2565D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AJ....112.2799H</bibcode>
			<title>The Palomar/MSU Nearby Star Spectroscopic Survey.II.The Southern M Dwarfs and Investigation of Magnetic Activity</title>
			<authors>Hawley, Suzanne L.; Gizis, John E.; Reid, I. Neill</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.112, p.2799</journal>
			<date>12/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AJ....112.2799H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AJ....112.2300W</bibcode>
			<title>Photometry of Stars with Large Proper Motion</title>
			<authors>Weis, Edward W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.112, p.2300</journal>
			<date>11/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AJ....112.2300W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AJ....111..466E</bibcode>
			<title>Distribution and Corrlation of Age, Abundance, and Motion of Lower Main Sequence Stars</title>
			<authors>Eggen, Olin J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.111, p.466</journal>
			<date>1/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AJ....111..466E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;AS..114..269D</bibcode>
			<title>Vitesses radiales. Catalogue WEB: Wilson Evans Batten. Subtittle: Radial velocities: The Wilson-Evans-Batten catalogue.</title>
			<authors>Duflot, M.; Figon, P.; Meyssonnier, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.114, p.269</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26AS..114..269D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995AJ....110.1838R</bibcode>
			<title>The Palomar/MSU Nearby-Star Spectroscopic Survey. I. The Northern M Dwarfs -Bandstrengths and Kinematics</title>
			<authors>Reid, I. Neill; Hawley, Suzanne L.; Gizis, John E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.110, p.1838</journal>
			<date>10/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995AJ....110.1838R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995gcts.book.....V</bibcode>
			<title>The general catalogue of trigonometric [stellar] paralaxes</title>
			<authors>van Altena, W. F.; Lee, J. T.; Hoffleit, E. D.</authors>
			<journal>New Haven, CT: Yale University Observatory, |c1995, 4th ed., completely revised and enlarged</journal>
			<date>0/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995gcts.book.....V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;A...280..181M</bibcode>
			<title>Far infrared properties of late type dwarfs. Infrared fluxes of K &amp; M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Mathioudakis, M.; Doyle, J. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 280, no. 1, p. 181-194</journal>
			<date>12/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26A...280..181M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993AJ....105.1962W</bibcode>
			<title>Photometry of dwarf K and M stars</title>
			<authors>Weis, Edward W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 105, no. 5, p. 1962-1966.</journal>
			<date>5/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993AJ....105.1962W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJS...82..351L</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared colors of low-mass stars</title>
			<authors>Leggett, S. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 82, no. 1, Sept. 1992, p. 351-394.</journal>
			<date>9/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJS...82..351L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJ...396..178F</bibcode>
			<title>Multiplicity among M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 396, no. 1, Sept. 1, 1992, p. 178-194.</journal>
			<date>9/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJ...396..178F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJ...390..550M</bibcode>
			<title>The rotation of M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Chen, Grace H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 390, no. 2, May 10, 1992, p. 550-559.</journal>
			<date>5/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJ...390..550M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991ApJS...77..417K</bibcode>
			<title>A standard stellar spectral sequence in the red/near-infrared - Classes K5 to M9</title>
			<authors>Kirkpatrick, J. D.; Henry, Todd J.; McCarthy, Donald W., Jr.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 77, Nov. 1991, p. 417-440.</journal>
			<date>11/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991ApJS...77..417K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991PASP..103..973D</bibcode>
			<title>Photoelectric UBV photometry of northern stars from the HK objective-prism survey. II</title>
			<authors>Doinidis, Steve P.; Beers, Timothy C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 103, Sept. 1991, p. 973-986.</journal>
			<date>9/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991PASP..103..973D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990PASP..102.1392D</bibcode>
			<title>Photoelectric UBV photometry of northern stars from the HK objective-prism survey</title>
			<authors>Doinidis, Steve P.; Beers, Timothy C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 102, Dec. 1990, p. 1392-1399.</journal>
			<date>12/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990PASP..102.1392D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990MNRAS.245..385M</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopy of faint, high latitude cataclysmic variable candidates.</title>
			<authors>Mukai, K.; Mason, K. O.; Howell, S. B.; Allington-Smith, J.; Callanan, P. J.; Charles, P. A.; Hassall, B. J. M.; Machin, G.; Naylor, T.; Smale, A. P.; van Paradijs, J.</authors>
			<journal>Mon. Not. R. Astron. Soc., Vol. 245, No. 3, p. 385 - 391</journal>
			<date>8/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990MNRAS.245..385M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989ApJ...345..536G</bibcode>
			<title>The CA II resonance lines in M dwarf stars without H-alpha emission</title>
			<authors>Giampapa, Mark S.; Cram, Lawrence E.; Wild, Walter J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 345, Oct. 1, 1989, p. 536-542.</journal>
			<date>10/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989ApJ...345..536G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989AJ.....98.1472D</bibcode>
			<title>High-proper-motion stars. II - Radial velocities of late-type dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Dawson, P. C.; De Robertis, M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 98, Oct. 1989, p. 1472-1476.</journal>
			<date>10/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989AJ.....98.1472D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989PASP..101..787G</bibcode>
			<title>Bolometric luminosities and colors for K and M dwarfs and the subluminous stars of the halo</title>
			<authors>Greenstein, Jesse L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 101, Sept. 1989, p. 787-810.</journal>
			<date>9/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989PASP..101..787G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989ApJ...344..441M</bibcode>
			<title>A search for substellar companions to low-mass stars</title>
			<authors>Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Benitz, Karsten J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 344, Sept. 1, 1989, p. 441-453.</journal>
			<date>9/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989ApJ...344..441M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989ApJ...343..400M</bibcode>
			<title>Far-infrared properties of flare stars and dM stars</title>
			<authors>Mullan, D. J.; Stencel, R. E.; Backman, D. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 343, Aug. 1, 1989, p. 400-408.</journal>
			<date>8/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989ApJ...343..400M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988MNRAS.234.1065L</bibcode>
			<title>The infrared luminosity function for low-mass stars</title>
			<authors>Leggett, S. K.; Hawkins, M. R. S.</authors>
			<journal>Royal Astronomical Society, Monthly Notices (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 234, Oct. 15, 1988, p. 1065-1090.</journal>
			<date>10/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988MNRAS.234.1065L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988AJ.....96..719U</bibcode>
			<title>Space motions of low-mass stars.</title>
			<authors>Upgren, A. R.; Caruso, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 96, Aug. 1988, p. 719-740.</journal>
			<date>8/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988AJ.....96..719U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987PASP...99..490M</bibcode>
			<title>Radial velocities of M dwarf stars</title>
			<authors>Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Lindsay, Victoria; Wilson, Karen</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 99, June 1987, p. 490-496.</journal>
			<date>6/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987PASP...99..490M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986ApJS...61..531S</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric activity, kinematics, and metallicities of nearby M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Stauffer, J. R.; Hartmann, L. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 61, July 1986, p. 531-568.</journal>
			<date>7/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986ApJS...61..531S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986AJ.....92..139S</bibcode>
			<title>Dwarf K and M stars of high proper motion found in a hemispheric survey</title>
			<authors>Stephenson, C. B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 92, July 1986, p. 139-165.</journal>
			<date>7/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986AJ.....92..139S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985ApJS...59..197B</bibcode>
			<title>G. P. Kuiper's spectral classifications of proper-motion stars</title>
			<authors>Bidelman, W. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 59, Oct. 1985, p. 197-227.</journal>
			<date>10/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985ApJS...59..197B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983ApJS...53..643J</bibcode>
			<title>Predicted infrared brightness of stars within 25 parsecs of the sun</title>
			<authors>Johnson, H. M.; Wright, C. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 53, Nov. 1983, p. 643-711. Research sponsored by the Lockheed Independent Research Program and Lockheed Independent Development Program.</journal>
			<date>11/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983ApJS...53..643J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1981MNRAS.194..403J</bibcode>
			<title>Narrow-band photometry of faint red stars. I</title>
			<authors>Jones, D. H. P.; Sinclair, J. E.; Alexander, J. B.</authors>
			<journal>Royal Astronomical Society, Monthly Notices, vol. 194, Feb. 1981, p. 403-419.</journal>
			<date>2/1981</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1981MNRAS.194..403J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979ApJ...230..786E</bibcode>
			<title>Luminosity and motion of large proper-motion stars. I - Stars with annual proper motion larger than 1 arcsec</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1, vol. 230, June 15, 1979, p. 786-801.</journal>
			<date>6/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979ApJ...230..786E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979AJ.....84..567L</bibcode>
			<title>Parallax and proper motion analyses of long-interval plate series taken with the Sproul 61-cm refractor.</title>
			<authors>Lippincott, S. L.; Borgman, E. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astron. J., Vol. 84, p. 567 - 569</journal>
			<date>4/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979AJ.....84..567L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979ApJS...39...89E</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogs of proper-motion stars. I - Stars brighter than visual magnitude 15 and with annual proper motion of 1 arcsec or more</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, vol. 39, Jan. 1979, p. 89-101.</journal>
			<date>1/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979ApJS...39...89E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979VKha..190...52Z</bibcode>
			<title>Nearest stars.</title>
			<authors>Zakhozhaj, V. A.</authors>
			<journal>Vestnik Khar'kovskogo Universiteta, 190, 52-77 (1979)</journal>
			<date>0/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979VKha..190...52Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1978AJ.....83..626U</bibcode>
			<title>The motions of K and M dwarf stars of different ages</title>
			<authors>Upgren, A. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, vol. 83, June 1978, p. 626-635.</journal>
			<date>6/1978</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1978AJ.....83..626U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1975AJ.....80..711U</bibcode>
			<title>Parallaxes and proper motions. X.</title>
			<authors>Upgren, A. R.; Weis, E. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astron. J., Vol. 80, p. 711 - 713</journal>
			<date>9/1975</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1975AJ.....80..711U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1956AJ.....61..219S</bibcode>
			<title>Photovisual magnitudes of 418 dwarf M stars and 34 parallax stars.</title>
			<authors>Stedman, W. D.; Vyssotsky, A. N.</authors>
			<journal>Astron. J., 61, 219-224 (1956)</journal>
			<date>0/1956</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1956AJ.....61..219S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1956AJ.....61..201V</bibcode>
			<title>Dwarf M stars found spectrophotometrically .</title>
			<authors>Vyssotsky, A. N.</authors>
			<journal>Astron. J., 61, 201-213 (1956)</journal>
			<date>0/1956</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1956AJ.....61..201V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1937AJ.....46..157R</bibcode>
			<title>New proper motion stars and errata</title>
			<authors>Ross, Frank E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, vol. 46, iss. 1073, p. 157-161 (1937).</journal>
			<date>11/1937</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1937AJ.....46..157R</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
