<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A..95M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal phase curves of nontransiting terrestrial exoplanets. II. Characterizing airless planets</title>
			<authors>Maurin, A. S.; Selsis, F.; Hersant, F.; Belu, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A95</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A..95M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534A..26V</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic characterization of the atmospheres of potentially habitable planets: GL 581 d as a model case study</title>
			<authors>von Paris, P.; Cabrera, J.; Godolt, M.; Grenfell, J. L.; Hedelt, P.; Rauer, H.; Schreier, F.; Stracke, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.A26</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534A..26V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.2523G</bibcode>
			<title>Bayesian re-analysis of the Gliese 581 exoplanet system</title>
			<authors>Gregory, Philip C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 3, pp. 2523-2545.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.2523G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A...1S</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal phase curves of nontransiting terrestrial exoplanets. I. Characterizing atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Selsis, F.; Wordsworth, R. D.; Forget, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A1</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A...1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...68B</bibcode>
			<title>Density Estimation for Projected Exoplanet Quantities</title>
			<authors>Brown, Robert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 68 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...68B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528L...5T</bibcode>
			<title>Bayesian re-analysis of the radial velocities of Gliese 581. Evidence in favour of only four planetary companions</title>
			<authors>Tuomi, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.L5</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528L...5T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1792B</bibcode>
			<title>Connecting planets around horizontal branch stars with known exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Bear, Ealeal; Soker, Noam</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 3, pp. 1792-1802.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1792B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729L..26V</bibcode>
			<title>Astrophysical Parameters and Habitable Zone of the Exoplanet Hosting Star GJ 581</title>
			<authors>von Braun, Kaspar; Boyajian, Tabetha S.; Kane, Stephen R.; van Belle, Gerard T.; Ciardi, David R.; Lpez-Morales, Mercedes; McAlister, Harold A.; Henry, Todd J.; Jao, Wei-Chun; Riedel, Adric R.; Subasavage, John P.; Schaefer, Gail; ten Brummelaar, Theo A.; Ridgway, Stephen; Sturmann, Laszlo; Sturmann, Judit; Mazingue, Jude; Turner, Nils H.; Farrington, Chris; Goldfinger, P. J.; Boden, Andrew F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. L26 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729L..26V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1204M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation and activity in the WASP-10 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuhuser, R.; Tetzlaff, N.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Chen, W. P.; Walter, F.; Marka, C.; Baar, S.; Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.; Krushevska, V.; Tachihara, K.; Takahashi, H.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 2, pp. 1204-1212.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1204M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727..103T</bibcode>
			<title>The Anglo-Australian Planet Search. XX. A Solitary Ice-giant Planet Orbiting HD 102365</title>
			<authors>Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. Paul; Jones, Hugh R. A.; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; O'Toole, Simon; Bailey, Jeremy; Carter, Brad D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 103 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727..103T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010BASI...38..137L</bibcode>
			<title>Evaporation of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the Astronomical Soceity of India, Vol. 38, p. 137-145, 2010</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010BASI...38..137L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..954V</bibcode>
			<title>The Lick-Carnegie Exoplanet Survey: A 3.1 M &amp;oplus; Planet in the Habitable Zone of the Nearby M3V Star Gliese 581</title>
			<authors>Vogt, Steven S.; Butler, R. Paul; Rivera, E. J.; Haghighipour, N.; Henry, Gregory W.; Williamson, Michael H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 954-965 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..954V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARep...54..550K</bibcode>
			<title>Resonance Properties of Extra-Solar Two-Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Kuznetsov, E. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Reports, Volume 54, Issue 6, pp.550-561</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARep...54..550K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..82F</bibcode>
			<title>The stability of ultra-compact planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Funk, B.; Wuchterl, G.; Schwarz, R.; Pilat-Lohinger, E.; Eggl, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A82</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..82F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..186...48J</bibcode>
			<title>On the Fundamental Mass-Period Functions of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jiang, Ing-Guey; Yeh, Li-Chin; Chang, Yen-Chang; Hung, Wen-Liang</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 186, Issue 1, pp. 48-62 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..186...48J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..149S</bibcode>
			<title>Models of Neptune-Mass Exoplanets: Emergent Fluxes and Albedos</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent; Hubeny, Ivan; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 149-158 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..149S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707.1000H</bibcode>
			<title>Tidally Heated Terrestrial Exoplanets: Viscoelastic Response Models</title>
			<authors>Henning, Wade G.; O'Connell, Richard J.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 2, pp. 1000-1015 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707.1000H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..487M</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XVIII. An Earth-mass planet in the GJ 581 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Mayor, M.; Bonfils, X.; Forveille, T.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Beust, H.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.487-494</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..487M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700.1732K</bibcode>
			<title>Geodynamics and Rate of Volcanism on Massive Earth-like Planets</title>
			<authors>Kite, E. S.; Manga, M.; Gaidos, E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 1732-1749 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700.1732K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...697.1263O</bibcode>
			<title>A Neptune-mass Planet Orbiting the Nearby G Dwarf HD 16417</title>
			<authors>O'Toole, Simon; Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. Paul; Jones, Hugh R. A.; Bailey, Jeremy; Carter, Brad D.; Vogt, Steven S.; Laughlin, Gregory; Rivera, Eugenio J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 697, Issue 2, pp. 1263-1268 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...697.1263O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694.1559S</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Follow-Up Observations of the Transiting Neptune-Mass Planet GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Shporer, Avi; Mazeh, Tsevi; Pont, Frederic; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Latham, David W.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 2, pp. 1559-1565 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694.1559S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693.1084W</bibcode>
			<title>Ten New and Updated Multiplanet Systems and a Survey of Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Upadhyay, S.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Ford, Eric B.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 2, pp. 1084-1099 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693.1084W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482..699C</bibcode>
			<title>Double-blind test program for astrometric planet detection with Gaia</title>
			<authors>Casertano, S.; Lattanzi, M. G.; Sozzetti, A.; Spagna, A.; Jancart, S.; Morbidelli, R.; Pannunzio, R.; Pourbaix, D.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 2, 2008, pp.699-729</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482..699C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.384..663R</bibcode>
			<title>Observable consequences of planet formation models in systems with close-in terrestrial planets</title>
			<authors>Raymond, Sean N.; Barnes, Rory; Mandell, Avi M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 384, Issue 2, pp. 663-674.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.384..663R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...479..277B</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical evolution of the Gliese 581 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 479, Issue 1, February III 2008, pp.277-282</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...479..277B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...672.1202B</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a Third Planet in the HD 74156 System Using the Hobby-Eberly Telescope</title>
			<authors>Bean, Jacob L.; McArthur, Barbara E.; Benedict, G. Fritz; Armstrong, Amber</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 672, Issue 2, pp. 1202-1208.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...672.1202B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007Icar..192..582B</bibcode>
			<title>UV habitable zones around M stars</title>
			<authors>Buccino, Andrea P.; Lemarchand, Guillermo A.; Mauas, Pablo J. D.</authors>
			<journal>Icarus, Volume 192, Issue 2, p. 582-587.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007Icar..192..582B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...476.1365V</bibcode>
			<title>The habitability of super-Earths in Gliese 581</title>
			<authors>von Bloh, W.; Bounama, C.; Cuntz, M.; Franck, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 476, Issue 3, December IV 2007, pp.1365-1371</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...476.1365V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...670..833J</bibcode>
			<title>A New Planet around an M Dwarf: Revealing a Correlation between Exoplanets and Stellar Mass</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Vogt, Steven S.; Wright, Jason T.; Peek, Kathryn M. G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 670, Issue 1, pp. 833-840.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...670..833J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669..606R</bibcode>
			<title>A Decreased Probability of Habitable Planet Formation around Low-Mass Stars</title>
			<authors>Raymond, Sean N.; Scalo, John; Meadows, Victoria S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 1, pp. 606-614.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669..606R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..359G</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting low-frequency radio fluxes of known extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Griemeier, J.-M.; Zarka, P.; Spreeuw, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 1, November III 2007, pp.359-368</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..359G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...666..475M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Planet Taxonomy: A New Statistical Approach</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 666, Issue 1, pp. 475-485.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...666..475M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...469L..43U</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XI. Super-Earths (5 and 8 M{&amp;oplus;}) in a 3-planet system</title>
			<authors>Udry, S.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Mayor, M.; Perrier, C.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 469, Issue 3, July III 2007, pp.L43-L47</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...469L..43U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..823M</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of Earth-like Planets During and After Giant Planet Migration</title>
			<authors>Mandell, Avi M.; Raymond, Sean N.; Sigurdsson, Steinn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 823-844.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..823M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...461.1185L</bibcode>
			<title>A diagram to determine the evaporation status of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 461, Issue 3, January III 2007, pp.1185-1193</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...461.1185L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MmSAI..78..612M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planet taxonomy: a new statistical approach</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.; Ortolani, S.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana, v.78, p.612 (2007)</journal>
			<date>0/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MmSAI..78..612M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653L..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Metallicities of M Dwarf Planet Hosts from Spectral Synthesis</title>
			<authors>Bean, Jacob L.; Benedict, G. Fritz; Endl, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 1, pp. L65-L68.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653L..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1506L</bibcode>
			<title>Limits to Transits of the Neptune-Mass Planet Orbiting GJ 581</title>
			<authors>Lpez-Morales, Mercedes; Morrell, Nidia I.; Butler, R. Paul; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 849, pp. 1506-1509.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1506L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1010J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of Known Exoplanetary Systems Based on Measured Stellar Properties</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick; Underwood, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1019.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1010J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.369.1267D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of a binary or planetary system during encounters with a third inclined body</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 369, Issue 3, pp. 1267-1280.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.369.1267D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..505B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of Nearby Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. P.; Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Penny, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 505-522.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..505B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644L..79B</bibcode>
			<title>Rapid Formation of Super-Earths around M Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 1, pp. L79-L82.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644L..79B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...447..361U</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. V. A 14 Earth-masses planet orbiting HD 4308</title>
			<authors>Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Mordasini, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Sivan, J.-P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 447, Issue 1, February III 2006, pp.361-367</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...447..361U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...443L..15B</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. VI. A Neptune-mass planet around the nearby M dwarf Gl 581</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Forveille, T.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Perrier, C.; Bouchy, F.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 443, Issue 3, December I 2005, pp.L15-L18</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...443L..15B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750L..37M</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the Cool Kepler Objects of Interests. New Effective Temperatures, Metallicities, Masses, and Radii of Low-mass Kepler Planet-candidate Host Stars</title>
			<authors>Muirhead, Philip S.; Hamren, Katherine; Schlawin, Everett; Rojas-Ayala, B rbara; Covey, Kevin R.; Lloyd, James P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. L37 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750L..37M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..40M</bibcode>
			<title>Metallicity of solar-type stars with debris discs and planets*</title>
			<authors>Maldonado, J.; Eiroa, C.; Villaver, E.; Montesinos, B.; Mora, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A40</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..40M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A...9G</bibcode>
			<title>Long-term magnetic activity of a sample of M-dwarf stars from the HARPS program . II. Activity and radial velocity</title>
			<authors>Gomes da Silva, J.; Santos, N. C.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Udry, S.; Dumusque, X.; Lovis, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A9</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A...9G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ARep...56..305T</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of planets during the evolution of single and binary stars</title>
			<authors>Tutukov, A. V.; Fedorova, A. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Reports, Volume 56, Issue 4, pp.305-314</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ARep...56..305T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749L...6L</bibcode>
			<title>On the Detectability of a Predicted Mesolensing Event Associated with the High Proper Motion Star VB 10</title>
			<authors>Lpine, Sbastien; DiStefano, Rosanne</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 749, Issue 1, article id. L6 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749L...6L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...748...93R</bibcode>
			<title>Metallicity and Temperature Indicators in M Dwarf K-band Spectra: Testing New and Updated Calibrations with Observations of 133 Solar Neighborhood M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Rojas-Ayala, Brbara; Covey, Kevin R.; Muirhead, Philip S.; Lloyd, James P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 748, Issue 2, article id. 93 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...748...93R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...747L..38T</bibcode>
			<title>An H-band Spectroscopic Metallicity Calibration for M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Terrien, Ryan C.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Bender, Chad F.; Deshpande, Rohit; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Bochanski, John J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 747, Issue 2, article id. L38 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...747L..38T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...67D</bibcode>
			<title>Refined Metallicity Indices for M Dwarfs Using the SLoWPoKES Catalog of Wide, Low-mass Binaries</title>
			<authors>Dhital, Saurav; West, Andrew A.; Stassun, Keivan G.; Bochanski, John J.; Massey, Angela P.; Bastien, Fabienne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 3, article id. 67 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143...67D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.419.2737H</bibcode>
			<title>Global models of planetary system formation in radiatively-inefficient protoplanetary discs</title>
			<authors>Hellary, Phil; Nelson, Richard P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 419, Issue 4, pp. 2737-2757.</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.419.2737H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A..95M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal phase curves of nontransiting terrestrial exoplanets. II. Characterizing airless planets</title>
			<authors>Maurin, A. S.; Selsis, F.; Hersant, F.; Belu, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A95</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A..95M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewAR..56...19M</bibcode>
			<title>From 51 Peg to Earth-type planets</title>
			<authors>Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 56, Issue 1, p. 19-24.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012NewAR..56...19M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143....2N</bibcode>
			<title>Potential Members of Stellar Kinematic Groups within 30 pc of the Sun</title>
			<authors>Nakajima, Tadashi; Morino, Jun-Ichi</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143....2N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011SerAJ.183....1J</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomical Optical Interferometry. II. Astrophysical Results</title>
			<authors>Jankov, S.</authors>
			<journal>Serbian Astronomical Journal, vol. 183, pp. 1-35</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011SerAJ.183....1J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...41K</bibcode>
			<title>Climate Instability on Tidally Locked Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Kite, Edwin S.; Gaidos, Eric; Manga, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...41K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2253P</bibcode>
			<title>Occurrence of the 2:1 commensurability in a gas giant-super-Earth system</title>
			<authors>Podlewska-Gaca, E.; Szuszkiewicz, E.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2253-2263.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2253P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740...49V</bibcode>
			<title>55 Cancri: Stellar Astrophysical Parameters, a Planet in the Habitable Zone, and Implications for the Radius of a Transiting Super-Earth</title>
			<authors>von Braun, Kaspar; Boyajian, Tabetha S.; ten Brummelaar, Theo A.; Kane, Stephen R.; van Belle, Gerard T.; Ciardi, David R.; Raymond, Sean N.; L pez-Morales, Mercedes; McAlister, Harold A.; Schaefer, Gail; Ridgway, Stephen T.; Sturmann, Laszlo; Sturmann, Judit; White, Russel; Turner, Nils H.; Farrington, Chris; Goldfinger, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 740, Issue 1, article id. 49 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740...49V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534A..58P</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for Earth-like planets in the habitable zone. I. Very low-mass planets around HD 20794, HD 85512, and HD 192310</title>
			<authors>Pepe, F.; Lovis, C.; Sgransan, D.; Benz, W.; Bouchy, F.; Dumusque, X.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.A58</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534A..58P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534A..30G</bibcode>
			<title>Long-term magnetic activity of a sample of M-dwarf stars from the HARPS program. I. Comparison of activity indices</title>
			<authors>Gomes da Silva, J.; Santos, N. C.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.A30</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534A..30G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534A..26V</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic characterization of the atmospheres of potentially habitable planets: GL 581 d as a model case study</title>
			<authors>von Paris, P.; Cabrera, J.; Godolt, M.; Grenfell, J. L.; Hedelt, P.; Rauer, H.; Schreier, F.; Stracke, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.A26</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534A..26V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.2523G</bibcode>
			<title>Bayesian re-analysis of the Gliese 581 exoplanet system</title>
			<authors>Gregory, Philip C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 3, pp. 2523-2545.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.2523G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415.2145H</bibcode>
			<title>Gliese 581g as a scaled-up version of Earth: atmospheric circulation simulations</title>
			<authors>Heng, Kevin; Vogt, Steven S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 3, pp. 2145-2157.</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415.2145H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A.116T</bibcode>
			<title>Application of Bayesian model inadequacy criterion for multiple data sets to radial velocity models of exoplanet systems</title>
			<authors>Tuomi, M.; Pinfield, D.; Jones, H. R. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A116</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A.116T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..79S</bibcode>
			<title>Defining and cataloging exoplanets: the exoplanet.eu database</title>
			<authors>Schneider, J.; Dedieu, C.; Le Sidaner, P.; Savalle, R.; Zolotukhin, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A79</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..79S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..58V</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric studies of habitability in the Gliese 581 system</title>
			<authors>von Paris, P.; Gebauer, S.; Godolt, M.; Rauer, H.; Stracke, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A58</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..58V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A...1S</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal phase curves of nontransiting terrestrial exoplanets. I. Characterizing atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Selsis, F.; Wordsworth, R. D.; Forget, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A1</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A...1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...72G</bibcode>
			<title>Effects of Stellar Flux on Tidally Locked Terrestrial Planets: Degree-1 Mantle Convection and Local Magma Ponds</title>
			<authors>Gelman, S. E.; Elkins-Tanton, L. T.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 2, article id. 72 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735...72G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A...5P</bibcode>
			<title>On the dynamics of resonant super-Earths in disks with turbulence driven by stochastic forcing</title>
			<authors>Pierens, A.; Baruteau, C.; Hersant, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A5</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A...5P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733L..48W</bibcode>
			<title>Gliese 581d is the First Discovered Terrestrial-mass Exoplanet in the Habitable Zone</title>
			<authors>Wordsworth, Robin D.; Forget, Franois; Selsis, Franck; Millour, Ehouarn; Charnay, Benjamin; Madeleine, Jean-Baptiste</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. L48 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733L..48W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...35K</bibcode>
			<title>Model Spectra of the First Potentially Habitable Super-Earth---Gl581d</title>
			<authors>Kaltenegger, Lisa; Segura, Antgona; Mohanty, Subhanjoy</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 35 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...35K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...31T</bibcode>
			<title>The Anglo-Australian Planet Search. XXI. A Gas-giant Planet in a One Year Orbit and the Habitability of Gas-giant Satellites</title>
			<authors>Tinney, C. G.; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Butler, R. Paul; Jones, Hugh R. A.; O'Toole, Simon J.; Bailey, Jeremy A.; Carter, Brad D.; Horner, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 31 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...31T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529C...1P</bibcode>
			<title>Coronal properties of planet-bearing stars (Corrigendum)</title>
			<authors>Poppenhaeger, K.; Robrade, J.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.C1</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529C...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A...8R</bibcode>
			<title>Potential biosignatures in super-Earth atmospheres. I. Spectral appearance of super-Earths around M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Rauer, H.; Gebauer, S.; Paris, P. V.; Cabrera, J.; Godolt, M.; Grenfell, J. L.; Belu, A.; Selsis, F.; Hedelt, P.; Schreier, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A8</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A...8R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011RMxAA..47..173F</bibcode>
			<title>A variant of the Titius-Bode Law</title>
			<authors>Flores-Gutirrez, J. D.; Garca-Guerra, C.</authors>
			<journal>Revista Mexicana de Astronoma y Astrofsica Vol. 47, pp. 173-184 (2011) (http://www.astroscu.unam.mx/~rmaa/)</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011RMxAA..47..173F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...95B</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the sin(I) Degeneracy in Low-mass Multi-planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Batygin, Konstantin; Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. 95 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...95B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...93W</bibcode>
			<title>The California Planet Survey. III. A Possible 2:1 Resonance in the Exoplanetary Triple System HD 37124</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Isaacson, H.; Fischer, D. A.; Spronck, J.; Anderson, J.; Valenti, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. 93 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...93W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528L...5T</bibcode>
			<title>Bayesian re-analysis of the radial velocities of Gliese 581. Evidence in favour of only four planetary companions</title>
			<authors>Tuomi, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.L5</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528L...5T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A.133V</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of the Goldilocks planet Gliese 581g: results from geodynamic models</title>
			<authors>von Bloh, W.; Cuntz, M.; Franck, S.; Bounama, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A133</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A.133V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A.112L</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XXVIII. Up to seven planets orbiting HD 10180: probing the architecture of low-mass planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Lovis, C.; Sgransan, D.; Mayor, M.; Udry, S.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Bouchy, F.; Correia, A. C. M.; Laskar, J.; Lo Curto, G.; Mordasini, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A112</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A.112L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A.111B</bibcode>
			<title>A short-period super-Earth orbiting the M2.5 dwarf GJ 3634. Detection with HARPS velocimetry and transit search with Spitzer photometry</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Gillon, M.; Forveille, T.; Delfosse, X.; Deming, D.; Demory, B.-O.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Neves, V.; Perrier, C.; Santos, N. C.; Seager, S.; Udry, S.; Boisse, I.; Bonnefoy, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A111</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A.111B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..27H</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal obliquity evolution of potentially habitable planets</title>
			<authors>Heller, R.; Leconte, J.; Barnes, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A27</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..27H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729L..26V</bibcode>
			<title>Astrophysical Parameters and Habitable Zone of the Exoplanet Hosting Star GJ 581</title>
			<authors>von Braun, Kaspar; Boyajian, Tabetha S.; Kane, Stephen R.; van Belle, Gerard T.; Ciardi, David R.; Lpez-Morales, Mercedes; McAlister, Harold A.; Henry, Todd J.; Jao, Wei-Chun; Riedel, Adric R.; Subasavage, John P.; Schaefer, Gail; ten Brummelaar, Theo A.; Ridgway, Stephen; Sturmann, Laszlo; Sturmann, Judit; Mazingue, Jude; Turner, Nils H.; Farrington, Chris; Goldfinger, P. J.; Boden, Andrew F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. L26 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729L..26V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...50M</bibcode>
			<title>A New Concept for Direct Imaging and Spectral Characterization of Exoplanets in Multi-planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Matsuo, Taro; Traub, Wesley A.; Hattori, Makoto; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 50 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...50M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...98B</bibcode>
			<title>The Sloan Digital Sky Survey Data Release 7 Spectroscopic M Dwarf Catalog. II. Statistical Parallax Analysis</title>
			<authors>Bochanski, John J.; Hawley, Suzanne L.; West, Andrew A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 3, article id. 98 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...98B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1204M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation and activity in the WASP-10 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuhuser, R.; Tetzlaff, N.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Chen, W. P.; Walter, F.; Marka, C.; Baar, S.; Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.; Krushevska, V.; Tachihara, K.; Takahashi, H.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 2, pp. 1204-1212.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1204M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727..108W</bibcode>
			<title>Forming Habitable Planets Around Dwarf Stars: Application to OGLE-06-109L</title>
			<authors>Wang, Su; Zhou, Ji-Lin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 108 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727..108W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727..103T</bibcode>
			<title>The Anglo-Australian Planet Search. XX. A Solitary Ice-giant Planet Orbiting HD 102365</title>
			<authors>Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. Paul; Jones, Hugh R. A.; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; O'Toole, Simon; Bailey, Jeremy; Carter, Brad D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 103 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727..103T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A.135H</bibcode>
			<title>Radiative constraints on the habitability of exoplanets Gliese 581c and Gliese 581d</title>
			<authors>Hu, Y.; Ding, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A135</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A.135H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A.111M</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XXIV. Companions to HD 85390, HD 90156, and HD 103197: a Neptune analog and two intermediate-mass planets</title>
			<authors>Mordasini, C.; Mayor, M.; Udry, S.; Lovis, C.; Sgransan, D.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Bouchy, F.; Lo Curto, G.; Moutou, C.; Naef, D.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A111</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A.111M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.410...94G</bibcode>
			<title>Bayesian exoplanet tests of a new method for MCMC sampling in highly correlated model parameter spaces</title>
			<authors>Gregory, Philip C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 410, Issue 1, pp. 94-110.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.410...94G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726L...8P</bibcode>
			<title>A Palette of Climates for Gliese 581g</title>
			<authors>Pierrehumbert, R. T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id. L8 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726L...8P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...73H</bibcode>
			<title>The NASA-UC Eta-Earth Program. II. A Planet Orbiting HD 156668 with a Minimum Mass of Four Earth Masses</title>
			<authors>Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Wright, Jason T.; Henry, Gregory W.; Isaacson, Howard; Valenti, Jeff A.; Anderson, Jay; Piskunov, Nikolai E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 73 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...73H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...11D</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer Infrared Spectrograph Study of Debris Disks Around Planet-host Stars</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Beichman, C. A.; Carpenter, John M.; Bryden, Geoffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 1, article id. 11 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...11D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..83B</bibcode>
			<title>Primary and secondary eclipse spectroscopy with JWST: exploring the exoplanet parameter space</title>
			<authors>Belu, A. R.; Selsis, F.; Morales, J.-C.; Ribas, I.; Cossou, C.; Rauer, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A83</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..83B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..78C</bibcode>
			<title>A fourth planet orbiting upsilo Andromedae</title>
			<authors>Curiel, S.; Cant, J.; Georgiev, L.; Chvez, C. E.; Poveda, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A78</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..65P</bibcode>
			<title>The barycentric motion of exoplanet host stars. Tests of solar spin-orbit coupling</title>
			<authors>Perryman, M. A. C.; Schulze-Hartung, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A65</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..65P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..32G</bibcode>
			<title>An educated search for transiting habitable planets:. Targetting M dwarfs with known transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Bonfils, X.; Demory, B.-O.; Seager, S.; Deming, D.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A32</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..32G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..954V</bibcode>
			<title>The Lick-Carnegie Exoplanet Survey: A 3.1 M &amp;oplus; Planet in the Habitable Zone of the Nearby M3V Star Gliese 581</title>
			<authors>Vogt, Steven S.; Butler, R. Paul; Rivera, E. J.; Haghighipour, N.; Henry, Gregory W.; Williamson, Michael H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 954-965 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..954V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..15N</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extrasolar planets. XXIII. 8 planetary companions to low-activity solar-type stars</title>
			<authors>Naef, D.; Mayor, M.; Lo Curto, G.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Moutou, C.; Benz, W.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Hbrard, G.; Mordasini, C.; Perrier, C.; Boisse, I.; Sosnowska, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A15</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..15N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A..60L</bibcode>
			<title>Explicit expansion of the three-body disturbing function for arbitrary eccentricities and inclinations</title>
			<authors>Laskar, J.; Bou, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A60</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...522A..60L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A..23V</bibcode>
			<title>The extrasolar planet Gliese 581d: a potentially habitable planet?</title>
			<authors>von Paris, P.; Gebauer, S.; Godolt, M.; Grenfell, J. L.; Hedelt, P.; Kitzmann, D.; Patzer, A. B. C.; Rauer, H.; Stracke, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A23</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...522A..23V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A..22W</bibcode>
			<title>Is Gliese 581d habitable? Some constraints from radiative-convective climate modeling</title>
			<authors>Wordsworth, R. D.; Forget, F.; Selsis, F.; Madeleine, J.-B.; Millour, E.; Eymet, V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A22</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...522A..22W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1195T</bibcode>
			<title>A High-Contrast Imaging Survey of SIM Lite Planet Search Targets</title>
			<authors>Tanner, Angelle M.; Gelino, Christopher R.; Law, Nicholas M.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 896, pp.1195-1206</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1195T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722..937D</bibcode>
			<title>Radial Velocity Planets De-aliased: A New, Short Period for Super-Earth 55 Cnc e</title>
			<authors>Dawson, Rebekah I.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. 937-953 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722..937D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721.1184O</bibcode>
			<title>Eccentricity Trap: Trapping of Resonantly Interacting Planets Near the Disk Inner Edge</title>
			<authors>Ogihara, Masahiro; Duncan, Martin J.; Ida, Shigeru</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. 1184-1192 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...721.1184O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720L.113R</bibcode>
			<title>Metal-rich M-Dwarf Planet Hosts: Metallicities with K-band Spectra</title>
			<authors>Rojas-Ayala, Brbara; Covey, Kevin R.; Muirhead, Philip S.; Lloyd, James P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 720, Issue 1, pp. L113-L118 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720L.113R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1290G</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Parameters and Metallicities of Stars Hosting Jovian and Neptunian Mass Planets: A Possible Dependence of Planetary Mass on Metallicity</title>
			<authors>Ghezzi, L.; Cunha, K.; Smith, V. V.; de Arajo, F. X.; Schuler, S. C.; de la Reza, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1290-1302 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1290G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140..713N</bibcode>
			<title>Potential Members of Stellar Kinematical Groups within 20 pc of the Sun</title>
			<authors>Nakajima, Tadashi; Morino, Jun-Ichi; Fukagawa, Misato</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 3, pp. 713-722 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140..713N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A.105S</bibcode>
			<title>A physically-motivated photometric calibration of M dwarf metallicity</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, K. C.; Laughlin, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A105</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A.105S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2016Z</bibcode>
			<title>A hybrid mechanism forming a 2:1 librating-circulating resonant configuration in the planetary system</title>
			<authors>Zhang, Niu; Ji, Jianghui; Sun, Zhao</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2016-2022.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2016Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405..573P</bibcode>
			<title>On the dynamics of multiple systems of hot super-Earths and Neptunes: tidal circularization, resonance and the HD 40307 system</title>
			<authors>Papaloizou, John C. B.; Terquem, Caroline</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 1, pp. 573-592.</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405..573P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARep...54..550K</bibcode>
			<title>Resonance Properties of Extra-Solar Two-Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Kuznetsov, E. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Reports, Volume 54, Issue 6, pp.550-561</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARep...54..550K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..82F</bibcode>
			<title>The stability of ultra-compact planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Funk, B.; Wuchterl, G.; Schwarz, R.; Pilat-Lohinger, E.; Eggl, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A82</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..82F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...515A..98P</bibcode>
			<title>Coronal properties of planet-bearing stars</title>
			<authors>Poppenhaeger, K.; Robrade, J.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 515, id.A98</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...515A..98P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.1949K</bibcode>
			<title>UBV(RI)C JHK observations of Hipparcos-selected nearby stars</title>
			<authors>Koen, C.; Kilkenny, D.; van Wyk, F.; Marang, F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 4, pp. 1949-1968.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.1949K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.1089P</bibcode>
			<title>Target selection for the SUNS and DEBRIS surveys for debris discs in the solar neighbourhood</title>
			<authors>Phillips, N. M.; Greaves, J. S.; Dent, W. R. F.; Matthews, B. C.; Holland, W. S.; Wyatt, M. C.; Sibthorpe, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 3, pp. 1089-1101.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.1089P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403..731G</bibcode>
			<title>A Bayesian periodogram finds evidence for three planets in 47UrsaeMajoris</title>
			<authors>Gregory, Philip C.; Fischer, Debra A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 2, pp. 731-747.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403..731G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..974R</bibcode>
			<title>A Framework for Quantifying the Degeneracies of Exoplanet Interior Compositions</title>
			<authors>Rogers, L. A.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 2, pp. 974-991 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..974R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1724B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-11b: A Super-Neptune Planet Transiting a Bright K Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Pl, A.; Hartman, J.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Isaacson, H.; Howard, A.; Vogt, S.; Kovcs, Gbor; Fernandez, J.; Mor, A.; Stefanik, R. P.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1724-1745 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....139..504B</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation and Magnetic Activity in a Sample of M-Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Browning, Matthew K.; Basri, Gibor; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; West, Andrew A.; Zhang, Jiahao</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 139, Issue 2, pp. 504-518 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....139..504B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...510A.107M</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-band transit observations of the TrES-2b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Schrter, S.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Cordes, O.; Reif, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 510, id.A107</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...510A.107M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..168A</bibcode>
			<title>How Eccentric Orbital Solutions Can Hide Planetary Systems in 2:1 Resonant Orbits</title>
			<authors>Anglada-Escud, Guillem; Lpez-Morales, Mercedes; Chambers, John E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 168-178 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..168A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708.1366V</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth and Two Neptunes Orbiting the Nearby Sun-like Star 61 Virginis</title>
			<authors>Vogt, Steven S.; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Butler, R. Paul; O'Toole, Simon; Henry, Gregory W.; Rivera, Eugenio J.; Meschiari, Stefano; Laughlin, Gregory; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, Hugh R. A.; Bailey, Jeremy; Carter, Brad D.; Batygin, Konstantin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 2, pp. 1366-1375 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...708.1366V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..185..289R</bibcode>
			<title>The Infrared Telescope Facility (IRTF) Spectral Library: Cool Stars</title>
			<authors>Rayner, John T.; Cushing, Michael C.; Vacca, William D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 185, Issue 2, pp. 289-432 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..185..289R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705.1226B</bibcode>
			<title>Planets and Debris Disks: Results from a Spitzer/MIPS Search for Infrared Excess</title>
			<authors>Bryden, G.; Beichman, C. A.; Carpenter, J. M.; Rieke, G. H.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Werner, M. W.; Tanner, A. M.; Lawler, S. M.; Wyatt, M. C.; Trilling, D. E.; Su, K. Y. L.; Blaylock, M.; Stansberry, J. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 705, Issue 2, pp. 1226-1236 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705.1226B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..487M</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XVIII. An Earth-mass planet in the GJ 581 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Mayor, M.; Bonfils, X.; Forveille, T.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Beust, H.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.487-494</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..487M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506.1455L</bibcode>
			<title>Search for cold debris disks around M-dwarfs. II</title>
			<authors>Lestrade, J.-F.; Wyatt, M. C.; Bertoldi, F.; Menten, K. M.; Labaigt, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1455-1467</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506.1455L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704..975J</bibcode>
			<title>Rotational Velocities for M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, J. S.; Ramsey, L. W.; Jones, H. R. A.; Pavlenko, Y.; Gallardo, J.; Barnes, J. R.; Pinfield, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 2, pp. 975-988 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704..975J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...505..859Z</bibcode>
			<title>The M dwarf planet search programme at the ESO VLT + UVES. A search for terrestrial planets in the habitable zone of M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Zechmeister, M.; Krster, M.; Endl, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 505, Issue 2, 2009, pp.859-871</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...505..859Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.1922B</bibcode>
			<title>Radio Interferometric Planet Search. I. First Constraints On Planetary Companions For Nearby, Low-Mass Stars From Radio Astrometry</title>
			<authors>Bower, Geoffrey C.; Bolatto, Alberto; Ford, Eric B.; Kalas, Paul</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 1922-1939 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.1922B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700L..73K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Relationship Between Debris Disks and Planets</title>
			<authors>Kspl, gnes; Ardila, David R.; Mor, Attila; brahm, Pter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. L73-L77 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700L..73K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009NewAR..53..202Z</bibcode>
			<title>Gravitational lensing: From micro to nano</title>
			<authors>Zakharov, Alexander F.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 53, Issue 7-10, p. 202-208.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009NewAR..53..202Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700L..30B</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Limits to Planetary Habitability</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Rory; Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Raymond, Sean N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. L30-L33 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700L..30B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699L..97W</bibcode>
			<title>A Third Giant Planet Orbiting HIP 14810</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Fischer, D. A.; Ford, Eric B.; Veras, D.; Wang, J.; Henry, G. W.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 699, Issue 2, pp. L97-L101 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699L..97W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..933J</bibcode>
			<title>On the Metal Richness of M Dwarfs with Planets</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Apps, Kevin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 2, pp. 933-937 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..933J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..824O</bibcode>
			<title>N-Body Simulations of Planetary Accretion Around M Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Ogihara, Masahiro; Ida, Shigeru</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 824-838 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..824O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Msngr.136...39K</bibcode>
			<title>The UVES M Dwarf Planet Search Programme</title>
			<authors>Krster, Martin; Zechmeister, Mathias; Endl, Michael; Meyer, Eva</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 136, p. 39-43</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Msngr.136...39K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698L...1H</bibcode>
			<title>On the Correlation Between Metallicity and the Presence of Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Haywood, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 698, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698L...1H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696...75H</bibcode>
			<title>The NASA-UC Eta-Earth Program. I. A Super-Earth Orbiting HD 7924</title>
			<authors>Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Wright, Jason T.; Henry, Gregory W.; Giguere, Matthew J.; Isaacson, Howard; Valenti, Jeff A.; Anderson, Jay; Piskunov, Nikolai E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 1, pp. 75-83 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696...75H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..853R</bibcode>
			<title>Activity-induced radial velocity jitter in a flaring M dwarf</title>
			<authors>Reiners, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 3, 2009, pp.853-861</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..853R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121..309J</bibcode>
			<title>International Year of Astronomy Invited Review on Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 878, pp.309-315</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121..309J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...695.1006B</bibcode>
			<title>The HD 40307 Planetary System: Super-Earths or Mini-Neptunes?</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Rory; Jackson, Brian; Raymond, Sean N.; West, Andrew A.; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 695, Issue 2, pp. 1006-1011 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...695.1006B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...497..583Z</bibcode>
			<title>Additional planets in the habitable zone of Gliese 581?</title>
			<authors>Zollinger, R.; Armstrong, J. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 497, Issue 2, 2009, pp.583-587</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...497..583Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693.1084W</bibcode>
			<title>Ten New and Updated Multiplanet Systems and a Survey of Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Upadhyay, S.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Ford, Eric B.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 2, pp. 1084-1099 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693.1084W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692.1590M</bibcode>
			<title>The Use of Absorption Cells as a Wavelength Reference for Precision Radial Velocity Measurements in the Near-Infrared</title>
			<authors>Mahadevan, Suvrath; Ge, Jian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 692, Issue 2, pp. 1590-1596 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692.1590M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AJ....137.3297W</bibcode>
			<title>Tracers of Chromospheric Structure. I. Observations of Ca II K and Halpha in M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Hawley, Suzanne L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 137, Issue 2, pp. 3297-3313 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AJ....137.3297W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392....2M</bibcode>
			<title>Secular dynamics of a coplanar, non-resonant planetary system under the general relativity and quadrupole moment perturbations</title>
			<authors>Migaszewski, Cezary; Gozdziewski, Krzysztof</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 1, pp. 2-18.</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392....2M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690.1056M</bibcode>
			<title>The Atmospheric Signatures of Super-Earths: How to Distinguish Between Hydrogen-Rich and Hydrogen-Poor Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Miller-Ricci, Eliza; Seager, Sara; Sasselov, Dimitar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 2, pp. 1056-1067 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690.1056M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690..743B</bibcode>
			<title>A Jupiter-Like Planet Orbiting the Nearby M dwarf GJ 832</title>
			<authors>Bailey, Jeremy; Butler, R. Paul; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, Hugh R. A.; O'Toole, Simon; Carter, Brad D.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 1, pp. 743-747 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690..743B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493..645F</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XIV. Gl 176b, a super-Earth rather than a Neptune, and at a different period</title>
			<authors>Forveille, T.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Gillon, M.; Udry, S.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 2, 2009, pp.645-650</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493..645F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493..639M</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XIII. A planetary system with 3 super-Earths (4.2, 6.9, and 9.2 M&amp;oplus;)</title>
			<authors>Mayor, M.; Udry, S.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Bouchy, F.; Mordasini, C.; Segransan, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 2, 2009, pp.639-644</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493..639M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PABei..27..247J</bibcode>
			<title>Current progress on astrometric catalogs and sky surveys.</title>
			<authors>Jin, W.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 27, 247-269 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PABei..27..247J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008Msngr.134...14M</bibcode>
			<title>Report on the JENAM 2008 Meeting Symposium Science with the E-ELT</title>
			<authors>Monnet, Guy</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 134, p. 14-18</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008Msngr.134...14M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389..585C</bibcode>
			<title>M dwarfs: effective temperatures, radii and metallicities</title>
			<authors>Casagrande, Luca; Flynn, Chris; Bessell, Michael</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 2, pp. 585-607.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389..585C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008PASP..120..860B</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Monitoring of Ultracool Dwarfs: Prospects for Searching for Transiting Companions</title>
			<authors>Blake, Cullen H.; Bloom, Joshua S.; Latham, David W.; Szentgyorgyi, Andrew H.; Skrutskie, Michael F.; Falco, Emilio E.; Starr, Dan S.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 120, Issue 870, pp. 860-871.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008PASP..120..860B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.388..789M</bibcode>
			<title>A secular theory of coplanar, non-resonant planetary system</title>
			<authors>Migaszewski, Cezary; Gozdziewski, Krzysztof</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 388, Issue 2, pp. 789-802.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.388..789M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1264K</bibcode>
			<title>Planet formation around stars of various masses: Hot Super-Earths</title>
			<authors>Kennedy, Grant M.; Kenyon, Scott J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1264-1276.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1264K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...487..373S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic parameters for 451 stars in the HARPS GTO planet search program. Stellar [Fe/H] and the frequency of exo-Neptunes</title>
			<authors>Sousa, S. G.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Udry, S.; Casagrande, L.; Israelian, G.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Monteiro, M. J. P. F. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 487, Issue 1, 2008, pp.373-381</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...487..373S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008NewAR..52..154S</bibcode>
			<title>Extra-solar planets: Detection methods and results</title>
			<authors>Santos, Nuno C.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 52, Issue 2-5, p. 154-166.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008NewAR..52..154S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AJ....135.2194S</bibcode>
			<title>Further Constraints on the Presence of a Debris Disk in the Multiplanet System Gliese 876</title>
			<authors>Shankland, P. D.; Blank, D. L.; Boboltz, D. A.; Lazio, T. J. W.; White, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 135, Issue 6, pp. 2194-2198 (2008).</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AJ....135.2194S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1347P</bibcode>
			<title>Jupiter and Super-Earth embedded in a gaseous disc</title>
			<authors>Podlewska, E.; Szuszkiewicz, E.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1347-1354.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1347P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678..463I</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical Mass of GJ 802B: A Brown Dwarf in a Triple System</title>
			<authors>Ireland, M. J.; Kraus, A.; Martinache, F.; Lloyd, J. P.; Tuthill, P. G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 1, pp. 463-471.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678..463I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...483..317K</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on additional planetary companions to OGLE 2005-BLG-390L</title>
			<authors>Kubas, D.; Cassan, A.; Dominik, M.; Bennett, D. P.; Wambsganss, J.; Brillant, S.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Albrow, M. D.; Batista, V.; Bode, M.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Calitz, H.; Cook, K. H.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu, P.; Greenhill, J.; Hill, K.; Hoffman, M.; Horne, K.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kains, N.; Kane, S.; Marquette, J. B.; Martin, R.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Tsapras, Y.; Vinter, C.; Williams, A.; Woller, K.; Zub, M.; PLANET/RoboNet Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 483, Issue 1, 2008, pp.317-324</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...483..317K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482..665G</bibcode>
			<title>Are retrograde resonances possible in multi-planet systems?</title>
			<authors>Gayon, J.; Bois, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 2, 2008, pp.665-672</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482..665G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677L..59R</bibcode>
			<title>A ~5 M&amp;oplus; Super-Earth Orbiting GJ 436? The Power of Near-Grazing Transits</title>
			<authors>Ribas, Ignasi; Font-Ribera, Andreu; Beaulieu, Jean-Philippe</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. L59-L62.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677L..59R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677..593W</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the Near-UV Environment of M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Hawley, Suzanne L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. 593-606.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677..593W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJS..175..191P</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Variability in the 2MASS Calibration Fields: A Search for Planetary Transit Candidates</title>
			<authors>Plavchan, Peter; Jura, M.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Cutri, Roc M.; Gallagher, S. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 175, Issue 1, pp. 191-228.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJS..175..191P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.384..663R</bibcode>
			<title>Observable consequences of planet formation models in systems with close-in terrestrial planets</title>
			<authors>Raymond, Sean N.; Barnes, Rory; Mandell, Avi M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 384, Issue 2, pp. 663-674.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.384..663R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673.1165E</bibcode>
			<title>An msini = 24 M&amp;oplus; Planetary Companion to the Nearby M Dwarf GJ 176</title>
			<authors>Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 2, pp. 1165-1168.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673.1165E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...479..579P</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray induced mass loss effects on exoplanets orbiting dM stars</title>
			<authors>Penz, T.; Micela, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 479, Issue 2, February IV 2008, pp.579-584</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...479..579P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...479..277B</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical evolution of the Gliese 581 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 479, Issue 1, February III 2008, pp.277-282</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...479..277B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...478..507M</bibcode>
			<title>The effect of activity on stellar temperatures and radii</title>
			<authors>Morales, J. C.; Ribas, I.; Jordi, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 478, Issue 2, February I 2008, pp.507-512</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...478..507M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...672.1202B</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a Third Planet in the HD 74156 System Using the Hobby-Eberly Telescope</title>
			<authors>Bean, Jacob L.; McArthur, Barbara E.; Benedict, G. Fritz; Armstrong, Amber</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 672, Issue 2, pp. 1202-1208.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...672.1202B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007Icar..192..582B</bibcode>
			<title>UV habitable zones around M stars</title>
			<authors>Buccino, Andrea P.; Lemarchand, Guillermo A.; Mauas, Pablo J. D.</authors>
			<journal>Icarus, Volume 192, Issue 2, p. 582-587.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007Icar..192..582B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...476.1373S</bibcode>
			<title>Habitable planets around the star Gliese 581?</title>
			<authors>Selsis, F.; Kasting, J. F.; Levrard, B.; Paillet, J.; Ribas, I.; Delfosse, X.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 476, Issue 3, December IV 2007, pp.1373-1387</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...476.1373S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...476.1365V</bibcode>
			<title>The habitability of super-Earths in Gliese 581</title>
			<authors>von Bloh, W.; Bounama, C.; Cuntz, M.; Franck, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 476, Issue 3, December IV 2007, pp.1365-1371</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...476.1365V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.381.1607G</bibcode>
			<title>A Bayesian periodogram finds evidence for three planets in HD 11964</title>
			<authors>Gregory, P. C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 381, Issue 4, pp. 1607-1616.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.381.1607G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.381.1597P</bibcode>
			<title>The potential for Earth-mass planet formation around brown dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Lodato, Giuseppe</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 381, Issue 4, pp. 1597-1606.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.381.1597P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...670..833J</bibcode>
			<title>A New Planet around an M Dwarf: Revealing a Correlation between Exoplanets and Stellar Mass</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Vogt, Steven S.; Wright, Jason T.; Peek, Kathryn M. G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 670, Issue 1, pp. 833-840.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...670..833J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669..606R</bibcode>
			<title>A Decreased Probability of Habitable Planet Formation around Low-Mass Stars</title>
			<authors>Raymond, Sean N.; Scalo, John; Meadows, Victoria S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 1, pp. 606-614.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669..606R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...474..345D</bibcode>
			<title>The spectroscopic binary system Gl 375. I. Orbital parameters and chromospheric activity</title>
			<authors>Daz, R. F.; Gonzlez, J. F.; Cincunegui, C.; Mauas, P. J. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 474, Issue 2, November I 2007, pp.345-353</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...474..345D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...474..293B</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. X. A m sin i = 11 M_&amp;oplus; planet around the nearby spotted M dwarf GJ 674</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Mayor, M.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Gillon, M.; Perrier, C.; Udry, S.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 474, Issue 1, October IV 2007, pp.293-299</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...474..293B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.380.1261K</bibcode>
			<title>Further observations of Hipparcos red stars and standards for UBV(RI)C photometry</title>
			<authors>Kilkenny, D.; Koen, C.; van Wyk, F.; Marang, F.; Cooper, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 380, Issue 3, pp. 1261-1270.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.380.1261K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...666.1198B</bibcode>
			<title>Multiepoch Radial Velocity Observations of L Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Blake, Cullen H.; Charbonneau, David; White, Russel J.; Marley, Mark S.; Saumon, Didier</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 666, Issue 2, pp. 1198-1204.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...666.1198B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.378.1418W</bibcode>
			<title>A possible stellar metallic enhancement in post-T Tauri stars by a planetesimal bombardment</title>
			<authors>Winter, O. C.; de La Reza, R.; Domingos, R. C.; Boldrin, L. A. G.; Chavero, C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 378, Issue 4, pp. 1418-1426.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.378.1418W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...469L..43U</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XI. Super-Earths (5 and 8 M{&amp;oplus;}) in a 3-planet system</title>
			<authors>Udry, S.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Mayor, M.; Perrier, C.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 469, Issue 3, July III 2007, pp.L43-L47</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...469L..43U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662.1282M</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Formation Scenarios Revisited: Core-Accretion versus Disk Instability</title>
			<authors>Matsuo, T.; Shibai, H.; Ootsubo, T.; Tamura, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 2, pp. 1282-1292.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662.1282M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..823M</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of Earth-like Planets During and After Giant Planet Migration</title>
			<authors>Mandell, Avi M.; Raymond, Sean N.; Sigurdsson, Steinn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 823-844.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..823M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASP..119...90M</bibcode>
			<title>The M Dwarf GJ 436 and its Neptune-Mass Planet</title>
			<authors>Maness, H. L.; Marcy, G. W.; Ford, E. B.; Hauschildt, P. H.; Shreve, A. T.; Basri, G. B.; Butler, R. P.; Vogt, S. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 119, Issue 851, pp. 90-101.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASP..119...90M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...462..345D</bibcode>
			<title>Properties of planets in binary systems. The role of binary separation</title>
			<authors>Desidera, S.; Barbieri, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 462, Issue 1, January IV 2007, pp.345-353</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...462..345D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1685B</bibcode>
			<title>A Long-Period Jupiter-Mass Planet Orbiting the Nearby M Dwarf GJ 849</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. Paul; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Wright, Jason T.; Vogt, Steven S.; Fischer, Debra A.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 850, pp. 1685-1689.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1685B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653L..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Metallicities of M Dwarf Planet Hosts from Spectral Synthesis</title>
			<authors>Bean, Jacob L.; Benedict, G. Fritz; Endl, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 1, pp. L65-L68.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653L..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653..700S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Search for Transits of the Planets Orbiting Gliese 876</title>
			<authors>Shankland, P. D.; Rivera, E. J.; Laughlin, G.; Blank, D. L.; Price, A.; Gary, B.; Bissinger, R.; Ringwald, F.; White, G.; Henry, G. W.; McGee, P.; Wolf, A. S.; Carter, B.; Lee, S.; Biggs, J.; Monard, B.; Ashley, M. C. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 1, pp. 700-707.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653..700S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460..733L</bibcode>
			<title>Search for cold debris disks around M-dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Lestrade, J.-F.; Wyatt, M. C.; Bertoldi, F.; Dent, W. R. F.; Menten, K. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 3, December IV 2006, pp.733-741</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460..733L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1506L</bibcode>
			<title>Limits to Transits of the Neptune-Mass Planet Orbiting GJ 581</title>
			<authors>Lpez-Morales, Mercedes; Morrell, Nidia I.; Butler, R. Paul; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 849, pp. 1506-1509.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1506L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AstL...32..759G</bibcode>
			<title>Pulkovo Compilation of Radial Velocities for 35 495 Hipparcos stars in a common system</title>
			<authors>Gontcharov, G. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Letters, Vol. 32, Issue 11, p.759-771</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AstL...32..759G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1010J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of Known Exoplanetary Systems Based on Measured Stellar Properties</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick; Underwood, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1019.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1010J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649..436E</bibcode>
			<title>Exploring the Frequency of Close-in Jovian Planets around M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Krster, Martin; Paulson, Diane B.; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Tull, Robert G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 1, pp. 436-443.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649..436E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..505B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of Nearby Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. P.; Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Penny, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 505-522.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..505B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644L..79B</bibcode>
			<title>Rapid Formation of Super-Earths around M Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 1, pp. L79-L82.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644L..79B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118..706P</bibcode>
			<title>Differential Radial Velocities and Stellar Parameters of Nearby Young Stars</title>
			<authors>Paulson, Diane B.; Yelda, Sylvana</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 843, pp. 706-715.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118..706P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...643..501B</bibcode>
			<title>Rapid Formation of Gas Giant Planets around M Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 643, Issue 1, pp. 501-508.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...643..501B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118..617R</bibcode>
			<title>Ca II H and K Chromospheric Emission Lines in Late-K and M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Rauscher, Emily; Marcy, Geoffrey W.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 842, pp. 617-635.</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118..617R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006Msngr.123...21K</bibcode>
			<title>In Search of Terrestrial Planets in the Habitable Zone of M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Kurster, M.; Endl, M.; Rodler, F.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, volume 123, page 21</journal>
			<date>3/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006Msngr.123...21K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...447..361U</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. V. A 14 Earth-masses planet orbiting HD 4308</title>
			<authors>Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Benz, W.; Bertaux, J.-L.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Mordasini, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Sivan, J.-P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 447, Issue 1, February III 2006, pp.361-367</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...447..361U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AN....327....9H</bibcode>
			<title>Monitor: transiting planets and brown dwarfs in star forming regions and young open clusters</title>
			<authors>Hodgkin, S. T.; Irwin, J. M.; Aigrain, S.; Hebb, L.; Moraux, E.; Irwin, M. J.; Monitor Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.327, Issue 1, p.9-13</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AN....327....9H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...443L..15B</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. VI. A Neptune-mass planet around the nearby M dwarf Gl 581</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Forveille, T.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Perrier, C.; Bouchy, F.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 443, Issue 3, December I 2005, pp.L15-L18</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...443L..15B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...442..635B</bibcode>
			<title>Metallicity of M dwarfs. I. A photometric calibration and the impact on the mass-luminosity relation at the bottom of the main sequence</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Udry, S.; Santos, N. C.; Forveille, T.; S gransan, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 442, Issue 2, November I 2005, pp.635-642</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...442..635B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005AJ....129.1954J</bibcode>
			<title>The Solar Neighborhood. XIII. Parallax Results from the CTIOPI 0.9 Meter Program: Stars with mu &gt;= 1.0" yr-1 (MOTION Sample)</title>
			<authors>Jao, Wei-Chun; Henry, Todd J.; Subasavage, John P.; Brown, Misty A.; Ianna, Philip A.; Bartlett, Jennifer L.; Costa, Edgardo; Mndez, Ren A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 129, Issue 4, pp. 1954-1967.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005AJ....129.1954J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.355..363L</bibcode>
			<title>The spectroscopic characteristics of intermediate-aged pre-main-sequence stars: the eta Chamaeleontis cluster</title>
			<authors>Lyo, A.-Ran; Lawson, Warrick A.; Bessell, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 355, Issue 2, pp. 363-373.</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.355..363L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004PASP..116.1105W</bibcode>
			<title>The chi Factor: Determining the Strength of Activity in Low-Mass Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Hawley, Suzanne L.; West, Andrew A.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 116, Issue 826, pp. 1105-1110.</journal>
			<date>11/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004PASP..116.1105W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJS..152..261W</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric Ca II Emission in Nearby F, G, K, and M Stars</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, S. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 152, Issue 2, pp. 261-295.</journal>
			<date>6/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJS..152..261W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJS..149..423T</bibcode>
			<title>Target Selection for SETI. II. Tycho-2 Dwarfs, Old Open Clusters, and the Nearest 100 Stars</title>
			<authors>Turnbull, Margaret C.; Tarter, Jill C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 149, Issue 2, pp. 423-436.</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJS..149..423T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...582.1011S</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Astrometry and Photometry for the Luyten Catalog. II. Faint Stars and the Revised Catalog</title>
			<authors>Salim, Samir; Gould, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 582, Issue 2, pp. 1011-1031.</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...582.1011S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003AJ....125..332J</bibcode>
			<title>The Solar Neighborhood. VII. Discovery and Characterization of Nearby Multiples in the CTIO Parallax Investigation</title>
			<authors>Jao, Wei-Chun; Henry, Todd J.; Subasavage, John P.; Bean, Jacob L.; Costa, Edgardo; Ianna, Philip A.; Mndez, Ren A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 125, Issue 1, pp. 332-342.</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003AJ....125..332J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...397..997P</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos red stars in the HpVT2 and VIC systems</title>
			<authors>Platais, I.; Pourbaix, D.; Jorissen, A.; Makarov, V. V.; Berdnikov, L. N.; Samus, N. N.; Lloyd Evans, T.; Lebzelter, T.; Sperauskas, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.397, p.997-1010 (2003)</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...397..997P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJS..141..503N</bibcode>
			<title>Radial Velocities for 889 Late-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Nidever, David L.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Fischer, Debra A.; Vogt, Steven S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 141, Issue 2, pp. 503-522.</journal>
			<date>8/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJS..141..503N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.334...20K</bibcode>
			<title>UBV(RI)C photometry of Hipparcos red stars</title>
			<authors>Koen, C.; Kilkenny, D.; van Wyk, F.; Cooper, D.; Marang, F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 334, Issue 1, pp. 20-38.</journal>
			<date>7/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.334...20K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJS..141..187B</bibcode>
			<title>Revised Coordinates and Proper Motions of the Stars in the Luyten Half-Second Catalog</title>
			<authors>Bakos, Gspr .; Sahu, Kailash C.; Nmeth, Pter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 141, Issue 1, pp. 187-193.</journal>
			<date>7/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJS..141..187B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AJ....123.3356G</bibcode>
			<title>The Palomar/MSU Nearby Star Spectroscopic Survey. III. Chromospheric Activity, M Dwarf Ages, and the Local Star Formation History</title>
			<authors>Gizis, John E.; Reid, I. Neill; Hawley, Suzanne L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 123, Issue 6, pp. 3356-3369.</journal>
			<date>6/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AJ....123.3356G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AJ....123.2027H</bibcode>
			<title>A Near-Infrared, Wide-Field, Proper-Motion Search for Brown Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Hinz, Joannah L.; McCarthy, Donald W., Jr.; Simons, Doug A.; Henry, Todd J.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; McGuire, Patrick C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 123, Issue 4, pp. 2027-2032.</journal>
			<date>4/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AJ....123.2027H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AJ....123.2002H</bibcode>
			<title>The Solar Neighborhood. VI. New Southern Nearby Stars Identified by Optical Spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Henry, Todd J.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Barto, Todd C.; Golimowski, David A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 123, Issue 4, pp. 2002-2009.</journal>
			<date>4/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AJ....123.2002H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001MNRAS.328...45M</bibcode>
			<title>Late-type members of young stellar kinematic groups - I. Single stars</title>
			<authors>Montes, D.; Lpez-Santiago, J.; Glvez, M. C.; Fernndez-Figueroa, M. J.; De Castro, E.; Cornide, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 328, Issue 1, pp. 45-63.</journal>
			<date>11/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001MNRAS.328...45M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001AJ....121.2189O</bibcode>
			<title>A Coronagraphic Survey for Companions of Stars within 8 Parsecs</title>
			<authors>Oppenheimer, B. R.; Golimowski, D. A.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Matthews, K.; Nakajima, T.; Creech-Eakman, M.; Durrance, S. T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 121, Issue 4, pp. 2189-2211.</journal>
			<date>4/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001AJ....121.2189O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...367..521P</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of Apparent Diameters and Absolute Radii of Stars (CADARS) - Third edition - Comments and statistics</title>
			<authors>Pasinetti Fracassini, L. E.; Pastori, L.; Covino, S.; Pozzi, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.367, p.521-524 (2001)</journal>
			<date>2/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...367..521P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...348..524B</bibcode>
			<title>Barnes-Evans relations for late-type giants and dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Beuermann, K.; Baraffe, I.; Hauschildt, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.348, p.524-532 (1999)</journal>
			<date>8/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...348..524B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...339..518B</bibcode>
			<title>Are the red dwarfs in cataclysmic variables main-sequence stars?</title>
			<authors>Beuermann, K.; Baraffe, I.; Kolb, U.; Weichhold, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.339, p.518-524 (1998)</journal>
			<date>11/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...339..518B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...331..581D</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation and chromospheric activity in field M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Perrier, C.; Mayor, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.331, p.581-595 (1998)</journal>
			<date>3/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...331..581D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998MNRAS.294...93K</bibcode>
			<title>Supplementary southern standards for UBV(RI)c photometry</title>
			<authors>Kilkenny, D.; van Wyk, F.; Roberts, G.; Marang, F.; Cooper, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, vol. 294, p. 93</journal>
			<date>2/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998MNRAS.294...93K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997PASP..109.1193S</bibcode>
			<title>The Mount Wilson Halo Mapping Project 1975-1985 I: The UBV(RI)_M_W Photometric System Compared with Other Standard Systems: The Adopted Trigonometric HR Diagram in (R-I)_M_W and (V-I)_M_W</title>
			<authors>Sandage, A.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, v.109, p.1193-1214</journal>
			<date>11/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997PASP..109.1193S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...484..499S</bibcode>
			<title>The FeH Wing-Ford Band in Spectra of M Stars</title>
			<authors>Schiavon, Ricardo P.; Barbuy, B.; Singh, Patan D.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.484, p.499</journal>
			<date>7/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...484..499S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997AJ....113.2246R</bibcode>
			<title>Low-Mass Binaries and the Stellar Luminosity Function</title>
			<authors>Reid, I. Neill; Gizis, John E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.113, p.2246</journal>
			<date>6/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997AJ....113.2246R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997IBVS.4471....1K</bibcode>
			<title>The 73rd Name-List of Variable Stars</title>
			<authors>Kazarovets, E. V.; Samus, N. N.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4471, 1.</journal>
			<date>4/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997IBVS.4471....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997MNRAS.285...95D</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared spectroscopy of cataclysmic variables - II. Intermediate polars</title>
			<authors>Dhillon, V. S.; Marsh, T. R.; Duck, S. R.; Rosen, S. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 285, Issue 1, pp. 95-101.</journal>
			<date>2/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997MNRAS.285...95D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AJ....112.2799H</bibcode>
			<title>The Palomar/MSU Nearby Star Spectroscopic Survey.II.The Southern M Dwarfs and Investigation of Magnetic Activity</title>
			<authors>Hawley, Suzanne L.; Gizis, John E.; Reid, I. Neill</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.112, p.2799</journal>
			<date>12/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AJ....112.2799H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AJ....112.2300W</bibcode>
			<title>Photometry of Stars with Large Proper Motion</title>
			<authors>Weis, Edward W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.112, p.2300</journal>
			<date>11/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AJ....112.2300W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AJ....112.2238S</bibcode>
			<title>The Solar Neighborhood.III.A Near-Infrared Search for Widely Separated Low-Mass Binaries</title>
			<authors>Simons, D. A.; Henry, Todd J.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.112, p.2238</journal>
			<date>11/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AJ....112.2238S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;AS..114..269D</bibcode>
			<title>Vitesses radiales. Catalogue WEB: Wilson Evans Batten. Subtittle: Radial velocities: The Wilson-Evans-Batten catalogue.</title>
			<authors>Duflot, M.; Figon, P.; Meyssonnier, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.114, p.269</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26AS..114..269D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995AJ....110.1838R</bibcode>
			<title>The Palomar/MSU Nearby-Star Spectroscopic Survey. I. The Northern M Dwarfs -Bandstrengths and Kinematics</title>
			<authors>Reid, I. Neill; Hawley, Suzanne L.; Gizis, John E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.110, p.1838</journal>
			<date>10/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995AJ....110.1838R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJ...450..401F</bibcode>
			<title>Correlations of Coronal X-Ray Emission with Activity, Mass, and Age of the Nearby K and M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Fleming, Thomas A.; Schmitt, Juergen H. M. M.; Giampapa, Mark S.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.450, p.401</journal>
			<date>9/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJ...450..401F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJ...450..392S</bibcode>
			<title>The X-Ray View of the Low-Mass Stars in the Solar Neighborhood</title>
			<authors>Schmitt, Juergen H. M. M.; Fleming, Thomas A.; Giampapa, Mark S.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.450, p.392</journal>
			<date>9/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJ...450..392S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995gcts.book.....V</bibcode>
			<title>The general catalogue of trigonometric [stellar] parallaxes</title>
			<authors>van Altena, W. F.; Lee, J. T.; Hoffleit, E. D.</authors>
			<journal>New Haven, CT: Yale University Observatory, |c1995, 4th ed., completely revised and enlarged</journal>
			<date>0/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995gcts.book.....V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994A&amp;A...291..517M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of EUV emission from the low activity dwarf HD 4628: Evidence for a cool corona</title>
			<authors>Mathioudakis, M.; Drake, J. J.; Vedder, P. W.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Bowyer, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 291, no. 2, p. 517-520</journal>
			<date>11/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994A%26A...291..517M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994AJ....108.1437H</bibcode>
			<title>The solar neighborhood, 1: Standard spectral types (K5-M8) for northern dwarfs within eight parsecs</title>
			<authors>Henry, Todd J.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Simons, Douglas A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, vol. 108, no. 4, p. 1437-1444</journal>
			<date>10/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994AJ....108.1437H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994ApJS...93..287W</bibcode>
			<title>A volume-limited ROSAT survey of extreme ultraviolet emission from all nondegenerate stars within 10 parsecs</title>
			<authors>Wood, Brian E.; Brown, Alexander; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Kellett, Barry J.; Bromage, Gordon E.; Hodgkin, Simon T.; Pye, John P.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 93, no. 1, p. 287-307</journal>
			<date>7/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994ApJS...93..287W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994ApJ...428..797N</bibcode>
			<title>A coronagraphic search for brown dwarfs around nearby stars</title>
			<authors>Nakajima, T.; Durrance, S. T.; Golimowski, D. A.; Kulkarni, S. R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, vol. 428, no. 2, pt. 1, p. 797-804</journal>
			<date>6/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994ApJ...428..797N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994AJ....107.1135W</bibcode>
			<title>Long term variability in dwarf M stars</title>
			<authors>Weis, Edward W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 107, no. 3, p. 1135-1140</journal>
			<date>3/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994AJ....107.1135W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;A...280..181M</bibcode>
			<title>Far infrared properties of late type dwarfs. Infrared fluxes of K &amp; M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Mathioudakis, M.; Doyle, J. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 280, no. 1, p. 181-194</journal>
			<date>12/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26A...280..181M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993AJ....106..773H</bibcode>
			<title>The mass-luminosity relation for stars of mass 1.0 to 0.08 solar mass</title>
			<authors>Henry, Todd J.; McCarthy, Donald W., Jr.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 106, no. 2, p. 773-789.</journal>
			<date>8/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993AJ....106..773H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;AS..100..343P</bibcode>
			<title>The importance of surface inhomogeneities for K and M dwarf chromospheric fluxes</title>
			<authors>Panagi, P. M.; Mathioudakis, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 100, no. 2, p. 343-369.</journal>
			<date>8/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26AS..100..343P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993AJ....105.1962W</bibcode>
			<title>Photometry of dwarf K and M stars</title>
			<authors>Weis, Edward W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 105, no. 5, p. 1962-1966.</journal>
			<date>5/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993AJ....105.1962W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJS...82..351L</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared colors of low-mass stars</title>
			<authors>Leggett, S. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 82, no. 1, Sept. 1992, p. 351-394.</journal>
			<date>9/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJS...82..351L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJ...396..178F</bibcode>
			<title>Multiplicity among M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 396, no. 1, Sept. 1, 1992, p. 178-194.</journal>
			<date>9/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJ...396..178F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJ...390..550M</bibcode>
			<title>The rotation of M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Chen, Grace H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 390, no. 2, May 10, 1992, p. 550-559.</journal>
			<date>5/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJ...390..550M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990MNRAS.246..637F</bibcode>
			<title>The 8190-A Sodium Doublet in Cataclysmic Variables - Part Two - too Cool for Comfort</title>
			<authors>Friend, M. T.; Martin, J. S.; Connon-Smith, R.; Jones, D. H. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 246, NO.4/OCT15, P. 637, 1990</journal>
			<date>10/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990MNRAS.246..637F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990A&amp;AS...85..971P</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of Variable or Suspected Stars Nearby the Sun</title>
			<authors>Petit, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, Vol.85, NO. 2/OCT, P. 971, 1990</journal>
			<date>10/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990A%26AS...85..971P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990A&amp;AS...83..357B</bibcode>
			<title>BVRI photometry of the Gliese Catalogue stars</title>
			<authors>Bessel, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 83, no. 2, May 1990, p. 357-378.</journal>
			<date>5/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990A%26AS...83..357B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989A&amp;A...224..179M</bibcode>
			<title>Flux-flux relation - MG II H and K versus X-rays in dwarf M and K stars</title>
			<authors>Mathioudakis, M.; Doyle, J. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 224, no. 1-2, Oct. 1989, p. 179-186.</journal>
			<date>10/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989A%26A...224..179M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989ApJ...344..441M</bibcode>
			<title>A search for substellar companions to low-mass stars</title>
			<authors>Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Benitz, Karsten J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 344, Sept. 1, 1989, p. 441-453.</journal>
			<date>9/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989ApJ...344..441M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989ApJ...343..400M</bibcode>
			<title>Far-infrared properties of flare stars and dM stars</title>
			<authors>Mullan, D. J.; Stencel, R. E.; Backman, D. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 343, Aug. 1, 1989, p. 400-408.</journal>
			<date>8/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989ApJ...343..400M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989A&amp;A...218..195D</bibcode>
			<title>H-alpha versus X-ray luminosity in dwarf M stars</title>
			<authors>Doyle, J. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 218, no. 1-2, July 1989, p. 195-198.</journal>
			<date>7/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989A%26A...218..195D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989AJ.....97..923C</bibcode>
			<title>The 77-81 intermediate-band photometric system</title>
			<authors>Cook, Kem Holland; Aaronson, Marc</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 97, March 1989, p. 923-934.</journal>
			<date>3/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989AJ.....97..923C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989SAAOC..13...29L</bibcode>
			<title>UBV(RI)c photometry of faint nearby stars.</title>
			<authors>Laing, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>South African Astronomical Observatory Circular, No. 13, p. 29 - 37</journal>
			<date>0/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989SAAOC..13...29L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988AJ.....96.1710W</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric parallaxes for selected stars of color class M from the NLTT Catalog. IV - The declination zone +45 to +90 deg</title>
			<authors>Weis, Edward W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 96, Nov. 1988, p. 1710-1722.</journal>
			<date>11/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988AJ.....96.1710W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988MNRAS.234.1065L</bibcode>
			<title>The infrared luminosity function for low-mass stars</title>
			<authors>Leggett, S. K.; Hawkins, M. R. S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 234, Oct. 15, 1988, p. 1065-1090.</journal>
			<date>10/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988MNRAS.234.1065L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988PASP..100..749B</bibcode>
			<title>Photometry of Dwarf K and M Stars</title>
			<authors>Booth, John; Caruso, Joseph; Weis, E. W.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific v.100, p.749</journal>
			<date>6/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988PASP..100..749B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987AJ.....94..150H</bibcode>
			<title>H-alpha photometry of dwarf K and M stars</title>
			<authors>Herbst, William; Layden, Andrew C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 94, July 1987, p. 150-157. Research supported by the Research Corp.</journal>
			<date>7/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987AJ.....94..150H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987PASP...99..490M</bibcode>
			<title>Radial velocities of M dwarf stars</title>
			<authors>Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Lindsay, Victoria; Wilson, Karen</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 99, June 1987, p. 490-496.</journal>
			<date>6/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987PASP...99..490M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987AJ.....93..451W</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric parallaxes for selected stars of color class M from the NLTT catalog. III - The declination zone +20 deg to +45 deg</title>
			<authors>Weis, Edward W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 93, Feb. 1987, p. 451-466.</journal>
			<date>2/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987AJ.....93..451W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986ApJS...61..531S</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric activity, kinematics, and metallicities of nearby M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Stauffer, J. R.; Hartmann, L. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 61, July 1986, p. 531-568.</journal>
			<date>7/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986ApJS...61..531S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986AJ.....92..139S</bibcode>
			<title>Dwarf K and M stars of high proper motion found in a hemispheric survey</title>
			<authors>Stephenson, C. B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 92, July 1986, p. 139-165.</journal>
			<date>7/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986AJ.....92..139S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986AJ.....91..808H</bibcode>
			<title>The luminosities of M supergiants and the distances to M101, NGC 2403, and M81</title>
			<authors>Humphreys, R. M.; Aaronson, M.; Lebofsky, M.; McAlary, C. W.; Strom, S. E.; Capps, R. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 91, April 1986, p. 808-821.</journal>
			<date>4/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986AJ.....91..808H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985ApJS...59..197B</bibcode>
			<title>G. P. Kuiper's spectral classifications of proper-motion stars</title>
			<authors>Bidelman, W. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 59, Oct. 1985, p. 197-227.</journal>
			<date>10/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985ApJS...59..197B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984ApJS...55..289W</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric parallaxes for selected stars of color class M from the NLTT catalog</title>
			<authors>Weis, E. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 55, June 1984, p. 289-299.</journal>
			<date>6/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984ApJS...55..289W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984A&amp;A...132..385T</bibcode>
			<title>Relations between spectral types, absolute magnitudes, and colour indices of red dwarfs in the Cousins photometric system</title>
			<authors>The, P. S.; Steenman, H. C.; Alcaino, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 132, no. 2, March 1984, p. 385-388.</journal>
			<date>3/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984A%26A...132..385T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983ApJS...53..643J</bibcode>
			<title>Predicted infrared brightness of stars within 25 parsecs of the sun</title>
			<authors>Johnson, H. M.; Wright, C. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 53, Nov. 1983, p. 643-711. Research sponsored by the Lockheed Independent Research Program and Lockheed Independent Development Program.</journal>
			<date>11/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983ApJS...53..643J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983AJ.....88..684L</bibcode>
			<title>Parallaxes and proper motions of 25 stars from plates taken with the 61-cm Sproul refractor</title>
			<authors>Lippincott, S. L.; Hershey, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 88, May 1983, p. 684-687.</journal>
			<date>5/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983AJ.....88..684L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983SAAOC...7..106W</bibcode>
			<title>A spectroscopic survey of 113 nearby red dwarf stars</title>
			<authors>Walker, A. R.</authors>
			<journal>In its South African Astron. Observ. Circ., No. 7 p 106-109 (SEE N85-10875 01-89)</journal>
			<date>0/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983SAAOC...7..106W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982ApJS...50..221E</bibcode>
			<title>The Hyades main sequence</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, vol. 50, Oct. 1982, p. 221-239.</journal>
			<date>11/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982ApJS...50..221E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1980AJ.....85..438R</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of late-type young stars in the Rho OPH dark cloud</title>
			<authors>Rydgren, A. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, vol. 85, Apr. 1980, p. 438-443.</journal>
			<date>4/1980</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1980AJ.....85..438R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979ApJ...230..786E</bibcode>
			<title>Luminosity and motion of large proper-motion stars. I - Stars with annual proper motion larger than 1 arcsec</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1, vol. 230, June 15, 1979, p. 786-801.</journal>
			<date>6/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979ApJ...230..786E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979AJ.....84..633K</bibcode>
			<title>A set of faint equatorial standard stars for BVRI photometry</title>
			<authors>Kunkel, W. E.; Rydgren, A. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, vol. 84, May 1979, p. 633-638.</journal>
			<date>5/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979AJ.....84..633K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979VKha..190...52Z</bibcode>
			<title>Nearest stars.</title>
			<authors>Zakhozhaj, V. A.</authors>
			<journal>Vestnik Khar'kovskogo Universiteta, 190, 52-77 (1979)</journal>
			<date>0/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979VKha..190...52Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1977ApJS...34..479L</bibcode>
			<title>Radii of nearby stars: an application of the Barnes-Evans relation.</title>
			<authors>Lacy, C. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Suppl. Ser., Vol. 34, p. 479 - 492</journal>
			<date>8/1977</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1977ApJS...34..479L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1977ApJ...215..845W</bibcode>
			<title>The velocity dispersion of faint red dwarf stars</title>
			<authors>Weistrop, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1, vol. 215, Aug. 1, 1977, p. 845-850.</journal>
			<date>8/1977</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1977ApJ...215..845W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1976ApJ...210..402M</bibcode>
			<title>The composition of Kapteyn's star and the M subdwarfs.</title>
			<authors>Mould, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Vol. 210, p. 402 - 415</journal>
			<date>12/1976</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1976ApJ...210..402M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1976ApJ...208..399M</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared observations and the structure of the lower main sequence.</title>
			<authors>Mould, J. R.; Hyland, A. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Vol. 208, p. 399 - 413</journal>
			<date>9/1976</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1976ApJ...208..399M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1976ApJ...207..535M</bibcode>
			<title>M dwarfs: band strengths in halo and disk populations.</title>
			<authors>Mould, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Vol. 207, p. 535 - 544</journal>
			<date>7/1976</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1976ApJ...207..535M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1975PASP...87..107E</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric standards on the UBV and RI systems.</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Vol. 87, p. 107 - 109</journal>
			<date>2/1975</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1975PASP...87..107E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1974ApJS...28....1J</bibcode>
			<title>Spectral Types of M Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Joy, Alfred H.; Abt, Helmut A.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement, vol. 28, p.1 (1974)</journal>
			<date>11/1974</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1974ApJS...28....1J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1974AJ.....79.1056V</bibcode>
			<title>Luminosities and temperatures of M dwarf stars from infrared photometry</title>
			<authors>Veeder, G. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, vol. 79, Oct. 1974, p. 1056-1072.</journal>
			<date>10/1974</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1974AJ.....79.1056V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1974A&amp;AS...15..141S</bibcode>
			<title>The space distribution of M giants in the Warner and Swasey luminosity function field LF 15.</title>
			<authors>Th, P. S.; Staller, R. F. A.; Meurs, E. J. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Suppl. Ser., Vol. 15, p. 141 - 171</journal>
			<date>0/1974</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1974A%26AS...15..141S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1973ApJ...183..923S</bibcode>
			<title>Scanner observations of M dwarfs.</title>
			<authors>Spinrad, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Vol. 183, p. 923 - 934</journal>
			<date>8/1973</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1973ApJ...183..923S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1973ApJ...182..821E</bibcode>
			<title>On the existence of subdwarfs in the (Mbol, log Te)-plane. III.</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Vol. 182, p. 821 - 837</journal>
			<date>6/1973</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1973ApJ...182..821E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1972ApJ...174L.155P</bibcode>
			<title>CaOH, a New Triatomic Molecule in Stellar Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Pesch, Peter</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 174, p.L155</journal>
			<date>6/1972</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1972ApJ...174L.155P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1972MNSSA..31....7C</bibcode>
			<title>UBV Photometry of 500 Southern Stars [erratum: 1973MNSSA..32...48C]</title>
			<authors>Corben, P. M.; Carter, B. S.; Banfield, R. M.; Harvey, G. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notes of the Astron. Soc. Southern Africa, Vol. 31, p. 7</journal>
			<date>0/1972</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1972MNSSA..31....7C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1970ApJS...22..289E</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar-Population Samples at the Galactic Poles. II. UBVRI Photometry of M Stars Near the South Pole</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement, vol. 22, p.289 (1970)</journal>
			<date>12/1970</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1970ApJS...22..289E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1970VA.....12..367E</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar kinematics and evolution</title>
			<authors>Eggen, Olin J.</authors>
			<journal>Vistas in Astronomy, vol. 12, Issue 1, pp.367-414</journal>
			<date>0/1970</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1970VA.....12..367E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1968MNRAS.139..189J</bibcode>
			<title>Narrow band photometry of K and M stars</title>
			<authors>Jones, D. H. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 139, p.189</journal>
			<date>0/1968</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1968MNRAS.139..189J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1960MNRAS.120..540E</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar groups, VII. The structure of the Hyades group</title>
			<authors>Eggen, Olin J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 120, p.540</journal>
			<date>0/1960</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1960MNRAS.120..540E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1958MNRAS.118...65E</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar groups. I. The Hyades and Sirius groups</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 118, p.65</journal>
			<date>0/1958</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1958MNRAS.118...65E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1957AJ.....62..205K</bibcode>
			<title>Red and infrared magnitudes for 282 stars with known trigonometric parallaxes.</title>
			<authors>Kron, G. E.; Gascoigne, S. C. B.; White, H. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, 62, 205-220 (1957)</journal>
			<date>0/1957</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1957AJ.....62..205K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1956MNSSA..15....9R</bibcode>
			<title>Positions for Some Nearby Faint Stars</title>
			<authors>Russo, T. W.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notes of the Astronomical Society of South Africa, Vol. 15, p. 9R</journal>
			<date>0/1956</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1956MNSSA..15....9R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1956AJ.....61..219S</bibcode>
			<title>Photovisual magnitudes of 418 dwarf M stars and 34 parallax stars.</title>
			<authors>Stedman, W. D.; Vyssotsky, A. N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, 61, 219-224 (1956)</journal>
			<date>0/1956</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1956AJ.....61..219S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1955AnAp...18..292J</bibcode>
			<title>A photometric system</title>
			<authors>Johnson, Harold L.</authors>
			<journal>Annales d'Astrophysique, Vol. 18, p.292</journal>
			<date>1/1955</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1955AnAp...18..292J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1954ApJ...120..196J</bibcode>
			<title>Three-Color Observations of 108 Stars Intended for Use as Photometric Standards.</title>
			<authors>Johnson, H. L.; Harris, D. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 120, p.196</journal>
			<date>9/1954</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1954ApJ...120..196J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1953ApJ...118..502K</bibcode>
			<title>Red and Infrared Magnitudes for 138 Stars Observed as Photometric Standards.</title>
			<authors>Kron, Gerald E.; White, Howard S.; Gascoigne, S. C. B.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 118, p.502</journal>
			<date>11/1953</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1953ApJ...118..502K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1952ApJ...115..129I</bibcode>
			<title>A Study of Low-Dispersion Spectra of M Stars in the Red Region.</title>
			<authors>Iwanowska, W.; Wayman, P. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 115, p.129</journal>
			<date>1/1952</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1952ApJ...115..129I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1946ApJ...104..234V</bibcode>
			<title>Dwarf M Stars Found Spectrophotometrically. Second List.</title>
			<authors>Vyssotsky, A. N.; Janssen, E. M.; Miller, W. J.; Walther, M. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 104, p.234</journal>
			<date>9/1946</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1946ApJ...104..234V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1926ApJ....64..225A</bibcode>
			<title>The absolute magnitudes and parallaxes of 410 stars of type M.</title>
			<authors>Adams, W. S.; Joy, A. H.; Humason, M. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, 64, 225-242 (1926)</journal>
			<date>11/1926</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1926ApJ....64..225A</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
