<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534A..30G</bibcode>
			<title>Long-term magnetic activity of a sample of M-dwarf stars from the HARPS program. I. Comparison of activity indices</title>
			<authors>Gomes da Silva, J.; Santos, N. C.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.A30</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534A..30G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.2259H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation and modelling of main-sequence star chromospheres - XV. New constraints on the dynamo mechanisms for dM1 stars</title>
			<authors>Houdebine, E. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 4, pp. 2259-2276.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.2259H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1657H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation and modelling of main-sequence star chromospheres - XIV. Rotation of dM1 stars</title>
			<authors>Houdebine, E. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 3, pp. 1657-1673.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1657H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.1949K</bibcode>
			<title>UBV(RI)C JHK observations of Hipparcos-selected nearby stars</title>
			<authors>Koen, C.; Kilkenny, D.; van Wyk, F.; Marang, F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 4, pp. 1949-1968.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.1949K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....139..504B</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation and Magnetic Activity in a Sample of M-Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Browning, Matthew K.; Basri, Gibor; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; West, Andrew A.; Zhang, Jiahao</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 139, Issue 2, pp. 504-518 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....139..504B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...505..859Z</bibcode>
			<title>The M dwarf planet search programme at the ESO VLT + UVES. A search for terrestrial planets in the habitable zone of M dwarfs</title>
			<authors>