<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744...59S</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-Radius Relationships for Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Swift, D. C.; Eggert, J. H.; Hicks, D. G.; Hamel, S.; Caspersen, K.; Schwegler, E.; Collins, G. W.; Nettelmann, N.; Ackland, G. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744...59S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63L..67N</bibcode>
			<title>XO-2b: a Prograde Planet with Negligible Eccentricity and an Additional Radial Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sato, Bun'ei; Harakawa, Hiroki; Fukui, Akihiko; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.6, pp.L67-L71</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63L..67N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742..116B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-20b-HAT-P-23b: Four Massive Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Kipping, D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Shporer, A.; B&#233;ky, B.; Buchhave, L. A.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...72N</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Distributions of Close-in Planets and Distant Planets Formed by Scattering and Dynamical Tides</title>
			<authors>Nagasawa, M.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 72 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...72N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...11D</bibcode>
			<title>The Atmospheres of the Hot-Jupiters Kepler-5b and Kepler-6b Observed during Occultations with Warm-Spitzer and Kepler</title>
			<authors>D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Charbonneau, David; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Knutson, Heather A.; Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Deming, Drake; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 11 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...11D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...10B</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Misalignment of KOI-13.01 from Its Gravity-darkened Kepler Transit Lightcurve</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.; Linscott, Ethan; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...10B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ChA&amp;A..35..409Z</bibcode>
			<title>Observation and Research of the Transits of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Zhang, Ji-Cheng; Cao, Chen; Song, Nan; Wang, Fei-Ge; Zhang, Xiao-Tong</authors>
			<journal>Chinese Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 35, Issue 4, p. 409-420.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ChA%26A..35..409Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740...61K</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Phase Variations of the 55 Cancri System</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.; Ciardi, David R.; Dragomir, Diana; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 740, Issue 2, article id. 61 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740...61K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..123S</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve of an Exozodiacal Dust Cloud</title>
			<authors>Stark, Christopher C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 4, article id. 123 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142..123S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735L..12D</bibcode>
			<title>The High Albedo of the Hot Jupiter Kepler-7 b</title>
			<authors>Demory, Brice-Olivier; Seager, Sara; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Kjeldsen, Hans; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Gillon, Micha&#235;l; Rowe, Jason F.; Welsh, William F.; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Dupree, Andrea; McCarthy, Don; Kulesa, Craig; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 735, Issue 1, article id. L12 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735L..12D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...41B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in Five of the Exoplanetary Systems Studied by the NASA EPOXI Mission</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...41B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A...6T</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for transits in data with long time baselines and poor sampling</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A6</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A...6T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A...2B</bibcode>
			<title>The mass-period distribution of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ben&#237;tez-Llambay, P.; Masset, F.; Beaug&#233;, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A2</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A...2B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...50K</bibcode>
			<title>An Independent Analysis of Kepler-4b Through Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. 50 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...50K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...74K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Inclination Dependence of Exoplanet Phase Signatures</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...74K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527L..11H</bibcode>
			<title>The retrograde orbit of the HAT-P-6b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Ehrenreich, D.; Bouchy, F.; Delfosse, X.; Moutou, C.; Arnold, L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.L11</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527L..11H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411L..46V</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for detection of exoplanet magnetic fields through bow-shock observations during transits</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. L46-L50.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411L..46V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411..167I</bibcode>
			<title>Classical and relativistic long-term time variations of some observables for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iorio, L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. 167-183.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411..167I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...75I</bibcode>
			<title>Explorations into the Viability of Coupled Radius-orbit Evolutionary Models for Inflated Planets</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...75I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...23B</bibcode>
			<title>Secondary Eclipse Photometry of WASP-4b with Warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Beerer, Ingrid M.; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Agol, Eric; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Deming, Drake; Desert, Jean-Michel; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 23 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 29, 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62L..61N</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect of the Transiting Exoplanet XO-4b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.6, pp.L61--L65</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62L..61N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725..261M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Inference of Thermal Inversions in Hot Jupiter Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 1, pp. 261-274 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725..261M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724.1108J</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect of Exoplanet Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Cochran, William D.; Welsh, William F.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John Asher; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Howard, Andrew W.; MacQueen, Phillip; Orosz, Jerome A.; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Allen, Christopher; Tenenbaum, Peter; Wu, Hayley; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Cote, Miles T.; McCauliff, Sean; Girouard, Forrest R.; Gunter, Jay P.; Wohler, Bill; Hall, Jennifer R.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Kamal Uddin, AKM; Wu, Michael S.; Bhavsar, Paresh A.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Pletcher, David L.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, article id. 1108-1119 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724.1108J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1758K</bibcode>
			<title>Binning is sinning: morphological light-curve distortions due to finite integration time</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1758-1769.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1758K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1666S</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation periods of exoplanet host stars</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Baliunas, S. L.; Henry, G. W.; Watson, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1666-1679.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1666S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1606W</bibcode>
			<title>Estimating the masses of extra-solar planets</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Littlefair, S. P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Dhillon, V. S.; Simpson, E. K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1606-1622.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1606W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..818K</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Phase Variations of Long-period Eccentric Planets</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. 818-826 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..818K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2589K</bibcode>
			<title>Nightside pollution of exoplanet transit depths</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.; Tinetti, Giovanna</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2589-2598.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2589K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722L.224B</bibcode>
			<title>Confirmation of a Retrograde Orbit for Exoplanet WASP-17b</title>
			<authors>Bayliss, Daniel D. R.; Winn, Joshua N.; Mardling, Rosemary A.; Sackett, Penny D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 722, Issue 2, pp. L224-L227 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722L.224B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722..871S</bibcode>
			<title>Atmosphere and Spectral Models of the Kepler-field Planets HAT-P-7b and TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. 871-879 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722..871S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721.1295D</bibcode>
			<title>Habitable Climates: The Influence of Eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Dressing, Courtney D.; Spiegel, David S.; Scharf, Caleb A.; Menou, Kristen; Raymond, Sean N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. 1295-1307 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...721.1295D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1077D</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Transit Search for Planets around Cool Stars from the Western Italian Alps: A Site Characterization Study</title>
			<authors>Damasso, M.; Giacobbe, P.; Calcidese, P.; Sozzetti, A.; Lattanzi, M. G.; Bernagozzi, A.; Bertolini, E.; Smart, R. L.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 895, pp.1077-1091</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1077D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407..507C</bibcode>
			<title>Line-profile tomography of exoplanet transits - II. A gas-giant planet transiting a rapidly rotating A5 star</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Guenther, E.; Smalley, B.; McDonald, I.; Hebb, L.; Andersen, J.; Augusteijn, Th.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Cochran, W. D.; Endl, M.; Fossey, S. J.; Hartmann, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Telting, J.; Waldmann, I. P.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 1, pp. 507-514.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407..507C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518L.153G</bibcode>
			<title>Possible detection of phase changes from the non-transiting planet HD 46375b by CoRoT</title>
			<authors>Gaulme, P.; Vannier, M.; Guillot, T.; Mosser, B.; Mary, D.; Weiss, W. W.; Schmider, F.-X.; Bourguignon, S.; Deeg, H. J.; R&#233;gulo, C.; Aigrain, S.; Schneider, J.; Bruntt, H.; Deheuvels, S.; Donati, J.-F.; Appourchaux, T.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Baudin, F.; Catala, C.; Michel, E.; Samadi, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.L153</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518L.153G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..779N</bibcode>
			<title>Search for Outer Massive Bodies around Transiting Planetary Systems: Candidates of Faint Stellar Companions around HAT-P-7</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Kudo, Tomoyuki; Bergfors, Carolina; Nagasawa, Makiko; Thalmann, Christian; Sato, Bun'ei; Suzuki, Ryuji; Kandori, Ryo; Janson, Markus; Goto, Miwa; Brandner, Wolfgang; Ida, Shigeru; Abe, Lyu; Carson, Joseph; Egner, Sebastian E.; Feldt, Markus; Golota, Taras; Guyon, Olivier; Hashimoto, Jun; Hayano, Yutaka; Hayashi, Masahiko; Hayashi, Saeko S.; Henning, Thomas; Hodapp, Klaus W.; Ishii, Miki; Knapp, Gillian R.; Kusakabe, Nobuhiko; Kuzuhara, Masayuki; Matsuo, Taro; McElwain, Michael W.; Miyama, Shoken M.; Morino, Jun-Ichi; Moro-Martin, Amaya; Nishimura, Tetsuo; Pyo, Tae-Soo; Serabyn, Eugene; Suenaga, Takuya; Suto, Hiroshi; Takahashi, Yasuhiro Haruhi; Takami, Michihiro; Takato, Naruhisa; Terada, Hiroshi; Tomono, Daigo; Turner, Edwin L.; Watanabe, Makoto; Yamada, Toru; Takami, Hideki; Usuda, Tomonori; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.3, pp.779--786</journal>
			<date>6/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..779N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..653N</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-Orbit Alignment of the TrES-4 Transiting Planetary System and Possible Additional Radial-Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Winn, Joshua N.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.3, pp.653--660</journal>
			<date>6/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..653N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...514A..23R</bibcode>
			<title>tau Bo&#246;tis b: Hunting for reflected starlight</title>
			<authors>Rodler, F.; K&#252;rster, M.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 514, id.A23</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...514A..23R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>The Discovery of Ellipsoidal Variations in the Kepler Light Curve of HAT-P-7</title>
			<authors>Welsh, William F.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Seager, Sara; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Jenkins, Jon; Rowe, Jason F.; Koch, David; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.103B</bibcode>
			<title>Pre-spectroscopic False-positive Elimination of Kepler Planet Candidates</title>
			<authors>Batalha, Natalie M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Jenkins, Jon J.; Caldwell, Douglas; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Howell, Steve B.; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoff W.; Prsa, Andrej</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L103-L108 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.103B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L..79K</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Mission Design, Realized Photometric Performance, and Early Science</title>
			<authors>Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gould, Alan; Jenkins, Jon; Kondo, Yoji; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey; Monet, David; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Brownlee, Donald; Caldwell, John; Dupree, Andrea K.; Howell, Steve B.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Morrison, David; Owen, Tobias; Reitsema, Harold; Tarter, Jill; Bryson, Stephen T.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Gazis, Paul; Haas, Michael R.; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Rowe, Jason F.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey E.; Allen, Christopher; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Quintana, Elisa V.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Twicken, Joseph D.; Wu, Hayley</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, article id. L79-L86 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L..79K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403..151C</bibcode>
			<title>Line-profile tomography of exoplanet transits - I. The Doppler shadow of HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Bruce, V. A.; Miller, G. R. M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 1, pp. 151-158.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403..151C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712L..86P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Variations for Inclined and Retrograde Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.; Veras, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. L86-L92 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712L..86P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...327..977B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Planet-Detection Mission: Introduction and First Results</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy; Caldwell, Douglas; Caldwell, John; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kondo, Yoji; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Kjeldsen, Hans; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Morrison, David; Sasselov, Dimitar; Tarter, Jill; Boss, Alan; Brownlee, Don; Owen, Toby; Buzasi, Derek; Charbonneau, David; Doyle, Laurance; Fortney, Jonathan; Ford, Eric B.; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Rowe, Jason; Anderson, Howard; Buchhave, Lars; Ciardi, David; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Sherry, William; Horch, Elliott; Isaacson, Howard; Everett, Mark E.; Fischer, Debra; Torres, Guillermo; Johnson, John Asher; Endl, Michael; MacQueen, Phillip; Bryson, Stephen T.; Dotson, Jessie; Haas, Michael; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Allen, Christopher; Li, Jie; Wu, Haley; Tenenbaum, Peter; Verner, Ekaterina; Bruhweiler, Frederick; Barnes, Jason; Prsa, Andrej</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 327, Issue 5968, pp. 977- (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...327..977B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710...97C</bibcode>
			<title>Studying the Atmosphere of the Exoplanet HAT-P-7b Via Secondary Eclipse Measurements with EPOXI, Spitzer, and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Holman, Matthew J.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Deming, Drake; A'Hearn, Michael F.; the EPOXI Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 97-104 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710...97C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707..446B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-13b,c: A Transiting Hot Jupiter with a Massive Outer Companion on an Eccentric Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Howard, A. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225; cs, G&#233;za; Fischer, D. A.; Latham, D. W.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sipocz, B.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Esquerdo, G. A.; P&#225;l, A.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, pp. 446-456 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707..446B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..877B</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting the Wind-Driven Shapes of Extrasolar Giant Planets from Transit Photometry</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.; Cooper, Curtis S.; Showman, Adam P.; Hubbard, William B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 877-884 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..877B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASJ...61L..35N</bibcode>
			<title>First Evidence of a Retrograde Orbit of a Transiting Exoplanet HAT-P-7b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.61, No.5, pp.L35-L40</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASJ...61L..35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703L..99W</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-7: A Retrograde or Polar Orbit, and a Third Body</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Albrecht, Simon; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Crossfield, Ian J.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. L99-L103 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703L..99W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..564S</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Circulation of Hot Jupiters: Coupled Radiative-Dynamical General Circulation Model Simulations of HD 189733b and HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Showman, Adam P.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Lian, Yuan; Marley, Mark S.; Freedman, Richard S.; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 564-584 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..564S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1950B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-10b: A Light and Moderately Hot Jupiter Transiting A K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; P&#225;l, A.; Torres, G.; Sipocz, B.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Hartman, J.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1950-1955 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1950B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394L..93M</bibcode>
			<title>On the various origins of close-in extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.; Ortolani, S.; Nagasawa, M.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. L93-L96.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394L..93M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...680.1450P</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-7b: An Extremely Hot Massive Planet Transiting a Bright Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, A.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 680, Issue 2, pp. 1450-1456.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...680.1450P</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....6G</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Mission Stellar and Instrument Noise Properties</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; Chaplin, William J.; Dunham, Edward W.; Argabright, Vic S.; Borucki, William J.; Basri, Gibor; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buzasi, Derek L.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Elsworth, Yvonne P.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Miglio, Andrea; van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Welsh, William F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 6 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....6G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....4W</bibcode>
			<title>KOI-54: The Kepler Discovery of Tidally Excited Pulsations and Brightenings in a Highly Eccentric Binary</title>
			<authors>Welsh, William F.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Aerts, Conny; Brown, Timothy M.; Brugamyer, Erik; Cochran, William D.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Guzik, Joyce Ann; Kurtz, D. W.; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Zima, Wolfgang; Allen, Christopher; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Steve; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Howell, Steve B.; Kinemuchi, K.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Prsa, Andrej; Still, Martin; Street, Rachel; Wohler, Bill; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 4 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....4W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A.116D</bibcode>
			<title>Prospecting transit duration variations in extrasolar planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Damiani, C.; Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A116</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...535A.116D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ChA&amp;A..35..409Z</bibcode>
			<title>Observation and Research of the Transits of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Zhang, Ji-Cheng; Cao, Chen; Song, Nan; Wang, Fei-Ge; Zhang, Xiao-Tong</authors>
			<journal>Chinese Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 35, Issue 4, p. 409-420.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ChA%26A..35..409Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740...33D</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler and Ground-based Transits of the Exo-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Sada, Pedro V.; Jackson, Brian; Peterson, Steven W.; Agol, Eric; Knutson, Heather A.; Jennings, Donald E.; Haase, Flynn; Bays, Kevin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 740, Issue 1, article id. 33 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740...33D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..123S</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve of an Exozodiacal Dust Cloud</title>
			<authors>Stark, Christopher C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 4, article id. 123 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142..123S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..112B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Input Catalog: Photometric Calibration and Stellar Classification</title>
			<authors>Brown, Timothy M.; Latham, David W.; Everett, Mark E.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 4, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142..112B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534L...6T</bibcode>
			<title>The time dependence of hot Jupiters' orbital inclinations</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.L6</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534L...6T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L...4S</bibcode>
			<title>Asymmetric Transit Curves as Indication of Orbital Obliquity: Clues from the Late-type Dwarf Companion in KOI-13</title>
			<authors>Szab&#243;, Gy. M.; Szab&#243;, R.; Benko, J. M.; Lehmann, H.; Mezo, Gy.; Simon, A. E.; Kov&#225;ri, Zs.; Hodos&#225;n, G.; Reg&#225;ly, Zs.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. L4 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L...4S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142....2F</bibcode>
			<title>The Burrell-Optical-Kepler-Survey (BOKS). I. Survey Description and Initial Results</title>
			<authors>Feldmeier, John J.; Howell, Steve B.; Sherry, William; von Braun, Kaspar; Everett, Mark E.; Ciardi, David R.; Harding, Paul; Mihos, J. Christopher; Rudick, Craig S.; Lee, Ting-Hui; Kutsko, Rebecca M.; van Belle, Gerard T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142....2F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414..108B</bibcode>
			<title>On the use of the Virtual Observatory to select calibrators for phase-referenced astrometry of exoplanet-host stars</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonneau, D.; Mourard, D.; Lafrasse, S.; Mella, G.; Duvert, G.; Chelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. 108-115.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414..108B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...530A..97B</bibcode>
			<title>Accurate p-mode measurements of the G0V metal-rich CoRoT target HD 52265</title>
			<authors>Ballot, J.; Gizon, L.; Samadi, R.; Vauclair, G.; Benomar, O.; Bruntt, H.; Mosser, B.; Stahn, T.; Verner, G. A.; Campante, T. L.; Garc&#237;a, R. A.; Mathur, S.; Salabert, D.; Gaulme, P.; R&#233;gulo, C.; Roxburgh, I. W.; Appourchaux, T.; Baudin, F.; Catala, C.; Chaplin, W. J.; Deheuvels, S.; Michel, E.; Bazot, M.; Creevey, O.; Dolez, N.; Elsworth, Y.; Sato, K. H.; Vauclair, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 530, id.A97</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...530A..97B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...41B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in Five of the Exoplanetary Systems Studied by the NASA EPOXI Mission</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...41B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A..50L</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining tidal dissipation in F-type main-sequence stars: the case of CoRoT-11</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Damiani, C.; Gandolfi, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A50</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A..50L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..108C</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the Variability of Stars with Early-release Kepler Data</title>
			<authors>Ciardi, David R.; von Braun, Kaspar; Bryden, Geoff; van Eyken, Julian; Howell, Steve B.; Kane, Stephen R.; Plavchan, Peter; Ram&#237;rez, Solange V.; Stauffer, John R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 4, article id. 108 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..108C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..63S</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. II. KOI-428b: a hot Jupiter transiting a subgiant F-star</title>
			<authors>Santerne, A.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Moutou, C.; H&#233;brard, G.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A63</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..63S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63S.531H</bibcode>
			<title>A Possible Tilted Orbit of the Super-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Narita, Norio; Shporer, Avi; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.SP2, pp.531--536</journal>
			<date>3/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63S.531H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...98P</bibcode>
			<title>An Analysis of Jitter and Transit Timing Variations in the HAT-P-13 System</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 98 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...98P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...27B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler's First Rocky Planet: Kepler-10b</title>
			<authors>Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Ciardi, David; Dunham, Edward W.; Fressin, Francois; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Torres, Guillermo; Basri, Gibor S.; Brown, Timothy M.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie; Clarke, Bruce; Cochran, William D.; Dupree, Andrea; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fischer, Debra; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Girouard, Forrest R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Johnson, John; Isaacson, Howard; Klaus, Todd C.; Machalek, Pavel; Moorehead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Twicken, Joseph; Quinn, Samuel; VanCleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Welsh, William F.; Devore, Edna; Gould, Alan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 27 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...27B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..73S</bibcode>
			<title>Gran Telescopio Canarias OSIRIS transiting exoplanet atmospheric survey: detection of potassium in XO-2b from narrowband spectrophotometry</title>
			<authors>Sing, D. K.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; Fortney, J. J.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Ballester, G. E.; Cepa, J.; Ehrenreich, D.; L&#243;pez-Morales, M.; Pont, F.; Shabram, M.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A73</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..73S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..117B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Kepler Planetary Candidates Based on the First Data Set</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Boss, Alan; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Monet, David G.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Tarter, Jill; Charbonneau, David; Doyle, Laurance; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David; Clarke, Bruce D.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Li, Jie; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Prsa, Andrej; Quintana, Elisa V.; Rowe, Jason; Sherry, William; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Wu, Hayley</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 117 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..117B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...63W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Orientations of Exoplanets: HAT-P-4b is Prograde and HAT-P-14b is Retrograde</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Hartman, Joel D.; Holman, Matthew J.; Albrecht, Simon; Crepp, Justin R.; Morton, Timothy D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 63 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...63W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526L..10H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-33: the first delta Scuti exoplanet host star</title>
			<authors>Herrero, E.; Morales, J. C.; Ribas, I.; Naves, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.L10</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526L..10H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...94C</bibcode>
			<title>System Parameters, Transit Times, and Secondary Eclipse Constraints of the Exoplanet Systems HAT-P-4, TrES-2, TrES-3, and WASP-3 from the NASA EPOXI Mission of Opportunity</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; A'Hearn, Michael F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 94 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...94C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726....2G</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of the Transiting Exoplanet Host HD 17156 with Hubble Space Telescope Fine Guidance Sensor</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; McCullough, Peter R.; Nelan, Edmund P.; Brown, Timothy M.; Charbonneau, David; Nutzman, Philip; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Kjeldsen, Hans</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id.2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726....2G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.2176Q</bibcode>
			<title>Automatic Determination of Stellar Parameters Via Asteroseismology of Stochastically Oscillating Stars: Comparison with Direct Measurements</title>
			<authors>Quirion, Pierre-Olivier; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Arentoft, Torben</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 2176-2189 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.2176Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724.1108J</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect of Exoplanet Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Cochran, William D.; Welsh, William F.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John Asher; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Howard, Andrew W.; MacQueen, Phillip; Orosz, Jerome A.; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Allen, Christopher; Tenenbaum, Peter; Wu, Hayley; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Cote, Miles T.; McCauliff, Sean; Girouard, Forrest R.; Gunter, Jay P.; Wohler, Bill; Hall, Jennifer R.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Kamal Uddin, AKM; Wu, Michael S.; Bhavsar, Paresh A.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Pletcher, David L.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, article id. 1108-1119 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724.1108J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A.110C</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission . XIII. CoRoT-13b: a dense hot Jupiter in transit around a star with solar metallicity and super-solar lithium content</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Bruntt, H.; Ollivier, M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; von Paris, P.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Titz-Weider, R.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A110</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...522A.110C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2589K</bibcode>
			<title>Nightside pollution of exoplanet transit depths</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.; Tinetti, Giovanna</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2589-2598.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2589K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722..871S</bibcode>
			<title>Atmosphere and Spectral Models of the Kepler-field Planets HAT-P-7b and TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. 871-879 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722..871S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521L..59M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of the ellipsoidal and the relativistic beaming effects in the CoRoT-3 lightcurve</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Faigler, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.L59</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521L..59M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1077D</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Transit Search for Planets around Cool Stars from the Western Italian Alps: A Site Characterization Study</title>
			<authors>Damasso, M.; Giacobbe, P.; Calcidese, P.; Sozzetti, A.; Lattanzi, M. G.; Bernagozzi, A.; Bertolini, E.; Smart, R. L.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 895, pp.1077-1091</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1077D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1048M</bibcode>
			<title>The determination of planetary structure in tidally relaxed inclined systems</title>
			<authors>Mardling, Rosemary A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1048-1069.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1048M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.1867S</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit alignment of the transiting exoplanet WASP-3b from Rossiter-McLaughlin observations</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Pollacco, D.; H&#233;brard, G.; Gibson, N. P.; Barros, S. C. C.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Miller, G. R. M.; Watson, C. A.; Keenan, F. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 1867-1872.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.1867S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..575W</bibcode>
			<title>The HAT-P-13 Exoplanetary System: Evidence for Spin-Orbit Alignment and a Third Companion</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Hartman, Joel; Torres, Guillermo; Albrecht, Simon; Narita, Norio</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 1, pp. 575-582 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..575W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..543M</bibcode>
			<title>Systemic: A Testbed for Characterizing the Detection of Extrasolar Planets. II. Numerical Approaches to the Transit Timing Inverse Problem</title>
			<authors>Meschiari, Stefano; Laughlin, Gregory P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 1, pp. 543-550 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..543M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..779N</bibcode>
			<title>Search for Outer Massive Bodies around Transiting Planetary Systems: Candidates of Faint Stellar Companions around HAT-P-7</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Kudo, Tomoyuki; Bergfors, Carolina; Nagasawa, Makiko; Thalmann, Christian; Sato, Bun'ei; Suzuki, Ryuji; Kandori, Ryo; Janson, Markus; Goto, Miwa; Brandner, Wolfgang; Ida, Shigeru; Abe, Lyu; Carson, Joseph; Egner, Sebastian E.; Feldt, Markus; Golota, Taras; Guyon, Olivier; Hashimoto, Jun; Hayano, Yutaka; Hayashi, Masahiko; Hayashi, Saeko S.; Henning, Thomas; Hodapp, Klaus W.; Ishii, Miki; Knapp, Gillian R.; Kusakabe, Nobuhiko; Kuzuhara, Masayuki; Matsuo, Taro; McElwain, Michael W.; Miyama, Shoken M.; Morino, Jun-Ichi; Moro-Martin, Amaya; Nishimura, Tetsuo; Pyo, Tae-Soo; Serabyn, Eugene; Suenaga, Takuya; Suto, Hiroshi; Takahashi, Yasuhiro Haruhi; Takami, Michihiro; Takato, Naruhisa; Terada, Hiroshi; Tomono, Daigo; Turner, Edwin L.; Watanabe, Makoto; Yamada, Toru; Takami, Hideki; Usuda, Tomonori; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.3, pp.779--786</journal>
			<date>6/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..779N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..653N</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-Orbit Alignment of the TrES-4 Transiting Planetary System and Possible Additional Radial-Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Winn, Joshua N.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.3, pp.653--660</journal>
			<date>6/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..653N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..421T</bibcode>
			<title>A Prograde, Low-inclination Orbit for the Very Hot Jupiter WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Tripathi, Anjali; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Halverson, Sam; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Holman, Matthew J.; de Kleer, Katherine R.; Carter, Joshua A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Cabrera, Nicole E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 421-428 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..421T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AN....331..489S</bibcode>
			<title>Pulsations and planets: The asteroseismology-extrasolar-planet connection</title>
			<authors>Schuh, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.331, Issue 5, p.489</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AN....331..489S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.164C</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismic Investigation of Known Planet Hosts in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Kjeldsen, H.; Brown, T. M.; Gilliland, R. L.; Arentoft, T.; Frandsen, S.; Quirion, P.-O.; Borucki, W. J.; Koch, D.; Jenkins, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L164-L168 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.164C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.160G</bibcode>
			<title>Initial Characteristics of Kepler Short Cadence Data</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer; Klaus, Todd; Koch, David; McCauliff, Sean; Quintana, Elisa V.; Twicken, Joseph D.; van Cleve, Jeffrey E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L160-L163 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.160G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>The Discovery of Ellipsoidal Variations in the Kepler Light Curve of HAT-P-7</title>
			<authors>Welsh, William F.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Seager, Sara; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Jenkins, Jon; Rowe, Jason F.; Koch, David; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.131K</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of the Transiting Planet Kepler-5b</title>
			<authors>Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Caldwell, John; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ron L.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoff W.; Morrison, David; Tarter, Jill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, article id. L131-L135 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.131K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L..79K</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Mission Design, Realized Photometric Performance, and Early Science</title>
			<authors>Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gould, Alan; Jenkins, Jon; Kondo, Yoji; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey; Monet, David; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Brownlee, Donald; Caldwell, John; Dupree, Andrea K.; Howell, Steve B.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Morrison, David; Owen, Tobias; Reitsema, Harold; Tarter, Jill; Bryson, Stephen T.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Gazis, Paul; Haas, Michael R.; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Rowe, Jason F.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey E.; Allen, Christopher; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Quintana, Elisa V.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Twicken, Joseph D.; Wu, Hayley</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, article id. L79-L86 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L..79K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712L..86P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Variations for Inclined and Retrograde Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.; Veras, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. L86-L92 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712L..86P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122..131G</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Asteroseismology Program: Introduction and First Results</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; Brown, Timothy M.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Kjeldsen, Hans; Aerts, Conny; Appourchaux, Thierry; Basu, Sarbani; Bedding, Timothy R.; Chaplin, William J.; Cunha, Margarida S.; De Cat, Peter; De Ridder, Joris; Guzik, Joyce A.; Handler, Gerald; Kawaler, Steven; Kiss, L&#225;szl&#243;; Kolenberg, Katrien; Kurtz, Donald W.; Metcalfe, Travis S.; Monteiro, Mario J. P. F. G.; Szab&#243; , Robert; Arentoft, Torben; Balona, Luis; Debosscher, Jonas; Elsworth, Yvonne P.; Quirion, Pierre-Olivier; Stello, Dennis; Su&#225;rez, Juan Carlos; Borucki, William J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David; Kondo, Yoji; Latham, David W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 888, pp.131-143</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122..131G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1724B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-11b: A Super-Neptune Planet Transiting a Bright K Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; P&#225;l, A.; Hartman, J.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Isaacson, H.; Howard, A.; Vogt, S.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Fernandez, J.; Mo&#243;r, A.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1724-1745 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1551O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Planetary Emission from the Exoplanet Tres-2 Using Spitzer/IRAC</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Harrington, Joseph; Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1551-1556 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1551O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710...97C</bibcode>
			<title>Studying the Atmosphere of the Exoplanet HAT-P-7b Via Secondary Eclipse Measurements with EPOXI, Spitzer, and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Holman, Matthew J.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Deming, Drake; A'Hearn, Michael F.; the EPOXI Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 97-104 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710...97C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A.103S</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos preliminary astrometric masses for the two close-in companions to HD 131664 and HD 43848. A brown dwarf and a low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Desidera, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A103</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A.103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASJ...61L..35N</bibcode>
			<title>First Evidence of a Retrograde Orbit of a Transiting Exoplanet HAT-P-7b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.61, No.5, pp.L35-L40</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASJ...61L..35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703L..99W</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-7: A Retrograde or Polar Orbit, and a Third Body</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Albrecht, Simon; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Crossfield, Ian J.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. L99-L103 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703L..99W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..769K</bibcode>
			<title>The 8 mum Phase Variation of the Hot Saturn HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Showman, Adam P.; Agol, Eric; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 769-784 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..769K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...680.1450P</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-7b: An Extremely Hot Massive Planet Transiting a Bright Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, A.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 680, Issue 2, pp. 1450-1456.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...680.1450P</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
