<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744...59S</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-Radius Relationships for Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Swift, D. C.; Eggert, J. H.; Hicks, D. G.; Hamel, S.; Caspersen, K.; Schwegler, E.; Collins, G. W.; Nettelmann, N.; Ackland, G. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744...59S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744....4G</bibcode>
			<title>A High-eccentricity Component in the Double-planet System around HD 163607 and a Planet around HD 164509</title>
			<authors>Giguere, Matthew J.; Fischer, Debra A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John A.; Henry, Gregory W.; Wright, Jason T.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard T.; Hou, Fengji; Spronck, Julien</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 1, article id. 4 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744....4G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..203J</bibcode>
			<title>A Survey of Alkali Line Absorption in Exoplanetary Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Jensen, Adam G.; Redfield, Seth; Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Koesterke, Lars; Barman, Travis S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 203 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..203J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..162P</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for the Transit of HD 168443b: Improved Orbital Parameters and Photometry</title>
			<authors>Pilyavsky, Genady; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Kane, Stephen R.; Howard, Andrew W.; Ciardi, David R.; de Pree, Chris; Dragomir, Diana; Fischer, Debra; Henry, Gregory W.; Jensen, Eric L. N.; Laughlin, Gregory; Marlowe, Hannah; Rabus, Markus; von Braun, Kaspar; Wright, Jason T.; Wang, Xuesong X.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 162 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..162P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...72N</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Distributions of Close-in Planets and Distant Planets Formed by Scattering and Dynamical Tides</title>
			<authors>Nagasawa, M.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 72 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...72N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...59H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-32b and HAT-P-33b: Two Highly Inflated Hot Jupiters Transiting High-jitter Stars</title>
			<authors>