<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749..134H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-17b,c: A Transiting, Eccentric, Hot Saturn and a Long-period, Cold Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Howard, A. W.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Mazeh, T.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Bky, B.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 2, article id. 134 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749..134H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..82K</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for enhanced chromospheric Ca II H and K emission in stars with close-in extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A82</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..82K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742..116B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-20b-HAT-P-23b: Four Massive Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Kipping, D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Shporer, A.; Bky, B.; Buchhave, L. A.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...95K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-31b,c: A Transiting, Eccentric, Hot Jupiter and a Long-period, Massive Third Body</title>
			<authors>Kipping, D. M.; Hartman, J.; Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Bayliss, D.; Kiss, L. L.; Sato, B.; Bky, B.; Kovcs, Gza; Quinn, S. N.; Buchhave, L. A.; Andersen, J.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.; Fursz, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 3, article id. 95 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142...95K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>The Heavy-element Masses of Extrasolar Giant Planets, Revealed</title>
			<authors>Miller, Neil; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A...8S</bibcode>
			<title>A much lower density for the transiting extrasolar planet WASP-7</title>
			<authors>Southworth, J.; Dominik, M.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Rahvar, S.; Snodgrass, C.; Alsubai, K.; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Burgdorf, M.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dodds, P.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Gerner, T.; Hardis, S.; Harpse, K.; Hellier, C.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Kains, N.; Kerins, E.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Mathiasen, M.; Penny, M. T.; Proft, S.; Ricci, D.; Sahu, K.; Scarpetta, G.; Schfer, S.; Schnebeck, F.; Surdej, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A8</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A...8S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..54B</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-38b: a transiting exoplanet in an eccentric, 6.87d period orbit</title>
			<authors>Barros, S. C. C.; Faedi, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Lister, T. A.; McCormac, J.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Hbrard, G.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Bento, J.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Skillen, I.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A54</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..54B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..866K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-15b: A 10.9 Day Extrasolar Planet Transiting a Solar-type Star</title>
			<authors>Kovcs, G.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J. D.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fernandez, J. M.; Lzr, B. Bky J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, pp. 866-877 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A.147H</bibcode>
			<title>Optimizing exoplanet transit searches around low-mass stars with inclination constraints</title>
			<authors>Herrero, E.; Ribas, I.; Jordi, C.; Guinan, E. F.; Engle, S. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 537, id.A147</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...537A.147H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63S.531H</bibcode>
			<title>A Possible Tilted Orbit of the Super-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Narita, Norio; Shporer, Avi; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.SP2, pp.531--536</journal>
			<date>3/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63S.531H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..866K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-15b: A 10.9 Day Extrasolar Planet Transiting a Solar-type Star</title>
			<authors>Kovcs, G.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J. D.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fernandez, J. M.; Lzr, B. Bky J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, pp. 866-877 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
