<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>The Heavy-element Masses of Extrasolar Giant Planets, Revealed</title>
			<authors>Miller, Neil; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...27K</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer Transmission Spectrum for the Exoplanet GJ 436b, Evidence for Stellar Variability, and Constraints on Dayside Flux Variations</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Agol, Eric; Deming, Drake; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Charbonneau, David; Henry, Gregory W.; Homeier, Derek; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 1, article id. 27 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735...27K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..166H</bibcode>
			<title>A Photometric Variability Survey of Field K and M Dwarf Stars with HATNet</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Noyes, R. W.; Sipocz, B.; Kov&#225;cs, G.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.; P&#225;l, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 5, article id. 166 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..166H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63S.531H</bibcode>
			<title>A Possible Tilted Orbit of the Super-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Narita, Norio; Shporer, Avi; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.SP2, pp.531--536</journal>
			<date>3/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63S.531H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...50K</bibcode>
			<title>An Independent Analysis of Kepler-4b Through Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. 50 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...50K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...10H</bibcode>
			<title>The NASA-UC Eta-Earth Program. III. A Super-Earth Orbiting HD 97658 and a Neptune-mass Planet Orbiting Gl 785</title>
			<authors>Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Wright, Jason T.; Henry, Gregory W.; Isaacson, Howard; Valenti, Jeff A.; Anderson, Jay; Piskunov, Nikolai E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. 10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...10H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...41M</bibcode>
			<title>High Metallicity and Non-equilibrium Chemistry in the Dayside Atmosphere of hot-Neptune GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...41M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527L..11H</bibcode>
			<title>The retrograde orbit of the HAT-P-6b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Ehrenreich, D.; Bouchy, F.; Delfosse, X.; Moutou, C.; Arnold, L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.L11</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527L..11H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1204M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation and activity in the WASP-10 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Tetzlaff, N.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Chen, W. P.; Walter, F.; Marka, C.; Baar, S.; Krejcov&#225;, T.; Budaj, J.; Krushevska, V.; Tachihara, K.; Takahashi, H.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 2, pp. 1204-1212.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1204M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..138H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-26b: A Low-density Neptune-mass Planet Transiting a K Star</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Kipping, D. M.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Quinn, S. N.; Buchhave, L. A.; B&#233;ky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Perumpilly, G.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 138 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727L..44S</bibcode>
			<title>A Short-period Censor of Sub-Jupiter Mass Exoplanets with Low Density</title>
			<authors>Szab&#243;, Gy. M.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. L44 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727L..44S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...82C</bibcode>
			<title>A Model for Thermal Phase Variations of Circular and Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 82 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...82C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..83B</bibcode>
			<title>Primary and secondary eclipse spectroscopy with JWST: exploring the exoplanet parameter space</title>
			<authors>Belu, A. R.; Selsis, F.; Morales, J.-C.; Ribas, I.; Cossou, C.; Rauer, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A83</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..83B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1758K</bibcode>
			<title>Binning is sinning: morphological light-curve distortions due to finite integration time</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1758-1769.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1758K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723L.223W</bibcode>
			<title>The Oblique Orbit of the Super-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Hartman, Joel D.; Albrecht, Simon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 723, Issue 2, pp. L223-L227 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723L.223W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723L..60H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-29b: A Saturn-sized Transiting Exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Enoch, B.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233; gransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. L60-L63 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723L..60H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..26N</bibcode>
			<title>Interior structure models of GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Nettelmann, N.; Kramm, U.; Redmer, R.; Neuh&#228;user, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A26</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..26N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722..871S</bibcode>
			<title>Atmosphere and Spectral Models of the Kepler-field Planets HAT-P-7b and TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. 871-879 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722..871S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..66B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XI. CoRoT-8b: a hot and dense sub-Saturn around a K1 dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Cabrera, J.; Jorda, L.; Lovis, C.; Csizmadia, S.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Ollivier, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A66</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..66B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717..235D</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Observations of the WASP-10 System</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, J. A.; Close, L. M.; Scuderi, L. J.; Morris, M. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 1, pp. 235-238 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717..235D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714..462S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Apparent Orbital Inclination Change of the Extrasolar Transiting Planet TrES-2b</title>
			<authors>Scuderi, Louis J.; Dittmann, Jason A.; Males, Jared R.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Close, Laird M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 462-468 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714..462S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.126B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-4b: A Hot Neptune-like Planet of a G0 Star Near Main-sequence Turnoff</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Brown, Timothy M.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Monet, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, article id. L126-L130 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.126B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..974R</bibcode>
			<title>A Framework for Quantifying the Degeneracies of Exoplanet Interior Compositions</title>
			<authors>Rogers, L. A.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 2, pp. 974-991 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..974R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...327..977B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Planet-Detection Mission: Introduction and First Results</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy; Caldwell, Douglas; Caldwell, John; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kondo, Yoji; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Kjeldsen, Hans; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Morrison, David; Sasselov, Dimitar; Tarter, Jill; Boss, Alan; Brownlee, Don; Owen, Toby; Buzasi, Derek; Charbonneau, David; Doyle, Laurance; Fortney, Jonathan; Ford, Eric B.; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Rowe, Jason; Anderson, Howard; Buchhave, Lars; Ciardi, David; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Sherry, William; Horch, Elliott; Isaacson, Howard; Everett, Mark E.; Fischer, Debra; Torres, Guillermo; Johnson, John Asher; Endl, Michael; MacQueen, Phillip; Bryson, Stephen T.; Dotson, Jessie; Haas, Michael; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Allen, Christopher; Li, Jie; Wu, Haley; Tenenbaum, Peter; Verner, Ekaterina; Bruhweiler, Frederick; Barnes, Jason; Prsa, Andrej</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 327, Issue 5968, pp. 977- (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...327..977B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1724B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-11b: A Super-Neptune Planet Transiting a Bright K Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; P&#225;l, A.; Hartman, J.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Isaacson, H.; Howard, A.; Vogt, S.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Fernandez, J.; Mo&#243;r, A.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1724-1745 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401.1691M</bibcode>
			<title>On the formation of hot Neptunes and super-Earths</title>
			<authors>McNeil, D. S.; Nelson, R. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 3, pp. 1691-1708.</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401.1691M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..149S</bibcode>
			<title>Models of Neptune-Mass Exoplanets: Emergent Fluxes and Albedos</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent; Hubeny, Ivan; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 149-158 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..149S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708.1492R</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth Orbiting the Nearby Sun-like Star HD 1461</title>
			<authors>Rivera, Eugenio J.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Laughlin, Gregory; Henry, Gregory W.; Meschiari, Stefano</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 2, pp. 1492-1499 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...708.1492R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PABei..28...53J</bibcode>
			<title>Proper motions and the frontier of studies on the Galaxy.</title>
			<authors>Jin, W.-J.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 28, 53-71 (2010)</journal>
			<date>0/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PABei..28...53J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Natur.462..891C</bibcode>
			<title>A super-Earth transiting a nearby low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Berta, Zachory K.; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; Nutzman, Philip; Buchhave, Lars A.; Lovis, Christophe; Bonfils, Xavier; Latham, David W.; Udry, St&#233;phane; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Falco, Emilio E.; Winn, Joshua N.; Queloz, Didier; Pepe, Francesco; Mayor, Michel; Delfosse, Xavier; Forveille, Thierry</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 462, Issue 7275, pp. 891-894 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Natur.462..891C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707..446B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-13b,c: A Transiting Hot Jupiter with a Massive Outer Companion on an Eccentric Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Howard, A. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225; cs, G&#233;za; Fischer, D. A.; Latham, D. W.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sipocz, B.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Esquerdo, G. A.; P&#225;l, A.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, pp. 446-456 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707..446B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508.1509H</bibcode>
			<title>Transit detections of extrasolar planets around main-sequence stars. I. Sky maps for hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Heller, R.; Mislis, D.; Antoniadis, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1509-1516</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508.1509H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..785H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-12b: A Low-Density Sub-Saturn Mass Planet Transiting a Metal-Poor K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; P&#225;l, A.; Latham, D. W.; Sipocz, B.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 785-796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..785H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..769K</bibcode>
			<title>The 8 mum Phase Variation of the Hot Saturn HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Showman, Adam P.; Agol, Eric; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 769-784 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..769K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1797K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon - II</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1797-1804.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1797K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1737P</bibcode>
			<title>An analytical solution for Kepler's problem</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1737-1742.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1737P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699L..48D</bibcode>
			<title>Follow-up Observations of the Neptune Mass Transiting Extrasolar Planet HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, Jason A.; Close, Laird M.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Scuderi, Louis J.; Males, Jared R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. L48-L51 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699L..48D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501.1161M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planet population synthesis. II. Statistical comparison with observations</title>
			<authors>Mordasini, C.; Alibert, Y.; Benz, W.; Naef, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1161-1184</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501.1161M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501.1139M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planet population synthesis. I. Method, formation tracks, and mass-distance distribution</title>
			<authors>Mordasini, C.; Alibert, Y.; Benz, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1139-1160</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501.1139M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...697.1263O</bibcode>
			<title>A Neptune-mass Planet Orbiting the Nearby G Dwarf HD 16417</title>
			<authors>O'Toole, Simon; Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. Paul; Jones, Hugh R. A.; Bailey, Jeremy; Carter, Brad D.; Vogt, Steven S.; Laughlin, Gregory; Rivera, Eugenio J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 697, Issue 2, pp. 1263-1268 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...697.1263O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1950B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-10b: A Light and Moderately Hot Jupiter Transiting A K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; P&#225;l, A.; Torres, G.; Sipocz, B.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Hartman, J.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1950-1955 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1950B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...24J</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-30b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter on a Highly Oblique Orbit</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, J. N.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J. D.; Morton, T. D.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Sato, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Fur&#233;sz, G.; Quinn, S. N.; B&#233;ky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 1, article id. 24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735...24J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733..127S</bibcode>
			<title>Starspots and Spin-orbit Alignment in the WASP-4 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Carter, Joshua A.; Osip, David J.; Fuentes, Cesar I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. 127 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733..127S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...530A..97B</bibcode>
			<title>Accurate p-mode measurements of the G0V metal-rich CoRoT target HD 52265</title>
			<authors>Ballot, J.; Gizon, L.; Samadi, R.; Vauclair, G.; Benomar, O.; Bruntt, H.; Mosser, B.; Stahn, T.; Verner, G. A.; Campante, T. L.; Garc&#237;a, R. A.; Mathur, S.; Salabert, D.; Gaulme, P.; R&#233;gulo, C.; Roxburgh, I. W.; Appourchaux, T.; Baudin, F.; Catala, C.; Chaplin, W. J.; Deheuvels, S.; Michel, E.; Bazot, M.; Creevey, O.; Dolez, N.; Elsworth, Y.; Sato, K. H.; Vauclair, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 530, id.A97</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...530A..97B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...82C</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. XIII. Sixteen Transits of the Super-Earth GJ 1214b</title>
			<authors>Carter, Joshua A.; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Berta, Zachory K.; Burke, Christopher J.; Nutzman, Philip</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. 82 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...82C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63S.531H</bibcode>
			<title>A Possible Tilted Orbit of the Super-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Narita, Norio; Shporer, Avi; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.SP2, pp.531--536</journal>
			<date>3/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63S.531H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...98P</bibcode>
			<title>An Analysis of Jitter and Transit Timing Variations in the HAT-P-13 System</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 98 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...98P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527L..11H</bibcode>
			<title>The retrograde orbit of the HAT-P-6b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Ehrenreich, D.; Bouchy, F.; Delfosse, X.; Moutou, C.; Arnold, L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.L11</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527L..11H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...63W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Orientations of Exoplanets: HAT-P-4b is Prograde and HAT-P-14b is Retrograde</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Hartman, Joel D.; Holman, Matthew J.; Albrecht, Simon; Crepp, Justin R.; Morton, Timothy D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 63 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...63W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726L..19A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-30b: A 61 M Jup Brown Dwarf Transiting a V = 12, F8 Star</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Todd, I.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Barros, S. C. C.; Enoch, B.; Gillon, M.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. L19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726L..19A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726....2G</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of the Transiting Exoplanet Host HD 17156 with Hubble Space Telescope Fine Guidance Sensor</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; McCullough, Peter R.; Nelan, Edmund P.; Brown, Timothy M.; Charbonneau, David; Nutzman, Philip; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Kjeldsen, Hans</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id.2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726....2G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724.1108J</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect of Exoplanet Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Cochran, William D.; Welsh, William F.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John Asher; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Howard, Andrew W.; MacQueen, Phillip; Orosz, Jerome A.; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Allen, Christopher; Tenenbaum, Peter; Wu, Hayley; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Cote, Miles T.; McCauliff, Sean; Girouard, Forrest R.; Gunter, Jay P.; Wohler, Bill; Hall, Jennifer R.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Kamal Uddin, AKM; Wu, Michael S.; Bhavsar, Paresh A.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Pletcher, David L.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, article id. 1108-1119 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724.1108J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723L.223W</bibcode>
			<title>The Oblique Orbit of the Super-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Hartman, Joel D.; Albrecht, Simon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 723, Issue 2, pp. L223-L227 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723L.223W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1290G</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Parameters and Metallicities of Stars Hosting Jovian and Neptunian Mass Planets: A Possible Dependence of Planetary Mass on Metallicity</title>
			<authors>Ghezzi, L.; Cunha, K.; Smith, V. V.; de Ara&#250;jo, F. X.; Schuler, S. C.; de la Reza, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1290-1302 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1290G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717..235D</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Observations of the WASP-10 System</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, J. A.; Close, L. M.; Scuderi, L. J.; Morris, M. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 1, pp. 235-238 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717..235D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.164C</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismic Investigation of Known Planet Hosts in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Kjeldsen, H.; Brown, T. M.; Gilliland, R. L.; Arentoft, T.; Frandsen, S.; Quirion, P.-O.; Borucki, W. J.; Koch, D.; Jenkins, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L164-L168 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.164C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.160G</bibcode>
			<title>Initial Characteristics of Kepler Short Cadence Data</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer; Klaus, Todd; Koch, David; McCauliff, Sean; Quintana, Elisa V.; Twicken, Joseph D.; van Cleve, Jeffrey E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L160-L163 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.160G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.131K</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of the Transiting Planet Kepler-5b</title>
			<authors>Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Caldwell, John; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ron L.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoff W.; Morrison, David; Tarter, Jill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, article id. L131-L135 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.131K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..974R</bibcode>
			<title>A Framework for Quantifying the Degeneracies of Exoplanet Interior Compositions</title>
			<authors>Rogers, L. A.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 2, pp. 974-991 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..974R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1724B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-11b: A Super-Neptune Planet Transiting a Bright K Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; P&#225;l, A.; Hartman, J.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Isaacson, H.; Howard, A.; Vogt, S.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Fernandez, J.; Mo&#243;r, A.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1724-1745 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..149S</bibcode>
			<title>Models of Neptune-Mass Exoplanets: Emergent Fluxes and Albedos</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent; Hubeny, Ivan; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 149-158 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..149S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..785H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-12b: A Low-Density Sub-Saturn Mass Planet Transiting a Metal-Poor K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; P&#225;l, A.; Latham, D. W.; Sipocz, B.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 785-796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..785H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699L..48D</bibcode>
			<title>Follow-up Observations of the Neptune Mass Transiting Extrasolar Planet HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, Jason A.; Close, Laird M.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Scuderi, Louis J.; Males, Jared R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. L48-L51 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699L..48D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AcA....59..213M</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Study of Kepler Asteroseismic Targets</title>
			<authors>Molenda-Zakowicz, J.; Jerzykiewicz, M.; Frasca, A.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, vol 59, no 2, p. 213-237</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AcA....59..213M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MmSAI..79..644M</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler primary asteroseismic targets - ground-based study .</title>
			<authors>Molenda-Zakowicz, J.; Frasca, A.; Latham, D.; Jerzykiewicz, M.; Bazot, M.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ&#224; Astronomica Italiana, v.79, p.644 (2008)</journal>
			<date>0/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MmSAI..79..644M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AcA....57..301M</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic Study of Kepler Asteroseismic Targets</title>
			<authors>Molenda-Zakowicz, J.; Frasca, A.; Latham, D. W.; Jerzykiewicz, M.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, v.57, pp. 301-321, (2007).</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AcA....57..301M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005AJ....129.1483L</bibcode>
			<title>A Catalog of Northern Stars with Annual Proper Motions Larger than 0.15" (LSPM-NORTH Catalog)</title>
			<authors>L&#233;pine, S&#233;bastien; Shara, Michael M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 129, Issue 3, pp. 1483-1522.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005AJ....129.1483L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...582.1011S</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Astrometry and Photometry for the Luyten Catalog. II. Faint Stars and the Revised Catalog</title>
			<authors>Salim, Samir; Gould, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 582, Issue 2, pp. 1011-1031.</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...582.1011S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984AJ.....89..702L</bibcode>
			<title>Spectral classification of high-proper-motion stars</title>
			<authors>Lee, S.-G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 89, May 1984, p. 702-719.</journal>
			<date>5/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984AJ.....89..702L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
