<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...80Q</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-25b: A Hot-Jupiter Transiting a Moderately Faint G Star</title>
			<authors>Quinn, S. N.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Szentgyorgyi, A.; Fursz, G.; Buchhave, L. A.; Bky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 80 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...80Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734..109B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-27b: A Hot Jupiter Transiting a G Star on a 3 Day Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bky, B.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Jordn, A.; Arriagada, P.; Bayliss, D.; Kiss, L. L.; Kovcs, Gza; Quinn, S. N.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 2, article id. 109 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734..109B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A.130S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-34b: a near-grazing transiting sub-Jupiter-mass exoplanet in a hierarchical triple system</title>
			<authors>Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Gillon, M.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wood, P. L.; Bento, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A130</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A.130S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...80Q</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-25b: A Hot-Jupiter Transiting a Moderately Faint G Star</title>
			<authors>Quinn, S. N.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Szentgyorgyi, A.; Fursz, G.; Buchhave, L. A.; Bky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 80 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...80Q</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
