<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750...84B</bibcode>
			<title>Qatar-2: A K Dwarf Orbited by a Transiting Hot Jupiter and a More Massive Companion in an Outer Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bryan, Marta L.; Alsubai, Khalid A.; Latham, David W.; Parley, Neil R.; Collier Cameron, Andrew; Quinn, Samuel N.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fulton, Benjamin J.; Berlind, Perry; Brown, Warren R.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Calkins, Michael L.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Fursz, Gbor; Gre Jrgensen, Uffe; Horne, Keith D.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Street, Rachel A.; Torres, Guillermo; West, Richard G.; Dominik, Martin; Harpse, Kennet B. W.; Liebig, Christine; Calchi Novati, Sebastiano; Ricci, Davide; Skottfelt, Jesper F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 1, article id. 84 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750...84B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749..134H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-17b,c: A Transiting, Eccentric, Hot Saturn and a Long-period, Cold Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Howard, A. W.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Mazeh, T.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Bky, B.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 2, article id. 134 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749..134H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749..134H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-17b,c: A Transiting, Eccentric, Hot Saturn and a Long-period, Cold Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Howard, A. W.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Mazeh, T.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Bky, B.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 2, article id. 134 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749..134H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1573V</bibcode>
			<title>Transit variability in bow shock-hosting planets</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1573-1582.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1573V</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
