<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..82K</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for enhanced chromospheric Ca II H and K emission in stars with close-in extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A82</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..82K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742..116B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-20b-HAT-P-23b: Four Massive Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Kipping, D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Shporer, A.; Bky, B.; Buchhave, L. A.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...59H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-32b and HAT-P-33b: Two Highly Inflated Hot Jupiters Transiting High-jitter Stars</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, Gza; Bky, B.; Quinn, S. N.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; Szklenr, T.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...59H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742..116B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-20b-HAT-P-23b: Four Massive Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Kipping, D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Shporer, A.; Bky, B.; Buchhave, L. A.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A.116D</bibcode>
			<title>Prospecting transit duration variations in extrasolar planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Damiani, C.; Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A116</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...535A.116D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..41C</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XVII. The hot Jupiter CoRoT-17b: a very old planet</title>
			<authors>Csizmadia, Sz.; Moutou, C.; Deleuil, M.; Cabrera, J.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Almenara, J.-M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cavarroc, C.; Cochran, W.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fruth, Th.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; Hbrard, G.; Jehin, E.; Jorda, L.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Mazeh, T.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Titz-Weider, R.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A41</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..41C</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
