<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751..158H</bibcode>
			<title>Migration Then Assembly: Formation of Neptune-mass Planets inside 1 AU</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Murray, Norm</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. 158 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...751..158H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751...96P</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Tidal Dissipation in Stars from the Destruction Rates of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Penev, Kaloyan; Jackson, Brian; Spada, Federico; Thom, Nicole</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. 96 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...751...96P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..82K</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for enhanced chromospheric Ca II H and K emission in stars with close-in extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A82</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..82K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....7C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-18b, c, and d: A System of Three Planets Confirmed by Transit Timing Variations, Light Curve Validation, Warm-Spitzer Photometry, and Radial Velocity Measurements</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran ois; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steve B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Borucki, William. J.; Koch, David G.; Winn, Joshua N.; Welsh, William F.; Uddin, Kamal; Tenenbaum, Peter; Still, M.; Seager, Sara; Quinn, Samuel N.; Mullally, F.; Miller, Neil; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Lucas, Phillip; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Knutson, Heather; Kinemuchi, K.; Johnson, John A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew; Horch, Elliott; Holman, Matthew J.; Henze, Christopher E.; Haas, Michael R.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Ford, Eric B.; Fischer, Debra A.; Everett, Mark; Endl, Michael; Demory, Brice-Oliver; Deming, Drake; Charbonneau, David; Caldwell, Douglas; Buchhave, Lars; Brown, Timothy M.; Batalha, Natalie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....7C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A.114D</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a transit of the super-Earth 55 Cancri e with warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Demory, B.-O.; Gillon, M.; Deming, D.; Valencia, D.; Seager, S.; Benneke, B.; Lovis, C.; Cubillos, P.; Harrington, J.; Stevenson, K. B.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A114</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A.114D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...50K</bibcode>
			<title>An Independent Analysis of Kepler-4b Through Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David; Bakos, Gspr</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. 50 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...50K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...10H</bibcode>
			<title>The NASA-UC Eta-Earth Program. III. A Super-Earth Orbiting HD 97658 and a Neptune-mass Planet Orbiting Gl 785</title>
			<authors>Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Wright, Jason T.; Henry, Gregory W.; Isaacson, Howard; Valenti, Jeff A.; Anderson, Jay; Piskunov, Nikolai E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. 10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...10H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...41M</bibcode>
			<title>High Metallicity and Non-equilibrium Chemistry in the Dayside Atmosphere of hot-Neptune GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...41M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..138H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-26b: A Low-density Neptune-mass Planet Transiting a K Star</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Kipping, D. M.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Quinn, S. N.; Buchhave, L. A.; Bky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 138 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727L..44S</bibcode>
			<title>A Short-period Censor of Sub-Jupiter Mass Exoplanets with Low Density</title>
			<authors>Szab, Gy. M.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. L44 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727L..44S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..138H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-26b: A Low-density Neptune-mass Planet Transiting a K Star</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Kipping, D. M.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Quinn, S. N.; Buchhave, L. A.; Bky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 138 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..138H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
