<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>The Heavy-element Masses of Extrasolar Giant Planets, Revealed</title>
			<authors>Miller, Neil; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734..109B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-27b: A Hot Jupiter Transiting a G Star on a 3 Day Orbit</title>
			<authors>B&#233;ky, B.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Jord&#225;n, A.; Arriagada, P.; Bayliss, D.; Kiss, L. L.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Quinn, S. N.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 2, article id. 109 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734..109B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..54B</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-38b: a transiting exoplanet in an eccentric, 6.87d period orbit</title>
			<authors>Barros, S. C. C.; Faedi, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Lister, T. A.; McCormac, J.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; H&#233;brard, G.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Bento, J.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Skillen, I.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A54</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..54B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..866K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-15b: A 10.9 Day Extrasolar Planet Transiting a Solar-type Star</title>
			<authors>Kov&#225;cs, G.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J. D.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, B. B&#233;ky J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, pp. 866-877 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..866K</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar />
</planet>
