<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewA...17..438D</bibcode>
			<title>A revised orbital ephemeris for HAT-P-9b</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, Jason A.; Close, Laird M.; Scuderi, Louis J.; Turner, Jake; Stephenson, Peter C.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 17, Issue 4, p. 438-441.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012NewA...17..438D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..191M</bibcode>
			<title>Carbon-rich Giant Planets: Atmospheric Chemistry, Thermal Inversions, Spectra, and Formation Conditions</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, Nikku; Mousis, Olivier; Johnson, Torrence V.; Lunine, Jonathan I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 191 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..191M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...61S</bibcode>
			<title>Starspots, Spin-Orbit Misalignment, and Active Latitudes in the HAT-P-11 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 61 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...61S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...10B</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Misalignment of KOI-13.01 from Its Gravity-darkened Kepler Transit Lightcurve</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.; Linscott, Ethan; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...10B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740L..10N</bibcode>
			<title>Using Star Spots to Measure the Spin-orbit Alignment of Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 740, Issue 1, article id. L10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740L..10N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740...33D</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler and Ground-based Transits of the Exo-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Sada, Pedro V.; Jackson, Brian; Peterson, Steven W.; Agol, Eric; Knutson, Heather A.; Jennings, Donald E.; Haase, Flynn; Bays, Kevin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 740, Issue 1, article id. 33 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740...33D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534L...6T</bibcode>
			<title>The time dependence of hot Jupiters' orbital inclinations</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.L6</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534L...6T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A.114D</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a transit of the super-Earth 55 Cancri e with warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>