<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..187S</bibcode>
			<title>The RAdial Velocity Experiment (RAVE): Third Data Release</title>
			<authors>Siebert, A.; Williams, M. E. K.; Siviero, A.; Reid, W.; Boeche, C.; Steinmetz, M.; Fulbright, J.; Munari, U.; Zwitter, T.; Watson, F. G.; Wyse, R. F. G.; de Jong, R. S.; Enke, H.; Anguiano, B.; Burton, D.; Cass, C. J. P.; Fiegert, K.; Hartley, M.; Ritter, A.; Russel, K. S.; Stupar, M.; Bienaym, O.; Freeman, K. C.; Gilmore, G.; Grebel, E. K.; Helmi, A.; Navarro, J. F.; Binney, J.; Bland-Hawthorn, J.; Campbell, R.; Famaey, B.; Gerhard, O.; Gibson, B. K.; Matijevic, G.; Parker, Q. A.; Seabroke, G. M.; Sharma, S.; Smith, M. C.; Wylie-de Boer, E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 6, article id. 187 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..187S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A..54Z</bibcode>
			<title>Distance determination for RAVE stars using stellar models . II. Most likely values assuming a standard stellar evolution scenario</title>
			<authors>Zwitter, T.; Matijevic, G.; Breddels, M. A.; Smith, M. C.; Helmi, A.; Munari, U.; Bienaym, O.; Binney, J.; Bland-Hawthorn, J.; Boeche, C.; Brown, A. G. A.; Campbell, R.; Freeman, K. C.; Fulbright, J.; Gibson, B.; Gilmore, G.; Grebel, E. K.; Navarro, J. F.; Parker, Q. A.; Seabroke, G. M.; Siebert, A.; Siviero, A.; Steinmetz, M.; Watson, F. G.; Williams, M.; Wyse, R. F. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A54</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...522A..54Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...511A..90B</bibcode>
			<title>Distance determination for RAVE stars using stellar models</title>
			<authors>Breddels, M. A.; Smith, M. C.; Helmi, A.; Bienaym, O.; Binney, J.; Bland-Hawthorn, J.; Boeche, C.; Burnett, B. C. M.; Campbell, R.; Freeman, K. C.; Gibson, B.; Gilmore, G.; Grebel, E. K.; Munari, U.; Navarro, J. F.; Parker, Q. A.; Seabroke, G. M.; Siebert, A.; Siviero, A.; Steinmetz, M.; Watson, F. G.; Williams, M.; Wyse, R. F. G.; Zwitter, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 511, id.A90</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...511A..90B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
