<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738...81W</bibcode>
			<title>The Frequency of Low-mass Exoplanets. III. Toward eta&amp;oplus; at Short Periods</title>
			<authors>Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. P.; O'Toole, Simon J.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Bailey, J.; Horner, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 81 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738...81W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...68B</bibcode>
			<title>Density Estimation for Projected Exoplanet Quantities</title>
			<authors>Brown, Robert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 68 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...68B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1792B</bibcode>
			<title>Connecting planets around horizontal branch stars with known exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Bear, Ealeal; Soker, Noam</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 3, pp. 1792-1802.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1792B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727..102W</bibcode>
			<title>On the Frequency of Jupiter Analogs</title>
			<authors>Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Tinney, C. G.; O'Toole, Simon J.; Jones, H. R. A.; Butler, R. P.; Carter, B. D.; Bailey, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 102 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727..102W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1015A</bibcode>
			<title>The Origin of the Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Abt, Helmut A.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 895, pp.1015-1019</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1015A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.1703J</bibcode>
			<title>A long-period planet orbiting a nearby Sun-like star</title>
			<authors>Jones, Hugh R. A.; Butler, R. Paul; Tinney, C. G.; O'Toole, Simon; Wittenmyer, Rob; Henry, Gregory W.; Meschiari, Stefano; Vogt, Steve; Rivera, Eugenio; Laughlin, Greg; Carter, Brad D.; Bailey, Jeremy; Jenkins, James S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 4, pp. 1703-1713.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.1703J</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar />
</planet>
