<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414..108B</bibcode>
			<title>On the use of the Virtual Observatory to select calibrators for phase-referenced astrometry of exoplanet-host stars</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonneau, D.; Mourard, D.; Lafrasse, S.; Mella, G.; Duvert, G.; Chelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. 108-115.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414..108B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733..126C</bibcode>
			<title>Estimates of the Planet Yield from Ground-based High-contrast Imaging Observations as a Function of Stellar Mass</title>
			<authors>Crepp, Justin R.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. 126 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733..126C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...68B</bibcode>
			<title>Density Estimation for Projected Exoplanet Quantities</title>
			<authors>Brown, Robert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 68 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...68B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..818K</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Phase Variations of Long-period Eccentric Planets</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. 818-826 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..818K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..47S</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. XXI. Three new giant planets orbiting the metal-poor stars HD 5388, HD 181720, and HD 190984</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Benz, W.; Bouchy, F.; Figueira, P.; Lo Curto, G.; Lovis, C.; Melo, C.; Moutou, C.; Naef, D.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Sousa, S. G.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A47</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..47S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A.112S</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extrasolar planets. XXV. Results from the metal-poor sample</title>
			<authors>