<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723L..60H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-29b: A Saturn-sized Transiting Exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Enoch, B.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233; gransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. L60-L63 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723L..60H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..66B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XI. CoRoT-8b: a hot and dense sub-Saturn around a K1 dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Cabrera, J.; Jorda, L.; Lovis, C.; Csizmadia, S.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Ollivier, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A66</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..66B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A..98B</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-21b: a hot-Saturn exoplanet transiting a thick disc star</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Hebb, L.; Skillen, I.; Collier Cameron, A.; Smalley, B.; Udry, S.; Anderson, D. R.; Boisse, I.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hellier, C.; Joshi, Y.; Kane, S. R.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Smith, A. M. S.; Stempels, H. C.; Street, R.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A98</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A..98B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719.1796B</bibcode>
			<title>NICMOS Observations of the Transiting Hot Jupiter XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Burke, Christopher J.; McCullough, P. R.; Bergeron, L. E.; Long, Douglas; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Nelan, Edmund P.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Janes, Kenneth A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 2, pp. 1796-1806 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719.1796B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1724B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-11b: A Super-Neptune Planet Transiting a Bright K Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; P&#225;l, A.; Hartman, J.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Isaacson, H.; Howard, A.; Vogt, S.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Fernandez, J.; Mo&#243;r, A.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1724-1745 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1551O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Planetary Emission from the Exoplanet Tres-2 Using Spitzer/IRAC</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Harrington, Joseph; Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1551-1556 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1551O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..186...48J</bibcode>
			<title>On the Fundamental Mass-Period Functions of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jiang, Ing-Guey; Yeh, Li-Chin; Chang, Yen-Chang; Hung, Wen-Liang</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 186, Issue 1, pp. 48-62 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..186...48J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..149S</bibcode>
			<title>Models of Neptune-Mass Exoplanets: Emergent Fluxes and Albedos</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent; Hubeny, Ivan; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 149-158 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..149S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Natur.462..891C</bibcode>
			<title>A super-Earth transiting a nearby low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Berta, Zachory K.; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; Nutzman, Philip; Buchhave, Lars A.; Lovis, Christophe; Bonfils, Xavier; Latham, David W.; Udry, St&#233;phane; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Falco, Emilio E.; Winn, Joshua N.; Queloz, Didier; Pepe, Francesco; Mayor, Michel; Delfosse, Xavier; Forveille, Thierry</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 462, Issue 7275, pp. 891-894 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Natur.462..891C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..785H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-12b: A Low-Density Sub-Saturn Mass Planet Transiting a Metal-Poor K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; P&#225;l, A.; Latham, D. W.; Sipocz, B.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 785-796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..785H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1016M</bibcode>
			<title>Systemic: A Testbed for Characterizing the Detection of Extrasolar Planets. I. The Systemic Console Package</title>
			<authors>Meschiari, Stefano; Wolf, Aaron S.; Rivera, Eugenio; Laughlin, Gregory; Vogt, Steve; Butler, Paul</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 883, pp.1016-1027</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1016M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..769K</bibcode>
			<title>The 8 mum Phase Variation of the Hot Saturn HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Showman, Adam P.; Agol, Eric; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 769-784 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..769K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701L..20Z</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Sulfur Photochemistry on Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Zahnle, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.; Lodders, K.; Fortney, J. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. L20-L24 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701L..20Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.1616A</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting Transits of Planetary Companions to Giant Stars</title>
			<authors>Assef, R. J.; Gaudi, B. S.; Stanek, K. Z.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 1616-1626 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.1616A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..514M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission of XO-2b: Evidence for a Weak Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 514-520 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..514M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1797K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon - II</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1797-1804.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1797K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699.1487S</bibcode>
			<title>Can TiO Explain Thermal Inversions in the Upper Atmospheres of Irradiated Giant Planets?</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Silverio, Katie; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 2, pp. 1487-1500 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699.1487S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501..785G</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and characterization of WASP-6b, an inflated sub-Jupiter mass planet transiting a solar-type star</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Anderson, D. R.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pollaco, D.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Parley, N.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 2, 2009, pp.785-792</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501..785G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...697.1256H</bibcode>
			<title>Heavy-element Enrichment of a Jupiter-mass Protoplanet as a Function of Orbital Location</title>
			<authors>Helled, R.; Schubert, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 697, Issue 2, pp. 1256-1262 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...697.1256H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1950B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-10b: A Light and Moderately Hot Jupiter Transiting A K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; P&#225;l, A.; Torres, G.; Sipocz, B.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Hartman, J.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1950-1955 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1950B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1230F</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Spin-Orbit Alignment: Results from the Ensemble of Rossiter-McLaughlin Observations</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1230-1240 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1230F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1116W</bibcode>
			<title>Nondetection of Polarized, Scattered Light from the HD 189733b Hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Wiktorowicz, Sloane J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1116-1124 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1116W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696..241C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Transit Photometry of the Exoplanet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Carter, Joshua A.; Winn, Joshua N.; Gilliland, Ronald; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 1, pp. 241-253 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696..241C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...695L.159D</bibcode>
			<title>Discovering the Growth Histories of Exoplanets: The Saturn Analog HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Bodenheimer, Peter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 695, Issue 2, pp. L159-L162 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...695L.159D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694..183F</bibcode>
			<title>Protostellar Cloud Fragmentation and Inward Migration by Disk Capture as the Origin of Massive Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Font-Ribera, Andreu; Miralda Escud&#233;, Jordi; Ribas, Ignasi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 1, pp. 183-191 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694..183F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694..107B</bibcode>
			<title>Analytical Solutions for Radiative Transfer: Implications for Giant Planet Formation by Disk Instability</title>
			<authors>Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 1, pp. 107-114 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694..107B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692..229N</bibcode>
			<title>A Precise Estimate of the Radius of the Exoplanet HD 149026b from Spitzer Photometry</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip; Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Knutson, Heather A.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Holman, Matthew J.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. 229-235 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692..229N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691.1145S</bibcode>
			<title>A New Spectroscopic and Photometric Analysis of the Transiting Planet Systems TrES-3 and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Korzennik, Sylvain G.; Holman, Matthew J.; Latham, David W.; Laird, John B.; Fernandez, Jos&#233;; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward; Everett, Mark E.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Belmonte, Juan A.; Deeg, Hans J.; Brown, Timothy N.; Hidas, M&#225;rton G.; Baliber, Nairn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 2, pp. 1145-1158 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691.1145S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392..181K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 1, pp. 181-189.</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392..181K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691..866K</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of A Temperature Inversion in the Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Burrows, Adam; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 1, pp. 866-874 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690..822K</bibcode>
			<title>Multiwavelength Constraints on the Day-Night Circulation Patterns of HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Showman, Adam P.; Agol, Eric; Henry, Gregory W.; Everett, Mark E.; Allen, Lori E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 1, pp. 822-836 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690..822K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PABei..27...14Z</bibcode>
			<title>The detection methods and statistical characteristics of exoplanet.</title>
			<authors>Zhang, N.; Ji, J.-H.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 27, 14-28 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PABei..27...14Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJS..179..484H</bibcode>
			<title>On the Absorption and Redistribution of Energy in Irradiated Planets</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 179, Issue 2, pp. 484-508.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJS..179..484H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689..492K</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Orbital Parameters through Planetary Transit Monitoring</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 1, pp. 492-498.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689..492K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.390.1258B</bibcode>
			<title>HD179949b: a close orbiting extrasolar giant planet with a stratosphere?</title>
			<authors>Barnes, J. R.; Barman, Travis S.; Jones, H. R. A.; Leigh, C. J.; Cameron, A. Collier; Barber, R. J.; Pinfield, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 390, Issue 3, pp. 1258-1266.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.390.1258B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origins of Eccentric Close-In Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Takeda, Genya; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. L29-L32.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..580C</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical Outcomes of Planet-Planet Scattering</title>
			<authors>Chatterjee, Sourav; Ford, Eric B.; Matsumura, Soko; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 580-602.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..580C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...685.1210L</bibcode>
			<title>Extent of Pollution in Planet-bearing Stars</title>
			<authors>Li, S.-L.; Lin, D. N. C.; Liu, X.-W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 685, Issue 2, pp. 1210-1219.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...685.1210L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...685..584I</bibcode>
			<title>Toward a Deterministic Model of Planetary Formation. V. Accumulation Near the Ice Line and Super-Earths</title>
			<authors>Ida, S.; Lin, D. N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 685, Issue 1, pp. 584-595.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...685..584I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684.1427M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission of Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Burrows, Adam; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 2, pp. 1427-1432.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684.1427M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488..763H</bibcode>
			<title>Misaligned spin-orbit in the XO-3 planetary system?</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Loeillet, B.; Rabus, M.; Bonfils, X.; Moutou, C.; Boisse, I.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488..763H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1277B</bibcode>
			<title>Optical Albedo Theory of Strongly Irradiated Giant Planets: The Case of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Ibgui, L.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1277-1282.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1277B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681.1631J</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 2, pp. 1631-1638.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681.1631J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1419F</bibcode>
			<title>A Unified Theory for the Atmospheres of the Hot and Very Hot Jupiters: Two Classes of Irradiated Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Lodders, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1419-1435.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1419F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1396J</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1396-1406.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1396J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482L..25B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. III. The spectroscopic transit of CoRoT-Exo-2b with SOPHIE and HARPS</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Queloz, D.; Deleuil, M.; Loeillet, B.; Hatzes, A. P.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 3, 2008, pp.L25-L28</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482L..25B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.385.1576P</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-3b: a strongly irradiated transiting gas-giant planet</title>
			<authors>Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Collier Cameron, A.; Loeillet, B.; Stempels, H. C.; Bouchy, F.; Gibson, N. P.; Hebb, L.; H&#233;brard, G.; Joshi, Y. C.; McDonald, I.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Wheatley, P. J.; Aigrain, S.; Alsubai, K.; Benn, C. R.; Bruce, V. A.; Christian, D. J.; Clarkson, W. I.; Enoch, B.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hickey, S.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, K.; Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Keenan, F. P.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J. P.; Parley, N.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Simpson, E.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 385, Issue 3, pp. 1576-1584.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.385.1576P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677..607B</bibcode>
			<title>Flux-limited Diffusion Approximation Models of Giant Planet Formation by Disk Instability</title>
			<authors>Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. 607-615.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677..607B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482..315B</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and evolution of super-Earth to super-Jupiter exoplanets. I. Heavy element enrichment in the interior</title>
			<authors>Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 1, 2008, pp.315-332</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482..315B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008PASP..120..317N</bibcode>
			<title>Design Considerations for a Ground-Based Transit Search for Habitable Planets Orbiting M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip; Charbonneau, David</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 120, issue 865, pp.317-327</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008PASP..120..317N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...675.1531W</bibcode>
			<title>Five New Transits of the Super-Neptune HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Henry, Gregory W.; Torres, Guillermo; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 675, Issue 2, pp. 1531-1537.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...675.1531W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673.1160A</bibcode>
			<title>Ocean Planet or Thick Atmosphere: On the Mass-Radius Relationship for Solid Exoplanets with Massive Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; Seager, S.; Elkins-Tanton, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 2, pp. 1160-1164.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673.1160A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671.2115B</bibcode>
			<title>XO-2b: Transiting Hot Jupiter in a Metal-rich Common Proper Motion Binary</title>
			<authors>Burke, Christopher J.; McCullough, P. R.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Janes, Kenneth A.; Heasley, J. N.; Summers, F. J.; Stys, J. E.; Bissinger, R.; Fleenor, Michael L.; Foote, Cindy N.; Garc&#237;a-Melendo, Enrique; Gary, Bruce L.; Howell, P. J.; Mallia, F.; Masi, G.; Taylor, B.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 2, pp. 2115-2128.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671.2115B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671..861H</bibcode>
			<title>Two Classes of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. 861-871.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671..861H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...670..826B</bibcode>
			<title>HD 147506b: A Supermassive Planet in an Eccentric Orbit Transiting a Bright Star</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Kov&#225;cs, G.; Torres, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.; Butler, R. P.; Stefanik, R. P.; Fern&#225;ndez, J. M.; Sozzetti, A.; P&#225;l, A.; Johnson, J.; Marcy, G. W.; Winn, J. N.; Sipocz, B.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 670, Issue 1, pp. 826-832.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...670..826B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1345H</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude Photometry for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Candidates. IV. Solution to the Puzzle of the Extremely Red OGLE-TR-82 Primary</title>
			<authors>Hoyer, Sergio; Ram&#237;rez Alegr&#237;a, Sebasti&#225;n; Ivanov, Valentin D.; Minniti, Dante; Pietrzynski, Grzegorz; Ru&#237;z, Mar&#237;a Teresa; Gieren, Wolfgang; Udalski, Andrzej; Zoccali, Manuela; Carrasco, Eleazar Rodrigo; D&#237;az, Rodrigo F.; Fern&#225;ndez, Jos&#233; Miguel; Gallardo, Jos&#233;; Rejkuba, Marina; P&#233;rez, Felipe</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1345-1353.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1345H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1298F</bibcode>
			<title>Shrinking Binary and Planetary Orbits by Kozai Cycles with Tidal Friction</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel; Tremaine, Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1298-1315.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1298F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1279S</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-Radius Relationships for Solid Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Seager, S.; Kuchner, M.; Hier-Majumder, C. A.; Militzer, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1279-1297.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1279S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..729F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting and predicting the yield of transit surveys: giant planets in the OGLE fields</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Morello, V.; Pont, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 2, November IV 2007, pp.729-746</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..729F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..359G</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting low-frequency radio fluxes of known extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Grie&#223;meier, J.-M.; Zarka, P.; Spreeuw, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 1, November III 2007, pp.359-368</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..359G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.380.1488K</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of exoplanetary transits from radial velocity surveys</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 380, Issue 4, pp. 1488-1496.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.380.1488K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...668L.171B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectral Models of the Planet HD 209458b with a Thermal Inversion and Water Emission Bands</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Knutson, H. A.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 668, Issue 2, pp. L171-L174.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...668L.171B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667L.191L</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission from Transiting Very Hot Jupiters: Prospects for Ground-based Detection at Optical Wavelengths</title>
			<authors>L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 2, pp. L191-L194.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667L.191L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...474..301B</bibcode>
			<title>A method to detect H{2} in the atmosphere of transiting extrasolar planets using the EUV spectrum</title>
			<authors>Barth&#233;l&#233;my, M.; Lilensten, J.; Parkinson, C. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 474, Issue 1, October IV 2007, pp.301-306</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...474..301B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.380..683W</bibcode>
			<title>Light-induced disassembly of dusty bodies in inner protoplanetary discs: implications for the formation of planets</title>
			<authors>Wurm, Gerhard</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 380, Issue 2, pp. 683-690.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.380..683W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667..549W</bibcode>
			<title>A Determination of the Spin-Orbit Alignment of the Anomalously Dense Planet Orbiting HD 149026</title>
			<authors>Wolf, Aaron S.; Laughlin, Gregory; Henry, Gregory W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Marcy, Geoff; Butler, Paul; Vogt, Steve</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 1, pp. 549-556.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667..549W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...666L.121T</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-3b: A Heavy-Element-rich Planet Transiting a K Dwarf Star</title>
			<authors>Torres, G.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Kov&#225;cs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Fern&#225;ndez, J. M.; Noyes, R. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sozzetti, A.; Fischer, D. A.; Butler, R. P.; Marcy, G. W.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 666, Issue 2, pp. L121-L124.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...666L.121T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...666..475M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Planet Taxonomy: A New Statistical Approach</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 666, Issue 1, pp. 475-485.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...666..475M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...666..447Z</bibcode>
			<title>Planetesimal Accretion onto Growing Proto-Gas Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Zhou, Ji-Lin; Lin, Douglas N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 666, Issue 1, pp. 447-465.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...666..447Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379..773S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-1: a lithium- and metal-rich star with an oversized planet</title>
			<authors>Stempels, H. C.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hebb, L.; Smalley, B.; Frandsen, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 379, Issue 2, pp. 773-778.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379..773S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664.1190S</bibcode>
			<title>Improving Stellar and Planetary Parameters of Transiting Planet Systems: The Case of TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Latham, David W.; Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Laird, John B.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 2, pp. 1190-1198.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664.1190S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AJ....134..749B</bibcode>
			<title>The Mass of the Candidate Exoplanet Companion to HD 33636 from Hubble Space Telescope Astrometry and High-Precision Radial Velocities</title>
			<authors>Bean, Jacob L.; McArthur, Barbara E.; Benedict, G. Fritz; Harrison, Thomas E.; Bizyaev, Dmitry; Nelan, Edmund; Smith, Verne V.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 134, Issue 2, pp. 749-758.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AJ....134..749B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...470.1137M</bibcode>
			<title>A new search for planet transits in NGC 6791</title>
			<authors>Montalto, M.; Piotto, G.; Desidera, S.; de Marchi, F.; Bruntt, H.; Stetson, P. B.; Arellano Ferro, A.; Momany, Y.; Gratton, R. G.; Poretti, E.; Aparicio, A.; Barbieri, M.; Claudi, R. U.; Grundahl, F.; Rosenberg, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 470, Issue 3, August II 2007, pp.1137-1156</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...470.1137M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AstL...33..488K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar low-orbit planets: Dissipation of their atmospheres and probable magnetic field</title>
			<authors>Ksanfomality, L. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Letters, Volume 33, Issue 7, pp.488-497</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AstL...33..488K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664L..51F</bibcode>
			<title>Using Transit Timing Observations to Search for Trojans of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 1, pp. L51-L54.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664L..51F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007Natur.447..691H</bibcode>
			<title>The hottest planet</title>
			<authors>Harrington, Joseph; Luszcz, Statia; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Richardson, L. Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 447, Issue 7145, pp. 691-693 (2007).</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007Natur.447..691H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.377.1511H</bibcode>
			<title>Using long-term transit timing to detect terrestrial planets</title>
			<authors>Heyl, Jeremy S.; Gladman, Brett J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 377, Issue 4, pp. 1511-1519.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.377.1511H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...661L.195B</bibcode>
			<title>Direct Measurement of the Radius and Density of the Transiting Exoplanet HD 189733b with the CHARA Array</title>
			<authors>Baines, Ellyn K.; van Belle, Gerard T.; ten Brummelaar, Theo A.; McAlister, Harold A.; Swain, Mark; Turner, Nils H.; Sturmann, Laszlo; Sturmann, Judit</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 661, Issue 2, pp. L195-L198.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...661L.195B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.377L..44B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical planetary mass spectra - a prediction for COROT</title>
			<authors>Broeg, C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 377, Issue 1, pp. L44-L48.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.377L..44B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...661..502B</bibcode>
			<title>Possible Solutions to the Radius Anomalies of Transiting Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Hubbard, W. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 661, Issue 1, pp. 502-514.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...661..502B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..823M</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of Earth-like Planets During and After Giant Planet Migration</title>
			<authors>Mandell, Avi M.; Raymond, Sean N.; Sigurdsson, Steinn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 823-844.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..823M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.376.1296S</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric follow-up of the transiting planet WASP-1b</title>
			<authors>Shporer, A.; Tamuz, O.; Zucker, S.; Mazeh, T.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 376, Issue 3, pp. 1296-1300.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.376.1296S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...659.1661F</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Radii across Five Orders of Magnitude in Mass and Stellar Insolation: Application to Transits</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Marley, M. S.; Barnes, J. W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 659, Issue 2, pp. 1661-1672.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...659.1661F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1322C</bibcode>
			<title>Precise Radius Estimates for the Exoplanets WASP-1b and WASP-2b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Everett, Mark E.; Latham, David W.; Holman, Matthew J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1322-1327.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1322C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.376L..62B</bibcode>
			<title>The formation of HD149026b</title>
			<authors>Broeg, C.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 376, Issue 1, pp. L62-L66.</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.376L..62B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...464.1133C</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting companions to extrasolar planets using mutual events</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Schneider, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 464, Issue 3, March IV 2007, pp.1133-1138</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...464.1133C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...656..552B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-1b: A Large-Radius, Low-Density Exoplanet Transiting One Member of a Stellar Binary</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Noyes, R. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Torres, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sato, B.; Johnson, J. A.; P&#225; l, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Stanek, K. Z.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.; Sipocz, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 656, Issue 1, pp. 552-559.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...656..552B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...655.1103H</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. IV. Five Transits of the Exoplanet OGLE-TR-10b</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Fuentes, Cesar I.; Hartman, Joel D.; Stanek, K. Z.; Torres, Guillermo; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Gaudi, B. Scott; Jones, R. Lynne; Fraser, Wesley</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 655, Issue 2, pp. 1103-1109.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...655.1103H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...655..564K</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Limb-Darkening to Refine the Properties of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Noyes, Robert W.; Brown, Timothy M.; Gilliland, Ronald L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 655, Issue 1, pp. 564-575.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...655..564K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...655..550G</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for the Characterization and Confirmation of Transiting Exoplanets via the Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. Scott; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 655, Issue 1, pp. 550-563.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...655..550G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...461.1185L</bibcode>
			<title>A diagram to determine the evaporation status of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 461, Issue 3, January III 2007, pp.1185-1193</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...461.1185L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AN....328..789E</bibcode>
			<title>Are extrasolar oceans common throughout the Galaxy?</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich,  D.; Cassan, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.328, Issue 8, p.789</journal>
			<date>0/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AN....328..789E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1621P</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy with Small Telescopes</title>
			<authors>Paczynski, Bohdan</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 850, pp. 1621-1625.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1621P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653..700S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Search for Transits of the Planets Orbiting Gliese 876</title>
			<authors>Shankland, P. D.; Rivera, E. J.; Laughlin, G.; Blank, D. L.; Price, A.; Gary, B.; Bissinger, R.; Ringwald, F.; White, G.; Henry, G. W.; McGee, P.; Wolf, A. S.; Carter, B.; Lee, S.; Biggs, J.; Monard, B.; Ashley, M. C. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 1, pp. 700-707.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653..700S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652L.137F</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Constraints on Trojans of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. L137-L140.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652L.137F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652.1715H</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. I. Four Consecutive Transits of the Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Hergenrother, Carl; Everett, Mark E.; P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. 1715-1723.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652.1715H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650.1160B</bibcode>
			<title>Refined Parameters of the Planet Orbiting HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Knutson, H.; Pont, F.; Moutou, C.; Charbonneau, D.; Shporer, A.; Bouchy, F.; Everett, M.; Hergenrother, C.; Latham, D. W.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Noyes, R. W.; Queloz, D.; P&#225;l, A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 2, pp. 1160-1171.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650.1160B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650.1150I</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origin of HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Ikoma, M.; Guillot, T.; Genda, H.; Tanigawa, T.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 2, pp. 1150-1159.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650.1150I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650.1140B</bibcode>
			<title>Theory for the Secondary Eclipse Fluxes, Spectra, Atmospheres, and Light Curves of Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Sudarsky, D.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 2, pp. 1140-1149.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650.1140B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650..394A</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Structure and Radius Evolution of Irradiated Gas Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Arras, Phil; Bildsten, Lars</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 1, pp. 394-407.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650..394A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1048C</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamics and Disequilibrium Carbon Chemistry in Hot Jupiter Atmospheres, with Application to HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Cooper, Curtis S.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1048-1063.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1048C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1020W</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the Surfaces of Extrasolar Planets with Secondary Eclipse Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Williams, Peter K. G.; Charbonneau, David; Cooper, Curtis S.; Showman, Adam P.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1020-1027.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1020W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1010J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of Known Exoplanetary Systems Based on Measured Stellar Properties</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick; Underwood, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1019.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1010J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...458..327M</bibcode>
			<title>ELODIE metallicity-biased search for transiting Hot Jupiters. III. A hot Jupiter orbiting the star HD 185269</title>
			<authors>Moutou, C.; Loeillet, B.; Bouchy, F.; da Silva, R.; Mayor, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 458, Issue 1, October IV 2006, pp.327-329</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...458..327M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1249B</bibcode>
			<title>The Search for an Atmospheric Signature of the Transiting Exoplanet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Bozorgnia, Nassim; Fortney, Jonathan J.; McCarthy, Chris; Fischer, Debra A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 847, pp. 1249-1256.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1249B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...648.1228M</bibcode>
			<title>A Transiting Planet of a Sun-like Star</title>
			<authors>McCullough, P. R.; Stys, J. E.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Johns-Krull, C. M.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Bye, B. A.; Dodd, C.; Fleming, S. W.; Pinnick, A.; Bissinger, R.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 648, Issue 2, pp. 1228-1238.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...648.1228M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.369.1267D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of a binary or planetary system during encounters with a third inclined body</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 369, Issue 3, pp. 1267-1280.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.369.1267D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..505B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of Nearby Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. P.; Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Penny, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 505-522.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..505B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...453L..21G</bibcode>
			<title>A correlation between the heavy element content of transiting extrasolar planets and the metallicity of their parent stars</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Iro, N.; Melo, C.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 453, Issue 2, July II 2006, pp.L21-L24</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...453L..21G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644.1237O</bibcode>
			<title>Rejecting Astrophysical False Positives from the TrES Transiting Planet Survey: The Example of GSC 03885-00829</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Torres, Guillermo; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Latham, David W.; Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Creevey, Orlagh L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 2, pp. 1237-1245.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644.1237O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118..716L</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude-Precision Photometry of Bright Stars with a 1 m Telescope and a Standard CCD</title>
			<authors>L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 843, pp. 716-721.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118..716L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...642..495F</bibcode>
			<title>Atmosphere, Interior, and Evolution of the Metal-rich Transiting Planet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Saumon, D.; Marley, M. S.; Lodders, K.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 642, Issue 1, pp. 495-504.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...642..495F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...451..345L</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. VII. A very hot Jupiter orbiting HD 212301</title>
			<authors>Lo Curto, G.; Mayor, M.; Clausen, J. V.; Benz, W.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Moutou, C.; Naef, D.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Sivan, J.-P.; Udry, S.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Mordasini, C.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Olsen, E. H.; Pritchard, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 451, Issue 1, May III 2006, pp.345-350</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...451..345L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...450..825S</bibcode>
			<title>High resolution spectroscopy of stars with transiting planets. The cases of OGLE-TR-10, 56, 111, 113, and TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Melo, C.; Israelian, G.; Bouchy, F.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Guillot, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 450, Issue 2, May I 2006, pp.825-831</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...450..825S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...637.1102R</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. V. Identifying Very Metal-rich Stars with Low-Resolution Spectra: Finding Planet-Search Targets</title>
			<authors>Robinson, Sarah E.; Strader, Jay; Ammons, S. Mark; Laughlin, Gregory; Fischer, Debra</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 637, Issue 2, pp. 1102-1112.</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...637.1102R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...637.1094F</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. III. Short-Period Planets Orbiting HD 149143 and HD 109749</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Laughlin, Gregory; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Johnson, John A.; Henry, Gregory W.; McCarthy, Chris; Ammons, Mark; Robinson, Sarah; Strader, Jay; Valenti, Jeff A.; McCullough, P. R.; Charbonneau, David; Haislip, Joshua; Knutson, Heather A.; Reichart, Daniel E.; McGee, Padric; Monard, Berto; Wright, Jason T.; Ida, Shigeru; Sato, Bun'ei; Minniti, Dante</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 637, Issue 2, pp. 1094-1101.</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...637.1094F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....131.1090M</bibcode>
			<title>Planets in Stellar Clusters Extensive Search. IV. A Detection of a Possible Transiting Planet Candidate in the Open Cluster NGC 2158</title>
			<authors>Mochejska, B. J.; Stanek, K. Z.; Sasselov, D. D.; Szentgyorgyi, A. H.; Adams, E.; Cooper, R. L.; Foster, J. B.; Hartman, J. D.; Hickox, R. C.; Lai, K.; Westover, M.; Winn, J. N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 131, Issue 2, pp. 1090-1105.</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....131.1090M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...446..717D</bibcode>
			<title>Elodie metallicity-biased search for transiting Hot Jupiters. I. Two Hot Jupiters orbiting the slightly evolved stars HD 118203 and HD 149143</title>
			<authors>da Silva, R.; Udry, S.; Bouchy, F.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 446, Issue 2, February I 2006, pp.717-722</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...446..717D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...636..445C</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Photometry of the Core-dominated Planet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r; Falco, Emilio E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Noyes, Robert W.; Cs&#225;k, Bal&#225;zs; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 636, Issue 1, pp. 445-452.</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...636..445C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...445..341H</bibcode>
			<title>A posteriori detection of the planetary transit of HD 189733 b in the Hipparcos photometry</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 445, Issue 1, 2006, pp.341-346</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...445..341H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...444L..15B</bibcode>
			<title>ELODIE metallicity-biased search for transiting Hot Jupiters. II. A very hot Jupiter transiting the bright K star HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pont, F.; Iribarne, N.; da Silva, R.; Ilovaisky, S.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 444, Issue 1, December II 2005, pp.L15-L19</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...444L..15B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...633..465S</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. II. A Transiting Hot Saturn around HD 149026 with a Large Dense Core</title>
			<authors>Sato, Bun'ei; Fischer, Debra A.; Henry, Gregory W.; Laughlin, Greg; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Vogt, Steven S.; Bodenheimer, Peter; Ida, Shigeru; Toyota, Eri; Wolf, Aaron; Valenti, Jeff A.; Boyd, Louis J.; Johnson, John A.; Wright, Jason T.; Ammons, Mark; Robinson, Sarah; Strader, Jay; McCarthy, Chris; Tah, K. L.; Minniti, Dante</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 633, Issue 1, pp. 465-473.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...633..465S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.2007M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-22 b: A Transiting "Hot Jupiter" Planet in a Hierarchical Triple System</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Cegla, H.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 2007-2012 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.2007M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723L..60H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-29b: A Saturn-sized Transiting Exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Enoch, B.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233; gransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. L60-L63 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723L..60H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..66B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XI. CoRoT-8b: a hot and dense sub-Saturn around a K1 dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Cabrera, J.; Jorda, L.; Lovis, C.; Csizmadia, S.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bruntt, H.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Guterman, P.; Hatzes, A.; Havel, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Ollivier, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A66</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..66B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.1368G</bibcode>
			<title>Parent stars of extrasolar planets - X. Lithium abundances and v sini revisited</title>
			<authors>Gonzalez, G.; Carlson, M. K.; Tobin, R. W.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 3, pp. 1368-1380.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.1368G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.126B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-4b: A Hot Neptune-like Planet of a G0 Star Near Main-sequence Turnoff</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Brown, Timothy M.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Monet, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L126-L130 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.126B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1724B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-11b: A Super-Neptune Planet Transiting a Bright K Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; P&#225;l, A.; Hartman, J.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Isaacson, H.; Howard, A.; Vogt, S.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Fernandez, J.; Mo&#243;r, A.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1724-1745 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..785H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-12b: A Low-Density Sub-Saturn Mass Planet Transiting a Metal-Poor K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; P&#225;l, A.; Latham, D. W.; Sipocz, B.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 785-796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..785H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705.1226B</bibcode>
			<title>Planets and Debris Disks: Results from a Spitzer/MIPS Search for Infrared Excess</title>
			<authors>Bryden, G.; Beichman, C. A.; Carpenter, J. M.; Rieke, G. H.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Werner, M. W.; Tanner, A. M.; Lawler, S. M.; Wyatt, M. C.; Trilling, D. E.; Su, K. Y. L.; Blaylock, M.; Stansberry, J. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 705, Issue 2, pp. 1226-1236 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705.1226B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705..683B</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Lightcurves of Extrasolar Planets Orbiting Rapidly Rotating Stars</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 705, Issue 1, pp. 683-692 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705..683B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..769K</bibcode>
			<title>The 8 mum Phase Variation of the Hot Saturn HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Showman, Adam P.; Agol, Eric; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 769-784 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..769K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..671S</bibcode>
			<title>A Substellar Companion in a 1.3 yr Nearly Circular Orbit of HD 16760</title>
			<authors>Sato, Bun'ei; Fischer, Debra A.; Ida, Shigeru; Harakawa, Hiroki; Omiya, Masashi; Johnson, John A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Toyota, Eri; Hori, Yasunori; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew W.; Peek, Kathryn M. G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 671-674 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..671S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701L..20Z</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Sulfur Photochemistry on Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Zahnle, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.; Lodders, K.; Fortney, J. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. L20-L24 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701L..20Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700L..73K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Relationship Between Debris Disks and Planets</title>
			<authors>K&#243;sp&#225;l, &#193;gnes; Ardila, David R.; Mo&#243;r, Attila; &#193;brah&#225;m, P&#233;ter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. L73-L77 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700L..73K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..965R</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Proper Motion and the Timing of Planetary Transits</title>
			<authors>Rafikov, Roman R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 965-970 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..965R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501..941H</bibcode>
			<title>The Geneva-Copenhagen survey of the solar neighbourhood. III. Improved distances, ages, and kinematics</title>
			<authors>Holmberg, J.; Nordstr&#246;m, B.; Andersen, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 3, 2009, pp.941-947</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501..941H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1230F</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Spin-Orbit Alignment: Results from the Ensemble of Rossiter-McLaughlin Observations</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1230-1240 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1230F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1116W</bibcode>
			<title>Nondetection of Polarized, Scattered Light from the HD 189733b Hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Wiktorowicz, Sloane J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1116-1124 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1116W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696..241C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Transit Photometry of the Exoplanet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Carter, Joshua A.; Winn, Joshua N.; Gilliland, Ronald; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 1, pp. 241-253 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696..241C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...695L.159D</bibcode>
			<title>Discovering the Growth Histories of Exoplanets: The Saturn Analog HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Bodenheimer, Peter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 695, Issue 2, pp. L159-L162 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...695L.159D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694.1085V</bibcode>
			<title>Directly Determined Linear Radii and Effective Temperatures of Exoplanet Host Stars</title>
			<authors>van Belle, Gerard T.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 2, pp. 1085-1098 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694.1085V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692..229N</bibcode>
			<title>A Precise Estimate of the Radius of the Exoplanet HD 149026b from Spitzer Photometry</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip; Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Knutson, Heather A.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Holman, Matthew J.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. 229-235 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692..229N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691.1145S</bibcode>
			<title>A New Spectroscopic and Photometric Analysis of the Transiting Planet Systems TrES-3 and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Korzennik, Sylvain G.; Holman, Matthew J.; Latham, David W.; Laird, John B.; Fernandez, Jos&#233;; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward; Everett, Mark E.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Belmonte, Juan A.; Deeg, Hans J.; Brown, Timothy N.; Hidas, M&#225;rton G.; Baliber, Nairn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 2, pp. 1145-1158 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691.1145S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690....1O</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting Photometric and Spectroscopic Signatures of Rings Around Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Ohta, Yasuhiro; Taruya, Atsushi; Suto, Yasushi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 1, pp. 1-12 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690....1O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..621F</bibcode>
			<title>Origins of Eccentric Extrasolar Planets: Testing the Planet-Planet Scattering Model</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 621-636.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..621F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...685.1210L</bibcode>
			<title>Extent of Pollution in Planet-bearing Stars</title>
			<authors>Li, S.-L.; Lin, D. N. C.; Liu, X.-W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 685, Issue 2, pp. 1210-1219.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...685.1210L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...483..933E</bibcode>
			<title>New observations of the extended hydrogen exosphere of the extrasolar planet HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; McConnell, J. C.; Parkinson, C. D.; Ballester, G. E.; Ferlet, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 483, Issue 3, 2008, pp.933-937</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...483..933E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008PASP..120..617V</bibcode>
			<title>Closure Phase Signatures of Planet Transit Events</title>
			<authors>van Belle, Gerard T.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 120, issue 868, pp.617-624</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008PASP..120..617V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677..657J</bibcode>
			<title>XO-3b: A Massive Planet in an Eccentric Orbit Transiting an F5 V Star</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Prato, L.; Bissinger, R.; Fleenor, M.; Foote, C. N.; Garcia-Melendo, E.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Mallia, F.; Masi, G.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. 657-670.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677..657J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482..315B</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and evolution of super-Earth to super-Jupiter exoplanets. I. Heavy element enrichment in the interior</title>
			<authors>Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 1, 2008, pp.315-332</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482..315B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...481..529L</bibcode>
			<title>Refined parameters and spectroscopic transit of the super-massive planet HD 147506b</title>
			<authors>Loeillet, B.; Shporer, A.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Mazeh, T.; Beuzit, J. L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; da Silva, R.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Ecuvillon, A.; Forveille, T.; Galland, F.; Gallenne, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sivan, J. P.; Santos, N. C.; Tsodikovich, Y.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 481, Issue 2, 2008, pp.529-533</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...481..529L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...675.1531W</bibcode>
			<title>Five New Transits of the Super-Neptune HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Henry, Gregory W.; Torres, Guillermo; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 675, Issue 2, pp. 1531-1537.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...675.1531W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..729F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting and predicting the yield of transit surveys: giant planets in the OGLE fields</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Morello, V.; Pont, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 2, November IV 2007, pp.729-746</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..729F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.380.1488K</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of exoplanetary transits from radial velocity surveys</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 380, Issue 4, pp. 1488-1496.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.380.1488K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.380..683W</bibcode>
			<title>Light-induced disassembly of dusty bodies in inner protoplanetary discs: implications for the formation of planets</title>
			<authors>Wurm, Gerhard</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 380, Issue 2, pp. 683-690.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.380..683W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667..549W</bibcode>
			<title>A Determination of the Spin-Orbit Alignment of the Anomalously Dense Planet Orbiting HD 149026</title>
			<authors>Wolf, Aaron S.; Laughlin, Gregory; Henry, Gregory W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Marcy, Geoff; Butler, Paul; Vogt, Steve</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 1, pp. 549-556.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667..549W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379..773S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-1: a lithium- and metal-rich star with an oversized planet</title>
			<authors>Stempels, H. C.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hebb, L.; Smalley, B.; Frandsen, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 379, Issue 2, pp. 773-778.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379..773S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379L..11S</bibcode>
			<title>A method for the direct determination of the surface gravities of transiting extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Wheatley, Peter J.; Sams, Giles</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 379, Issue 1, pp. L11-L15.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379L..11S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.378L...1G</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting the frequencies of diverse exo-planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Greaves, J. S.; Fischer, D. A.; Wyatt, M. C.; Beichman, C. A.; Bryden, G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 378, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.378L...1G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.377.1511H</bibcode>
			<title>Using long-term transit timing to detect terrestrial planets</title>
			<authors>Heyl, Jeremy S.; Gladman, Brett J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 377, Issue 4, pp. 1511-1519.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.377.1511H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662.1282M</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Formation Scenarios Revisited: Core-Accretion versus Disk Instability</title>
			<authors>Matsuo, T.; Shibai, H.; Ootsubo, T.; Tamura, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 2, pp. 1282-1292.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662.1282M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...661..502B</bibcode>
			<title>Possible Solutions to the Radius Anomalies of Transiting Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Hubbard, W. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 661, Issue 1, pp. 502-514.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...661..502B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..850D</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude Photometry for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Candidates. II. Transits of OGLE-TR-113-b in the Optical and Near-IR</title>
			<authors>D&#237;az, Rodrigo F.; Ram&#237;rez, Sebasti&#225;n; Fern&#225;ndez, Jos&#233; Miguel; Gallardo, Jos&#233;; Gieren, Wolfgang; Ivanov, Valentin D.; Mauas, Pablo; Minniti, Dante; Pietrzynski, Grzegorz; P&#233;rez, Felipe; Ru&#237;z, Mar&#237;a Teresa; Udalski, Andrzej; Zoccali, Manuela</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 850-857.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..850D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..823M</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of Earth-like Planets During and After Giant Planet Migration</title>
			<authors>Mandell, Avi M.; Raymond, Sean N.; Sigurdsson, Steinn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 823-844.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..823M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJS..169..430R</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. VII. Atmospheric Parameters of 1907 Metal-rich Stars: Finding Planet-Search Targets</title>
			<authors>Robinson, Sarah E.; Ammons, S. Mark; Kretke, Katherine A.; Strader, Jay; Wertheimer, Jeremy G.; Fischer, Debra A.; Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 169, Issue 2, pp. 430-438.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJS..169..430R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1322C</bibcode>
			<title>Precise Radius Estimates for the Exoplanets WASP-1b and WASP-2b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Everett, Mark E.; Latham, David W.; Holman, Matthew J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1322-1327.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1322C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...656..552B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-1b: A Large-Radius, Low-Density Exoplanet Transiting One Member of a Stellar Binary</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Noyes, R. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Torres, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sato, B.; Johnson, J. A.; P&#225; l, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Stanek, K. Z.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.; Sipocz, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 656, Issue 1, pp. 552-559.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...656..552B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...655..550G</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for the Characterization and Confirmation of Transiting Exoplanets via the Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. Scott; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 655, Issue 1, pp. 550-563.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...655..550G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.373..799C</bibcode>
			<title>A fast hybrid algorithm for exoplanetary transit searches</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Street, R. A.; Lister, T. A.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Pont, F.; Christian, D. J.; Clarkson, W. I.; Enoch, B.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Keenan, F. P.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N. R.; Osborne, J.; Ryans, R.; Skillen, I.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 373, Issue 2, pp. 799-810.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.373..799C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653L..69W</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Alignment in the Exoplanetary System HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Henry, Gregory W.; Roussanova, Anna; Holman, Matthew J.; Enya, Keigo; Narita, Norio; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 1, pp. L69-L72.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653L..69W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653..700S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Search for Transits of the Planets Orbiting Gliese 876</title>
			<authors>Shankland, P. D.; Rivera, E. J.; Laughlin, G.; Blank, D. L.; Price, A.; Gary, B.; Bissinger, R.; Ringwald, F.; White, G.; Henry, G. W.; McGee, P.; Wolf, A. S.; Carter, B.; Lee, S.; Biggs, J.; Monard, B.; Ashley, M. C. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 1, pp. 700-707.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653..700S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652L.137F</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Constraints on Trojans of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. L137-L140.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652L.137F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460..251M</bibcode>
			<title>On the age of stars harboring transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Melo, C.; Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 1, December II 2006, pp.251-256</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460..251M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AstL...32..759G</bibcode>
			<title>Pulkovo Compilation of Radial Velocities for 35 495 Hipparcos stars in a common system</title>
			<authors>Gontcharov, G. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Letters, Vol. 32, Issue 11, p.759-771</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AstL...32..759G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650.1160B</bibcode>
			<title>Refined Parameters of the Planet Orbiting HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Knutson, H.; Pont, F.; Moutou, C.; Charbonneau, D.; Shporer, A.; Bouchy, F.; Everett, M.; Hergenrother, C.; Latham, D. W.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Noyes, R. W.; Queloz, D.; P&#225;l, A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 2, pp. 1160-1171.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650.1160B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650.1150I</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origin of HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Ikoma, M.; Guillot, T.; Genda, H.; Tanigawa, T.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 2, pp. 1150-1159.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650.1150I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650..394A</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Structure and Radius Evolution of Irradiated Gas Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Arras, Phil; Bildsten, Lars</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 1, pp. 394-407.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650..394A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1010J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of Known Exoplanetary Systems Based on Measured Stellar Properties</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick; Underwood, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1019.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1010J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...458..327M</bibcode>
			<title>ELODIE metallicity-biased search for transiting Hot Jupiters. III. A hot Jupiter orbiting the star HD 185269</title>
			<authors>Moutou, C.; Loeillet, B.; Bouchy, F.; da Silva, R.; Mayor, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 458, Issue 1, October IV 2006, pp.327-329</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...458..327M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1249B</bibcode>
			<title>The Search for an Atmospheric Signature of the Transiting Exoplanet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Bozorgnia, Nassim; Fortney, Jonathan J.; McCarthy, Chris; Fischer, Debra A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 847, pp. 1249-1256.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1249B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...455L..25A</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and structure of the three Neptune-mass planets system around HD 69830</title>
			<authors>Alibert, Y.; Baraffe, I.; Benz, W.; Chabrier, G.; Mordasini, C.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Bouchy, F.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 455, Issue 2, August IV 2006, pp.L25-L28</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...455L..25A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..523R</bibcode>
			<title>Two Suns in The Sky: Stellar Multiplicity in Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Raghavan, Deepak; Henry, Todd J.; Mason, Brian D.; Subasavage, John P.; Jao, Wei-Chun; Beaulieu, Thom D.; Hambly, Nigel C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 523-542.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..523R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..505B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of Nearby Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. P.; Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Penny, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 505-522.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..505B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...453L..21G</bibcode>
			<title>A correlation between the heavy element content of transiting extrasolar planets and the metallicity of their parent stars</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Iro, N.; Melo, C.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 453, Issue 2, July II 2006, pp.L21-L24</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...453L..21G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...642..495F</bibcode>
			<title>Atmosphere, Interior, and Evolution of the Metal-rich Transiting Planet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Saumon, D.; Marley, M. S.; Lodders, K.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 642, Issue 1, pp. 495-504.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...642..495F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...450..825S</bibcode>
			<title>High resolution spectroscopy of stars with transiting planets. The cases of OGLE-TR-10, 56, 111, 113, and TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Melo, C.; Israelian, G.; Bouchy, F.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Guillot, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 450, Issue 2, May I 2006, pp.825-831</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...450..825S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...450..735M</bibcode>
			<title>Effective temperature scale and bolometric corrections from 2MASS photometry</title>
			<authors>Masana, E.; Jordi, C.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 450, Issue 2, 2006, pp.735-746</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...450..735M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...449..699R</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos astrometric orbits for two brown dwarf companions: HD 38529 and HD 168443</title>
			<authors>Reffert, S.; Quirrenbach, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 449, Issue 2, April II 2006, pp.699-702</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...449..699R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...448..379E</bibcode>
			<title>The transmission spectrum of Earth-size transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Tinetti, G.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; Selsis, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 448, Issue 1, March II 2006, pp.379-393</journal>
			<date>3/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...448..379E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...637.1094F</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. III. Short-Period Planets Orbiting HD 149143 and HD 109749</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Laughlin, Gregory; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Johnson, John A.; Henry, Gregory W.; McCarthy, Chris; Ammons, Mark; Robinson, Sarah; Strader, Jay; Valenti, Jeff A.; McCullough, P. R.; Charbonneau, David; Haislip, Joshua; Knutson, Heather A.; Reichart, Daniel E.; McGee, Padric; Monard, Berto; Wright, Jason T.; Ida, Shigeru; Sato, Bun'ei; Minniti, Dante</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 637, Issue 2, pp. 1094-1101.</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...637.1094F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...446..717D</bibcode>
			<title>Elodie metallicity-biased search for transiting Hot Jupiters. I. Two Hot Jupiters orbiting the slightly evolved stars HD 118203 and HD 149143</title>
			<authors>da Silva, R.; Udry, S.; Bouchy, F.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 446, Issue 2, February I 2006, pp.717-722</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...446..717D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...636..445C</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Photometry of the Core-dominated Planet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r; Falco, Emilio E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Noyes, Robert W.; Cs&#225;k, Bal&#225;zs; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 636, Issue 1, pp. 445-452.</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...636..445C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005AN....326..909G</bibcode>
			<title>Interactions between hot Jupiters and their host stars</title>
			<authors>Gu, Pin-Gao; Shkolnik, E.; Li, Shu-Lin; Liu, Xiao-Wei</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.326, Issue 10, p.909-912</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005AN....326..909G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...444L..15B</bibcode>
			<title>ELODIE metallicity-biased search for transiting Hot Jupiters. II. A very hot Jupiter transiting the bright K star HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pont, F.; Iribarne, N.; da Silva, R.; Ilovaisky, S.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 444, Issue 1, December II 2005, pp.L15-L19</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...444L..15B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...633..465S</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. II. A Transiting Hot Saturn around HD 149026 with a Large Dense Core</title>
			<authors>Sato, Bun'ei; Fischer, Debra A.; Henry, Gregory W.; Laughlin, Greg; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Vogt, Steven S.; Bodenheimer, Peter; Ida, Shigeru; Toyota, Eri; Wolf, Aaron; Valenti, Jeff A.; Boyd, Louis J.; Johnson, John A.; Wright, Jason T.; Ammons, Mark; Robinson, Sarah; Strader, Jay; McCarthy, Chris; Tah, K. L.; Minniti, Dante</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 633, Issue 1, pp. 465-473.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...633..465S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...442..731G</bibcode>
			<title>On the potential of extrasolar planet transit surveys</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Courbin, F.; Magain, P.; Borguet, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 442, Issue 2, November I 2005, pp.731-744</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...442..731G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...418..989N</bibcode>
			<title>The Geneva-Copenhagen survey of the Solar neighbourhood. Ages, metallicities, and kinematic properties of &amp;tilde14 000 F and G dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Nordstr&#246;m, B.; Mayor, M.; Andersen, J.; Holmberg, J.; Pont, F.; J&#248; rgensen, B. R.; Olsen, E. H.; Udry, S.; Mowlavi, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.418, p.989-1019 (2004)</journal>
			<date>5/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...418..989N</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
