<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011SerAJ.183....1J</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomical Optical Interferometry. II. Astrophysical Results</title>
			<authors>Jankov, S.</authors>
			<journal>Serbian Astronomical Journal, vol. 183, pp. 1-35</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011SerAJ.183....1J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ARep...55.1051A</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of light curves of eclipsing systems with exoplanets: HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Abubekerov, M. K.; Gostev, N. Yu.; Cherepashchuk, A. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Reports, Volume 55, Issue 12, pp.1051-1073</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ARep...55.1051A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...10B</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Misalignment of KOI-13.01 from Its Gravity-darkened Kepler Transit Lightcurve</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.; Linscott, Ethan; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...10B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...741L..18P</bibcode>
			<title>X-Ray Activity Phased with Planet Motion in HD 189733?</title>
			<authors>Pillitteri, I.; G&#252;nther, H. M.; Wolk, S. J.; Kashyap, V. L.; Cohen, O.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 741, Issue 1, article id. L18 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...741L..18P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...741...52K</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of Exoplanet Periastron Passage in the Infrared</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 741, Issue 1, article id. 52 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...741...52K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740L..10N</bibcode>
			<title>Using Star Spots to Measure the Spin-orbit Alignment of Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 740, Issue 1, article id. L10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740L..10N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..166C</bibcode>
			<title>The Dynamics of Stellar Coronae Harboring Hot Jupiters. II. A Space Weather Event on a Hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Cohen, O.; Kashyap, V. L.; Drake, J. J.; Sokolov, I. V.; Gombosi, T. I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 166 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..166C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738...97B</bibcode>
			<title>Silicon and Oxygen Abundances in Planet-host Stars</title>
			<authors>Brugamyer, Erik; Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Cochran, William D.; Sneden, Christopher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 97 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738...97B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738...72V</bibcode>
			<title>Quenching of Carbon Monoxide and Methane in the Atmospheres of Cool Brown Dwarfs and Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Visscher, Channon; Moses, Julianne I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 72 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738...72V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..50L</bibcode>
			<title>GMRT search for 150 MHz radio emission from the transiting extrasolar planets HD 189733 b and HD 209458 b</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Sirothia, S. K.; Gopal-Krishna; Zarka, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A50</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..50L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..44L</bibcode>
			<title>Deriving the radial-velocity variations induced by stellar activity from high-precision photometry. Test on HD 189733 with simultaneous MOST/SOPHIE data</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Moutou, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A44</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..44L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737...58K</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Variability of the Exoplanet Hosting Star HD 63454</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Dragomir, Diana; Ciardi, David R.; Lee, Jae-Woo; Lo Curto, Gaspare; Lovis, Christophe; Naef, Dominique; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Pilyavsky, Genady; Udry, Stephane; Wang, Xuesong; Wright, Jason</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 737, Issue 2, article id. 58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737...58K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737...15M</bibcode>
			<title>Disequilibrium Carbon, Oxygen, and Nitrogen Chemistry in the Atmospheres of HD 189733b and HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Moses, Julianne I.; Visscher, C.; Fortney, J. J.; Showman, A. P.; Lewis, N. K.; Griffith, C. A.; Klippenstein, S. J.; Shabram, M.; Friedson, A. J.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 737, Issue 1, article id. 15 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737...15M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A...6S</bibcode>
			<title>Estimation of the XUV radiation onto close planets and their evaporation</title>
			<authors>Sanz-Forcada, J.; Micela, G.; Ribas, I.; Pollock, A. M. T.; Eiroa, C.; Velasco, A.; Solano, E.; Garc&#237;a-&#193;lvarez, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A6</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A...6S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...12B</bibcode>
			<title>The GJ1214 Super-Earth System: Stellar Variability, New Transits, and a Search for Additional Planets</title>
			<authors>Berta, Zachory K.; Charbonneau, David; Bean, Jacob; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Nutzman, Philip; Falco, Emilio E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 12 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...12B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...27K</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer Transmission Spectrum for the Exoplanet GJ 436b, Evidence for Stellar Variability, and Constraints on Dayside Flux Variations</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Agol, Eric; Deming, Drake; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Charbonneau, David; Henry, Gregory W.; Homeier, Derek; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 1, article id. 27 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735...27K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...98G</bibcode>
			<title>Escaping Particle Fluxes in the Atmospheres of Close-in Exoplanets. I. Model of Hydrogen</title>
			<authors>Guo, J. H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. 98 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...98G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...530A..73C</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric activity of stars with planets</title>
			<authors>Canto Martins, B. L.; Das Chagas, M. L.; Alves, S.; Le&#227;o, I. C.; de Souza Neto, L. P.; de Medeiros, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 530, id.A73</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...530A..73C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...67C</bibcode>
			<title>The Dynamics of Stellar Coronae Harboring Hot Jupiters. I. A Time-dependent Magnetohydrodynamic Simulation of the Interplanetary Environment in the HD 189733 Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Cohen, O.; Kashyap, V. L.; Drake, J. J.; Sokolov, I. V.; Garraffo, C.; Gombosi, T. I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 67 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...67C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...28K</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Orbital Parameters and Transit Monitoring for HD 156846b</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Howard, Andrew W.; Pilyavsky, Genady; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Henry, Gregory W.; von Braun, Kaspar; Ciardi, David R.; Dragomir, Diana; Fischer, Debra A.; Jensen, Eric; Laughlin, Gregory; Ramirez, Solange V.; Wright, Jason T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 28 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...28K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529C...1P</bibcode>
			<title>Coronal properties of planet-bearing stars</title>
			<authors>Poppenhaeger, K.; Robrade, J.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.C1</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529C...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A..50L</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining tidal dissipation in F-type main-sequence stars: the case of CoRoT-11</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Damiani, C.; Gandolfi, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A50</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A..50L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...731...16B</bibcode>
			<title>Methane in the Atmosphere of the Transiting Hot Neptune GJ436B?</title>
			<authors>Beaulieu, J.-P.; Tinetti, G.; Kipping, D. M.; Ribas, I.; Barber, R. J.; Cho, J. Y.-K.; Polichtchouk, I.; Tennyson, J.; Yurchenko, S. N.; Griffith, C. A.; Batista, V.; Waldmann, I.; Miller, S.; Carey, S.; Mousis, O.; Fossey, S. J.; Aylward, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 731, Issue 1, article id. 16 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...731...16B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..49D</bibcode>
			<title>The GROUSE project. II. Detection of the Ks-band secondary eclipse of exoplanet HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>de Mooij, E. J. W.; de Kok, R. J.; Nefs, S. V.; Snellen, I. A. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A49</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..49D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A...4B</bibcode>
			<title>Disentangling between stellar activity and planetary signals</title>
			<authors>Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; H&#233;brard, G.; Bonfils, X.; Santos, N.; Vauclair, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A4</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A...4B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Msngr.143...16E</bibcode>
			<title>GRAVITY: Observing the Universe in Motion</title>
			<authors>Eisenhauer, F.; Perrin, G.; Brandner, W.; Straubmeier, C.; Perraut, K.; Amorim, A.; Sch&#246;ller, M.; Gillessen, S.; Kervella, P.; Benisty, M.; Araujo-Hauck, C.; Jocou, L.; Lima, J.; Jakob, G.; Haug, M.; Cl&#233;net, Y.; Henning, T.; Eckart, A.; Berger, J.-P.; Garcia, P.; Abuter, R.; Kellner, S.; Paumard, T.; Hippler, S.; Fischer, S.; Moulin, T.; Villate, J.; Avila, G.; Gr&#228;ter, A.; Lacour, S.; Huber, A.; Wiest, M.; Nolot, A.; Carvas, P.; Dorn, R.; Pfuhl, O.; Gendron, E.; Kendrew, S.; Yazici, S.; Anton, S.; Jung, Y.; Thiel, M.; Choquet, &#201;.; Klein, R.; Teixeira, P.; Gitton, P.; Moch, D.; Vincent, F.; Kudryavtseva, N.; Str&#246;bele, S.; Sturm, S.; F&#233;dou, P.; Lenzen, R.; Jolley, P.; Kister, C.; Lapeyr&#232;re, V.; Naranjo, V.; Lucuix, C.; Hofmann, R.; Chapron, F.; Neumann, U.; Mehrgan, L.; Hans, O.; Rousset, G.; Ramos, J.; Suarez, M.; Lederer, R.; Reess, J.-M.; Rohloff, R.-R.; Haguenauer, P.; Bartko, H.; Sevin, A.; Wagner, K.; Lizon, J.-L.; Rabien, S.; Collin, C.; Finger, G.; Davies, R.; Rouan, D.; Wittkowski, M.; Dodds-Eden, K.; Ziegler, D.; Cassaing, F.; Bonnet, H.; Casali, M.; Genzel, R.; Lena, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 143, p. 16-24</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Msngr.143...16E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.2199G</bibcode>
			<title>A new look at NICMOS transmission spectroscopy of HD 189733, GJ-436 and XO-1: no conclusive evidence for molecular features</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Pont, F.; Aigrain, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 4, pp. 2199-2213.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.2199G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1953P</bibcode>
			<title>Reassessing the radial-velocity evidence for planets around CoRoT-7</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Aigrain, Suzanne; Zucker, Shay</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 3, pp. 1953-1962.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1953P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729L...7L</bibcode>
			<title>On the Anomalous Radii of the Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Crismani, Matteo; Adams, Fred C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. L7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729L...7L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729..116K</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetohydrodynamic Simulations of the Magnetic Interaction of Hot Jupiters with Their Host Stars: A Numerical Experiment</title>
			<authors>Kopp, A.; Schilp, S.; Preusse, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729..116K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..73S</bibcode>
			<title>Gran Telescopio Canarias OSIRIS transiting exoplanet atmospheric survey: detection of potassium in XO-2b from narrowband spectrophotometry</title>
			<authors>Sing, D. K.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; Fortney, J. J.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Ballester, G. E.; Cepa, J.; Ehrenreich, D.; L&#243;pez-Morales, M.; Pont, F.; Shabram, M.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A73</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..73S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...27B</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: Exoplanets on the cheap</title>
			<authors>Billings, Lee</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 27-29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...27B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728L...6B</bibcode>
			<title>Polarized Reflected Light from the Exoplanet HD189733b: First Multicolor Observations and Confirmation of Detection</title>
			<authors>Berdyugina, S. V.; Berdyugin, A. V.; Fluri, D. M.; Piirola, V.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 728, Issue 1, article id. L6 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728L...6B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728...18M</bibcode>
			<title>Non-detection of L-band Line Emission from the Exoplanet HD189733b</title>
			<authors>Mandell, Avi M.; Drake Deming, L.; Blake, Geoffrey A.; Knutson, Heather A.; Mumma, Michael J.; Villanueva, Geronimo L.; Salyk, Colette</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 1, article id. 18 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728...18M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...30C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from WASP-12b: Detections of the Secondary Eclipse in Ks, H, and J</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Lafreniere, David; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...30C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A..12D</bibcode>
			<title>Transit spectrophotometry of the exoplanet HD 189733b. II. New Spitzer observations at 3.6 mum</title>
			<authors>D&#233;sert, J.-M.; Sing, D.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Ehrenreich, D.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Parmentier, V.; Ferlet, R.; Henry, G. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A12</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A..12D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...95D</bibcode>
			<title>Warm Spitzer Photometry of the Transiting Exoplanets CoRoT-1 and CoRoT-2 at Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather; Agol, Eric; Desert, Jean-Michel; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan; Showman, Adam P.; Lewis, Nikole K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 95 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...95D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 29, 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.409..963B</bibcode>
			<title>Water in the atmosphere of HD 209458b from 3.6-8 mum IRAC photometric observations in primary transit</title>
			<authors>Beaulieu, J. P.; Kipping, D. M.; Batista, V.; Tinetti, G.; Ribas, I.; Carey, S.; Noriega-Crespo, J. A.; Griffith, C. A.; Campanella, G.; Dong, S.; Tennyson, J.; Barber, R. J.; Deroo, P.; Fossey, S. J.; Liang, D.; Swain, M. R.; Yung, Y.; Allard, N.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 409, Issue 3, pp. 963-974.</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.409..963B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010BASI...38..137L</bibcode>
			<title>Evaporation of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the Astronomical Soceity of India, Vol. 38, p. 137-145, 2010</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010BASI...38..137L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.2176Q</bibcode>
			<title>Automatic Determination of Stellar Parameters Via Asteroseismology of Stochastically Oscillating Stars: Comparison with Direct Measurements</title>
			<authors>Quirion, Pierre-Olivier; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Arentoft, Torben</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 2176-2189 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.2176Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1938L</bibcode>
			<title>Forming Planetesimals by Gravitational Instability. II. How Dust Settles to its Marginally Stable State</title>
			<authors>Lee, Aaron T.; Chiang, Eugene; Asay-Davis, Xylar; Barranco, Joseph</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1938-1954 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1938L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..866K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-15b: A 10.9 Day Extrasolar Planet Transiting a Solar-type Star</title>
			<authors>Kov&#225;cs, G.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J. D.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, B. B&#233;ky J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, pp. 866-877 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...524A..47G</bibcode>
			<title>HD 46375: seismic and spectropolarimetric analysis of a young Sun hosting a Saturn-like planet</title>
			<authors>Gaulme, P.; Deheuvels, S.; Weiss, W. W.; Mosser, B.; Moutou, C.; Bruntt, H.; Donati, J.-F.; Vannier, M.; Guillot, T.; Appourchaux, T.; Michel, E.; Auvergne, M.; Samadi, R.; Baudin, F.; Catala, C.; Baglin, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 524, id.A47</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...524A..47G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723L.223W</bibcode>
			<title>The Oblique Orbit of the Super-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Hartman, Joel D.; Albrecht, Simon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 723, Issue 2, pp. L223-L227 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723L.223W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..88B</bibcode>
			<title>The SOPHIE search for northern extrasolar planets. III. A Jupiter-mass companion around HD 109246</title>
			<authors>Boisse, I.; Eggenberger, A.; Santos, N. C.; Lovis, C.; Bouchy, F.; H&#233; brard, G.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Gallenne, A.; Lagrange, A. M.; Moutou, C.; Udry, S.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Perruchot, S.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; S&#233; gransan, D.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A88</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..88B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..35T</bibcode>
			<title>Selective principal component extraction and reconstruction: a novel method for ground based exoplanet spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Thatte, A.; Deroo, P.; Swain, M. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A35</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..35T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2625M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation in exoplanet WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Ginski, Ch.; Adam, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2625-2631.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2625M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2589K</bibcode>
			<title>Nightside pollution of exoplanet transit depths</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.; Tinetti, Giovanna</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2589-2598.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2589K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722.1216P</bibcode>
			<title>XMM-Newton Observations of HD 189733 During Planetary Transits</title>
			<authors>Pillitteri, I.; Wolk, S. J.; Cohen, O.; Kashyap, V.; Knutson, H.; Lisse, C. M.; Henry, G. W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 2, pp. 1216-1225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722.1216P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..40A</bibcode>
			<title>The ability of intermediate-band Str&#246;mgren photometry to correctly identify dwarf, subgiant, and giant stars and provide stellar metallicities and surface gravities</title>
			<authors>&#193;rnad&#243;ttir, A. S.; Feltzing, S.; Lundstr&#246;m, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A40</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..40A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406..409F</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for star-planet interactions within the magnetosphere of HD189733</title>
			<authors>Fares, R.; Donati, J.-F.; Moutou, C.; Jardine, M. M.; Grie&#223;meier, J.-M.; Zarka, P.; Shkolnik, E. L.; Bohlender, D.; Catala, C.; Collier Cameron, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 1, pp. 409-419.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406..409F</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
