<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..175R</bibcode>
			<title>Know the Star, Know the Planet. I. Adaptive Optics of Exoplanet Host Stars</title>
			<authors>Roberts, Lewis C., Jr.; Turner, Nils H.; ten Brummelaar, Theo A.; Mason, Brian D.; Hartkopf, William I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 5, article id. 175 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142..175R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...68B</bibcode>
			<title>Density Estimation for Projected Exoplanet Quantities</title>
			<authors>Brown, Robert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 68 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...68B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...31T</bibcode>
			<title>The Anglo-Australian Planet Search. XXI. A Gas-giant Planet in a One Year Orbit and the Habitability of Gas-giant Satellites</title>
			<authors>Tinney, C. G.; Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Butler, R. Paul; Jones, Hugh R. A.; O'Toole, Simon J.; Bailey, Jeremy A.; Carter, Brad D.; Horner, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 31 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...31T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1666S</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation periods of exoplanet host stars</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Baliunas, S. L.; Henry, G. W.; Watson, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1666-1679.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1666S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1606W</bibcode>
			<title>Estimating the masses of extra-solar planets</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Littlefair, S. P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Dhillon, V. S.; Simpson, E. K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1606-1622.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1606W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..186...48J</bibcode>
			<title>On the Fundamental Mass-Period Functions of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jiang, Ing-Guey; Yeh, Li-Chin; Chang, Yen-Chang; Hung, Wen-Liang</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 186, Issue 1, pp. 48-62 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..186...48J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..168A</bibcode>
			<title>How Eccentric Orbital Solutions Can Hide Planetary Systems in 2:1 Resonant Orbits</title>
			<authors>