<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...747L..20M</bibcode>
			<title>A Two-dimensional Infrared Map of the Extrasolar Planet HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Majeau, Carl; Agol, Eric; Cowan, Nicolas B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 747, Issue 2, article id. L20 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...747L..20M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...747...25M</bibcode>
			<title>Analytic Models for Albedos, Phase Curves, and Polarization of Reflected Light from Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, Nikku; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 747, Issue 1, article id. 25 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...747...25M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...747...12W</bibcode>
			<title>Of "Cocktail Parties" and Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Waldmann, I. P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 747, Issue 1, article id. 12 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...747...12W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.420..170L</bibcode>
			<title>Optimal estimation retrievals of the atmospheric structure and composition of HD 189733b from secondary eclipse spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Lee, J.-M.; Fletcher, L. N.; Irwin, P. G. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 420, Issue 1, pp. 170-182.</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.420..170L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746..111T</bibcode>
			<title>Warm Spitzer Observations of Three Hot Exoplanets: XO-4b, HAT-P-6b, and HAT-P-8b</title>
			<authors>Todorov, Kamen O.; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Sada, Pedro V.; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric; Desert, Jean-Michel; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Charbonneau, David; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan; Showman, Adam P.; Lewis, Nikole K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 1, article id. 111 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...746..111T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746...46C</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based, Near-infrared Exospectroscopy. II. Tentative Detection of Emission from the Extremely Hot Jupiter WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Crossfield, Ian J. M.; Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 1, article id. 46 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...746...46C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746...45T</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the Atmospheres of Transiting Planets with a Dedicated Space Telescope</title>
			<authors>