<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746..111T</bibcode>
			<title>Warm Spitzer Observations of Three Hot Exoplanets: XO-4b, HAT-P-6b, and HAT-P-8b</title>
			<authors>Todorov, Kamen O.; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Sada, Pedro V.; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric; Desert, Jean-Michel; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Charbonneau, David; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan; Showman, Adam P.; Lewis, Nikole K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 1, article id. 111 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...746..111T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745..138M</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic Scaling Laws for the Atmospheres of Hot Giant Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Menou, Kristen</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 2, article id. 138 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745..138M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...78R</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Drag in the Energetics of Strongly Forced Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Rauscher, Emily; Menou, Kristen</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 78 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...78R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...77K</bibcode>
			<title>A Photochemical Model for the Carbon-rich Planet WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Kopparapu, Ravi kumar; Kasting, James F.; Zahnle, Kevin J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 77 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...77K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...25L</bibcode>
			<title>Far-ultraviolet Continuum Emission: Applying This Diagnostic to the Chromospheres of Solar-mass Stars</title>
			<authors>Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Bushinsky, Rachel; Ayres, Tom; Fontenla, Juan; France, Kevin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 25 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...25L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745....3M</bibcode>
			<title>The Atmospheric Chemistry of GJ 1214b: Photochemistry and Clouds</title>
			<authors>Miller-Ricci Kempton, Eliza; Zahnle, Kevin; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 3 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745....3M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745....2L</bibcode>
			<title>Interaction of Close-in Planets with the Magnetosphere of Their Host Stars. II. Super-Earths as Unipolar Inductors and Their Orbital Evolution</title>
			<authors>Laine, Randy O.; Lin, Douglas N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745....2L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..121Y</bibcode>
			<title>A Far-ultraviolet Atlas of Low-resolution Hubble Space Telescope Spectra of T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Yang, Hao; Herczeg, Gregory J.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Brown, Alexander; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Ingleby, Laura; Calvet, Nuria; Bergin, Edwin; Valenti, Jeff A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 121 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744..121Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744...70K</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetospheres of "Hot Jupiters": The Importance of Magnetodisks in Shaping a Magnetospheric Obstacle</title>
			<authors>