<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...10B</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Misalignment of KOI-13.01 from Its Gravity-darkened Kepler Transit Lightcurve</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.; Linscott, Ethan; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...10B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...741...52K</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of Exoplanet Periastron Passage in the Infrared</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 741, Issue 1, article id. 52 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...741...52K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A...7B</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and evolution of planetary systems in presence of highly inclined stellar perturbers</title>
			<authors>Batygin, K.; Morbidelli, A.; Tsiganis, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A7</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A...7B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>The Heavy-element Masses of Extrasolar Giant Planets, Revealed</title>
			<authors>Miller, Neil; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735..109W</bibcode>
			<title>Secular Chaos and the Production of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Wu, Yanqin; Lithwick, Yoram</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 2, article id. 109 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735..109W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...24J</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-30b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter on a Highly Oblique Orbit</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, J. N.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J. D.; Morton, T. D.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Sato, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Fur&#233;sz, G.; Quinn, S. N.; B&#233;ky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 1, article id. 24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735...24J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011BASI...39..297S</bibcode>
			<title>Highlights from the observatories</title>
			<authors>Saikia, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the Astromical Society of India, Vol. 39, p. 297-312 (2011)</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011BASI...39..297S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...68B</bibcode>
			<title>Density Estimation for Projected Exoplanet Quantities</title>
			<authors>Brown, Robert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 68 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...68B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...28K</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Orbital Parameters and Transit Monitoring for HD 156846b</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Howard, Andrew W.; Pilyavsky, Genady; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Henry, Gregory W.; von Braun, Kaspar; Ciardi, David R.; Dragomir, Diana; Fischer, Debra A.; Jensen, Eric; Laughlin, Gregory; Ramirez, Solange V.; Wright, Jason T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 28 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...28K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..53B</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variations in eccentric hierarchical triple exoplanetary systems. I. Perturbations on the time scale of the orbital period of the perturber</title>
			<authors>Borkovits, T.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Forg&#225;cs-Dajka, E.; Heged&#252;s, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A53</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..53B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...74K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Inclination Dependence of Exoplanet Phase Signatures</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...74K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727L..44S</bibcode>
			<title>A Short-period Censor of Sub-Jupiter Mass Exoplanets with Low Density</title>
			<authors>Szab&#243;, Gy. M.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. L44 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727L..44S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...82C</bibcode>
			<title>A Model for Thermal Phase Variations of Circular and Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 82 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...82C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726....3N</bibcode>
			<title>Precise Estimates of the Physical Parameters for the Exoplanet System HD 17156 Enabled by Hubble Space Telescope Fine Guidance Sensor Transit and Asteroseismic Observations</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip; Gilliland, Ronald L.; McCullough, Peter R.; Charbonneau, David; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Kjeldsen, Hans; Nelan, Edmund P.; Brown, Timothy M.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id. 3 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726....3N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141....8S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-37b: A 1.8 M J Exoplanet Transiting a Metal-poor Star</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hebb, L.; Pollacco, D.; Smalley, B.; Todd, I.; Butters, O. W.; H&#233;brard, G.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Santerne, A.; Street, R. A.; Skillen, I.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Anderson, D. R.; Bento, J.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Horne, K.; Keenan, F. P.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Segransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Stempels, H. C.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 1, article id. 8 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141....8S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..54B</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-38b: a transiting exoplanet in an eccentric, 6.87d period orbit</title>
			<authors>Barros, S. C. C.; Faedi, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Lister, T. A.; McCormac, J.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; H&#233;brard, G.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Bento, J.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Skillen, I.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A54</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..54B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62L..61N</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect of the Transiting Exoplanet XO-4b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.6, pp.L61--L65</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62L..61N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..866K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-15b: A 10.9 Day Extrasolar Planet Transiting a Solar-type Star</title>
			<authors>Kov&#225;cs, G.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J. D.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, B. B&#233;ky J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, pp. 866-877 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.1929L</bibcode>
			<title>Radio Observations of HD 80606 Near Planetary Periastron</title>
			<authors>Lazio, T. Joseph W.; Shankland, P. D.; Farrell, W. M.; Blank, D. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 1929-1933 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.1929L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1606W</bibcode>
			<title>Estimating the masses of extra-solar planets</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Littlefair, S. P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Dhillon, V. S.; Simpson, E. K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1606-1622.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1606W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..818K</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Phase Variations of Long-period Eccentric Planets</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. 818-826 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..818K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722..880S</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based Multisite Observations of Two Transits of HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Shporer, A.; Winn, J. N.; Dreizler, S.; Col&#243;n, K. D.; Wood-Vasey, W. M.; Choi, P. I.; Morley, C.; Moutou, C.; Welsh, W. F.; Pollaco, D.; Starkey, D.; Adams, E.; Barros, S. C. C.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera-Lavers, A.; Cerutti, S.; Coban, L.; Costello, K.; Deeg, H.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fernandez, J.; Fleming, S. W.; Ford, E. B.; Fulton, B. J.; Good, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Holman, M. J.; Hunt, M.; Kadakia, S.; Lander, G.; Lockhart, M.; Mazeh, T.; Morehead, R. C.; Nelson, B. E.; Nortmann, L.; Reyes, F.; Roebuck, E.; Rudy, A. R.; Ruth, R.; Simpson, E.; Vincent, C.; Weaver, G.; Xie, J.-W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. 880-887 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722..880S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721.1308S</bibcode>
			<title>Generalized Milankovitch Cycles and Long-Term Climatic Habitability</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Raymond, Sean N.; Dressing, Courtney D.; Scharf, Caleb A.; Mitchell, Jonathan L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. 1308-1318 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...721.1308S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1020A</bibcode>
			<title>Observing Exoplanets with SOFIA</title>
			<authors>Angerhausen, D.; Krabbe, A.; Iserlohe, C.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 895, pp.1020-1029</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1020A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407..301K</bibcode>
			<title>Investigations of approximate expressions for the transit duration</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 1, pp. 301-313.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407..301K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1644K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Transit Potential of the Planet Orbiting Iota Draconis</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Reffert, Sabine; Henry, Gregory W.; Fischer, Debra; Schwab, Christian; Clubb, Kelsey I.; Bergmann, Christoph</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1644-1649 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1644K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1146H</bibcode>
			<title>An ingress and a complete transit of HD80606 b</title>
			<authors>Hidas, M. G.; Tsapras, Y.; Mislis, D.; Ramaprakash, A. N.; Barros, S. C. C.; Street, R. A.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Steele, I.; Pollacco, D.; Ayiomamitis, A.; Antoniadis, J.; Nitsos, A.; Seiradakis, J. H.; Urakawa, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 2, pp. 1146-1151.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1146H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1140K</bibcode>
			<title>Application of Double Beltrami states to solar eruptions</title>
			<authors>Kagan, D.; Mahajan, S. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 2, pp. 1140-1145.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1140K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..779N</bibcode>
			<title>Search for Outer Massive Bodies around Transiting Planetary Systems: Candidates of Faint Stellar Companions around HAT-P-7</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Kudo, Tomoyuki; Bergfors, Carolina; Nagasawa, Makiko; Thalmann, Christian; Sato, Bun'ei; Suzuki, Ryuji; Kandori, Ryo; Janson, Markus; Goto, Miwa; Brandner, Wolfgang; Ida, Shigeru; Abe, Lyu; Carson, Joseph; Egner, Sebastian E.; Feldt, Markus; Golota, Taras; Guyon, Olivier; Hashimoto, Jun; Hayano, Yutaka; Hayashi, Masahiko; Hayashi, Saeko S.; Henning, Thomas; Hodapp, Klaus W.; Ishii, Miki; Knapp, Gillian R.; Kusakabe, Nobuhiko; Kuzuhara, Masayuki; Matsuo, Taro; McElwain, Michael W.; Miyama, Shoken M.; Morino, Jun-Ichi; Moro-Martin, Amaya; Nishimura, Tetsuo; Pyo, Tae-Soo; Serabyn, Eugene; Suenaga, Takuya; Suto, Hiroshi; Takahashi, Yasuhiro Haruhi; Takami, Michihiro; Takato, Naruhisa; Terada, Hiroshi; Tomono, Daigo; Turner, Edwin L.; Watanabe, Makoto; Yamada, Toru; Takami, Hideki; Usuda, Tomonori; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.3, pp.779--786</journal>
			<date>6/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..779N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..653N</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-Orbit Alignment of the TrES-4 Transiting Planetary System and Possible Additional Radial-Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Winn, Joshua N.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.3, pp.653--660</journal>
			<date>6/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..653N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...513A..69H</bibcode>
			<title>The SOPHIE search for northern extrasolar planets. II. A multiple planet system around HD 9446</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Bonfils, X.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Moutou, C.; Delfosse, X.; Bouchy, F.; Boisse, I.; Arnold, L.; Desort, M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 513, id.A69</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...513A..69H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.464..384D</bibcode>
			<title>A transiting giant planet with a temperature between 250K and 430K</title>
			<authors>Deeg, H. J.; Moutou, C.; Erikson, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Tingley, B.; Barge, P.; Bruntt, H.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Ciardi, D.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hartog, R. Den; Hatzes, A.; Hidas, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Lister, T.; Llebaria, A.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Street, R.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 464, Issue 7287, pp. 384-387 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Natur.464..384D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403..151C</bibcode>
			<title>Line-profile tomography of exoplanet transits - I. The Doppler shadow of HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Bruce, V. A.; Miller, G. R. M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 1, pp. 151-158.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403..151C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..14F</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. IX. CoRoT-6b: a transiting ``hot Jupiter'' planet in an 8.9d orbit around a low-metallicity star</title>
			<authors>Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Alonso, R.; Deleuil, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Bruntt, H.; Alapini, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Guillot, T.; Lammer, H.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Guenther, E.; Gondoin, P.; den Hartog, R.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Stecklum, B.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..14F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709.1219C</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on the Oblateness of an Exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Carter, Joshua A.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 2, pp. 1219-1229 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709.1219C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..186...48J</bibcode>
			<title>On the Fundamental Mass-Period Functions of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jiang, Ing-Guey; Yeh, Li-Chin; Chang, Yen-Chang; Hung, Wen-Liang</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 186, Issue 1, pp. 48-62 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..186...48J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1386K</bibcode>
			<title>Refining Exoplanet Ephemerides and Transit Observing Strategies</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; von Braun, Kaspar; Laughlin, Gregory; Ciardi, David R.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 886, pp.1386-1394</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1386K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..505M</bibcode>
			<title>Planet formation in highly inclined binaries</title>
			<authors>Marzari, F.; Th&#233;bault, P.; Scholl, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.505-511</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..505M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..481C</bibcode>
			<title>High cadence near infrared timing observations of extrasolar planets. I. GJ 436b and XO-1b</title>
			<authors>C&#225;ceres, C.; Ivanov, V. D.; Minniti, D.; Naef, D.; Melo, C.; Mason, E.; Selman, F.; Pietrzynski, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.481-486</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..481C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1096K</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Transit Constraints Based upon Secondary Eclipse Observations</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 884, pp.1096-1103</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1096K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASJ...61L..35N</bibcode>
			<title>First Evidence of a Retrograde Orbit of a Transiting Exoplanet HAT-P-7b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.61, No.5, pp.L35-L40</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASJ...61L..35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASJ...61..991N</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Measurement of the Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect in the Exoplanetary System HD 17156</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sato, Bun'ei; Winn, Joshua N.; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide; Yamada, Toru</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.61, No.5, pp.991--997</journal>
			<date>10/2009 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASJ...61..991N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703L..99W</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-7: A Retrograde or Polar Orbit, and a Third Body</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Albrecht, Simon; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Crossfield, Ian J.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. L99-L103 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703L..99W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.2091W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Ingress and the Tilted Orbit of the Extraordinarily Eccentric Exoplanet HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Gazak, J. Zachary; Starkey, Donn; Ford, Eric B.; Col&#243;n, Knicole D.; Reyes, Francisco; Nortmann, Lisa; Dreizler, Stefan; Odewahn, Stephen; Welsh, William F.; Kadakia, Shimonee; Vanderbei, Robert J.; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Lockhart, Matthew; Crossfield, Ian J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Dantowitz, Ronald; Carter, Joshua A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. 2091-2100 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.2091W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.1734V</bibcode>
			<title>Simulations of Winds of Weak-Lined T Tauri Stars: The Magnetic Field Geometry and the Influence of the Wind on Giant Planet Migration</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Opher, M.; Jatenco-Pereira, V.; Gombosi, T. I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. 1734-1742 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.1734V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..377T</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin effect of CoRoT-3b and HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Queloz, D.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Collier Cameron, A.; Claret, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Deleuil, M.; Guillot, T.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lecavelier Des &#201;tangs, A.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.377-384</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..377T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...505..853B</bibcode>
			<title>The SOPHIE search for northern extrasolar planets . I. A companion around HD 16760 with mass close to the planet/brown-dwarf transition</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; H&#233;brard, G.; Udry, S.; Delfosse, X.; Boisse, I.; Desort, M.; Bonfils, X.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A. M.; Le Coroller, H.; Lovis, C.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 505, Issue 2, 2009, pp.853-858</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...505..853B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1016M</bibcode>
			<title>Systemic: A Testbed for Characterizing the Detection of Extrasolar Planets. I. The Systemic Console Package</title>
			<authors>Meschiari, Stefano; Wolf, Aaron S.; Rivera, Eugenio; Laughlin, Gregory; Vogt, Steve; Butler, Paul</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 883, pp.1016-1027</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1016M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...502..695P</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-orbit misalignment in the HD 80606 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; H&#233;brard, G.; Irwin, J. M.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Guillot, T.; Aigrain, S.; Bonfils, X.; Berta, Z.; Boisse, I.; Burke, C.; Charbonneau, D.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Nutzman, P.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 502, Issue 2, 2009, pp.695-703</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...502..695P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396L..16F</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a transit by the planetary companion of HD 80606</title>
			<authors>Fossey, Stephen J.; Waldmann, Ingo P.; Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 396, Issue 1, pp. L16-L20.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396L..16F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698..558G</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Detection of a Transit of HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Garcia-Melendo, E.; McCullough, P. R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 1, pp. 558-561 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698..558G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..182...97W</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Multi-Planet Systems Using the Hobby-Eberly Telescope</title>
			<authors>Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Levison, Harold F.; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 182, Issue 1, pp. 97-119 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..182...97W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498L...5M</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric and spectroscopic detection of the primary transit of the 111-day-period planet HD 80 606 b</title>
			<authors>Moutou, C.; H&#233;brard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Eggenberger, A.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; Gravallon, D.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 1, 2009, pp.L5-L8</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498L...5M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Natur.457..562L</bibcode>
			<title>Rapid heating of the atmosphere of an extrasolar planet</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Deming, Drake; Langton, Jonathan; Kasen, Daniel; Vogt, Steve; Butler, Paul; Rivera, Eugenio; Meschiari, Stefano</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 457, Issue 7229, pp. 562-564 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Natur.457..562L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PABei..27...14Z</bibcode>
			<title>The detection methods and statistical characteristics of exoplanet.</title>
			<authors>Zhang, N.; Ji, J.-H.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 27, 14-28 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PABei..27...14Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MmSAI..80..658B</bibcode>
			<title>Cloud formation and dynamics in cool dwarf and hot exoplanetary atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Burgasser, Adam J.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ&#224; Astronomica Italiana, v.80, p.658 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MmSAI..80..658B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689..492K</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Orbital Parameters through Planetary Transit Monitoring</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 1, pp. 492-498.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689..492K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..621F</bibcode>
			<title>Origins of Eccentric Extrasolar Planets: Testing the Planet-Planet Scattering Model</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 621-636.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..621F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..603J</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical Origin of Extrasolar Planet Eccentricity Distribution</title>
			<authors>Juric, Mario; Tremaine, Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 603-620.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..603J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681..636I</bibcode>
			<title>Parameters and Predictions for the Long-Period Transiting Planet HD 17156b</title>
			<authors>Irwin, Jonathan; Charbonneau, David; Nutzman, Philip; Welsh, William F.; Rajan, Abhijith; Hidas, Marton; Brown, Timothy M.; Lister, Timothy A.; Davies, Donald; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 1, pp. 636-643.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681..636I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...679.1566B</bibcode>
			<title>Impact of Orbital Eccentricity on the Detection of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Burke, Christopher J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 679, Issue 2, pp. 1566-1573.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...679.1566B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...483L..25L</bibcode>
			<title>Persistent circumpolar vortices on the extrasolar giant planet HD 37605 b</title>
			<authors>Langton, J.; Laughlin, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 483, Issue 3, 2008, pp.L25-L28</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...483L..25L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...480L..33T</bibcode>
			<title>The CORALIE survey for southern extra-solar planets. XV. Discovery of two eccentric planets orbiting HD 4113 and HD 156846</title>
			<authors>Tamuz, O.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Naef, D.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Demory, B.-O.; Figuera, P.; Marmier, M.; Montagnier, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 480, Issue 3, 2008, pp.L33-L36</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...480L..33T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...476L..13B</bibcode>
			<title>HD 17156b: a transiting planet with a 21.2-day period and an eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Barbieri, M.; Alonso, R.; Laughlin, G.; Almenara, J. M.; Bissinger, R.; Davies, D.; Gasparri, D.; Guido, E.; Lopresti, C.; Manzini, F.; Sostero, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 476, Issue 2, December III 2007, pp.L13-L16</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...476L..13B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...670..820W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters in Binary Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Wu, Yanqin; Murray, Norman W.; Ramsahai, J. Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 670, Issue 1, pp. 820-825.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...670..820W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1336F</bibcode>
			<title>Five Intermediate-Period Planets from the N2K Sample</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Vogt, Steven S.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Sato, Bun'ei; Henry, Gregory W.; Robinson, Sarah; Laughlin, Gregory; Ida, Shigeru; Toyota, Eri; Omiya, Masashi; Driscoll, Peter; Takeda, Genya; Wright, Jason T.; Johnson, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1336-1344.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1336F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1298F</bibcode>
			<title>Shrinking Binary and Planetary Orbits by Kozai Cycles with Tidal Friction</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel; Tremaine, Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1298-1315.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1298F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..359G</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting low-frequency radio fluxes of known extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Grie&#223;meier, J.-M.; Zarka, P.; Spreeuw, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 1, November III 2007, pp.359-368</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..359G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASP..119..986B</bibcode>
			<title>Effects of Orbital Eccentricity on Extrasolar Planet Transit Detectability and Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 119, Issue 859, pp. 986-993.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASP..119..986B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...666..475M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Planet Taxonomy: A New Statistical Approach</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 666, Issue 1, pp. 475-485.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...666..475M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AJ....134.1276W</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical and Observational Constraints on Additional Planets in Highly Eccentric Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Levison, Harold F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 134, Issue 3, pp. 1276-1284 (2007).</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AJ....134.1276W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1312M</bibcode>
			<title>Are Debris Disks and Massive Planets Correlated?</title>
			<authors>Moro-Mart&#237;n, Amaya; Carpenter, John M.; Meyer, Michael R.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Malhotra, Renu; Hollenbach, David; Najita, Joan; Henning, Thomas; Kim, Jinyoung S.; Bouwman, Jeroen; Silverstone, Murray D.; Hines, Dean C.; Wolf, Sebastian; Pascucci, Ilaria; Mamajek, Eric E.; Lunine, Jonathan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1312-1321.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1312M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJS..168..297T</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and Evolution of Nearby Stars with Planets. II. Physical Properties of ~1000 Cool Stars from the SPOCS Catalog</title>
			<authors>Takeda, Genya; Ford, Eric B.; Sills, Alison; Rasio, Frederic A.; Fischer, Debra A.; Valenti, Jeff A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 168, Issue 2, pp. 297-318.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJS..168..297T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...462..345D</bibcode>
			<title>Properties of planets in binary systems. The role of binary separation</title>
			<authors>Desidera, S.; Barbieri, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 462, Issue 1, January IV 2007, pp.345-353</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...462..345D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653..700S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Search for Transits of the Planets Orbiting Gliese 876</title>
			<authors>Shankland, P. D.; Rivera, E. J.; Laughlin, G.; Blank, D. L.; Price, A.; Gary, B.; Bissinger, R.; Ringwald, F.; White, G.; Henry, G. W.; McGee, P.; Wolf, A. S.; Carter, B.; Lee, S.; Biggs, J.; Monard, B.; Ashley, M. C. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 1, pp. 700-707.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653..700S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1010J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of Known Exoplanetary Systems Based on Measured Stellar Properties</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick; Underwood, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1019.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1010J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.370.1379J</bibcode>
			<title>Data analysis on the extrasolar planets using robust clustering</title>
			<authors>Jiang, Ing-Guey; Yeh, Li-Chin; Hung, Wen-Liang; Yang, Miin-Shen</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 370, Issue 3, pp. 1379-1392.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.370.1379J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.369.1267D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of a binary or planetary system during encounters with a third inclined body</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 369, Issue 3, pp. 1267-1280.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.369.1267D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..523R</bibcode>
			<title>Two Suns in The Sky: Stellar Multiplicity in Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Raghavan, Deepak; Henry, Todd J.; Mason, Brian D.; Subasavage, John P.; Jao, Wei-Chun; Beaulieu, Thom D.; Hambly, Nigel C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 523-542.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..523R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..505B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of Nearby Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. P.; Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Penny, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 505-522.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..505B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AN....327..321M</bibcode>
			<title>A search for wide visual companions of exoplanet host stars: The Calar Alto Survey</title>
			<authors>Mugrauer, M.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Mazeh, T.; Guenther, E.; Fern&#225;ndez, M.; Broeg, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.327, Issue 4, p.321</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AN....327..321M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...449..417S</bibcode>
			<title>A massive planet to the young disc star HD 81040</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Udry, S.; Zucker, S.; Torres, G.; Beuzit, J. L.; Latham, D. W.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Naef, D.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Sivan, J.-P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 449, Issue 1, April I 2006, pp.417-424</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...449..417S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...447.1159E</bibcode>
			<title>The CORALIE survey for southern extrasolar planets. XIV. HD 142022 b: a long-period planetary companion in a wide binary</title>
			<authors>Eggenberger, A.; Mayor, M.; Naef, D.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Udry, S.; Lovis, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 447, Issue 3, March I 2006, pp.1159-1163</journal>
			<date>3/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...447.1159E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006RPPh...69..119P</bibcode>
			<title>Planet formation and migration</title>
			<authors>Papaloizou, John C. B.; Terquem, Caroline</authors>
			<journal>Reports on Progress in Physics, Volume 69, Issue 1, pp. 119-180 (2006).</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006RPPh...69..119P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.358.1273V</bibcode>
			<title>An extension of Newton's apsidal precession theorem</title>
			<authors>Valluri, S. R.; Yu, P.; Smith, G. E.; Wiegert, P. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 358, Issue 4, pp. 1273-1284.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.358.1273V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622.1091J</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for Habitable ``Earths'' in Known Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Underwood, David R.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 2, pp. 1091-1101.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622.1091J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...431.1129H</bibcode>
			<title>Statistical properties of exoplanets.  IV. The period-eccentricity relations of exoplanets and of binary stars</title>
			<authors>Halbwachs, J. L.; Mayor, M.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 431, Issue 3, March I 2005, pp.1129-1137</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...431.1129H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...612..511L</bibcode>
			<title>The Radiometric Bode's Law and Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Lazio, T. Joseph, W.; Farrell, W. M.; Dietrick, Jill; Greenlees, Elizabeth; Hogan, Emily; Jones, Christopher; Hennig, L. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 612, Issue 1, pp. 511-518.</journal>
			<date>9/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...612..511L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...611L.133C</bibcode>
			<title>The First Hobby-Eberly Telescope Planet: A Companion to HD 37605</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; McArthur, Barbara; Paulson, Diane B.; Smith, Verne V.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Tull, Robert G.; Good, John; Booth, John; Shetrone, Matthew; Roman, Brian; Odewahn, Stephen; Deglman, Frank; Graver, Michelle; Soukup, Michael; Villarreal, Martin L., Jr.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 611, Issue 2, pp. L133-L136.</journal>
			<date>8/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...611L.133C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...417..353E</bibcode>
			<title>Statistical properties of exoplanets. III. Planet properties and stellar multiplicity</title>
			<authors>Eggenberger, A.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.417, p.353-360 (2004)</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...417..353E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...410.1039P</bibcode>
			<title>The ELODIE survey for northern extra-solar planets. I. Six new extra-solar planet candidates</title>
			<authors>Perrier, C.; Sivan, J.-P.; Naef, D.; Beuzit, J. L.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.410, p.1039-1049 (2003)</journal>
			<date>11/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...410.1039P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...589..605W</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Migration and Binary Companions: The Case of HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Wu, Y.; Murray, N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 589, Issue 1, pp. 605-614.</journal>
			<date>5/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...589..605W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...588.1121S</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Atmospheres of Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Sudarsky, David; Burrows, Adam; Hubeny, Ivan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 588, Issue 2, pp. 1121-1148.</journal>
			<date>5/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...588.1121S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...586.1394F</bibcode>
			<title>A Planetary Companion to HD 40979 and Additional Planets Orbiting HD 12661 and HD 38529</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Henry, Gregory W.; Pourbaix, Dimitri; Walp, Bernard; Misch, Anthony A.; Wright, Jason T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 586, Issue 2, pp. 1394-1408.</journal>
			<date>4/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...586.1394F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...583..473M</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical Habitability of Known Extrasolar Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Menou, Kristen; Tabachnik, Serge</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 583, Issue 1, pp. 473-488.</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...583..473M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...582..449J</bibcode>
			<title>On the Fate of Close-in Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jiang, Ing-Guey; Ip, Wing-Huen; Yeh, Li-Chin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 582, Issue 1, pp. 449-454.</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...582..449J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003BASI...31...37V</bibcode>
			<title>Search for periodicities in distribution of orbits of planets.</title>
			<authors>Vahia, M. N.; Mahajani, P.; Rao, A. R.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the Astronomical Society of India, 31, 37-47 (2003)</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003BASI...31...37V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ASPC..294..213W</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Circularization and Kozai Migration</title>
			<authors>Wu, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Scientific Frontiers in Research on Extrasolar Planets, ASP Conference Series, Vol 294, Edited by Drake Deming and Sara Seager. (San Francisco: ASP) ISBN: 1-58381-141-9, 2003, pp. 213-216</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ASPC..294..213W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ASPC..294....1M</bibcode>
			<title>Properties of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.</authors>
			<journal>Scientific Frontiers in Research on Extrasolar Planets, ASP Conference Series, Vol 294, Edited by Drake Deming and Sara Seager. (San Francisco: ASP) ISBN: 1-58381-141-9, 2003, pp. 1-16</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ASPC..294....1M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.337.1170J</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planets around HD 196050, HD 216437 and HD 160691</title>
			<authors>Jones, Hugh R. A.; Paul Butler, R.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Tinney, Chris G.; Penny, Alan J.; McCarthy, Chris; Carter, Brad D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notice of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 337, Issue 4, pp. 1170-1178.</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.337.1170J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...578..565B</bibcode>
			<title>On the Double-Planet System around HD 83443</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Vogt, Steven S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, Hugh R. A.; McCarthy, Chris; Penny, Alan J.; Apps, Kevin; Carter, Brad D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 578, Issue 1, pp. 565-572.</journal>
			<date>10/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...578..565B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...573..829M</bibcode>
			<title>Calculating the Tidal, Spin, and Dynamical Evolution of Extrasolar Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Mardling, Rosemary A.; Lin, D. N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 573, Issue 2, pp. 829-844.</journal>
			<date>7/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...573..829M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...572L..79L</bibcode>
			<title>A Distant Stellar Companion in the upsilo Andromedae System</title>
			<authors>Lowrance, Patrick J.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Beichman, Charles A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 572, Issue 1, pp. L79-L81.</journal>
			<date>6/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...572L..79L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...562.1038Z</bibcode>
			<title>Derivation of the Mass Distribution of Extrasolar Planets with MAXLIMA, a Maximum Likelihood Algorithm</title>
			<authors>Zucker, Shay; Mazeh, Tsevi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 562, Issue 2, pp. 1038-1044.</journal>
			<date>12/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...562.1038Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...375L..27N</bibcode>
			<title>HD 80606 b, a planet on an extremely elongated orbit</title>
			<authors>Naef, D.; Latham, D. W.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Beuzit, J. L.; Drukier, G. A.; Perrier-Bellet, C.; Queloz, D.; Sivan, J. P.; Torres, G.; Udry, S.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.375, p.L27-L30 (2001)</journal>
			<date>8/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...375L..27N</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..90D</bibcode>
			<title>A giant planet in the triple system HD 132563</title>
			<authors>Desidera, S.; Carolo, E.; Gratton, R.; Martinez Fiorenzano, A. F.; Endl, M.; Mesa, D.; Barbieri, M.; Bonavita, M.; Cecconi, M.; Claudi, R. U.; Cosentino, R.; Marzari, F.; Scuderi, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A90</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..90D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A...7B</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and evolution of planetary systems in presence of highly inclined stellar perturbers</title>
			<authors>Batygin, K.; Morbidelli, A.; Tsiganis, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A7</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A...7B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...530A..73C</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric activity of stars with planets</title>
			<authors>Canto Martins, B. L.; Das Chagas, M. L.; Alves, S.; Le&#227;o, I. C.; de Souza Neto, L. P.; de Medeiros, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 530, id.A73</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...530A..73C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...731...16B</bibcode>
			<title>Methane in the Atmosphere of the Transiting Hot Neptune GJ436B?</title>
			<authors>Beaulieu, J.-P.; Tinetti, G.; Kipping, D. M.; Ribas, I.; Barber, R. J.; Cho, J. Y.-K.; Polichtchouk, I.; Tennyson, J.; Yurchenko, S. N.; Griffith, C. A.; Batista, V.; Waldmann, I.; Miller, S.; Carey, S.; Mousis, O.; Fossey, S. J.; Aylward, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 731, Issue 1, article id. 16 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...731...16B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..53B</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variations in eccentric hierarchical triple exoplanetary systems. I. Perturbations on the time scale of the orbital period of the perturber</title>
			<authors>Borkovits, T.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Forg&#225;cs-Dajka, E.; Heged&#252;s, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A53</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..53B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63S.531H</bibcode>
			<title>A Possible Tilted Orbit of the Super-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Narita, Norio; Shporer, Avi; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.SP2, pp.531--536</journal>
			<date>3/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63S.531H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527L..11H</bibcode>
			<title>The retrograde orbit of the HAT-P-6b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Ehrenreich, D.; Bouchy, F.; Delfosse, X.; Moutou, C.; Arnold, L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.L11</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527L..11H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...63W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Orientations of Exoplanets: HAT-P-4b is Prograde and HAT-P-14b is Retrograde</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Hartman, Joel D.; Holman, Matthew J.; Albrecht, Simon; Crepp, Justin R.; Morton, Timothy D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 63 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...63W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A..12D</bibcode>
			<title>Transit spectrophotometry of the exoplanet HD 189733b. II. New Spitzer observations at 3.6 mum</title>
			<authors>D&#233;sert, J.-M.; Sing, D.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Ehrenreich, D.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Parmentier, V.; Ferlet, R.; Henry, G. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A12</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A..12D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724.1108J</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect of Exoplanet Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Cochran, William D.; Welsh, William F.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John Asher; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Howard, Andrew W.; MacQueen, Phillip; Orosz, Jerome A.; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Allen, Christopher; Tenenbaum, Peter; Wu, Hayley; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Cote, Miles T.; McCauliff, Sean; Girouard, Forrest R.; Gunter, Jay P.; Wohler, Bill; Hall, Jennifer R.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Kamal Uddin, AKM; Wu, Michael S.; Bhavsar, Paresh A.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Pletcher, David L.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, article id. 1108-1119 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724.1108J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.1929L</bibcode>
			<title>Radio Observations of HD 80606 Near Planetary Periastron</title>
			<authors>Lazio, T. Joseph W.; Shankland, P. D.; Farrell, W. M.; Blank, D. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 1929-1933 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.1929L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1606W</bibcode>
			<title>Estimating the masses of extra-solar planets</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Littlefair, S. P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Dhillon, V. S.; Simpson, E. K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1606-1622.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1606W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..88B</bibcode>
			<title>The SOPHIE search for northern extrasolar planets. III. A Jupiter-mass companion around HD 109246</title>
			<authors>Boisse, I.; Eggenberger, A.; Santos, N. C.; Lovis, C.; Bouchy, F.; H&#233; brard, G.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Gallenne, A.; Lagrange, A. M.; Moutou, C.; Udry, S.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Perruchot, S.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; S&#233; gransan, D.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A88</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..88B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..15N</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extrasolar planets. XXIII. 8 planetary companions to low-activity solar-type stars</title>
			<authors>Naef, D.; Mayor, M.; Lo Curto, G.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Moutou, C.; Benz, W.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; H&#233;brard, G.; Mordasini, C.; Perrier, C.; Boisse, I.; Sosnowska, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A15</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..15N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A..60L</bibcode>
			<title>Explicit expansion of the three-body disturbing function for arbitrary eccentricities and inclinations</title>
			<authors>Laskar, J.; Bou&#233;, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A60</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...522A..60L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722..880S</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based Multisite Observations of Two Transits of HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Shporer, A.; Winn, J. N.; Dreizler, S.; Col&#243;n, K. D.; Wood-Vasey, W. M.; Choi, P. I.; Morley, C.; Moutou, C.; Welsh, W. F.; Pollaco, D.; Starkey, D.; Adams, E.; Barros, S. C. C.; Bouchy, F.; Cabrera-Lavers, A.; Cerutti, S.; Coban, L.; Costello, K.; Deeg, H.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fernandez, J.; Fleming, S. W.; Ford, E. B.; Fulton, B. J.; Good, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Holman, M. J.; Hunt, M.; Kadakia, S.; Lander, G.; Lockhart, M.; Mazeh, T.; Morehead, R. C.; Nelson, B. E.; Nortmann, L.; Reyes, F.; Roebuck, E.; Rudy, A. R.; Ruth, R.; Simpson, E.; Vincent, C.; Weaver, G.; Xie, J.-W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. 880-887 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722..880S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721.1861A</bibcode>
			<title>The Climate of HD 189733b from Fourteen Transits and Eclipses Measured by Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Agol, Eric; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Knutson, Heather A.; Deming, Drake; Steffen, Jason H.; Henry, Gregory W.; Charbonneau, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. 1861-1877 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...721.1861A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721.1308S</bibcode>
			<title>Generalized Milankovitch Cycles and Long-Term Climatic Habitability</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Raymond, Sean N.; Dressing, Courtney D.; Scharf, Caleb A.; Mitchell, Jonathan L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. 1308-1318 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...721.1308S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1020A</bibcode>
			<title>Observing Exoplanets with SOFIA</title>
			<authors>Angerhausen, D.; Krabbe, A.; Iserlohe, C.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 895, pp.1020-1029</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1020A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1118B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-16b: A 4 M J Planet Transiting a Bright Star on an Eccentric Orbit</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, L. A.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J. D.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Howard, A. W.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Andersen, J.; Fur&#233;sz, G.; Perumpilly, G.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; B&#233;ky, B.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1118-1125 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1118B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1140K</bibcode>
			<title>Application of Double Beltrami states to solar eruptions</title>
			<authors>Kagan, D.; Mahajan, S. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 2, pp. 1140-1145.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1140K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.1867S</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit alignment of the transiting exoplanet WASP-3b from Rossiter-McLaughlin observations</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Pollacco, D.; H&#233;brard, G.; Gibson, N. P.; Barros, S. C. C.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Miller, G. R. M.; Watson, C. A.; Keenan, F. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 1867-1872.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.1867S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716..766L</bibcode>
			<title>Lithium Abundance in Solar-type Stars with Low Chromospheric Activity: Application to the Search for Maunder Minimum Analogs</title>
			<authors>Lubin, Dan; Tytler, David; Kirkman, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 1, pp. 766-775 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716..766L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..64L</bibcode>
			<title>Is tidal heating sufficient to explain bloated exoplanets? Consistent calculations accounting for finite initial eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Chabrier, G.; Baraffe, I.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A64</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..64L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.404..409T</bibcode>
			<title>Eccentricity pumping of a planet on an inclined orbit by a disc</title>
			<authors>Terquem, Caroline; Ajmia, Aikel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 404, Issue 1, pp. 409-414.</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.404..409T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..421T</bibcode>
			<title>A Prograde, Low-inclination Orbit for the Very Hot Jupiter WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Tripathi, Anjali; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Halverson, Sam; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Holman, Matthew J.; de Kleer, Katherine R.; Carter, Joshua A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Cabrera, Nicole E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 421-428 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..421T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.1368G</bibcode>
			<title>Parent stars of extrasolar planets - X. Lithium abundances and v sini revisited</title>
			<authors>Gonzalez, G.; Carlson, M. K.; Tobin, R. W.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 3, pp. 1368-1380.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.1368G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.136D</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-6b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Orbiting a Metal-rich Star</title>
			<authors>Dunham, Edward W.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra; Fur&#233;sz, Gabor; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Monet, David G.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, article id. L136-L139 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.136D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..54C</bibcode>
			<title>An absolutely calibrated Teff scale from the infrared flux method. Dwarfs and subgiants</title>
			<authors>Casagrande, L.; Ram&#237;rez, I.; Mel&#233;ndez, J.; Bessell, M.; Asplund, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A54</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401.2665P</bibcode>
			<title>Refined stellar, orbital and planetary parameters of the eccentric HAT-P-2 planetary system</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Torres, Guillermo; Noyes, Robert W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Johnson, John A.; Henry, Gregory W.; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Howard, Andrew W.; Sipocz, Brigitta; Latham, David W.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 4, pp. 2665-2674.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401.2665P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401.1029C</bibcode>
			<title>An integrated analysis of radial velocities in planet searches</title>
			<authors>Cumming, Andrew; Dragomir, Diana</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 2, pp. 1029-1042.</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401.1029C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A.103S</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos preliminary astrometric masses for the two close-in companions to HD 131664 and HD 43848. A brown dwarf and a low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Desidera, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A103</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A.103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707..446B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-13b,c: A Transiting Hot Jupiter with a Massive Outer Companion on an Eccentric Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Howard, A. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225; cs, G&#233;za; Fischer, D. A.; Latham, D. W.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sipocz, B.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Esquerdo, G. A.; P&#225;l, A.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, pp. 446-456 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707..446B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707..167S</bibcode>
			<title>Physical Properties of the 0.94-Day Period Transiting Planetary System WASP-18</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Dominik, M.; Glitrup, M.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Mathiasen, M.; Anderson, D. R.; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Burgdorf, M.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Harps&#248;e, K.; Hessman, F.; Hundertmark, M.; Maier, G.; Mancini, L.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Skottfelt, J.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.; Zimmer, F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, article id. 167-172 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707..167S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1104J</bibcode>
			<title>A Third Exoplanetary System with Misaligned Orbital and Stellar Spin Axes</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.; Albrecht, Simon; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Gazak, J. Zachary</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 884, pp.1104-1111</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1104J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1096K</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Transit Constraints Based upon Secondary Eclipse Observations</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 884, pp.1096-1103</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1096K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.2091W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Ingress and the Tilted Orbit of the Extraordinarily Eccentric Exoplanet HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Gazak, J. Zachary; Starkey, Donn; Ford, Eric B.; Col&#243;n, Knicole D.; Reyes, Francisco; Nortmann, Lisa; Dreizler, Stefan; Odewahn, Stephen; Welsh, William F.; Kadakia, Shimonee; Vanderbei, Robert J.; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Lockhart, Matthew; Crossfield, Ian J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Dantowitz, Ronald; Carter, Joshua A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. 2091-2100 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.2091W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1016M</bibcode>
			<title>Systemic: A Testbed for Characterizing the Detection of Extrasolar Planets. I. The Systemic Console Package</title>
			<authors>Meschiari, Stefano; Wolf, Aaron S.; Rivera, Eugenio; Laughlin, Gregory; Vogt, Steve; Butler, Paul</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 883, pp.1016-1027</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1016M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..514M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission of XO-2b: Evidence for a Weak Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 514-520 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..514M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700L..73K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Relationship Between Debris Disks and Planets</title>
			<authors>K&#243;sp&#225;l, &#193;gnes; Ardila, David R.; Mo&#243;r, Attila; &#193;brah&#225;m, P&#233;ter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. L73-L77 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700L..73K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...502..695P</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-orbit misalignment in the HD 80606 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; H&#233;brard, G.; Irwin, J. M.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Guillot, T.; Aigrain, S.; Bonfils, X.; Berta, Z.; Boisse, I.; Burke, C.; Charbonneau, D.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Nutzman, P.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 502, Issue 2, 2009, pp.695-703</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...502..695P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..302W</bibcode>
			<title>On the Spin-Orbit Misalignment of the XO-3 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Fabrycky, Daniel; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Narita, Norio; Crossfield, Ian J.; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Esquerdo, Gil; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 302-308 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..302W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501..941H</bibcode>
			<title>The Geneva-Copenhagen survey of the solar neighbourhood. III. Improved distances, ages, and kinematics</title>
			<authors>Holmberg, J.; Nordstr&#246;m, B.; Andersen, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 3, 2009, pp.941-947</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501..941H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396L..16F</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a transit by the planetary companion of HD 80606</title>
			<authors>Fossey, Stephen J.; Waldmann, Ingo P.; Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 396, Issue 1, pp. L16-L20.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396L..16F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698..558G</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Detection of a Transit of HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Garcia-Melendo, E.; McCullough, P. R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 1, pp. 558-561 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698..558G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..182...97W</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Multi-Planet Systems Using the Hobby-Eberly Telescope</title>
			<authors>Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Levison, Harold F.; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 182, Issue 1, pp. 97-119 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..182...97W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696...75H</bibcode>
			<title>The NASA-UC Eta-Earth Program. I. A Super-Earth Orbiting HD 7924</title>
			<authors>Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Wright, Jason T.; Henry, Gregory W.; Giguere, Matthew J.; Isaacson, Howard; Valenti, Jeff A.; Anderson, Jay; Piskunov, Nikolai E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 1, pp. 75-83 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696...75H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694.1085V</bibcode>
			<title>Directly Determined Linear Radii and Effective Temperatures of Exoplanet Host Stars</title>
			<authors>van Belle, Gerard T.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 2, pp. 1085-1098 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694.1085V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498L...5M</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric and spectroscopic detection of the primary transit of the 111-day-period planet HD 80 606 b</title>
			<authors>Moutou, C.; H&#233;brard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Eggenberger, A.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; Gravallon, D.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 1, 2009, pp.L5-L8</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498L...5M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..181..197C</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and Evolution of Planetary Systems: Properties of Debris Dust Around Solar-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Carpenter, John M.; Bouwman, Jeroen; Mamajek, Eric E.; Meyer, Michael R.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Backman, Dana E.; Henning, Thomas; Hines, Dean C.; Hollenbach, David; Kim, Jinyoung Serena; Moro-Martin, Amaya; Pascucci, Ilaria; Silverstone, Murray D.; Stauffer, John R.; Wolf, Sebastian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 181, Issue 1, pp. 197-226 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..181..197C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..181...62M</bibcode>
			<title>The Palomar/Keck Adaptive Optics Survey of Young Solar Analogs: Evidence for a Universal Companion Mass Function</title>
			<authors>Metchev, Stanimir A.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 181, Issue 1, pp. 62-109 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..181...62M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Natur.457..562L</bibcode>
			<title>Rapid heating of the atmosphere of an extrasolar planet</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Deming, Drake; Langton, Jonathan; Kasen, Daniel; Vogt, Steve; Butler, Paul; Rivera, Eugenio; Meschiari, Stefano</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 457, Issue 7229, pp. 562-564 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Natur.457..562L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...494..373M</bibcode>
			<title>The multiplicity of exoplanet host stars. New low-mass stellar companions of the exoplanet host stars HD 125612 and HD 212301</title>
			<authors>Mugrauer, M.; Neuh&#228;user, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 494, Issue 1, 2009, pp.373-378</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...494..373M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PABei..27...14Z</bibcode>
			<title>The detection methods and statistical characteristics of exoplanet.</title>
			<authors>Zhang, N.; Ji, J.-H.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 27, 14-28 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PABei..27...14Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJS..179..423C</bibcode>
			<title>The Formation and Evolution of Planetary Systems: Description of the Spitzer Legacy Science Database</title>
			<authors>Carpenter, John M.; Bouwman, Jeroen; Silverstone, Murray D.; Kim, Jinyoung Serena; Stauffer, John; Cohen, Martin; Hines, Dean C.; Meyer, Michael R.; Crockett, Nathan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 179, Issue 2, pp. 423-450.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJS..179..423C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AJ....136.1901L</bibcode>
			<title>Two Jupiter-Mass Planets Orbiting HD 154672 and HD 205739</title>
			<authors>L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Butler, R. Paul; Fischer, Debra A.; Minniti, Dante; Shectman, Stephen A.; Takeda, Genya; Adams, Fred C.; Wright, Jason T.; Arriagada, Pamela</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 136, Issue 5, pp. 1901-1905 (2008).</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AJ....136.1901L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..621F</bibcode>
			<title>Origins of Eccentric Extrasolar Planets: Testing the Planet-Planet Scattering Model</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 621-636.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..621F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...480L..33T</bibcode>
			<title>The CORALIE survey for southern extra-solar planets. XV. Discovery of two eccentric planets orbiting HD 4113 and HD 156846</title>
			<authors>Tamuz, O.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Naef, D.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Demory, B.-O.; Figuera, P.; Marmier, M.; Montagnier, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 480, Issue 3, 2008, pp.L33-L36</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...480L..33T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...480...91S</bibcode>
			<title>Vertical distribution of Galactic disk stars. IV. AMR and AVR from clump giants</title>
			<authors>Soubiran, C.; Bienaym&#233;, O.; Mishenina, T. V.; Kovtyukh, V. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 480, Issue 1, March II 2008, pp.91-101</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...480...91S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671.2115B</bibcode>
			<title>XO-2b: Transiting Hot Jupiter in a Metal-rich Common Proper Motion Binary</title>
			<authors>Burke, Christopher J.; McCullough, P. R.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Janes, Kenneth A.; Heasley, J. N.; Summers, F. J.; Stys, J. E.; Bissinger, R.; Fleenor, Michael L.; Foote, Cindy N.; Garc&#237;a-Melendo, Enrique; Gary, Bruce L.; Howell, P. J.; Mallia, F.; Masi, G.; Taylor, B.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 2, pp. 2115-2128.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671.2115B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1336F</bibcode>
			<title>Five Intermediate-Period Planets from the N2K Sample</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Vogt, Steven S.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Sato, Bun'ei; Henry, Gregory W.; Robinson, Sarah; Laughlin, Gregory; Ida, Shigeru; Toyota, Eri; Omiya, Masashi; Driscoll, Peter; Takeda, Genya; Wright, Jason T.; Johnson, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1336-1344.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1336F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1298F</bibcode>
			<title>Shrinking Binary and Planetary Orbits by Kozai Cycles with Tidal Friction</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel; Tremaine, Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1298-1315.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1298F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AJ....134.1276W</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical and Observational Constraints on Additional Planets in Highly Eccentric Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Wittenmyer, Robert A.; Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Levison, Harold F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 134, Issue 3, pp. 1276-1284 (2007).</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AJ....134.1276W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.378.1141G</bibcode>
			<title>Parent stars of extrasolar planets - VIII. Chemical abundances for 18 elements in 31 stars</title>
			<authors>Gonzalez, Guillermo; Laws, Chris</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 378, Issue 3, pp. 1141-1152.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.378.1141G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...469..755M</bibcode>
			<title>The multiplicity of exoplanet host stars. Spectroscopic confirmation of the companions GJ 3021 B and HD 27442 B, one new planet host triple-star system, and global statistics</title>
			<authors>Mugrauer, M.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Mazeh, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 469, Issue 2, July II 2007, pp.755-770</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...469..755M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662.1282M</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Formation Scenarios Revisited: Core-Accretion versus Disk Instability</title>
			<authors>Matsuo, T.; Shibai, H.; Ootsubo, T.; Tamura, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 2, pp. 1282-1292.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662.1282M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AJ....133.2524W</bibcode>
			<title>High-Dispersion Optical Spectra of Nearby Stars Younger Than the Sun</title>
			<authors>White, Russel J.; Gabor, Jared M.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 133, Issue 6, pp. 2524-2536.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AJ....133.2524W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJS..169..430R</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. VII. Atmospheric Parameters of 1907 Metal-rich Stars: Finding Planet-Search Targets</title>
			<authors>Robinson, Sarah E.; Ammons, S. Mark; Kretke, Katherine A.; Strader, Jay; Wertheimer, Jeremy G.; Fischer, Debra A.; Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 169, Issue 2, pp. 430-438.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJS..169..430R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1312M</bibcode>
			<title>Are Debris Disks and Massive Planets Correlated?</title>
			<authors>Moro-Mart&#237;n, Amaya; Carpenter, John M.; Meyer, Michael R.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Malhotra, Renu; Hollenbach, David; Najita, Joan; Henning, Thomas; Kim, Jinyoung S.; Bouwman, Jeroen; Silverstone, Murray D.; Hines, Dean C.; Wolf, Sebastian; Pascucci, Ilaria; Mamajek, Eric E.; Lunine, Jonathan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1312-1321.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1312M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJS..168..297T</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and Evolution of Nearby Stars with Planets. II. Physical Properties of ~1000 Cool Stars from the SPOCS Catalog</title>
			<authors>Takeda, Genya; Ford, Eric B.; Sills, Alison; Rasio, Frederic A.; Fischer, Debra A.; Valenti, Jeff A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 168, Issue 2, pp. 297-318.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJS..168..297T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...462..345D</bibcode>
			<title>Properties of planets in binary systems. The role of binary separation</title>
			<authors>Desidera, S.; Barbieri, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 462, Issue 1, January IV 2007, pp.345-353</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...462..345D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1690M</bibcode>
			<title>The Formation and Evolution of Planetary Systems: Placing Our Solar System in Context with Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Meyer, Michael R.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Backman, Dana; Beckwith, Steve; Bouwman, Jeroen; Brooke, Tim; Carpenter, John; Cohen, Martin; Cortes, Stephanie; Crockett, Nathan; Gorti, Uma; Henning, Thomas; Hines, Dean; Hollenbach, David; Kim, Jinyoung Serena; Lunine, Jonathan; Malhotra, Renu; Mamajek, Eric; Metchev, Stanimir; Moro-Martin, Amaya; Morris, Pat; Najita, Joan; Padgett, Deborah; Pascucci, Ilaria; Rodmann, Jens; Schlingman, Wayne; Silverstone, Murray; Soderblom, David; Stauffer, John; Stobie, Elizabeth; Strom, Steve; Watson, Dan; Weidenschilling, Stuart; Wolf, Sebastian; Young, Erick</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 850, pp. 1690-1710.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1690M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.373.1227D</bibcode>
			<title>Stable satellites around extrasolar giant planets</title>
			<authors>Domingos, R. C.; Winter, O. C.; Yokoyama, T.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 373, Issue 3, pp. 1227-1234.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.373.1227D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006JAVSO..34..322W</bibcode>
			<title>Committee Reports: Charge-Coupled Device (CCD).</title>
			<authors>Walker, G.</authors>
			<journal>Journal of the American Association of Variable Star Observers, 34, 322-323 (2006)</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006JAVSO..34..322W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1010J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of Known Exoplanetary Systems Based on Measured Stellar Properties</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick; Underwood, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1019.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1010J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..523R</bibcode>
			<title>Two Suns in The Sky: Stellar Multiplicity in Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Raghavan, Deepak; Henry, Todd J.; Mason, Brian D.; Subasavage, John P.; Jao, Wei-Chun; Beaulieu, Thom D.; Hambly, Nigel C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 523-542.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..523R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..505B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of Nearby Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. P.; Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Penny, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 505-522.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..505B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.369..249J</bibcode>
			<title>High-eccentricity planets from the Anglo-Australian Planet Search</title>
			<authors>Jones, Hugh R. A.; Butler, R. Paul; Tinney, C. G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Carter, Brad D.; Penny, Alan J.; McCarthy, Chris; Bailey, Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 369, Issue 1, pp. 249-256.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.369..249J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644..543H</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical Stability and Habitability of the gamma Cephei Binary-Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Haghighipour, Nader</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 1, pp. 543-550.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644..543H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....131.3069L</bibcode>
			<title>Dwarfs in the Local Region</title>
			<authors>Luck, R. Earle; Heiter, Ulrike</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 131, Issue 6, pp. 3069-3092.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....131.3069L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AN....327..321M</bibcode>
			<title>A search for wide visual companions of exoplanet host stars: The Calar Alto Survey</title>
			<authors>Mugrauer, M.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Mazeh, T.; Guenther, E.; Fern&#225;ndez, M.; Broeg, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.327, Issue 4, p.321</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AN....327..321M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....131.2274S</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical Composition of the Planet-harboring Star TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Yong, David; Carney, Bruce W.; Laird, John B.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 131, Issue 4, pp. 2274-2289.</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....131.2274S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...449..809E</bibcode>
			<title>Abundance ratios of volatile vs. refractory elements in planet-harbouring stars: hints of pollution?</title>
			<authors>Ecuvillon, A.; Israelian, G.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Gilli, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 449, Issue 2, April II 2006, pp.809-816</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...449..809E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...449..723G</bibcode>
			<title>Abundances of refractory elements in the atmospheres of stars with extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Gilli, G.; Israelian, G.; Ecuvillon, A.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 449, Issue 2, April II 2006, pp.723-736</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...449..723G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006JRASC.100...12F</bibcode>
			<title>Deep-Sky Contemplations</title>
			<authors>Finlay, Warren; Hube, Doug</authors>
			<journal>Journal of the Royal Astronomical Society of Canada, Vol. 100, Issue 1, p.12</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006JRASC.100...12F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...637.1102R</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. V. Identifying Very Metal-rich Stars with Low-Resolution Spectra: Finding Planet-Search Targets</title>
			<authors>Robinson, Sarah E.; Strader, Jay; Ammons, S. Mark; Laughlin, Gregory; Fischer, Debra</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 637, Issue 2, pp. 1102-1112.</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...637.1102R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...445.1159S</bibcode>
			<title>Can stellar wobble in triple systems mimic a planet?</title>
			<authors>Schneider, J.; Cabrera, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 445, Issue 3, January III 2006, pp.1159-1163</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...445.1159S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...445..633E</bibcode>
			<title>Oxygen abundances in planet-harbouring stars. Comparison of different abundance indicators</title>
			<authors>Ecuvillon, A.; Israelian, G.; Santos, N. C.; Shchukina, N. G.; Mayor, M.; Rebolo, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 445, Issue 2, January II 2006, pp.633-645</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...445..633E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.364...29P</bibcode>
			<title>A link between the semimajor axis of extrasolar gas giant planets and stellar metallicity</title>
			<authors>Pinotti, R.; Arany-Prado, L.; Lyra, W.; Porto de Mello, G. F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 364, Issue 1, pp. 29-36.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.364...29P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...443..609S</bibcode>
			<title>On the ages of exoplanet host stars</title>
			<authors>Saffe, C.; G&#243;mez, M.; Chavero, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 443, Issue 2, November IV 2005, pp.609-626</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...443..609S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...441..533C</bibcode>
			<title>Sulphur abundance in Galactic stars</title>
			<authors>Caffau, E.; Bonifacio, P.; Faraggiana, R.; Fran&#231;ois, P.; Gratton, R. G.; Barbieri, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 441, Issue 2, October II 2005, pp.533-548</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...441..533C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJS..159..141V</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic Properties of Cool Stars (SPOCS). I. 1040 F, G, and K Dwarfs from Keck, Lick, and AAT Planet Search Programs</title>
			<authors>Valenti, Jeff A.; Fischer, Debra A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 159, Issue 1, pp. 141-166.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJS..159..141V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...438..317D</bibcode>
			<title>Outbursts on normal stars. FH Leo misclassified as a novalike variable</title>
			<authors>dall, T. H.; Schmidtobreick, L.; Santos, N. C.; Israelian, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 438, Issue 1, July IV 2005, pp.317-324</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...438..317D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...438..251B</bibcode>
			<title>Abundances of Na, Mg and Al in stars with giant planets</title>
			<authors>Beir&#227;o, P.; Santos, N. C.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 438, Issue 1, July IV 2005, pp.251-256</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...438..251B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...437.1127S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic metallicities for planet-host stars: Extending the samples</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Bento, J. P.; Almeida, P. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Ecuvillon, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 437, Issue 3, July III 2005, pp.1127-1133</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...437.1127S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...626..446R</bibcode>
			<title>The Effective Temperature Scale of FGK Stars. I. Determination of Temperatures and Angular Diameters with the Infrared Flux Method</title>
			<authors>Ram&#237;rez, Iv&#225;n; Mel&#233;ndez, Jorge</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 626, Issue 1, pp. 446-464.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...626..446R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622.1102F</bibcode>
			<title>The Planet-Metallicity Correlation</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Valenti, Jeff</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 2, pp. 1102-1117.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622.1102F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622.1091J</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for Habitable ``Earths'' in Known Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Underwood, David R.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 2, pp. 1091-1101.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622.1091J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...431.1129H</bibcode>
			<title>Statistical properties of exoplanets.  IV. The period-eccentricity relations of exoplanets and of binary stars</title>
			<authors>Halbwachs, J. L.; Mayor, M.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 431, Issue 3, March I 2005, pp.1129-1137</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...431.1129H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.354.1194S</bibcode>
			<title>On the possible correlation between the orbital periods of extrasolar planets and the metallicity of the host stars</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 354, Issue 4, pp. 1194-1200.</journal>
			<date>11/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.354.1194S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.354.1165C</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of extrasolar planets in radial velocity surveys</title>
			<authors>Cumming, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 354, Issue 4, pp. 1165-1176.</journal>
			<date>11/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.354.1165C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...426..619E</bibcode>
			<title>C, S, Zn and Cu abundances in planet-harbouring stars</title>
			<authors>Ecuvillon, A.; Israelian, G.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Villar, V.; Bihain, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.426, p.619-630 (2004)</journal>
			<date>11/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...426..619E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...612..511L</bibcode>
			<title>The Radiometric Bode's Law and Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Lazio, T. Joseph, W.; Farrell, W. M.; Dietrick, Jill; Greenlees, Elizabeth; Hogan, Emily; Jones, Christopher; Hennig, L. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 612, Issue 1, pp. 511-518.</journal>
			<date>9/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...612..511L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004RMxAC..21..207U</bibcode>
			<title>Planets in multiple-star systems:properties and detections</title>
			<authors>Udry, S.; Eggenberger, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Environment and Evolution of Double and Multiple Stars, Proceedings of IAU Colloquium 191, held 3-7 February, 2002 in Merida, Yucatan, Mexico. Edited by Christine Allen &amp; Colin Scarfe. Revista Mexicana de Astronom&#237;a y Astrof&#237;sica (Serie de Conferencias) Vol. 21, pp. 207-214 (2004) (http://www.astroscu.unam.mx/~rmaa/)</journal>
			<date>8/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004RMxAC..21..207U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJS..152..261W</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric Ca II Emission in Nearby F, G, K, and M Stars</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, S. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 152, Issue 2, pp. 261-295.</journal>
			<date>6/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJS..152..261W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...418..989N</bibcode>
			<title>The Geneva-Copenhagen survey of the Solar neighbourhood. Ages, metallicities, and kinematic properties of &amp;tilde14 000 F and G dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Nordstr&#246;m, B.; Mayor, M.; Andersen, J.; Holmberg, J.; Pont, F.; J&#248; rgensen, B. R.; Olsen, E. H.; Udry, S.; Mowlavi, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.418, p.989-1019 (2004)</journal>
			<date>5/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...418..989N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...418..703E</bibcode>
			<title>Nitrogen abundances in planet-harbouring stars</title>
			<authors>Ecuvillon, A.; Israelian, G.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Garc&#237;a L&#243;pez, R. J.; Randich, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.418, p.703-715 (2004)</journal>
			<date>5/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...418..703E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004Icar..168..223A</bibcode>
			<title>Obliquity variations of terrestrial planets in habitable zones</title>
			<authors>Atobe, Keiko; Ida, Shigeru; Ito, Takashi</authors>
			<journal>Icarus, Volume 168, Issue 2, p. 223-236.</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004Icar..168..223A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...417..353E</bibcode>
			<title>Statistical properties of exoplanets. III. Planet properties and stellar multiplicity</title>
			<authors>Eggenberger, A.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.417, p.353-360 (2004)</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...417..353E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...415.1153S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic [Fe/H] for 98 extra-solar planet-host stars.  Exploring the probability of planet formation</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.415, p.1153-1166 (2004)</journal>
			<date>3/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...415.1153S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...414..601I</bibcode>
			<title>Lithium in stars with exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Israelian, G.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Rebolo, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.414, p.601-611 (2004)</journal>
			<date>2/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...414..601I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...411L.501R</bibcode>
			<title>Effective temperatures and radii of planet-hosting stars   from IR photometry</title>
			<authors>Ribas, I.; Solano, E.; Masana, E.; Gim&#233;nez, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.411, p.L501-L504 (2003)</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...411L.501R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003AJ....126.2015H</bibcode>
			<title>Abundance Analysis of Planetary Host Stars. I. Differential Iron Abundances</title>
			<authors>Heiter, U.; Luck, R. E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 126, Issue 4, pp. 2015-2036.</journal>
			<date>10/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003AJ....126.2015H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...404..715B</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical abundances of planet-host stars.  Results for alpha and Fe-group elements</title>
			<authors>Bodaghee, A.; Santos, N. C.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.404, p.715-727 (2003)</journal>
			<date>6/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...404..715B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...589..605W</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Migration and Binary Companions: The Case of HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Wu, Y.; Murray, N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 589, Issue 1, pp. 605-614.</journal>
			<date>5/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...589..605W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003AJ....125.2692L</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Giant Planets in Terrestrial Planet Formation</title>
			<authors>Levison, Harold F.; Agnor, Craig</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 125, Issue 5, pp. 2692-2713.</journal>
			<date>5/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003AJ....125.2692L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...586.1394F</bibcode>
			<title>A Planetary Companion to HD 40979 and Additional Planets Orbiting HD 12661 and HD 38529</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Henry, Gregory W.; Pourbaix, Dimitri; Walp, Bernard; Misch, Anthony A.; Wright, Jason T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 586, Issue 2, pp. 1394-1408.</journal>
			<date>4/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...586.1394F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003RvMP...75..101G</bibcode>
			<title>Colloquium: Stars, planets, and metals</title>
			<authors>Gonzalez, Guillermo</authors>
			<journal>Reviews of Modern Physics, vol. 75, Issue 1, pp. 101-120</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003RvMP...75..101G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...582..449J</bibcode>
			<title>On the Fate of Close-in Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jiang, Ing-Guey; Ip, Wing-Huen; Yeh, Li-Chin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 582, Issue 1, pp. 449-454.</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...582..449J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...398..363S</bibcode>
			<title>Statistical properties of exoplanets.  II. Metallicity, orbital parameters, and space velocities</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Rebolo, R.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.398, p.363-376 (2003)</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...398..363S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003BASI...31...37V</bibcode>
			<title>Search for periodicities in distribution of orbits of planets.</title>
			<authors>Vahia, M. N.; Mahajani, P.; Rao, A. R.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the Astronomical Society of India, 31, 37-47 (2003)</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003BASI...31...37V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ASPC..294..213W</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Circularization and Kozai Migration</title>
			<authors>Wu, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Scientific Frontiers in Research on Extrasolar Planets, ASP Conference Series, Vol 294, Edited by Drake Deming and Sara Seager. (San Francisco: ASP) ISBN: 1-58381-141-9, 2003, pp. 213-216</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ASPC..294..213W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ASPC..294...43E</bibcode>
			<title>Planets in Binaries</title>
			<authors>Eggenberger, A.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.</authors>
			<journal>Scientific Frontiers in Research on Extrasolar Planets, ASP Conference Series, Vol 294, Edited by Drake Deming and Sara Seager. (San Francisco: ASP) ISBN: 1-58381-141-9, 2003, pp. 43-46</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ASPC..294...43E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ASPC..294....1M</bibcode>
			<title>Properties of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.</authors>
			<journal>Scientific Frontiers in Research on Extrasolar Planets, ASP Conference Series, Vol 294, Edited by Drake Deming and Sara Seager. (San Francisco: ASP) ISBN: 1-58381-141-9, 2003, pp. 1-16</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ASPC..294....1M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002Msngr.110...32S</bibcode>
			<title>Extra-solar planets</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger (ISSN 0722-6691), No. 110, p. 32 - 38 (December 2002)</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002Msngr.110...32S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002KFNT...18..419V</bibcode>
			<title>Brightness variations of an extrasolar giant planet rotating around its central star</title>
			<authors>Vid'Machenko, A. P.; Krushevskaya, V. N.; Kuznetsova, Yu. G.</authors>
			<journal>Kinematika i Fizika Nebesnykh Tel, vol. 18, no. 5, p. 419-432.</journal>
			<date>10/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002KFNT...18..419V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...578..565B</bibcode>
			<title>On the Double-Planet System around HD 83443</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Vogt, Steven S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, Hugh R. A.; McCarthy, Chris; Penny, Alan J.; Apps, Kevin; Carter, Brad D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 578, Issue 1, pp. 565-572.</journal>
			<date>10/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...578..565B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002S&amp;T...104b..32K</bibcode>
			<title>The Puzzles of Planethood</title>
			<authors>Kaisler, Denise</authors>
			<journal>Sky and Telescope, Vol. 104, Issue 2, p. 32 (2002)</journal>
			<date>8/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002S%26T...104b..32K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...573..829M</bibcode>
			<title>Calculating the Tidal, Spin, and Dynamical Evolution of Extrasolar Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Mardling, Rosemary A.; Lin, D. N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 573, Issue 2, pp. 829-844.</journal>
			<date>7/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...573..829M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...572L..79L</bibcode>
			<title>A Distant Stellar Companion in the upsilo Andromedae System</title>
			<authors>Lowrance, Patrick J.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Beichman, Charles A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 572, Issue 1, pp. L79-L81.</journal>
			<date>6/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...572L..79L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002PASP..114..306R</bibcode>
			<title>On the Nature of Stars with Planets</title>
			<authors>Reid, I. Neill</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 114, Issue 793, pp. 306-329.</journal>
			<date>3/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002PASP..114..306R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...568..363Z</bibcode>
			<title>A Planet Candidate in the Stellar Triple System HD 178911</title>
			<authors>Zucker, S.; Naef, D.; Latham, D. W.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Beuzit, J. L.; Drukier, G.; Perrier-Bellet, C.; Queloz, D.; Sivan, J. P.; Torres, G.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 568, Issue 1, pp. 363-368.</journal>
			<date>3/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...568..363Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...384..879B</bibcode>
			<title>Galactic orbits of stars with planets</title>
			<authors>Barbieri, M.; Gratton, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.384, p.879-883 (2002)</journal>
			<date>3/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...384..879B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...562.1038Z</bibcode>
			<title>Derivation of the Mass Distribution of Extrasolar Planets with MAXLIMA, a Maximum Likelihood Algorithm</title>
			<authors>Zucker, Shay; Mazeh, Tsevi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 562, Issue 2, pp. 1038-1044.</journal>
			<date>12/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...562.1038Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001Sci...293.1127K</bibcode>
			<title>Runaway Growth of Planetary Embryos Facilitated by Massive Bodies in a Protoplanetary Disk</title>
			<authors>Kortenkamp, Stephen J.; Wetherill, George W.; Inaba, Satoshi</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 293, Issue 5532, pp. 1127-1129 (2001).</journal>
			<date>8/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001Sci...293.1127K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001AcASn..42..225W</bibcode>
			<title>The discovering of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Wu, G. J.; Chen, D. H.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica Sinica, Vol.42, no.3,  p.225-239</journal>
			<date>8/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001AcASn..42..225W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...375L..27N</bibcode>
			<title>HD 80606 b, a planet on an extremely elongated orbit</title>
			<authors>Naef, D.; Latham, D. W.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Beuzit, J. L.; Drukier, G. A.; Perrier-Bellet, C.; Queloz, D.; Sivan, J. P.; Torres, G.; Udry, S.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.375, p.L27-L30 (2001)</journal>
			<date>8/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...375L..27N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...375..205N</bibcode>
			<title>The CORALIE survey for southern extrasolar planets. V. 3 new extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Naef, D.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Udry, S.; Burnet, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.375, p.205-218 (2001)</journal>
			<date>8/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...375..205N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...373.1019S</bibcode>
			<title>The metal-rich nature of stars with planets</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.373, p.1019-1031 (2001)</journal>
			<date>7/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...373.1019S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001LAstr.115..314S</bibcode>
			<title>La vie en dehors du systeme solaire les 50 prochaines annees.</title>
			<authors>Schneider, J.</authors>
			<journal>L'astronomie, 115, 314-315 (2001)</journal>
			<date>0/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001LAstr.115..314S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000ApJ...545.1064L</bibcode>
			<title>Mining the Metal-rich Stars for Planets</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 545, Issue 2, pp. 1064-1073.</journal>
			<date>12/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000ApJ...545.1064L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
