<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewA...17..356I</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital effects of non-isotropic mass depletion of the atmospheres of evaporating hot Jupiters in extrasolar systems</title>
			<authors>Iorio, Lorenzo</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 17, Issue 3, p. 356-361.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012NewA...17..356I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...78R</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Drag in the Energetics of Strongly Forced Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Rauscher, Emily; Menou, Kristen</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 78 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...78R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63L..67N</bibcode>
			<title>XO-2b: a Prograde Planet with Negligible Eccentricity and an Additional Radial Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sato, Bun'ei; Harakawa, Hiroki; Fukui, Akihiko; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.6, pp.L67-L71</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63L..67N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..203J</bibcode>
			<title>A Survey of Alkali Line Absorption in Exoplanetary Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Jensen, Adam G.; Redfield, Seth; Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Koesterke, Lars; Barman, Travis S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 203 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..203J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..162P</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for the Transit of HD 168443b: Improved Orbital Parameters and Photometry</title>
			<authors>Pilyavsky, Genady; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Kane, Stephen R.; Howard, Andrew W.; Ciardi, David R.; de Pree, Chris; Dragomir, Diana; Fischer, Debra; Henry, Gregory W.; Jensen, Eric L. N.; Laughlin, Gregory; Marlowe, Hannah; Rabus, Markus; von Braun, Kaspar; Wright, Jason T.; Wang, Xuesong X.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 162 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..162P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742..116B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-20b-HAT-P-23b: Four Massive Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>