<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720L.113R</bibcode>
			<title>Metal-rich M-Dwarf Planet Hosts: Metallicities with K-band Spectra</title>
			<authors>Rojas-Ayala, B&#225;rbara; Covey, Kevin R.; Muirhead, Philip S.; Lloyd, James P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 720, Issue 1, pp. L113-L118 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720L.113R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A.105S</bibcode>
			<title>A physically-motivated photometric calibration of M dwarf metallicity</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, K. C.; Laughlin, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A105</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A.105S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.1949K</bibcode>
			<title>UBV(RI)C JHK observations of Hipparcos-selected nearby stars</title>
			<authors>Koen, C.; Kilkenny, D.; van Wyk, F.; Marang, F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 4, pp. 1949-1968.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.1949K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122..156A</bibcode>
			<title>M2K: I. A Jupiter-Mass Planet Orbiting the M3V Star HIP 79431</title>
			<authors>Apps, Kevin; Clubb, Kelsey I.; Fischer, Debra A.; Gaidos, Eric; Howard, Andrew; Johnson, John A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Giguere, Matthew J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Rodriguez, Victor; Chubak, Carly; Lepine, Sebastien</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 888, pp.156-161</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122..156A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122..149J</bibcode>
			<title>The California Planet Survey. II. A Saturn-Mass Planet Orbiting the M Dwarf Gl 649</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Bowler, Brendan P.; Henry, Gregory W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Apps, Kevin; Isaacson, Howard; Wright, Jason T.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, Issue 888, pp. 149-155.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122..149J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....132..161G</bibcode>
			<title>Contributions to the Nearby Stars (NStars) Project: Spectroscopy of Stars Earlier than M0 within 40 pc-The Southern Sample</title>
			<authors>Gray, R. O.; Corbally, C. J.; Garrison, R. F.; McFadden, M. T.; Bubar, E. J.; McGahee, C. E.; O'Donoghue, A. A.; Knox, E. R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 132, Issue 1, pp. 161-170.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....132..161G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...582.1011S</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Astrometry and Photometry for the Luyten Catalog. II. Faint Stars and the Revised Catalog</title>
			<authors>Salim, Samir; Gould, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 582, Issue 2, pp. 1011-1031.</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...582.1011S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
