<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...89J</bibcode>
			<title>High-contrast Imaging Search for Planets and Brown Dwarfs around the Most Massive Stars in the Solar Neighborhood</title>
			<authors>Janson, Markus; Bonavita, Mariangela; Klahr, Hubert; Lafreni&#232;re, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; Zinnecker, Hans</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. 89 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...89J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733..126C</bibcode>
			<title>Estimates of the Planet Yield from Ground-based High-contrast Imaging Observations as a Function of Stellar Mass</title>
			<authors>Crepp, Justin R.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. 126 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733..126C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...65B</bibcode>
			<title>Clouds and Chemistry in the Atmosphere of Extrasolar Planet HR8799b</title>
			<authors>Barman, Travis S.; Macintosh, Bruce; Konopacky, Quinn M.; Marois, Christian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 65 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..29R</bibcode>
			<title>The Ultra Cool Brown Dwarf Companion of WD 0806-661B: Age, Mass, and Formation Mechanism</title>
			<authors>Rodriguez, David R.; Zuckerman, B.; Melis, Carl; Song, Inseok</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..29R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729..128C</bibcode>
			<title>A Combined Subaru/VLT/MMT 1-5 mum Study of Planets Orbiting HR 8799: Implications for Atmospheric Properties, Masses, and Formation</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Burrows, Adam; Itoh, Yoichi; Matsumura, Soko; Fukagawa, Misato; Apai, Daniel; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Hinz, Philip M.; Rodigas, T. J.; Kasper, Markus; Pyo, T.-S.; Ogino, Satoshi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 128 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729..128C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.468.1080M</bibcode>
			<title>Images of a fourth planet orbiting HR 8799</title>
			<authors>Marois, Christian; Zuckerman, B.; Konopacky, Quinn M.; Macintosh, Bruce; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 468, Issue 7327, pp. 1080-1083 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Natur.468.1080M</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...739L..41G</bibcode>
			<title>M-band Imaging of the HR&#160;8799 Planetary System Using an Innovative LOCI-based Background Subtraction Technique</title>
			<authors>Galicher, Rapha&#235;l; Marois, Christian; Macintosh, Bruce; Barman, Travis; Konopacky, Quinn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 739, Issue 2, article id. L41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...739L..41G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..131D</bibcode>
			<title>Transitional Disks as Signposts of Young, Multiplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Salyk, Colette</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 131 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..131D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738...32L</bibcode>
			<title>Thermochemical and Photochemical Kinetics in Cooler Hydrogen-dominated Extrasolar Planets: A Methane-poor GJ436b?</title>
			<authors>Line, Michael R.; Vasisht, Gautam; Chen, Pin; Angerhausen, D.; Yung, Yuk L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 32 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738...32L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737...34M</bibcode>
			<title>Model Atmospheres for Massive Gas Giants with Thick Clouds: Application to the HR 8799 Planets and Predictions for Future Detections</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, Nikku; Burrows, Adam; Currie, Thayne</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 737, Issue 1, article id. 34 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737...34M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..33C</bibcode>
			<title>A 5 mum Image of beta Pictoris b at a Sub-Jupiter Projected Separation: Evidence for a Misalignment Between the Planet and the Inner, Warped Disk</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Thalmann, Christian; Matsumura, Soko; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Burrows, Adam; Kuchner, Marc</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L33 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..33C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..32Q</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for Gas Giant Planets on Solar System Scales: VLT NACO/APP Observations of the Debris Disk Host Stars HD172555 and HD115892</title>
			<authors>Quanz, Sascha P.; Kenworthy, Matthew A.; Meyer, Michael R.; Girard, Julien H. V.; Kasper, Markus</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L32 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..32Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...89J</bibcode>
			<title>High-contrast Imaging Search for Planets and Brown Dwarfs around the Most Massive Stars in the Solar Neighborhood</title>
			<authors>Janson, Markus; Bonavita, Mariangela; Klahr, Hubert; Lafreni&#232;re, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; Zinnecker, Hans</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. 89 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...89J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...39H</bibcode>
			<title>A Volume-limited Photometric Survey of 114 gamma Doradus Candidates</title>
			<authors>Henry, Gregory W.; Fekel, Francis C.; Henry, Stephen M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 2, article id. 39 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142...39H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..72L</bibcode>
			<title>Sparse aperture masking at the VLT. I. Faint companion detection limits for the two debris disk stars HD 92945 and HD 141569</title>
			<authors>Lacour, S.; Tuthill, P.; Amico, P.; Ireland, M.; Ehrenreich, D.; Huelamo, N.; Lagrange, A.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A72</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..72L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A...6S</bibcode>
			<title>Estimation of the XUV radiation onto close planets and their evaporation</title>
			<authors>Sanz-Forcada, J.; Micela, G.; Ribas, I.; Pollock, A. M. T.; Eiroa, C.; Velasco, A.; Solano, E.; Garc&#237;a-&#193;lvarez, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A6</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A...6S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735L..39B</bibcode>
			<title>The Young Planet-mass Object 2M1207b: A Cool, Cloudy, and Methane-poor Atmosphere</title>
			<authors>Barman, Travis S.; Macintosh, Bruce; Konopacky, Quinn M.; Marois, Christian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 735, Issue 2, article id. L39 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735L..39B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...30B</bibcode>
			<title>The Heavy-element Composition of Disk Instability Planets Can Range from Sub- to Super-nebular</title>
			<authors>Boley, Aaron C.; Helled, Ravit; Payne, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 1, article id. 30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735...30B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AN....332..547N</bibcode>
			<title>The Young Exoplanet Transit Initiative (YETI)</title>
			<authors>Neuh&#228;user, R.; Errmann, R.; Berndt, A.; Maciejewski, G.; Takahashi, H.; Chen, W. P.; Dimitrov, D. P.; Pribulla, T.; Nikogossian, E. H.; Jensen, E. L. N.; Marschall, L.; Wu, Z.-Y.; Kellerer, A.; Walter, F. M.; Brice&#241;o, C.; Chini, R.; Fernandez, M.; Raetz, St.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Quinn, S. N.; Niedzielski, A.; Bukowiecki, L.; Nowak, G.; Tomov, T.; Tachihara, K.; Hu, S. C.-L.; Hung, L. W.; Kjurkchieva, D. P.; Radeva, V. S.; Mihov, B. M.; Slavcheva-Mihova, L.; Bozhinova, I. N.; Budaj, J.; Vanko, M.; Kundra, E.; Hamb&#225;lek, L.; Krushevska, V.; Movsessian, T.; Harutyunyan, H.; Downes, J. J.; Hernandez, J.; Hoffmeister, V. H.; Cohen, D. H.; Abel, I.; Ahmad, R.; Chapman, S.; Eckert, S.; Goodman, J.; Guerard, A.; Kim, H. M.; Koontharana, A.; Sokol, J.; Trinh, J.; Wang, Y.; Zhou, X.; Redmer, R.; Kramm, U.; Nettelmann, N.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, J.; Moualla, M.; Ginski, C.; Marka, C.; Adam, C.; Seeliger, M.; Baar, S.; Roell, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Trepl, L.; Eisenbei&#223;, T.; Fiedler, S.; Tetzlaff, N.; Schmidt, E.; Hohle, M. M.; Kitze, M.; Chakrova, N.; Gr&#228;fe, C.; Schreyer, K.; Hambaryan, V. V.; Broeg, C. H.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Pandey, A. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.332, Issue 6, p.547</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AN....332..547N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531L..17P</bibcode>
			<title>Spatially resolved submillimeter imaging of the HR 8799 debris disk</title>
			<authors>Patience, J.; Bulger, J.; King, R. R.; Ayliffe, B.; Bate, M. R.; Song, I.; Pinte, C.; Koda, J.; Dowell, C. D.; Kov&#225;cs, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.L17</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531L..17P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A.145B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical seismic properties of pre-main sequence gamma Doradus pulsators</title>
			<authors>Bouabid, M.-P.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Miglio, A.; Dupret, M.-A.; Grigahc&#232;ne, A.; Noels, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A145</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A.145B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733..126C</bibcode>
			<title>Estimates of the Planet Yield from Ground-based High-contrast Imaging Observations as a Function of Stellar Mass</title>
			<authors>Crepp, Justin R.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. 126 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733..126C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...65B</bibcode>
			<title>Clouds and Chemistry in the Atmosphere of Extrasolar Planet HR8799b</title>
			<authors>Barman, Travis S.; Macintosh, Bruce; Konopacky, Quinn M.; Marois, Christian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 65 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..29R</bibcode>
			<title>The Ultra Cool Brown Dwarf Companion of WD 0806-661B: Age, Mass, and Formation Mechanism</title>
			<authors>Rodriguez, David R.; Zuckerman, B.; Melis, Carl; Song, Inseok</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..29R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732..107S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence Against an Edge-on Disk Around the Extrasolar Planet, 2MASS 1207 b and a New Thick-cloud Explanation for Its Underluminosity</title>
			<authors>Skemer, Andrew J.; Close, Laird M.; Szucs, L&#225;szl&#243;; Apai, D&#225;niel; Pascucci, Ilaria; Biller, Beth A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. 107 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732..107S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...61Z</bibcode>
			<title>The Tucana/Horologium, Columba, AB Doradus, and Argus Associations: New Members and Dusty Debris Disks</title>
			<authors>Zuckerman, B.; Rhee, Joseph H.; Song, Inseok; Bessell, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. 61 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...61Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...42A</bibcode>
			<title>Resolved Images of Large Cavities in Protoplanetary Transition Disks</title>
			<authors>Andrews, Sean M.; Wilner, David J.; Espaillat, Catherine; Hughes, A. M.; Dullemond, C. P.; McClure, M. K.; Qi, Chunhua; Brown, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 42 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...42A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...10R</bibcode>
			<title>Direct Imaging Constraints on the Putative Exoplanet 14 Her C</title>
			<authors>Rodigas, Timothy J.; Males, Jared R.; Hinz, Philip M.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Knox, Russell P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...10R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.131M</bibcode>
			<title>Simulation of planet detection with the SPHERE integral field spectrograph</title>
			<authors>Mesa, D.; Gratton, R.; Berton, A.; Antichi, J.; Verinaud, C.; Boccaletti, A.; Kasper, M.; Claudi, R. U.; Desidera, S.; Giro, E.; Beuzit, J.-L.; Dohlen, K.; Feldt, M.; Mouillet, D.; Chauvin, G.; Vigan, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A131</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.131M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.412.2353L</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of '3D' multiplanet systems by dynamical disruption of multiple-resonance configurations</title>
			<authors>Libert, A.-S.; Tsiganis, K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 412, Issue 4, pp. 2353-2360.</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.412.2353L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.412.2137K</bibcode>
			<title>Collisional evolution of irregular satellite swarms: detectable dust around Solar system and extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Kennedy, G. M.; Wyatt, M. C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 412, Issue 4, pp. 2137-2153.</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.412.2137K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...731..101B</bibcode>
			<title>A New Hybrid N-body-coagulation Code for the Formation of Gas Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Bromley, Benjamin C.; Kenyon, Scott J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 731, Issue 2, article id. 101 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...731..101B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...731...74B</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of Giant Planets by Disk Instability on Wide Orbits Around Protostars with Varied Masses</title>
			<authors>Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 731, Issue 1, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...731...74B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>Common Warm Dust Temperatures Around Main-sequence Stars</title>
			<authors>Morales, Farisa Y.; Rieke, G. H.; Werner, M. W.; Bryden, G.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Su, K. Y. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730L..21H</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Constraints on Companions Inside of 10 AU in the HR 8799 Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Hinkley, Sasha; Carpenter, John M.; Ireland, Michael J.; Kraus, Adam L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. L21 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730L..21H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...93W</bibcode>
			<title>The California Planet Survey. III. A Possible 2:1 Resonance in the Exoplanetary Triple System HD 37124</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Isaacson, H.; Fischer, D. A.; Spronck, J.; Anderson, J.; Valenti, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. 93 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...93W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..119K</bibcode>
			<title>The Widest-separation Substellar Companion Candidate to a Binary T Tauri Star</title>
			<authors>Kuzuhara, M.; Tamura, M.; Ishii, M.; Kudo, T.; Nishiyama, S.; Kandori, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 4, article id. 119 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..119K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A.134B</bibcode>
			<title>VLT/NACO astrometry of the HR 8799 planetary system. L'-band observations of the three outer planets</title>
			<authors>Bergfors, C.; Brandner, W.; Janson, M.; K&#246;hler, R.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A134</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A.134B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..193....4M</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and Evolution of Debris Disks Around F-type Stars. I. Observations, Database, and Basic Evolutionary Aspects</title>
			<authors>Mo&#243;r, A.; Pascucci, I.; K&#243;sp&#225;l, &#193;.; &#193;brah&#225;m, P.; Csengeri, T.; Kiss, L. L.; Apai, D.; Grady, C.; Henning, Th.; Kiss, Cs.; Bayliss, D.; Juh&#225;sz, A.; Kov&#225;cs, J.; Szalai, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 193, Issue 1, article id. 4 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..193....4M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...42L</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of an ~23 M Jup Brown Dwarf Orbiting ~700 AU from the Massive Star HIP 78530 in Upper Scorpius</title>
			<authors>Lafreni&#232;re, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; Janson, Markus; Helling, Christiane; Witte, Soeren; Hauschildt, Peter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. 42 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...42L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729..139W</bibcode>
			<title>The Gemini NICI Planet-finding Campaign: Discovery of a Substellar L Dwarf Companion to the Nearby Young M Dwarf CD-35 2722</title>
			<authors>Wahhaj, Zahed; Liu, Michael C.; Biller, Beth A.; Clarke, Fraser; Nielsen, Eric L.; Close, Laird M.; Hayward, Thomas L.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Cushing, Michael; Dupuy, Trent; Tecza, Matthias; Thatte, Niranjan; Chun, Mark; Ftaclas, Christ; Hartung, Markus; Reid, I. Neill; Shkolnik, Evgenya L.; Alencar, Silvia H. P.; Artymowicz, Pawel; Boss, Alan; de Gouveia Dal Pino, Elisabethe; Gregorio-Hetem, Jane; Ida, Shigeru; Kuchner, Marc; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Toomey, Douglas W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 139 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729..139W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729..132C</bibcode>
			<title>Speckle Suppression with the Project 1640 Integral Field Spectrograph</title>
			<authors>Crepp, Justin R.; Pueyo, Laurent; Brenner, Douglas; Oppenheimer, Ben R.; Zimmerman, Neil; Hinkley, Sasha; Parry, Ian; King, David; Vasisht, Gautam; Beichman, Charles; Hillenbrand, Lynne; Dekany, Richard; Shao, Mike; Burruss, Rick; Roberts, Lewis C.; Bouchez, Antonin; Roberts, Jenny; Soummer, R&#233;mi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 132 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729..132C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729..128C</bibcode>
			<title>A Combined Subaru/VLT/MMT 1-5 mum Study of Planets Orbiting HR 8799: Implications for Atmospheric Properties, Masses, and Formation</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Burrows, Adam; Itoh, Yoichi; Matsumura, Soko; Fukagawa, Misato; Apai, Daniel; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Hinz, Philip M.; Rodigas, T. J.; Kasper, Markus; Pyo, T.-S.; Ogino, Satoshi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 128 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729..128C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...50M</bibcode>
			<title>A New Concept for Direct Imaging and Spectral Characterization of Exoplanets in Multi-planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Matsuo, Taro; Traub, Wesley A.; Hattori, Makoto; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 50 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...50M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411L...1M</bibcode>
			<title>Non-convergence of the critical cooling time-scale for fragmentation of self-gravitating discs</title>
			<authors>Meru, Farzana; Bate, Matthew R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411L...1M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411..859M</bibcode>
			<title>The effects of fly-bys on planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Malmberg, Daniel; Davies, Melvyn B.; Heggie, Douglas C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 2, pp. 859-877.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411..859M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411....2D</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary mass function and planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Dominik, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. 2-8.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411....2D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728L..20W</bibcode>
			<title>Determination of the Inclination of the Multi-planet Hosting Star HR 8799 Using Asteroseismology</title>
			<authors>Wright, D. J.; Chen&#233;, A.-N.; De Cat, P.; Marois, C.; Mathias, P.; Macintosh, B.; Isaacs, J.; Lehmann, H.; Hartmann, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 728, Issue 1, article id. L20 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728L..20W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728...85J</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Multi-band Photometry of the Substellar Companion GJ 758 B</title>
			<authors>Janson, M.; Carson, J.; Thalmann, C.; McElwain, M. W.; Goto, M.; Crepp, J.; Wisniewski, J.; Abe, L.; Brandner, W.; Burrows, A.; Egner, S.; Feldt, M.; Grady, C. A.; Golota, T.; Guyon, O.; Hashimoto, J.; Hayano, Y.; Hayashi, M.; Hayashi, S.; Henning, T.; Hodapp, K. W.; Ishii, M.; Iye, M.; Kandori, R.; Knapp, G. R.; Kudo, T.; Kusakabe, N.; Kuzuhara, M.; Matsuo, T.; Mayama, S.; Miyama, S.; Morino, J.-I.; Moro-Mart&#237;n, A.; Nishimura, T.; Pyo, T.-S.; Serabyn, E.; Suto, H.; Suzuki, R.; Takami, M.; Takato, N.; Terada, H.; Tofflemire, B.; Tomono, D.; Turner, E. L.; Watanabe, M.; Yamada, T.; Takami, H.; Usuda, T.; Tamura, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 85 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728...85J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727L..42W</bibcode>
			<title>Millimeter Imaging of the beta Pictoris Debris Disk: Evidence for a Planetesimal Belt</title>
			<authors>Wilner, David J.; Andrews, Sean M.; Hughes, A. Meredith</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. L42 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727L..42W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASP..123...14H</bibcode>
			<title>An Investigation of the Loss of Planet-Forming Potential in Intermediate-Sized Young Embedded Star Clusters</title>
			<authors>Holden, Lisa; Landis, Edward; Spitzig, Jeremy; Adams, Fred C.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 123, issue 899, pp.14-25</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASP..123...14H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011NewA...16...27K</bibcode>
			<title>The outcome of the protoplanetary disk of very massive stars</title>
			<authors>Kashi, Amit; Soker, Noam</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 16, Issue 1, p. 27-32.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011NewA...16...27K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...57S</bibcode>
			<title>The Deuterium-burning Mass Limit for Brown Dwarfs and Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 57 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...57S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..113I</bibcode>
			<title>Two Wide Planetary-mass Companions to Solar-type Stars in Upper Scorpius</title>
			<authors>Ireland, M. J.; Kraus, A.; Martinache, F.; Law, N.; Hillenbrand, L. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 113 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..113I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.468.1080M</bibcode>
			<title>Images of a fourth planet orbiting HR 8799</title>
			<authors>Marois, Christian; Zuckerman, B.; Konopacky, Quinn M.; Macintosh, Bruce; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 468, Issue 7327, pp. 1080-1083 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Natur.468.1080M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.468.1048C</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planets: A giant surprise</title>
			<authors>Close, Laird</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 468, Issue 7327, pp. 1048-1049 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Natur.468.1048C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.409..975P</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of radial velocity variations in multiple planetary systems</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 409, Issue 3, pp. 975-984.</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.409..975P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725L.145B</bibcode>
			<title>Giant Planet Formation by Disk Instability in Low Mass Disks?</title>
			<authors>Boss, Alan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725L.145B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725..721G</bibcode>
			<title>Metallicities of Planet-hosting Stars: A Sample of Giants and Subgiants</title>
			<authors>Ghezzi, L.; Cunha, K.; Schuler, S. C.; Smith, V. V.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 1, pp. 721-733 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725..721G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724.1238S</bibcode>
			<title>The Structure of the beta Leonis Debris Disk</title>
			<authors>Stock, Nathan D.; Su, Kate Y. L.; Liu, Wilson; Hinz, Phil M.; Rieke, George H.; Marengo, Massimo; Stapelfeldt, Karl R.; Hines, Dean C.; Trilling, David E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, pp. 1238-1255 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724.1238S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724.1006M</bibcode>
			<title>Formation Process of the Circumstellar Disk: Long-term Simulations in the Main Accretion Phase of Star Formation</title>
			<authors>Machida, Masahiro N.; Inutsuka, Shu-ichiro; Matsumoto, Tomoaki</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, pp. 1006-1020 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724.1006M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...524L...1B</bibcode>
			<title>Dissecting the Moth: discovery of an off-centered ring in the HD 61005 debris disk with high-resolution imaging</title>
			<authors>Buenzli, E.; Thalmann, C.; Vigan, A.; Boccaletti, A.; Chauvin, G.; Augereau, J. C.; Meyer, M. R.; M&#233;nard, F.; Desidera, S.; Messina, S.; Henning, T.; Carson, J.; Montagnier, G.; Beuzit, J. L.; Bonavita, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Lagrange, A. M.; Mesa, D.; Mouillet, D.; Quanz, S. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 524, id.L1</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...524L...1B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..618B</bibcode>
			<title>On the Possibility of Enrichment and Differentiation in Gas Giants During Birth by Disk Instability</title>
			<authors>Boley, Aaron C.; Durisen, Richard H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. 618-639 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..618B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724..189C</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Albedo Spectra and Colors as a Function of Planet Phase, Separation, and Metallicity</title>
			<authors>Cahoy, Kerri L.; Marley, Mark S.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. 189-214 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724..189C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724....1S</bibcode>
			<title>The Search for Planetary Mass Companions to Field Brown Dwarfs with HST/NICMOS</title>
			<authors>Stumpf, M. B.; Brandner, W.; Joergens, V.; Henning, Th.; Bouy, H.; K&#246; hler, R.; Kasper, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 1, pp. 1-11 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724....1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723L.248K</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a Molecular Disk Orbiting the Nearby, "old," Classical T Tauri Star MP Muscae</title>
			<authors>Kastner, Joel H.; Hily-Blant, Pierry; Sacco, G. G.; Forveille, Thierry; Zuckerman, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 723, Issue 2, pp. L248-L251 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723L.248K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..850B</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Spectroscopy of the Extrasolar Planet HR 8799 b</title>
			<authors>Bowler, Brendan P.; Liu, Michael C.; Dupuy, Trent J.; Cushing, Michael C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 850-868 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..850B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..73E</bibcode>
			<title>Deep infrared imaging of close companions to austral A- and F-type stars</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Montagnier, G.; Chauvin, G.; Galland, F.; Beuzit, J.-L.; Rameau, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A73</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..73E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..69R</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of giant planets in protoplanetary disks by CO emission lines</title>
			<authors>Reg&#225;ly, Zs.; S&#225;ndor, Zs.; Dullemond, C. P.; van Boekel, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A69</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..69R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A...2B</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for the sub-stellar companions in the LkCa15 proto-planetary disk</title>
			<authors>Bonavita, M.; Chauvin, G.; Boccaletti, A.; Pietu, V.; Baudoz, P.; Beuzit, J. L.; Dutrey, A.; Guilloteau, S.; Lagrange, A. M.; Mouillet, D.; Niccolini, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A2</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...522A...2B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1195T</bibcode>
			<title>A High-Contrast Imaging Survey of SIM Lite Planet Search Targets</title>
			<authors>Tanner, Angelle M.; Gelino, Christopher R.; Law, Nicholas M.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 896, pp.1195-1206</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1195T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010JRASC.104..203G</bibcode>
			<title>2010 General Assembly Report</title>
			<authors>Grey, Denis</authors>
			<journal>Journal of the Royal Astronomical Society of Canada, Vol. 104, No. 5, p.203</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010JRASC.104..203G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722L..49Q</bibcode>
			<title>First Results from Very Large Telescope NACO Apodizing Phase Plate: 4 mum Images of The Exoplanet beta Pictoris b</title>
			<authors>Quanz, Sascha P.; Meyer, Michael R.; Kenworthy, Matthew A.; Girard, Julien H. V.; Kasper, Markus; Lagrange, Anne-Marie; Apai, Daniel; Boccaletti, Anthony; Bonnefoy, Micka&#235;l; Chauvin, Gael; Hinz, Philip M.; Lenzen, Rainer</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. L49-L53 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722L..49Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722..725Z</bibcode>
			<title>Ancient Planetary Systems are Orbiting a Large Fraction of White Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Zuckerman, B.; Melis, C.; Klein, B.; Koester, D.; Jura, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. 725-736 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722..725Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721L.199M</bibcode>
			<title>Could the Planets Around HR 8799 be Brown Dwarfs?</title>
			<authors>Moro-Mart&#237;n, Amaya; Rieke, George H.; Su, Kate Y. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. L199-L202 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...721L.199M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721L.177C</bibcode>
			<title>High-contrast 3.8 mum Imaging of the Brown Dwarf/Planet-mass Companion to GJ 758</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Bailey, Vanessa; Fabrycky, Daniel; Murray-Clay, Ruth; Rodigas, Timothy; Hinz, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. L177-L181 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...721L.177C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407...71V</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric characterization of exoplanets using angular and spectral differential imaging</title>
			<authors>Vigan, A.; Moutou, C.; Langlois, M.; Allard, F.; Boccaletti, A.; Carbillet, M.; Mouillet, D.; Smith, I.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 1, pp. 71-82.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407...71V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122..905J</bibcode>
			<title>Giant Planet Occurrence in the Stellar Mass-Metallicity Plane</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Aller, Kimberly M.; Howard, Andrew W.; Crepp, Justin R.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 894, pp.905-915</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122..905J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.2279M</bibcode>
			<title>Exploring the conditions required to form giant planets via gravitational instability in massive protoplanetary discs</title>
			<authors>Meru, Farzana; Bate, Matthew R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 4, pp. 2279-2288.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.2279M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..497L</bibcode>
			<title>The Directly Imaged Planet Around the Young Solar Analog 1RXS J160929.1 - 210524: Confirmation of Common Proper Motion, Temperature, and Mass</title>
			<authors>Lafreni&#232;re, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; van Kerkwijk, Marten H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 497-504 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..497L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...329...57L</bibcode>
			<title>A Giant Planet Imaged in the Disk of the Young Star beta Pictoris</title>
			<authors>Lagrange, A.-M.; Bonnefoy, M.; Chauvin, G.; Apai, D.; Ehrenreich, D.; Boccaletti, A.; Gratadour, D.; Rouan, D.; Mouillet, D.; Lacour, S.; Kasper, M.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 329, Issue 5987, pp. 57- (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...329...57L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406..566M</bibcode>
			<title>The planetary system host HR8799: on its lambda Bootis nature</title>
			<authors>Moya, A.; Amado, P. J.; Barrado, D.; Hern&#225;ndez, A. Garc&#237;a; Aberasturi, M.; Montesinos, B.; Aceituno, F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 1, pp. 566-575.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406..566M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717.1123M</bibcode>
			<title>Locating Planetesimal Belts in the Multiple-planet Systems HD 128311, HD 202206, HD 82943, and HR 8799</title>
			<authors>Moro-Mart&#237;n, Amaya; Malhotra, Renu; Bryden, Geoffrey; Rieke, George H.; Su, Kate Y. L.; Beichman, Charles A.; Lawler, Samantha M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. 1123-1139 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717.1123M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717..878N</bibcode>
			<title>A Uniform Analysis of 118 Stars with High-contrast Imaging: Long-period Extrasolar Giant Planets are Rare Around Sun-like Stars</title>
			<authors>Nielsen, Eric L.; Close, Laird M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. 878-896 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717..878N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140..206K</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of Exoplanets in the beta Pic Moving Group with the Gemini Planet Imager</title>
			<authors>Kataria, Tiffany; Simon, Michal</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 1, pp. 206-214 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140..206K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;ARv..18..317A</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and evolution of planetary systems: the impact of high-angular resolution optical techniques</title>
			<authors>Absil, Olivier; Mawet, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomy and Astrophysics Review, Volume 18, Issue 3, pp.317-382</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26ARv..18..317A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518L.134T</bibcode>
			<title>A search for debris disks in the Herschel-ATLAS</title>
			<authors>Thompson, M. A.; Smith, D. J. B.; Stevens, J. A.; Jarvis, M. J.; Vidal Perez, E.; Marshall, J.; Dunne, L.; Eales, S.; White, G. J.; Leeuw, L.; Sibthorpe, B.; Baes, M.; Gonz&#225;lez-Solares, E.; Scott, D.; Vieiria, J.; Amblard, A.; Auld, R.; Bonfield, D. G.; Burgarella, D.; Buttiglione, S.; Cava, A.; Clements, D. L.; Cooray, A.; Dariush, A.; de Zotti, G.; Dye, S.; Eales, S.; Frayer, D.; Fritz, J.; Gonzalez-Nuevo, J.; Herranz, D.; Ibar, E.; Ivison, R. J.; Lagache, G.; Lopez-Caniego, M.; Maddox, S.; Negrello, M.; Pascale, E.; Pohlen, M.; Rigby, E.; Rodighiero, G.; Samui, S.; Serjeant, S.; Temi, P.; Valtchanov, I.; Verma, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.L134</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518L.134T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518A..40N</bibcode>
			<title>Kuiper belts around nearby stars</title>
			<authors>Nilsson, R.; Liseau, R.; Brandeker, A.; Olofsson, G.; Pilbratt, G. L.; Risacher, C.; Rodmann, J.; Augereau, J.-C.; Bergman, P.; Eiroa, C.; Fridlund, M.; Th&#233; bault, P.; White, G. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518A..40N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518A..16F</bibcode>
			<title>Planet gaps in the dust layer of 3D protoplanetary disks. I. Hydrodynamical simulations of T Tauri disks</title>
			<authors>Fouchet, L.; Gonzalez, J.-F.; Maddison, S. T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.A16</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518A..16F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405L..81M</bibcode>
			<title>Age determination of the HR8799 planetary system using asteroseismology</title>
			<authors>Moya, A.; Amado, P. J.; Barrado, D.; Garc&#237;a Hern&#225;ndez, A.; Aberasturi, M.; Montesinos, B.; Aceituno, F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 405, Issue 1, pp. L81-L85.</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405L..81M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716..417H</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Infrared MMTAO Observations of the HR 8799 Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Hinz, Philip M.; Rodigas, Timothy J.; Kenworthy, Matthew A.; Sivanandam, Suresh; Heinze, Aren N.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Meyer, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 1, pp. 417-426 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716..417H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715.1533C</bibcode>
			<title>On-sky Demonstration of a Linear Band-limited Mask with Application to Visual Binary Stars</title>
			<authors>Crepp, J.; Serabyn, E.; Carson, J.; Ge, J.; Kravchenko, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 2, pp. 1533-1538 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715.1533C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715.1036D</bibcode>
			<title>Dusty Disks Around White Dwarfs. I. Origin of Debris Disks</title>
			<authors>Dong, Ruobing; Wang, Yan; Lin, D. N. C.; Liu, X.-W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 2, pp. 1036-1049 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715.1036D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..803V</bibcode>
			<title>Secular Orbital Dynamics of Hierarchical Two-planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 2, pp. 803-822 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..803V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..724B</bibcode>
			<title>A Close Companion Search Around L Dwarfs Using Aperture Masking Interferometry and Palomar Laser Guide Star Adaptive Optics</title>
			<authors>Bernat, David; Bouchez, Antonin H.; Ireland, Michael; Tuthill, Peter; Martinache, Frantz; Angione, John; Burruss, Rick S.; Cromer, John L.; Dekany, Richard G.; Guiwits, Stephen R.; Henning, John R.; Hickey, Jeff; Kibblewhite, Edward; McKenna, Daniel L.; Moore, Anna M.; Petrie, Harold L.; Roberts, Jennifer; Shelton, J. Chris; Thicksten, Robert P.; Trinh, Thang; Tripathi, Renu; Troy, Mitchell; Truong, Tuan; Velur, Viswa; Lloyd, James P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 2, pp. 724-735 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..38R</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray emission from the remarkable A-type star HR 8799</title>
			<authors>Robrade, J.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A38</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..38R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...515A..17J</bibcode>
			<title>NACO-SDI imaging of known companion host stars from the AAPS and Keck planet search surveys</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, J. S.; Jones, H. R. A.; Biller, B.; O'Toole, S. J.; Pinfield, D. J.; Close, L.; Tinney, C. G.; Butler, R. P.; Wittenmyer, R.; Carter, B.; Day-Jones, A. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 515, id.A17</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...515A..17J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122..701J</bibcode>
			<title>Retired A Stars and Their Companions. IV. Seven Jovian Exoplanets from Keck Observatory</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Bowler, Brendan P.; Henry, Gregory W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Wright, Jason T.; Fischer, Debra A.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, Issue 892, pp. 701-711.</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122..701J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..188..242K</bibcode>
			<title>Variations on Debris Disks. II. Icy Planet Formation as a Function of the Bulk Properties and Initial Sizes of Planetesimals</title>
			<authors>Kenyon, Scott J.; Bromley, Benjamin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 188, Issue 1, pp. 242-279 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..188..242K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..561A</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of A Young L Dwarf Binary, SDSS J224953.47+004404.6AB</title>
			<authors>Allers, K. N.; Liu, Michael C.; Dupuy, Trent J.; Cushing, Michael C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 561-571 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..561A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714L.142J</bibcode>
			<title>Radiative Transfer Models of a Possible Planet in the AB Aurigae Disk</title>
			<authors>Jang-Condell, Hannah; Kuchner, Marc J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. L142-L146 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714L.142J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714.1570H</bibcode>
			<title>Constraints on Long-period Planets from an L'- and M-band Survey of Nearby Sun-like Stars: Modeling Results</title>
			<authors>Heinze, A. N.; Hinz, Philip M.; Kenworthy, Matthew; Meyer, Michael; Sivanandam, Suresh; Miller, Douglas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 2, pp. 1570-1581 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714.1570H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714..772M</bibcode>
			<title>Achromatic Eight-octant Phase-mask Coronagraph using Photonic Crystal</title>
			<authors>Murakami, Naoshi; Nishikawa, Jun; Yokochi, Kaito; Tamura, Motohide; Baba, Naoshi; Abe, Lyu</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 772-777 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714..772M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..347F</bibcode>
			<title>Subaru Near-Infrared Imaging of Herbig Ae Stars</title>
			<authors>Fukagawa, Misato; Tamura, Motohide; Itoh, Yoichi; Oasa, Yumiko; Kudo, Tomoyuki; Hayashi, Saeko S.; Kato, Eri; Ootsubo, Takafumi; Itoh, Yusuke; Shibai, Hiroshi; Hayashi, Masahiko</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.2, pp.347--370</journal>
			<date>4/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..347F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.464.1018S</bibcode>
			<title>An image of an exoplanet separated by two diffraction beamwidths from a star</title>
			<authors>Serabyn, E.; Mawet, D.; Burruss, R.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 464, Issue 7291, pp. 1018-1020 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Natur.464.1018S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711.1087K</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision Dynamical Masses of Very Low Mass Binaries</title>
			<authors>Konopacky, Q. M.; Ghez, A. M.; Barman, T. S.; Rice, E. L.; Bailey, J. I., III; White, R. J.; McLean, I. S.; Duch&#234;ne, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 2, article id. 1087-1122 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711.1087K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..772R</bibcode>
			<title>Planet-Planet Scattering in Planetesimal Disks. II. Predictions for Outer Extrasolar Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Raymond, Sean N.; Armitage, Philip J.; Gorelick, Noel</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 2, pp. 772-795 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..772R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..52B</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared integral-field spectra of the planet/brown dwarf companion AB Pictoris b</title>
			<authors>Bonnefoy, M.; Chauvin, G.; Rojo, P.; Allard, F.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Homeier, D.; Dumas, C.; Beuzit, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A52</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..52B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122..162B</bibcode>
			<title>Imaging Young Giant Planets From Ground and Space</title>
			<authors>Beichman, Charles A.; Krist, John; Trauger, John T.; Greene, Tom; Oppenheimer, Ben; Sivaramakrishnan, Anand; Doyon, Ren&#233;; Boccaletti, Anthony; Barman, Travis S.; Rieke, Marcia</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, Issue 888, pp. 162-200.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122..162B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401.2587C</bibcode>
			<title>The effects of opacity on gravitational stability in protoplanetary discs</title>
			<authors>Cossins, Peter; Lodato, Giuseppe; Clarke, Cathie</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 4, pp. 2587-2598.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401.2587C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710L..35J</bibcode>
			<title>Spatially Resolved Spectroscopy of the Exoplanet HR 8799 c</title>
			<authors>Janson, M.; Bergfors, C.; Goto, M.; Brandner, W.; Lafreni&#232;re, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. L35-L38 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710L..35J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1408F</bibcode>
			<title>Stability of the Directly Imaged Multiplanet System HR 8799: Resonance and Masses</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1408-1421 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1408F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1375K</bibcode>
			<title>The Runts of the Litter: Why Planets Formed Through Gravitational Instability Can Only Be Failed Binary Stars</title>
			<authors>Kratter, Kaitlin M.; Murray-Clay, Ruth A.; Youdin, Andrew N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1375-1386 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1375K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....139..626D</bibcode>
			<title>Millimeter Dust Emission in the GQ Lup System</title>
			<authors>Dai, Yu; Wilner, David J.; Andrews, Sean M.; Ohashi, Nagayoshi</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 139, Issue 2, pp. 626-629 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....139..626D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401..867H</bibcode>
			<title>Long-lived planetesimal discs</title>
			<authors>Heng, Kevin; Tremaine, Scott</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 2, pp. 867-889.</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401..867H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..396B</bibcode>
			<title>Retired A Stars and Their Companions. III. Comparing the Mass-Period Distributions of Planets Around A-Type Stars and Sun-Like Stars</title>
			<authors>Bowler, Brendan P.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Henry, Gregory W.; Peek, Kathryn M. G.; Fischer, Debra A.; Clubb, Kelsey I.; Liu, Michael C.; Reffert, Sabine; Schwab, Christian; Lowe, Thomas B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 396-410 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..396B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..342C</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Wide Companions to the Extrasolar Planetary System HR 8799</title>
			<authors>Close, Laird M.; Males, Jared R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 342-348 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..342C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709...53M</bibcode>
			<title>The Vector Vortex Coronagraph: Laboratory Results and First Light at Palomar Observatory</title>
			<authors>Mawet, D.; Serabyn, E.; Liewer, K.; Burruss, R.; Hickey, J.; Shemo, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 53-57 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709...53M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A..52C</bibcode>
			<title>Deep imaging survey of young, nearby austral stars . VLT/NACO near-infrared Lyot-coronographic observations</title>
			<authors>Chauvin, G.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Bonavita, M.; Zuckerman, B.; Dumas, C.; Bessell, M. S.; Beuzit, J.-L.; Bonnefoy, M.; Desidera, S.; Farihi, J.; Lowrance, P.; Mouillet, D.; Song, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A52</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A..52C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707...79D</bibcode>
			<title>The Formation Mechanism of Gas Giants on Wide Orbits</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Beichman, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, pp. 79-88 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707...79D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1232L</bibcode>
			<title>Phase-Induced Amplitude Apodization on Centrally Obscured Pupils: Design and First Laboratory Demonstration for the Subaru Telescope Pupil</title>
			<authors>Lozi, Julien; Martinache, Frantz; Guyon, Olivier</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, Issue 885, pp. 1232-1244.</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1232L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705L.204M</bibcode>
			<title>Pre-Discovery 2007 Image of the HR 8799 Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Metchev, Stanimir; Marois, Christian; Zuckerman, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 705, Issue 2, pp. L204-L207 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705L.204M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705L.148C</bibcode>
			<title>Long Range Outward Migration of Giant Planets, with Application to Fomalhaut b</title>
			<authors>Crida, Aur&#233;lien; Masset, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Morbidelli, Alessandro</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 705, Issue 2, pp. L148-L152 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705L.148C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705.1226B</bibcode>
			<title>Planets and Debris Disks: Results from a Spitzer/MIPS Search for Infrared Excess</title>
			<authors>Bryden, G.; Beichman, C. A.; Carpenter, J. M.; Rieke, G. H.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Werner, M. W.; Tanner, A. M.; Lawler, S. M.; Wyatt, M. C.; Trilling, D. E.; Su, K. Y. L.; Blaylock, M.; Stansberry, J. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 705, Issue 2, pp. 1226-1236 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705.1226B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705.1219K</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on Unresolved Planetary Companions to White Dwarf Remnants of 14 Intermediate-Mass Stars</title>
			<authors>Kilic, Mukremin; Gould, Andrew; Koester, Detlev</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 705, Issue 2, pp. 1219-1225 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705.1219K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705..314S</bibcode>
			<title>The Debris Disk Around HR 8799</title>
			<authors>Su, K. Y. L.; Rieke, G. H.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Malhotra, R.; Bryden, G.; Smith, P. S.; Misselt, K. A.; Moro-Martin, A.; Williams, J. P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 705, Issue 1, pp. 314-327 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705..314S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705...89L</bibcode>
			<title>Explorations Beyond the Snow Line: Spitzer/IRS Spectra of Debris Disks Around Solar-type Stars</title>
			<authors>Lawler, S. M.; Beichman, C. A.; Bryden, G.; Ciardi, D. R.; Tanner, A. M.; Su, K. Y. L.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Lisse, C. M.; Harker, D. E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 705, Issue 1, pp. 89-111 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705...89L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASJ...61.1165T</bibcode>
			<title>Can Sodium Abundances of A-Type Stars Be Reliably Determined from Na I 5890/5896 Lines?</title>
			<authors>Takeda, Yoichi; Kang, Dong-Il; Han, Inwoo; Lee, Byeong-Cheol; Kim, Kang-Min</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.61, No.5, pp.1165--1178</journal>
			<date>10/2009 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASJ...61.1165T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.399..377J</bibcode>
			<title>Imaging search for the unseen companion to &amp;epsil Ind A - improving the detection limits with 4 mum observations</title>
			<authors>Janson, M.; Apai, D.; Zechmeister, M.; Brandner, W.; K&#252;rster, M.; Kasper, M.; Reffert, S.; Endl, M.; Lafreni&#232;re, D.; Gei&#223;ler, K.; Hippler, S.; Henning, Th.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 399, Issue 1, pp. 377-384.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.399..377J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704.1098L</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Observations of GQ Lup b Using the Gemini Integral Field Spectrograph NIFS</title>
			<authors>Lavigne, Jean-Fran&#231;ois; Doyon, Ren&#233;; Lafreni&#232;re, David; Marois, Christian; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 2, pp. 1098-1106 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704.1098L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Msngr.137....8K</bibcode>
			<title>Direct Imaging of Exoplanets and Brown Dwarfs with the VLT: NACO Pupil-stabilised Lyot Coronagraphy at 4 &#181;m</title>
			<authors>Kasper, Markus; Amico, Paola; Pompei, Emanuela; Ageorges, Nancy; Apai, Daniel; Argomedo, Javier; Kornweibel, Nick; Lidman, Chris</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 137, p. 8-13</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Msngr.137....8K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ARA&amp;A..47..253O</bibcode>
			<title>High-Contrast Observations in Optical and Infrared Astronomy</title>
			<authors>Oppenheimer, Ben R.; Hinkley, Sasha</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, vol. 47, Issue 1, pp.253-289</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ARA%26A..47..253O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702L.163N</bibcode>
			<title>Did Fomalhaut, HR 8799, and HL Tauri Form Planets Via the Gravitational Instability? Placing Limits on the Required Disk Masses</title>
			<authors>Nero, D.; Bjorkman, J. E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. L163-L167 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702L.163N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702L..47M</bibcode>
			<title>Imaging the Debris Disk of HD 32297 with a Phase-Mask Coronagraph at High Strehl Ratio</title>
			<authors>Mawet, D.; Serabyn, E.; Stapelfeldt, K.; Crepp, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 702, Issue 1, pp. L47-L50 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702L..47M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702..672C</bibcode>
			<title>Direct Detection of Planets Orbiting Large Angular Diameter Stars: Sensitivity of an Internally Occulting Space-based Coronagraph</title>
			<authors>Crepp, Justin R.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Ge, Jian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 1, pp. 672-679 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702..672C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.2019L</bibcode>
			<title>Abundant Circumstellar Silica Dust and SiO Gas Created by a Giant Hypervelocity Collision in the ~12 Myr HD172555 System</title>
			<authors>Lisse, C. M.; Chen, C. H.; Wyatt, M. C.; Morlok, A.; Song, I.; Bryden, G.; Sheehan, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 2019-2032 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.2019L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.1367C</bibcode>
			<title>Solar System Analogs Around IRAS-Discovered Debris Disks</title>
			<authors>Chen, Christine H.; Sheehan, Patrick; Watson, Dan M.; Manoj, P.; Najita, Joan R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 1367-1372 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.1367C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...503..247R</bibcode>
			<title>A possible architecture of the planetary system HR 8799</title>
			<authors>Reidemeister, M.; Krivov, A. V.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Fiedler, S.; M&#252;ller, S.; L&#246;hne, T.; Neuh&#228;user, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 503, Issue 1, 2009, pp.247-258</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...503..247R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.397L..16G</bibcode>
			<title>Is the HR8799 extrasolar system destined for planetary scattering?</title>
			<authors>Gozdziewski, Krzysztof; Migaszewski, Cezary</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 397, Issue 1, pp. L16-L20.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.397L..16G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..820J</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Shadows in Protoplanetary Disks. II. Observable Signatures</title>
			<authors>Jang-Condell, Hannah</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 820-831 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..820J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699L..88R</bibcode>
			<title>Planet-Planet Scattering in Planetesimal Disks</title>
			<authors>Raymond, Sean N.; Armitage, Philip J.; Gorelick, Noel</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 699, Issue 2, pp. L88-L92 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699L..88R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699.1067M</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Mid-IR Spectra of Dust Debris Around A and Late B Type Stars: Asteroid Belt Analogs and Power-Law Dust Distributions</title>
			<authors>Morales, Farisa Y.; Werner, M. W.; Bryden, G.; Plavchan, P.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Rieke, G. H.; Su, K. Y. L.; Beichman, C. A.; Chen, C. H.; Grogan, K.; Kenyon, S. J.; Moro-Martin, A.; Wolf, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 2, pp. 1067-1086 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699.1067M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..330S</bibcode>
			<title>High-resolution 5 mum Spectroscopy of Transitional Disks</title>
			<authors>Salyk, C.; Blake, G. A.; Boogert, A. C. A.; Brown, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 330-347 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..330S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1989B</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer/IRAC-MIPS Survey of NGC 2451A AND B: Debris Disks at 50-80 Million Years</title>
			<authors>Balog, Zoltan; Kiss, L&#225;szl&#243; L.; Vink&#243;, J&#243;zsef; Rieke, G. H.; Muzerolle, James; G&#225;sp&#225;r, Andr&#225;s; Young, Erick T.; Gorlova, Nadya</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1989-2013 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1989B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...697.1928K</bibcode>
			<title>MMT/AO 5 mum Imaging Constraints on the Existence of Giant Planets Orbiting Fomalhaut at ~13-40 AU</title>
			<authors>Kenworthy, Matthew A.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Hinz, Philip M.; Meyer, Michael R.; Heinze, Aren N.; Miller, Douglas L.; Sivanandam, Suresh; Freed, Melanie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 697, Issue 2, pp. 1928-1933 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...697.1928K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...500.1077B</bibcode>
			<title>The physical conditions in Gomez's Hamburger (IRAS 18059-3211), a pre-MS rotating disk</title>
			<authors>Bujarrabal, V.; Young, K.; Castro-Carrizo, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 500, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1077-1087</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...500.1077B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...499..967C</bibcode>
			<title>Long-term photometric monitoring with the Mercator telescope. Frequencies and multicolour amplitudes of gamma Doradus stars</title>
			<authors>Cuypers, J.; Aerts, C.; De Cat, P.; De Ridder, J.; Goossens, K.; Schoenaers, C.; Uytterhoeven, K.; Acke, B.; Davignon, G.; Debosscher, J.; Decin, L.; De Meester, W.; Deroo, P.; Drummond, R.; Kolenberg, K.; Lefever, K.; Raskin, G.; Reyniers, M.; Saesen, S.; Vandenbussche, B.; van Malderen, R.; Verhoelst, T.; van Winckel, H.; Waelkens, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 499, Issue 3, 2009, pp.967-982</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...499..967C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696L...1F</bibcode>
			<title>H-Band Image of a Planetary Companion Around HR 8799 in 2002</title>
			<authors>Fukagawa, Misato; Itoh, Yoichi; Tamura, Motohide; Oasa, Yumiko; Hayashi, Saeko S.; Fujita, Yutaka; Shibai, Hiroshi; Hayashi, Masahiko</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 696, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696L...1F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1600V</bibcode>
			<title>Formation, Survival, and Detectability of Planets Beyond 100 AU</title>
			<authors>Veras, Dimitri; Crepp, Justin R.; Ford, Eric B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1600-1611 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1600V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121..309J</bibcode>
			<title>International Year of Astronomy Invited Review on Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 878, pp.309-315</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121..309J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694L.148L</bibcode>
			<title>HST/NICMOS Detection of HR 8799 b in 1998</title>
			<authors>Lafreni&#232;re, David; Marois, Christian; Doyon, Ren&#233;; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 694, Issue 2, pp. L148-L152 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694L.148L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694.1085V</bibcode>
			<title>Directly Determined Linear Radii and Effective Temperatures of Exoplanet Host Stars</title>
			<authors>van Belle, Gerard T.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 2, pp. 1085-1098 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694.1085V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009CoAst.159...61K</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of chemically peculiar stars</title>
			<authors>Kochukhov, O.</authors>
			<journal>Communications in Asteroseismology, Vol. 159, p. 61-70. Proceedings of "JENAM 2008 Symposium No 4: Asteroseismology and Stellar Evolution", held on September 8-12 2008, edited by Sonja Schuh and Gerald Handler.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009CoAst.159...61K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MmSAI..80..658B</bibcode>
			<title>Cloud formation and dynamics in cool dwarf and hot exoplanetary atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Burgasser, Adam J.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ&#224; Astronomica Italiana, v.80, p.658 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MmSAI..80..658B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...683.1085Z</bibcode>
			<title>Gas and Dust Associated with the Strange, Isolated Star BP Piscium</title>
			<authors>Zuckerman, B.; Melis, C.; Song, Inseok; Meier, David S.; Perrin, Marshall D.; Macintosh, Bruce; Marois, Christian; Weinberger, Alycia J.; Rhee, Joseph H.; Graham, James R.; Kastner, Joel H.; Palmer, Patrick; Forveille, T.; Becklin, E. E.; Wilner, D. J.; Barman, T. S.; Marcy, G. W.; Bessell, M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 683, Issue 2, pp. 1085-1103.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...683.1085Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJS..176..276V</bibcode>
			<title>The Palomar Testbed Interferometer Calibrator Catalog</title>
			<authors>van Belle, G. T.; van Belle, G.; Creech-Eakman, M. J.; Coyne, J.; Boden, A. F.; Akeson, R. L.; Ciardi, D. R.; Rykoski, K. M.; Thompson, R. R.; Lane, B. F.; PTI Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 176, Issue 1, pp. 276-292.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJS..176..276V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...478..487B</bibcode>
			<title>A spectroscopic study of southern (candidate) gamma Doradus stars. II. Detailed abundance analysis and fundamental parameters</title>
			<authors>Bruntt, H.; De Cat, P.; Aerts, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 478, Issue 2, February I 2008, pp.487-496</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...478..487B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008CoAst.152..116G</bibcode>
			<title>Observing gamma Doradus Stars with BRITE - an Outlook</title>
			<authors>Gruberbauer, M.; Neuteufel, R.; Weiss, W. W.</authors>
			<journal>Communications in Asteroseismology, Vol.152, p. 116-120</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008CoAst.152..116G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.382.1823F</bibcode>
			<title>The total number of giant planets in debris discs with central clearings</title>
			<authors>Faber, Peter; Quillen, Alice C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 382, Issue 4, pp. 1823-1828.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.382.1823F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..677S</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray emission from A-type stars</title>
			<authors>Schr&#246;der, C.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 2, November IV 2007, pp.677-684</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..677S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...472..241G</bibcode>
			<title>UV flux distributions of gamma Doradus stars</title>
			<authors>Gerbaldi, M.; Faraggiana, R.; Caffau, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 472, Issue 1, September II 2007, pp.241-246</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...472..241G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660.1556R</bibcode>
			<title>Characterization of Dusty Debris Disks: The IRAS and Hipparcos Catalogs</title>
			<authors>Rhee, Joseph H.; Song, Inseok; Zuckerman, B.; McElwain, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 2, pp. 1556-1571.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660.1556R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AJ....133.1421H</bibcode>
			<title>Photometry and Spectroscopy of 11 gamma Doradus Stars</title>
			<authors>Henry, Gregory W.; Fekel, Francis C.; Henry, Stephen M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 133, Issue 4, pp. 1421-1440 (2007).</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AJ....133.1421H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...463..671R</bibcode>
			<title>Rotational velocities of A-type stars. III. Velocity distributions</title>
			<authors>Royer, F.; Zorec, J.; G&#243;mez, A. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 463, Issue 2, February IV 2007, pp.671-682</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...463..671R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASJ...58.1033S</bibcode>
			<title>Phase-Reference VLBI Observations of the Compact Steep-Spectrum Source 3C 138</title>
			<authors>Shen, Zhi-Qiang; Shang, Lin-Lin; Jiang, Dong-Rong; Cai, Hong-Bing; Chen, Xi</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.58, No.6, pp.1033-1037</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASJ...58.1033S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASJ...58.1023S</bibcode>
			<title>lambda Bootis-Like Abundances in the Vega-Like, gamma Doradus Type-Pulsator HD 218396</title>
			<authors>Sadakane, Kozo</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.58, No.6, pp.1023-1032</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASJ...58.1023S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...653.1480W</bibcode>
			<title>The Dust Properties of Eight Debris Disk Candidates as Determined by Submillimeter Photometry</title>
			<authors>Williams, Jonathan P.; Andrews, Sean M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 653, Issue 2, pp. 1480-1485.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...653.1480W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460..733L</bibcode>
			<title>Search for cold debris disks around M-dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Lestrade, J.-F.; Wyatt, M. C.; Bertoldi, F.; Dent, W. R. F.; Menten, K. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 3, December IV 2006, pp.733-741</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460..733L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AstL...32..759G</bibcode>
			<title>Pulkovo Compilation of Radial Velocities for 35 495 Hipparcos stars in a common system</title>
			<authors>Gontcharov, G. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Letters, Vol. 32, Issue 11, p.759-771</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AstL...32..759G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJS..166..351C</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer IRS Spectroscopy of IRAS-discovered Debris Disks</title>
			<authors>Chen, C. H.; Sargent, B. A.; Bohac, C.; Kim, K. H.; Leibensperger, E.; Jura, M.; Najita, J.; Forrest, W. J.; Watson, D. M.; Sloan, G. C.; Keller, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 166, Issue 1, pp. 351-377.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJS..166..351C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...456..261R</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of the new multiperiodic gamma Dor variable HD 239276</title>
			<authors>Rodr&#237;guez, E.; Costa, V.; Zhou, A.-Y.; Grigahc&#232;ne, A.; Dupret, M. A.; Su&#225;rez, J. C.; Moya, A.; L&#243;pez-Gonz&#225;lez, M. J.; Wei, J.-Y.; Fan, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 456, Issue 1, September II 2006, pp.261-268</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...456..261R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...453.1041J</bibcode>
			<title>Non-radial pulsations in the gamma Doradus star HD 195068</title>
			<authors>Jankov, S.; Mathias, P.; Chapellier, E.; Le Contel, J.-M.; Sareyan, J.-P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 453, Issue 3, July III 2006, pp.1041-1050</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...453.1041J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644..525M</bibcode>
			<title>Nearby Debris Disk Systems with High Fractional Luminosity Reconsidered</title>
			<authors>Mo&#243;r, A.; &#193;brah&#225;m, P.; Derekas, A.; Kiss, Cs.; Kiss, L. L.; Apai, D.; Grady, C.; Henning, Th.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 1, pp. 525-542.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644..525M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...450..715R</bibcode>
			<title>The frequency ratio method and the new multiperiodic gamma Doradus star HD 218427</title>
			<authors>Rodr&#237;guez, E.; Amado, P. J.; Su&#225;rez, J. C.; Moya, A.; Dupret, M. A.; Poretti, E.; Grigahc&#232;ne, A.; Costa, V.; L&#243;pez-Gonz&#225;lez, M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 450, Issue 2, May I 2006, pp.715-723</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...450..715R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006CoAst.147...52C</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of MERCATOR data - Part II: variable A &amp; F stars</title>
			<authors>Cuypers, J.; Goossens, K.; Schoenaers, C.; De Cat, P.; Aerts, C.</authors>
			<journal>Communications in Asteroseismology, vol. 147, p. 52-55</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006CoAst.147...52C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MmSAI..77..429J</bibcode>
			<title>Fourier-Doppler imaging of non-radial pulsations in gamma  Doradus stars .</title>
			<authors>Jankov, S.; Mathias, P.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ&#224; Astronomica Italiana, v.77, p.429 (2006)</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MmSAI..77..429J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005AJ....130.1845L</bibcode>
			<title>An Infrared Coronagraphic Survey for Substellar Companions</title>
			<authors>Lowrance, Patrick J.; Becklin, E. E.; Schneider, Glenn; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Weinberger, Alycia J.; Zuckerman, B.; Dumas, Christophe; Beuzit, Jean-Luc; Plait, Phil; Malumuth, Eliot; Heap, Sally; Terrile, Richard J.; Hines, Dean C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 130, Issue 4, pp. 1845-1861.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005AJ....130.1845L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJS..154..453J</bibcode>
			<title>Mid-Infrared Spectra of Dust Debris around Main-Sequence Stars</title>
			<authors>Jura, M.; Chen, C. H.; Furlan, E.; Green, J.; Sargent, B.; Forrest, W. J.; Watson, D. M.; Barry, D. J.; Hall, P.; Herter, T. L.; Houck, J. R.; Sloan, G. C.; Uchida, K.; D'Alessio, P.; Brandl, B. R.; Keller, L. D.; Kemper, F.; Morris, P.; Najita, J.; Calvet, N.; Hartmann, L.; Myers, P. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 154, Issue 1, pp. 453-457.</journal>
			<date>9/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJS..154..453J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AJ....127.2871M</bibcode>
			<title>The Brown Dwarf Desert at 75-1200 AU</title>
			<authors>McCarthy, C.; Zuckerman, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 127, Issue 5, pp. 2871-2884.</journal>
			<date>5/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AJ....127.2871M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...417..189M</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-site, multi-technique survey of gamma Doradus candidates. I. Spectroscopic results for 59 stars</title>
			<authors>Mathias, P.; Le Contel, J.-M.; Chapellier, E.; Jankov, S.; Sareyan, J.-P.; Poretti, E.; Garrido, R.; Rodr&#237;guez, E.; Arellano Ferro, A.; Alvarez, M.; Parrao, L.; Pe&#241;a, J.; Eyer, L.; Aerts, C.; De Cat, P.; Weiss, W. W.; Zhou, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.417, p.189-199 (2004)</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...417..189M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...603..738Z</bibcode>
			<title>Dusty Debris Disks as Signposts of Planets: Implications for Spitzer Space Telescope</title>
			<authors>Zuckerman, B.; Song, Inseok</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 603, Issue 2, pp. 738-743.</journal>
			<date>3/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...603..738Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003AJ....126.3058H</bibcode>
			<title>A Dozen New gamma Doradus Stars</title>
			<authors>Henry, Gregory W.; Fekel, Francis C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 126, Issue 6, pp. 3058-3075.</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003AJ....126.3058H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...412..447G</bibcode>
			<title>The heterogeneous class of lambda  Bootis stars</title>
			<authors>Gerbaldi, M.; Faraggiana, R.; Lai, O.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.412, p.447-464 (2003)</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...412..447G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003AJ....126.2048G</bibcode>
			<title>Contributions to the Nearby Stars (NStars) Project: Spectroscopy of Stars Earlier than M0 within 40 Parsecs: The Northern Sample. I.</title>
			<authors>Gray, R. O.; Corbally, C. J.; Garrison, R. F.; McFadden, M. T.; Robinson, P. E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 126, Issue 4, pp. 2048-2059.</journal>
			<date>10/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003AJ....126.2048G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003AJ....125.2156F</bibcode>
			<title>The Orbit and Pulsation Periods of the gamma Doradus Variable HR 6844 (V2502 Ophiuchi)</title>
			<authors>Fekel, Francis C.; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 125, Issue 4, pp. 2156-2162.</journal>
			<date>4/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003AJ....125.2156F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...393..897R</bibcode>
			<title>Rotational velocities of A-type stars in the northern hemisphere. II. Measurement of v sin i</title>
			<authors>Royer, F.; Grenier, S.; Baylac, M.-O.; G&#243;mez, A. E.; Zorec, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.393, p.897-911 (2002)</journal>
			<date>10/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...393..897R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002PASP..114..988H</bibcode>
			<title>Six New gamma Doradus Stars</title>
			<authors>Henry, Gregory W.; Fekel, Francis C.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 114, Issue 799, pp. 988-998.</journal>
			<date>9/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002PASP..114..988H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AJ....124..989G</bibcode>
			<title>A Spectroscopic Search for lambda Bootis and Other Peculiar A-Type Stars in Intermediate-Age Open Clusters</title>
			<authors>Gray, R. O.; Corbally, C. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 124, Issue 2, pp. 989-1000.</journal>
			<date>8/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AJ....124..989G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.333..251H</bibcode>
			<title>On the relationship between the delta Scuti and gamma Doradus pulsators</title>
			<authors>Handler, G.; Shobbrook, R. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 333, Issue 2, pp. 251-262.</journal>
			<date>6/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.333..251H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001AJ....122.3383H</bibcode>
			<title>10 New gamma Doradus and delta Scuti Stars</title>
			<authors>Henry, Gregory W.; Fekel, Francis C.; Kaye, Anthony B.; Kaul, Ann</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 122, Issue 6, pp. 3383-3395.</journal>
			<date>12/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001AJ....122.3383H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...367..521P</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of Apparent Diameters and Absolute Radii of Stars (CADARS) - Third edition - Comments and statistics</title>
			<authors>Pasinetti Fracassini, L. E.; Pastori, L.; Covino, S.; Pozzi, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.367, p.521-524 (2001)</journal>
			<date>2/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...367..521P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...546..352S</bibcode>
			<title>Ages of A-Type Vega-like Stars from uvbybeta Photometry</title>
			<authors>Song, Inseok; Caillault, J.-P.; Barrado y Navascu&#233;s, David; Stauffer, John R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 546, Issue 1, pp. 352-357.</journal>
			<date>1/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...546..352S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...366..178R</bibcode>
			<title>delta Scuti and related stars: Analysis of the R00 Catalogue</title>
			<authors>Rodr&#237;guez, E.; Breger, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.366, p.178-196 (2001)</journal>
			<date>1/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...366..178R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...365..110E</bibcode>
			<title>EXPORT: Near-IR observations of Vega-type and pre-main sequence stars</title>
			<authors>Eiroa, C.; Garz&#243;n, F.; Alberdi, A.; de Winter, D.; Ferlet, R.; Grady, C. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Davies, J. K.; Deeg, H. J.; Harris, A. W.; Horne, K.; Mer&#237;n, B.; Miranda, L. F.; Montesinos, B.; Mora, A.; Oudmaijer, R.; Palacios, J.; Penny, A.; Quirrenbach, A.; Rauer, H.; Schneider, J.; Solano, E.; Tsapras, Y.; Wesselius, P. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.365, p.110-114 (2001)</journal>
			<date>1/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...365..110E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ARA&amp;A..39..549Z</bibcode>
			<title>Dusty Circumstellar Disks</title>
			<authors>Zuckerman, B.</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, Vol. 39, p. 549-580 (2001).</journal>
			<date>0/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ARA%26A..39..549Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000IBVS.4969....1A</bibcode>
			<title>On the Variability of A3-F0 Luminosity Class III-V Stars</title>
			<authors>Adelman, S. J.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4969, 1.</journal>
			<date>10/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000IBVS.4969....1A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000ApJ...542L..57G</bibcode>
			<title>Driving the Gravity-Mode Pulsations in gamma Doradus Variables</title>
			<authors>Guzik, Joyce A.; Kaye, Anthony B.; Bradley, Paul A.; Cox, Arthur N.; Neuforge, Corinne</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 542, Issue 1, pp. L57-L60.</journal>
			<date>10/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000ApJ...542L..57G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...358..287M</bibcode>
			<title>Search for gamma Doradus variable stars in the Pleiades cluster</title>
			<authors>Mart&#237;n, S.; Rodr&#237;guez, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.358, p.287-298 (2000)</journal>
			<date>6/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...358..287M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000MNRAS.313...73S</bibcode>
			<title>Optical, infrared and millimetre-wave properties of Vega-like systems - IV. Observations of a new sample of candidate Vega-like sources</title>
			<authors>Sylvester, Roger J.; Mannings, Vincent</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 313, Issue 1, pp. 73-86.</journal>
			<date>3/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000MNRAS.313...73S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999AJ....118.2997K</bibcode>
			<title>HD 62454 and HD 68192: Two New gamma Doradus Variables</title>
			<authors>Kaye, Anthony B.; Henry, Gregory W.; Fekel, Francis C.; Gray, Richard O.; Rodr&#237;guez, Eloy; Mart&#237;n, Susana; Gies, Douglas R.; Bagnuolo, William G.; Hall, Douglas S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 118, Issue 6, pp. 2997-3005.</journal>
			<date>12/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999AJ....118.2997K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999AJ....118.2993G</bibcode>
			<title>HR 8799: A Link between gamma Doradus Variables and lambda Bootis Stars</title>
			<authors>Gray, Richard O.; Kaye, Anthony B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 118, Issue 6, pp. 2993-2996.</journal>
			<date>12/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999AJ....118.2993G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999MNRAS.308.1081K</bibcode>
			<title>Simultaneous photometry and spectroscopy of the newly discovered gamma Doradus variable HR 8330=HD 207223</title>
			<authors>Kaye, Anthony B.; Henry, Gregory W.; Fekel, Francis C.; Hall, Douglas S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 308, Issue 4, pp. 1081-1086.</journal>
			<date>10/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999MNRAS.308.1081K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999PASP..111..840K</bibcode>
			<title>Gamma Doradus Stars: Defining a New Class of Pulsating Variables</title>
			<authors>Kaye, Anthony B.; Handler, Gerald; Krisciunas, Kevin; Poretti, Ennio; Zerbi, Filippo M.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 111, Issue 761, pp. 840-844.</journal>
			<date>7/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999PASP..111..840K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999IBVS.4692....1K</bibcode>
			<title>A transit of the planet 51 Peg B?</title>
			<authors>Krisciunas, K.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4692, 1.</journal>
			<date>4/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999IBVS.4692....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999MNRAS.303..275Z</bibcode>
			<title>The gamma DOR variable HR 8799: results from a multisite campaign</title>
			<authors>Zerbi, F. M.; Rodr&#237;guez, E.; Garrido, R.; Mart&#237;n, S.; Arellano Ferro, A.; Sareyan, J. P.; Krisciunas, K.; Akan, M. C.; Evren, S.; Ibanoglu, C.; Keskin, V.; Pekunlu, R.; Tunca, Z.; Luedeke, K.; Paparo, M.; Nuspl, J.; Guerrero, G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 303, Issue 2, pp. 275-283.</journal>
			<date>2/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999MNRAS.303..275Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999IBVS.4659....1K</bibcode>
			<title>The 74th Special Name-list of Variable Stars</title>
			<authors>Kazarovets, E. V.; Samus, N. N.; Durlevich, O. V.; Frolov, M. S.; Antipin, S. V.; Kireeva, N. N.; Pastukhova, E. N.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4659, 1.</journal>
			<date>1/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999IBVS.4659....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998AJ....116.1810E</bibcode>
			<title>The Pleiades and alpha Persei Clusters</title>
			<authors>Eggen, Olin J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 116, Issue 4, pp. 1810-1815.</journal>
			<date>10/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998AJ....116.1810E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;AS..132..155H</bibcode>
			<title>The ROSAT all-sky survey catalogue of optically bright main-sequence stars and subgiant stars</title>
			<authors>Huensch, M.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Voges, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.132, p.155-171</journal>
			<date>10/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26AS..132..155H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;A...337..790A</bibcode>
			<title>The discovery of new gamma Doradus stars from the HIPPARCOS mission</title>
			<authors>Aerts, C.; Eyer, L.; Kestens, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.337, p.790-796 (1998)</journal>
			<date>9/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26A...337..790A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998MNRAS.294L..35K</bibcode>
			<title>CA II H&amp;K survey of Gamma Doradus candidates</title>
			<authors>Kaye, Anthony B.; Strassmeier, Klaus G.</authors>
			<journal>Royal Astronomical Society, Monthly Notices, vol. 294, p. L35-L39</journal>
			<date>2/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998MNRAS.294L..35K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997MNRAS.292..621P</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and analysis of Gamma Doradus type pulsations in the F0 IV star HR 2740=QW PUP</title>
			<authors>Poretti, E.; Koen, C.; Martinez, P.; Breuer, F.; Haupt, H.; de Alwis, D.</authors>
			<journal>Royal Astronomical Society, Monthly Notices, vol. 292, p. 621</journal>
			<date>12/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997MNRAS.292..621P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997BaltA...6..499B</bibcode>
			<title>Classification of Population II Stars in the Vilnius Photometric System. II. Results</title>
			<authors>Bartkevicius, A.; Lazauskaite, R.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.6, p.499-572.</journal>
			<date>12/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997BaltA...6..499B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997MNRAS.292...43Z</bibcode>
			<title>The Gamma DOR variable HD 164615 - Results from a multisite photometric campaign</title>
			<authors>Zerbi, F. M.; Rodr&#237;guez, E.; Garrido, R.; Mart&#237;n, S.; Akan, K.; Luedeke, K.; Keskin, V.; Ibanoglu, C.; Evren, S.; Tunca, Z.; Pekunlu, R.; Paparo, M.; Nuspl, J.; Krisciunas, K.; Jiang, S. Y.</authors>
			<journal>Royal Astronomical Society, Monthly Notices, vol. 292, p. 43</journal>
			<date>11/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997MNRAS.292...43Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997MNRAS.290..401Z</bibcode>
			<title>The gamma Doradus-type variable 9 Aurigae: results from a multi-site campaign</title>
			<authors>Zerbi, F. M.; Garrido, R.; Rodriguez, E.; Krisciunas, K.; Crowe, R. A.; Roberts, M.; Guinan, E. F.; McCook, G. P.; Sperauskas, J.; Griffin, R. F.; Luedeke, K. D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 290, Issue 3, pp. 401-410.</journal>
			<date>9/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997MNRAS.290..401Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997IBVS.4513....1D</bibcode>
			<title>True and Possible Contact Binaries in the Hipparcos Catalogue</title>
			<authors>Duerbeck, Hilmar W.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4513, 1.</journal>
			<date>9/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997IBVS.4513....1D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997MNRAS.289..831S</bibcode>
			<title>Optical, infrared and millimetre-wave properties of Vega-like systems - III. Models with thermally spiking grains</title>
			<authors>Sylvester, R. J.; Skinner, C. J.; Barlow, M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 289, Issue 4, pp. 831-846.</journal>
			<date>8/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997MNRAS.289..831S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997ApJ...481..926M</bibcode>
			<title>The Planet around 51 Pegasi</title>
			<authors>Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Williams, Eric; Bildsten, Lars; Graham, James R.; Ghez, Andrea M.; Jernigan, J. Garrett</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.481, p.926</journal>
			<date>5/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997ApJ...481..926M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;AS..122..131S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic survey of delta Scuti stars. I. Rotation velocities and effective temperatures</title>
			<authors>Solano, E.; Fernley, J.</authors>
			<journal>A &amp; A Supplement series, Vol. 122, April I 1997, 131-147.</journal>
			<date>4/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26AS..122..131S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996MNRAS.283..457S</bibcode>
			<title>Optical, infrared and millimetre-wave properties of Vega-like systems - II. Radiative transfer modelling</title>
			<authors>Sylvester, R. J.; Skinner, C. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 283, Issue 2, pp. 457-470.</journal>
			<date>11/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996MNRAS.283..457S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996A&amp;A...313..851B</bibcode>
			<title>gamma Doradus and delta Scuti stars: cousins or twins?</title>
			<authors>Breger, M.; Beichbuchner, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.313, p.851-856</journal>
			<date>9/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996A%26A...313..851B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996A&amp;AS..118..239H</bibcode>
			<title>The photoelectric astrolabe catalogue of Yunnan Observatory (YPAC).</title>
			<authors>Hu, Hui; Li, Dongming; Li, Yongsheng; Wang, Rui; Li, Xiaoming</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.118, p.239-241</journal>
			<date>8/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996A%26AS..118..239H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996MNRAS.279..915S</bibcode>
			<title>Optical, infrared and millimetre-wave properties of Vega-like systems.</title>
			<authors>Sylvester, R. J.; Skinner, C. J.; Barlow, M. J.; Mannings, V.</authors>
			<journal>Mon. Not. R. Astron. Soc., Vol. 279, No. 3, p. 915 - 939</journal>
			<date>4/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996MNRAS.279..915S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995MNRAS.277.1404K</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Gamma-Doradus Type Variable Stars in the Hyades</title>
			<authors>Krisciunas, K.; Crowe, R. A.; Luedeke, K. D.; Roberts, M.</authors>
			<journal>R.A.S. MONTHLY NOTICES V.277, NO. 4/DEC15, P.1404, 1995</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995MNRAS.277.1404K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995AAS...18710214K</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-longitude campaigns on gamma Doradus stars</title>
			<authors>Krisciunas, K.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 187th AAS Meeting, #102.14; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 27, p.1430</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995AAS...18710214K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;AS..114..269D</bibcode>
			<title>Vitesses radiales. Catalogue WEB: Wilson Evans Batten. Subtittle: Radial velocities: The Wilson-Evans-Batten catalogue.</title>
			<authors>Duflot, M.; Figon, P.; Meyssonnier, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.114, p.269</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26AS..114..269D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995IAUC.6261....2G</bibcode>
			<title>51 Pegasi</title>
			<authors>Guinan, E.; Dukes, R.; Nations, H.; Buzasi, D.; McCook, G.</authors>
			<journal>IAU Circ., 6261, 2 (1995).  Edited by Green, D. W. E.</journal>
			<date>11/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995IAUC.6261....2G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJS...99..135A</bibcode>
			<title>The Relation between Rotational Velocities and Spectral Peculiarities among A-Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Abt, Helmut A.; Morrell, Nidia I.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement v.99, p.135</journal>
			<date>7/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJS...99..135A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995IBVS.4210....1E</bibcode>
			<title>Young Pulsating Stars in the Bohm-Vitense Decrement</title>
			<authors>Eggen, Olin J.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4210, 1.</journal>
			<date>6/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995IBVS.4210....1E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995IBVS.4195....1K</bibcode>
			<title>A List of Variable Stars Similar to gamma Dor</title>
			<authors>Krisciunas, K.; Handler, G.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4195, 1.</journal>
			<date>5/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995IBVS.4195....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995IBVS.4170....1R</bibcode>
			<title>A long period early F-type variable: HR8799</title>
			<authors>Rodriguez, E.; Zerbi, F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4170, 1.</journal>
			<date>3/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995IBVS.4170....1R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994A&amp;AS..106..257O</bibcode>
			<title>Stroemgren photometry of F- and G-type stars brighter than V = 9.6. I. UVBY photometry</title>
			<authors>Olsen, E. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astron. Astrophys. Suppl. 106, 257-266 (1994)</journal>
			<date>8/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994A%26AS..106..257O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994Ap&amp;SS.212..261S</bibcode>
			<title>Millimetre photometry and infrared spectroscopy of Vega-excess stars</title>
			<authors>Sylvester, R. J.; Barlow, M. J.; Skinner, C. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, vol. 212, nos. 1-2, p. 261-270</journal>
			<date>2/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994Ap%26SS.212..261S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;AS..102...89O</bibcode>
			<title>Stromgren Four-Colour UVBY Photometry of G5-TYPE Hd-Stars Brighter than MV=8.6</title>
			<authors>Olsen, E. H.</authors>
			<journal>ASTRON. AND ASTROPHYS. SUPPL. V.102, NO.1/NOVII, P. 89, 1993</journal>
			<date>11/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26AS..102...89O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993VeARI..34....1S</bibcode>
			<title>Improved mean positions and proper motions for the 995 FK4 Sup stars not included in the FK5 Extension.</title>
			<authors>Schwan, H.; Bastian, U.; Bien, R.; J&#228;hrling, R.; Jahrei&#223;, H.; R&#246;ser, S.</authors>
			<journal>Ver&#246;ff. - Astron. Rechen-Inst. Heidelb., No. 34,</journal>
			<date>0/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993VeARI..34....1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992A&amp;AS...96..477V</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of stars observed with the photoelectric CERGA astrolabe (March 1988 - July 1991)</title>
			<authors>Vigouroux, G.; Billaud, G.; Boche, R.; Chauvineau, B.; Furia, M.; Journet, A.; Kovalevsky, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 96, no. 3, p. 477-484.</journal>
			<date>12/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992A%26AS...96..477V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992A&amp;A...261..499S</bibcode>
			<title>An optical search for Beta Pictoris-like disks around nearby stars</title>
			<authors>Smith, B. A.; Fountain, J. W.; Terrile, R. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 261, no. 2, p. 499-502.</journal>
			<date>8/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992A%26A...261..499S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1991ApJS...75..905S</bibcode>
			<title>A survey for infrared excesses among high galactic latitude SAO stars</title>
			<authors>Stencel, Robert E.; Backman, Dana E.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 75, March 1991, p. 905-924. Research supported by University of Colorado.</journal>
			<date>3/1991</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1991ApJS...75..905S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990A&amp;AS...85.1089L</bibcode>
			<title>Search for Beta Pictoris-like star</title>
			<authors>Lagrange-Henri, A. M.; Ferlet, R.; Vidal-Madjar, A.; Beust, H.; Gry, C.; Lallement, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 85, no. 3, Nov. 1990, p. 1089-1100.</journal>
			<date>11/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990A%26AS...85.1089L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989ApJ...346..232W</bibcode>
			<title>On the nearest molecular clouds. III - MBM 40, 53, 54, and 55</title>
			<authors>Welty, D. E.; Hobbs, L. M.; Penprase, B. E.; Blitz, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 346, Nov. 1, 1989, p. 232-242.</journal>
			<date>11/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989ApJ...346..232W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987A&amp;AS...71..275F</bibcode>
			<title>Radial velocity measurements. II - Ground-based observations of the program stars for the HIPPARCOS satellite</title>
			<authors>Fehrenbach, C.; Duflot, M.; Burnage, R.; Mannone, C.; Peton, A.; Genty, V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 71, no. 2, Nov. 1987, p. 275-295. In French.</journal>
			<date>11/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987A%26AS...71..275F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987Obs...107...12P</bibcode>
			<title>Two-colour diagrams for differentially rotating stars</title>
			<authors>Peacock, T.; Connon-Smith, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Observatory, vol. 107, p. 12-20 (1987)</journal>
			<date>2/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987Obs...107...12P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986IBVS.2943....1S</bibcode>
			<title>Possible Metal-Poor Variable Stars</title>
			<authors>Schuster, W. J.; Nissen, P. E.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 2943, 1.</journal>
			<date>10/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986IBVS.2943....1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986PASP...98..685S</bibcode>
			<title>Twelve additional 'Vega-like' stars</title>
			<authors>Sadakane, K.; Nishida, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 98, July 1986, p. 685-689.</journal>
			<date>7/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986PASP...98..685S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985A&amp;AS...60..365M</bibcode>
			<title>Observed and computed spectral flux distribution of non-supergiant O9-G8 stars. III - Determination of T(eff) for the stars in the Breger Catalogue</title>
			<authors>Morossi, C.; Malagnini, M. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement Series (ISSN 0365-0138), vol. 60, June 1985, p. 365-372. Research supported by the Consiglio Nazionale delle Ricerche, Ministero della Pubblica Istruzione, and Universita di Trieste.</journal>
			<date>6/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985A%26AS...60..365M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984A&amp;A...141..116J</bibcode>
			<title>The Boehm-Vitense gap in the Geneva photometric system</title>
			<authors>Jasniewicz, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 141, no. 1, Dec. 1984, p. 116-126. Research supported by the Swiss National Science Foundation.</journal>
			<date>12/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984A%26A...141..116J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983A&amp;A...123...39P</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric boxes in the four-color system</title>
			<authors>Philip, A. G. D.; Egret, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 123, no. 1, June 1983, p. 39-47.</journal>
			<date>6/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983A%26A...123...39P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1978A&amp;AS...34..441P</bibcode>
			<title>Photoelectric K-line indices for 165 B, A, and F stars.</title>
			<authors>Pedersen, H.; Rudkj&#248;bing, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astron. Astrophys., Suppl. Ser., Vol. 34, p. 441 - 444</journal>
			<date>12/1978</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1978A%26AS...34..441P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1977A&amp;A....61..563H</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of errors in spectral classification by cluster analysis</title>
			<authors>Heck, A.; Albert, A.; Delays, D.; Mersch, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 61, no. 4, Nov. 1977, p. 563-566.</journal>
			<date>11/1977</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1977A%26A....61..563H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1977A&amp;A....59..303G</bibcode>
			<title>Model atmosphere analysis of HR 8799</title>
			<authors>Gehren, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 59, no. 3, Aug. 1977, p. 303-315.  Research supported by the Deutsche Forschungsgemeinschaft.</journal>
			<date>8/1977</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1977A%26A....59..303G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1976ApJS...32....7B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of spectrophotometric scans of stars.</title>
			<authors>Breger, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophys. J., Suppl. Ser., Vol. 32, p. 7 - 87</journal>
			<date>9/1976</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1976ApJS...32....7B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1976A&amp;AS...24...69O</bibcode>
			<title>uvbybeta photometry and MK spectral classification.</title>
			<authors>Oblak, E.; Consid&#232;re, S.; Chareton, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astron. Astrophys., Suppl. Ser., Vol. 24, p. 69 - 88</journal>
			<date>4/1976</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1976A%26AS...24...69O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1974ApJ...192..391H</bibcode>
			<title>Further observations of stars in the intermediate-age open cluster NGC 2477.</title>
			<authors>Hartwick, F. D. A.; Hesser, J. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophys. J., Vol. 192, p. 391 - 404</journal>
			<date>9/1974</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1974ApJ...192..391H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1973ApJ...182..809A</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation and shell spectra among A-type dwarfs.</title>
			<authors>Abt, H. A.; Moyd, K. I.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophys. J., Vol. 182, p. 809 - 816</journal>
			<date>6/1973</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1973ApJ...182..809A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1971ApJS...23..421H</bibcode>
			<title>K-Line Photometry of Southern a Stars</title>
			<authors>Henry, Richard C.; Hesser, James E.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement, vol. 23, p.421 (1971)</journal>
			<date>12/1971</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1971ApJS...23..421H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1970ApJ...160.1129B</bibcode>
			<title>Effective Temperatures, Gravities, and the Mass Determination of a and F Stars</title>
			<authors>Breger, Michel; Kuhi, Leonard V.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 160, p.1129</journal>
			<date>6/1970</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1970ApJ...160.1129B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1970ApJS...19..281B</bibcode>
			<title>Spectral Classification of a and F Stars</title>
			<authors>Barry, Don C.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement, vol. 19, p.281 (1970)</journal>
			<date>1/1970</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1970ApJS...19..281B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1970A&amp;AS....1....7B</bibcode>
			<title>Classification des spectres de 112 d'&#233;toiles A et F dont 89 d'&#233;toiles AM</title>
			<authors>Bertaud, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics Supplement Series Vol. 1, No. 1, p.7</journal>
			<date>1/1970</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1970A%26AS....1....7B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1969ApJS...19...79B</bibcode>
			<title>Short-Period Variability of b, a, and F Stars. III. a Survey of Delta Scuti Variable Stars</title>
			<authors>Breger, Michel</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement, vol. 19, p.79 (1969)</journal>
			<date>12/1969</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1969ApJS...19...79B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1968AJ.....73...84B</bibcode>
			<title>UBV and narrow-band UVBY photometry of bright stars.</title>
			<authors>Breger, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astron. J., 73, 84-85 (1968)</journal>
			<date>3/1968</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1968AJ.....73...84B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
