<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Sci...337..556C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-36: A Pair of Planets with Neighboring Orbits and Dissimilar Densities</title>
			<authors>Carter, Joshua A.; Agol, Eric; Chaplin, William J.; Basu, Sarbani; Bedding, Timothy R.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Deck, Katherine M.; Elsworth, Yvonne; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Hale, Steven J.; Handberg, Rasmus; Hekker, Saskia; Holman, Matthew J.; Huber, Daniel; Karoff, Christopher; Kawaler, Steven D.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Lissauer, Jack J.; Lopez, Eric D.; Lund, Mikkel N.; Lundkvist, Mia; Metcalfe, Travis S.; Miglio, Andrea; Rogers, Leslie A.; Stello, Dennis; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer; Howard, Andrew W.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Klaus, Todd; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Steffen, Jason H.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 337, Issue 6094, pp. 556- (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Sci...337..556C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...755...41S</bibcode>
			<title>Vaporization of the Earth: Application to Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Schaefer, Laura; Lodders, Katharina; Fegley, Bruce</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 755, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...755...41S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..113F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. II. Confirmation of Two Multiplanet Systems via a Non-parametric Correlation Analysis</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Steffen, Jason H.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fressin, Francois; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Moorhead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Rowe, Jason F.; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Burke, Christopher J.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Charbonneau, David; Clarke, Bruce D.; Cochran, William D.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Everett, Mark E.; Fischer, Debra A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ron L.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Haas, Michael R.; Horch, Elliott; Howell, Steve B.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Isaacson, Howard; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCauliff, Sean; Mullally, Fergal R.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa; Shporer, Avi; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Wohler, Bill; the Kepler Science Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 113 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750..113F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749...15G</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-20: A Sun-like Star with Three Sub-Neptune Exoplanets and Two Earth-size Candidates</title>
			<authors>Gautier, Thomas N., III; Charbonneau, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Francois; Rogers, Leslie A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ciardi, David R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Howell, Steve B.; Horch, Elliott P.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Borucki, William J.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Silverio, Kathryn; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Still, Martin; Stumpe, Martin C.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 1, article id. 15 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749...15G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....7C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-18b, c, and d: A System of Three Planets Confirmed by Transit Timing Variations, Light Curve Validation, Warm-Spitzer Photometry, and Radial Velocity Measurements</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran ois; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steve B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Borucki, William. J.; Koch, David G.; Winn, Joshua N.; Welsh, William F.; Uddin, Kamal; Tenenbaum, Peter; Still, M.; Seager, Sara; Quinn, Samuel N.; Mullally, F.; Miller, Neil; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Lucas, Phillip; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Knutson, Heather; Kinemuchi, K.; Johnson, John A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew; Horch, Elliott; Holman, Matthew J.; Henze, Christopher E.; Haas, Michael R.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Ford, Eric B.; Fischer, Debra A.; Everett, Mark; Endl, Michael; Demory, Brice-Oliver; Deming, Drake; Charbonneau, David; Caldwell, Douglas; Buchhave, Lars; Brown, Timothy M.; Batalha, Natalie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....7C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....2F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. I. Statistical Analysis of the First Four Months</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rowe, Jason F.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Carter, Joshua A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Steffen, Jason H.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCauliff, Sean; Mullally, Fergal R.; Quintana, Elisa; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....2F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534A..26V</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic characterization of the atmospheres of potentially habitable planets: GL 581 d as a model case study</title>
			<authors>von Paris, P.; Cabrera, J.; Godolt, M.; Grenfell, J. L.; Hedelt, P.; Rauer, H.; Schreier, F.; Stracke, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.A26</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534A..26V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A.136H</bibcode>
			<title>Venus transit 2004: Illustrating the capability of exoplanet transmission spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Hedelt, P.; Alonso, R.; Brown, T.; Collados Vera, M.; Rauer, H.; Schleicher, H.; Schmidt, W.; Schreier, F.; Titz, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A136</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A.136H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737L..18W</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth Transiting a Naked-eye Star</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Dawson, Rebekah I.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Holman, Matthew J.; Kallinger, Thomas; Kuschnig, Rainer; Sasselov, Dimitar; Dragomir, Diana; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Rucinski, Slavek; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 737, Issue 1, article id. L18 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737L..18W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, Sren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...24R</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: Beyond the stars</title>
			<authors>Reich, Eugenie Samuel</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 24-26 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...24R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, Vol. 29, p. 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...756..186S</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. VI. Potentially Interesting Candidate Systems from Fourier-based Statistical Tests</title>
			<authors>Steffen, Jason H.; Ford, Eric B.; Rowe, Jason F.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Holman, Matthew J.; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Ciardi, David R.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Koch, David G.; Prsa, Andrej; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Seader, Shawn; Twicken, Joseph D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 756, Issue 2, article id. 186 (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...756..186S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...756..185F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. V. Transit Timing Variation Candidates in the First Sixteen Months from Polynomial Models</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Ragozzine, Darin; Rowe, Jason F.; Steffen, Jason H.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kinemuchi, Karen; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Uddin, Kamal; Welsh, William</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 756, Issue 2, article id. 185 (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...756..185F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Sci...337..556C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-36: A Pair of Planets with Neighboring Orbits and Dissimilar Densities</title>
			<authors>Carter, Joshua A.; Agol, Eric; Chaplin, William J.; Basu, Sarbani; Bedding, Timothy R.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Deck, Katherine M.; Elsworth, Yvonne; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Hale, Steven J.; Handberg, Rasmus; Hekker, Saskia; Holman, Matthew J.; Huber, Daniel; Karoff, Christopher; Kawaler, Steven D.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Lissauer, Jack J.; Lopez, Eric D.; Lund, Mikkel N.; Lundkvist, Mia; Metcalfe, Travis S.; Miglio, Andrea; Rogers, Leslie A.; Stello, Dennis; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer; Howard, Andrew W.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Klaus, Todd; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Steffen, Jason H.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 337, Issue 6094, pp. 556- (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Sci...337..556C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJS..201...15H</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Occurrence within 0.25 AU of Solar-type Stars from Kepler</title>
			<authors>Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Cochran, William D.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Torres, Guillermo; Brown, Timothy M.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Ciardi, David; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael R.; Howell, Steve B.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Seager, Sara; Rogers, Leslie; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Steffen, Jason H.; Basri, Gibor S.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie; Clarke, Bruce; Dupree, Andrea; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fischer, Debra A.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Tarter, Jill; Girouard, Forrest R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Johnson, John Asher; Klaus, Todd C.; Machalek, Pavel; Moorhead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Twicken, Joseph D.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Lucas, Philip W.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Welsh, William F.; Boss, Alan; Devore, Edna; Gould, Alan; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Morris, Robert L.; Prsa, Andrej; Morton, Timothy D.; Still, Martin; Thompson, Susan E.; Mullally, Fergal; Endl, Michael; MacQueen, Phillip J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 201, Issue 2, article id. 15 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJS..201...15H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...755L..21D</bibcode>
			<title>Rapid Dynamical Chaos in an Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Deck, Katherine M.; Holman, Matthew J.; Agol, Eric; Carter, Joshua A.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 755, Issue 1, article id. L21 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...755L..21D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754...57B</bibcode>
			<title>Interactions between Moderate- and Long-period Giant Planets: Scattering Experiments for Systems in Isolation and with Stellar Flybys</title>
			<authors>Boley, Aaron C.; Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 754, Issue 1, article id. 57 (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754...57B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...753...66I</bibcode>
			<title>In Situ Accretion of Hydrogen-rich Atmospheres on Short-period Super-Earths: Implications for the Kepler-11 Planets</title>
			<authors>Ikoma, M.; Hori, Y.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 753, Issue 1, article id. 66 (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...753...66I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...543A..52T</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for nine planets in the HD 10180 system</title>
			<authors>Tuomi, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 543, id.A52</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...543A..52T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.486..375B</bibcode>
			<title>An abundance of small exoplanets around stars with a wide range of metallicities</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Johansen, Anders; Bizzarro, Martin; Torres, Guillermo; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brugamyer, Erik; Caldwell, Caroline; Bryson, Stephen T.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Ford, Eric B.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Hansen, Terese; Isaacson, Howard; Laird, John B.; Lucas, Philip W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Morse, Jon A.; Robertson, Paul; Shporer, Avi; Stefanik, Robert P.; Still, Martin; Quinn, Samuel N.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 486, Issue 7403, pp. 375-377 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.486..375B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...72D</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation between the Eclipse Depths of Kepler Gas Giant Candidates and the Metallicities of Their Parent Stars</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 72 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...72D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751..158H</bibcode>
			<title>Migration Then Assembly: Formation of Neptune-mass Planets inside 1 AU</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Murray, Norm</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. 158 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...751..158H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewA...17..438D</bibcode>
			<title>A revised orbital ephemeris for HAT-P-9b</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, Jason A.; Close, Laird M.; Scuderi, Louis J.; Turner, Jake; Stephenson, Peter C.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 17, Issue 4, p. 438-441.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012NewA...17..438D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.2024J</bibcode>
			<title>The coronal X-ray-age relation and its implications for the evaporation of exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Alan P.; Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 3, pp. 2024-2043.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.2024J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751...23F</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting Planets in Kepler Multi-planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Fang, Julia; Margot, Jean-Luc</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 1, article id. 23 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...751...23F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..148W</bibcode>
			<title>The Effect of Population-wide Mass-to-radius Relationships on the Interpretation of Kepler and HARPS Super-Earth Occurrence Rates</title>
			<authors>Wolfgang, Angie; Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 148 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750..148W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..114F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. IV. Confirmation of Four Multiple-planet Systems by Simple Physical Models</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Rowe, Jason F.; Carter, Joshua A.; Moorhead, Althea V.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fischer, Debra; Fressin, Francois; Geary, John; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Lissauer, Jack J.; Lucas, Philip; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Mazeh, Tsevi; McCauliff, Sean; Quinn, Samuel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 114 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750..114F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..112L</bibcode>
			<title>Almost All of Kepler's Multiple-planet Candidates Are Planets</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Adams, Elisabeth; Buchhave, Lars A.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Fressin, Francois; Geary, John; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Koch, David G.; Morehead, Robert C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Seader, Shawn E.; Tanenbaum, Peter G.; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750..112L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749...15G</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-20: A Sun-like Star with Three Sub-Neptune Exoplanets and Two Earth-size Candidates</title>
			<authors>Gautier, Thomas N., III; Charbonneau, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Francois; Rogers, Leslie A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ciardi, David R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Howell, Steve B.; Horch, Elliott P.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Borucki, William J.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Silverio, Kathryn; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Still, Martin; Stumpe, Martin C.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 1, article id. 15 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749...15G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...94T</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Multi-planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Tremaine, Scott; Dong, Subo</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 4, article id. 94 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143...94T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..62O</bibcode>
			<title>Transit-timing measurements with the model-independent barycenter method: application to the LHS 6343 system</title>
			<authors>Oshagh, M.; Bou, G.; Haghighipour, N.; Montalto, M.; Figueira, P.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A62</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..62O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJS..199...24T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Potential Transit Signals in the First Three Quarters of Kepler Mission Data</title>
			<authors>Tenenbaum, Peter; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Seader, Shawn; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Quintana, Elisa V.; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Stumpe, Martin C.; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Borucki, William J.; Cote, Miles T.; Haas, Michael R.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Girouard, Forrest R.; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Wohler, Bill; Batalha, Natalie M.; Barclay, Thomas; Nickerson, James E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 199, Issue 1, article id. 24 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJS..199...24T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...748...22H</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Monitoring in the South (TraMoS) Project: Discarding Transit Timing Variations in WASP-5b</title>
			<authors>Hoyer, S.; Rojo, P.; Lpez-Morales, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 748, Issue 1, article id. 22 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...748...22H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..28G</bibcode>
			<title>Improved precision on the radius of the nearby super-Earth 55 Cnc e</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Demory, B.-O.; Benneke, B.; Valencia, D.; Deming, D.; Seager, S.; Lovis, Ch.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A28</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..28G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.482..166Q</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planets: An Earth-sized duo</title>
			<authors>Queloz, Didier</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 482, Issue 7384, pp. 166-167 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.482..166Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.420.1630P</bibcode>
			<title>Light-curve modelling for mutual transits</title>
			<authors>Pl, Andrs.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 420, Issue 2, pp. 1630-1635.</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.420.1630P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.419.2737H</bibcode>
			<title>Global models of planetary system formation in radiatively-inefficient protoplanetary discs</title>
			<authors>Hellary, Phil; Nelson, Richard P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 419, Issue 4, pp. 2737-2757.</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.419.2737H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745..120B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-22b: A 2.4 Earth-radius Planet in the Habitable Zone of a Sun-like Star</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Batalha, Natalie; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason; Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Kaltenegger, Lisa; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Steffen, Jason H.; Mullally, Fergal; Still, Martin; Tarter, Jill; Ballard, Sarah; Buchhave, Lars A.; Carter, Josh; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Demory, Brice-Olivier; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Dressing, Courtney; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fischer, Debra; Haas, Michael R.; Henze, Christopher; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Johnson, John Asher; Klaus, Todd; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Barclay, Thomas; Li, Jie; Meibom, Sren; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Robertson, Paul; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Welsh, William F.; Basu, Sarbani; Chaplin, William; Miglio, Andrea; Kawaler, Steven D.; Arentoft, Torben; Stello, Dennis; Metcalfe, Travis S.; Verner, Graham A.; Karoff, Christoffer; Lundkvist, Mia; Lund, Mikkel N.; Handberg, Rasmus; Elsworth, Yvonne; Hekker, Saskia; Huber, Daniel; Bedding, Timothy R.; Rapin, William</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 2, article id. 120 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745..120B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A.145D</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XX. CoRoT-20b: A very high density, high eccentricity transiting giant planet</title>
			<authors>Deleuil, M.; Bonomo, A. S.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Erikson, A.; Bouchy, F.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J.-M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord, P.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carpano, S.; Cavarroc, C.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Damiani, C.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Fridlund, M.; Hbrard, G.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Jorda, L.; Lger, A.; Lammer, H.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Parviainen, H.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rodrguez, A.; Rouan, D.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tal-Or, L.; Tingley, B.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A145</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A.145D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A..95M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal phase curves of nontransiting terrestrial exoplanets. II. Characterizing airless planets</title>
			<authors>Maurin, A. S.; Selsis, F.; Hersant, F.; Belu, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A95</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A..95M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745....2L</bibcode>
			<title>Interaction of Close-in Planets with the Magnetosphere of Their Host Stars. II. Super-Earths as Unipolar Inductors and Their Orbital Evolution</title>
			<authors>Laine, Randy O.; Lin, Douglas N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745....2L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418.1335J</bibcode>
			<title>Terrestrial planet formation in inclined systems: application to the OGLE-2006-BLG-109L system</title>
			<authors>Jin, Sheng; Ji, Jianghui</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 418, Issue 2, pp. 1335-1345.</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.418.1335J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418.1043Q</bibcode>
			<title>Three-body resonance overlap in closely spaced multiple-planet systems</title>
			<authors>Quillen, Alice C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 418, Issue 2, pp. 1043-1054.</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.418.1043Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...75H</bibcode>
			<title>The Mass of CoRoT-7b</title>
			<authors>Hatzes, Artie P.; Fridlund, Malcolm; Nachmani, Gil; Mazeh, Tsevi; Valencia, Diana; Hbrard, Guillaume; Carone, Ludmila; Ptzold, Martin; Udry, Stephane; Bouchy, Francois; Deleuil, Magali; Moutou, Claire; Barge, Pierre; Bord , Pascal; Deeg, Hans; Tingley, Brandon; Dvorak, Rudolf; Gandolfi, Davide; Ferraz-Mello, Sylvio; Wuchterl, Gnther; Guenther, Eike; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike; Erikson, Anders; Cabrera, Juan; Csizmadia, Szilard; Lger, Alain; Lammer, Helmut; Weingrill, Jrg; Queloz, Didier; Alonso, Roi; Rouan, Daniel; Schneider, Jean</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...75H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...41K</bibcode>
			<title>Climate Instability on Tidally Locked Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Kite, Edwin S.; Gaidos, Eric; Manga, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...41K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...536L...9T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of transit timing variations in excess of one hour in the Kepler multi-planet candidate system KOI 806 with the GTC</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Palle, E.; Parviainen, H.; Deeg, H. J.; Zapatero Osorio, M. R.; Cabrera-Lavers, A.; Belmonte, J. A.; Rodriguez, P. M.; Murgas, F.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 536, id.L9</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...536L...9T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...536A..70S</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. IV. KOI-196b: a non-inflated hot Jupiter with a high albedo</title>
			<authors>Santerne, A.; Bonomo, A. S.; Hbrard, G.; Deleuil, M.; Moutou, C.; Almenara, J.-M.; Bouchy, F.; Daz, R. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 536, id.A70</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...536A..70S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...10B</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Misalignment of KOI-13.01 from Its Gravity-darkened Kepler Transit Lightcurve</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.; Linscott, Ethan; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...10B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....9F</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Atmospheric Characterization of Giant Planet Kepler-12b: An Inflated Radius Outlier</title>
			<authors>Fortney, Jonathan J.; Demory, Brice-Olivier; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Rowe, Jason; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Buchhave, Lars A.; Ciardi, David; Gautier, Thomas N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Nutzman, Philip; Jenkins, Jon M.; Howard, Andrew; Charbonneau, David; Knutson, Heather A.; Howell, Steve B.; Everett, Mark; Fressin, Franois; Deming, Drake; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Latham, David W.; Miller, Neil; Seager, Sara; Fischer, Debra A.; Koch, David; Lissauer, Jack J.; Haas, Michael R.; Still, Martin; Lucas, Philip; Gillon, Michael; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 9 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....9F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....8L</bibcode>
			<title>Architecture and Dynamics of Kepler's Candidate Multiple Transiting Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Steffen, Jason H.; Ford, Eric B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Shporer, Avi; Holman, Matthew J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David; Dunham, Edward W.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Howell, Steve B.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Morehead, Robert C.; Sasselov, Dimitar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 8 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....8L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....7C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-18b, c, and d: A System of Three Planets Confirmed by Transit Timing Variations, Light Curve Validation, Warm-Spitzer Photometry, and Radial Velocity Measurements</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran ois; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steve B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Borucki, William. J.; Koch, David G.; Winn, Joshua N.; Welsh, William F.; Uddin, Kamal; Tenenbaum, Peter; Still, M.; Seager, Sara; Quinn, Samuel N.; Mullally, F.; Miller, Neil; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Lucas, Phillip; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Knutson, Heather; Kinemuchi, K.; Johnson, John A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew; Horch, Elliott; Holman, Matthew J.; Henze, Christopher E.; Haas, Michael R.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Ford, Eric B.; Fischer, Debra A.; Everett, Mark; Endl, Michael; Demory, Brice-Oliver; Deming, Drake; Charbonneau, David; Caldwell, Douglas; Buchhave, Lars; Brown, Timothy M.; Batalha, Natalie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....7C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....5F</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-10 c: a 2.2 Earth Radius Transiting Planet in a Multiple System</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Franois; Torres, Guillermo; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Charbonneau, David; Batalha, Natalie M.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Allen, Christopher; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Deming, Drake; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Knutson, Heather; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Uddin, Kamal</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 5 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....5F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....2F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. I. Statistical Analysis of the First Four Months</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rowe, Jason F.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Carter, Joshua A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Steffen, Jason H.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCauliff, Sean; Mullally, Fergal R.; Quintana, Elisa; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....2F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417L..31S</bibcode>
			<title>The architecture of the hierarchical triple star KOI 928 from eclipse timing variations seen in Kepler photometry</title>
			<authors>Steffen, J. H.; Quinn, S. N.; Borucki, W. J.; Brugamyer, E.; Bryson, S. T.; Buchhave, L. A.; Cochran, W. D.; Endl, M.; Fabrycky, D. C.; Ford, E. B.; Holman, M. J.; Jenkins, J.; Koch, D.; Latham, D. W.; MacQueen, P.; Mullally, F.; Prsa, A.; Ragozzine, D.; Rowe, J. F.; Sanderfer, D. T.; Seader, S. E.; Short, D.; Shporer, A.; Thompson, S. E.; Torres, G.; Twicken, J. D.; Welsh, W. F.; Windmiller, G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 417, Issue 1, pp. L31-L35.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417L..31S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417L..16G</bibcode>
			<title>Potential biases in the detection of planetary systems with large transit timing variations</title>
			<authors>Garca-Melendo, E.; Lpez-Morales, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 417, Issue 1, pp. L16-L20.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417L..16G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740...61K</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Phase Variations of the 55 Cancri System</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.; Ciardi, David R.; Dragomir, Diana; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 740, Issue 2, article id. 61 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740...61K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...739...31L</bibcode>
			<title>Theory of Secular Chaos and Mercury's Orbit</title>
			<authors>Lithwick, Yoram; Wu, Yanqin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 739, Issue 1, article id. 31 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...739...31L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..177S</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Exoplanet Candidate Host Stars Are Preferentially Metal Rich</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.; Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 177 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..177S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738...59R</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and Structure of Low-density exo-Neptunes</title>
			<authors>Rogers, Leslie A.; Bodenheimer, Peter; Lissauer, Jack J.; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738...59R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737L..18W</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth Transiting a Naked-eye Star</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Dawson, Rebekah I.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Holman, Matthew J.; Kallinger, Thomas; Kuschnig, Rainer; Sasselov, Dimitar; Dragomir, Diana; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Rucinski, Slavek; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 737, Issue 1, article id. L18 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737L..18W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..24N</bibcode>
			<title>TASTE II. A new observational study of transit time variations in HAT-P-13b</title>
			<authors>Nascimbeni, V.; Piotto, G.; Bedin, L. R.; Damasso, M.; Malavolta, L.; Borsato, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A24</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..24N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, Sren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AN....332..547N</bibcode>
			<title>The Young Exoplanet Transit Initiative (YETI)</title>
			<authors>Neuhuser, R.; Errmann, R.; Berndt, A.; Maciejewski, G.; Takahashi, H.; Chen, W. P.; Dimitrov, D. P.; Pribulla, T.; Nikogossian, E. H.; Jensen, E. L. N.; Marschall, L.; Wu, Z.-Y.; Kellerer, A.; Walter, F. M.; Briceo, C.; Chini, R.; Fernandez, M.; Raetz, St.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Quinn, S. N.; Niedzielski, A.; Bukowiecki, L.; Nowak, G.; Tomov, T.; Tachihara, K.; Hu, S. C.-L.; Hung, L. W.; Kjurkchieva, D. P.; Radeva, V. S.; Mihov, B. M.; Slavcheva-Mihova, L.; Bozhinova, I. N.; Budaj, J.; Vanko, M.; Kundra, E.; Hamblek, L.; Krushevska, V.; Movsessian, T.; Harutyunyan, H.; Downes, J. J.; Hernandez, J.; Hoffmeister, V. H.; Cohen, D. H.; Abel, I.; Ahmad, R.; Chapman, S.; Eckert, S.; Goodman, J.; Guerard, A.; Kim, H. M.; Koontharana, A.; Sokol, J.; Trinh, J.; Wang, Y.; Zhou, X.; Redmer, R.; Kramm, U.; Nettelmann, N.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, J.; Moualla, M.; Ginski, C.; Marka, C.; Adam, C.; Seeliger, M.; Baar, S.; Roell, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Trepl, L.; Eisenbei, T.; Fiedler, S.; Tetzlaff, N.; Schmidt, E.; Hohle, M. M.; Kitze, M.; Chakrova, N.; Grfe, C.; Schreyer, K.; Hambaryan, V. V.; Broeg, C. H.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Pandey, A. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.332, Issue 6, p.547</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AN....332..547N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..24L</bibcode>
			<title>A First Comparison of Kepler Planet Candidates in Single and Multiple Systems</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Wohler, Bill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..24L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...24R</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: Beyond the stars</title>
			<authors>Reich, Eugenie Samuel</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 24-26 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...24R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, Vol. 29, p. 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
