<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...13E</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-15b: A Hot Jupiter Enriched in Heavy Elements and the First Kepler Mission Planet Confirmed with the Hobby-Eberly Telescope</title>
			<authors>Endl, Michael; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Cochran, William D.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Rowe, Jason; Lucas, Phillip; Isaacson, Howard; Bryson, Steve; Howell, Steve B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Hansen, Terese; Borucki, William J.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Demory, Brice-Olivier; Everett, Mark; Ford, Eric B.; Haas, Michael R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Horch, Elliott; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Machalek, Pavel; Still, Martin; Welsh, William F.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Seader, Shawn E.; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 13 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...13E</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...13E</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-15b: A Hot Jupiter Enriched in Heavy Elements and the First Kepler Mission Planet Confirmed with the Hobby-Eberly Telescope</title>
			<authors>Endl, Michael; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Cochran, William D.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Rowe, Jason; Lucas, Phillip; Isaacson, Howard; Bryson, Steve; Howell, Steve B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Hansen, Terese; Borucki, William J.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Demory, Brice-Olivier; Everett, Mark; Ford, Eric B.; Haas, Michael R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Horch, Elliott; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Machalek, Pavel; Still, Martin; Welsh, William F.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Seader, Shawn E.; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 13 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...13E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....2F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. I. Statistical Analysis of the First Four Months</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rowe, Jason F.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Carter, Joshua A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Steffen, Jason H.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCauliff, Sean; Mullally, Fergal R.; Quintana, Elisa; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....2F</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
