<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....3B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-14b: A Massive Hot Jupiter Transiting an F Star in a Close Visual Binary</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Carter, Joshua A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Charbonneau, David B.; Ciardi, David R.; Kulesa, Craig; Dupree, Andrea K.; Fischer, Debra A.; Fressin, Franois; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCarthy, Donald W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Deming, Drake; Dunham, Edward W.; Everett, Mark; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Geary, John C.; Girouard, Forrest R.; Haas, Michael R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Horch, Elliott; Klaus, Todd C.; Knutson, Heather A.; Koch, David G.; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Lissauer, Jack J.; Machalek, Pavel; Mullally, Fergal; Still, Martin D.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Seager, Sara; Thompson, Susan E.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 3 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....3B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....144...42A</bibcode>
			<title>Adaptive Optics Images of Kepler Objects of Interest</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; Ciardi, D. R.; Dupree, A. K.; Gautier, T. N., III; Kulesa, C.; McCarthy, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 144, Issue 2, article id. 42 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....144...42A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.486..375B</bibcode>
			<title>An abundance of small exoplanets around stars with a wide range of metallicities</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Johansen, Anders; Bizzarro, Martin; Torres, Guillermo; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brugamyer, Erik; Caldwell, Caroline; Bryson, Stephen T.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Ford, Eric B.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Hansen, Terese; Isaacson, Howard; Laird, John B.; Lucas, Philip W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Morse, Jon A.; Robertson, Paul; Shporer, Avi; Stefanik, Robert P.; Still, Martin; Quinn, Samuel N.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 486, Issue 7403, pp. 375-377 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.486..375B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...72D</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation between the Eclipse Depths of Kepler Gas Giant Candidates and the Metallicities of Their Parent Stars</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 72 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...72D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749...15G</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-20: A Sun-like Star with Three Sub-Neptune Exoplanets and Two Earth-size Candidates</title>
			<authors>Gautier, Thomas N., III; Charbonneau, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Francois; Rogers, Leslie A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ciardi, David R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Howell, Steve B.; Horch, Elliott P.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Borucki, William J.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Silverio, Kathryn; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Still, Martin; Stumpe, Martin C.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 1, article id. 15 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749...15G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....3B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-14b: A Massive Hot Jupiter Transiting an F Star in a Close Visual Binary</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Carter, Joshua A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Charbonneau, David B.; Ciardi, David R.; Kulesa, Craig; Dupree, Andrea K.; Fischer, Debra A.; Fressin, Franois; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCarthy, Donald W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Deming, Drake; Dunham, Edward W.; Everett, Mark; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Geary, John C.; Girouard, Forrest R.; Haas, Michael R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Horch, Elliott; Klaus, Todd C.; Knutson, Heather A.; Koch, David G.; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Lissauer, Jack J.; Machalek, Pavel; Mullally, Fergal; Still, Martin D.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Seager, Sara; Thompson, Susan E.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 3 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....3B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, Sren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
