<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.482..195F</bibcode>
			<title>Two Earth-sized planets orbiting Kepler-20</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Rowe, Jason F.; Charbonneau, David; Rogers, Leslie A.; Ballard, Sarah; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Ciardi, David R.; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Dressing, Courtney D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howard, Andrew; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Barclay, Thomas; Mullally, Fergal; Seader, Shawn E.; Still, Martin; Twicken, Joseph D.; Thompson, Susan E.; Uddin, Kamal</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 482, Issue 7384, pp. 195-198 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.482..195F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....7C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-18b, c, and d: A System of Three Planets Confirmed by Transit Timing Variations, Light Curve Validation, Warm-Spitzer Photometry, and Radial Velocity Measurements</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran&#231; ois; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steve B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Borucki, William. J.; Koch, David G.; Winn, Joshua N.; Welsh, William F.; Uddin, Kamal; Tenenbaum, Peter; Still, M.; Seager, Sara; Quinn, Samuel N.; Mullally, F.; Miller, Neil; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Lucas, Phillip; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Knutson, Heather; Kinemuchi, K.; Johnson, John A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew; Horch, Elliott; Holman, Matthew J.; Henze, Christopher E.; Haas, Michael R.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Ford, Eric B.; Fischer, Debra A.; Everett, Mark; Endl, Michael; Demory, Brice-Oliver; Deming, Drake; Charbonneau, David; Caldwell, Douglas; Buchhave, Lars; Brown, Timothy M.; Batalha, Natalie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....7C</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...536L...9T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of transit timing variations in excess of one hour in the Kepler multi-planet candidate system KOI 806 with the GTC</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Palle, E.; Parviainen, H.; Deeg, H. J.; Zapatero Osorio, M. R.; Cabrera-Lavers, A.; Belmonte, J. A.; Rodriguez, P. M.; Murgas, F.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 536, id.L9</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...536L...9T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....7C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-18b, c, and d: A System of Three Planets Confirmed by Transit Timing Variations, Light Curve Validation, Warm-Spitzer Photometry, and Radial Velocity Measurements</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran&#231; ois; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steve B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Borucki, William. J.; Koch, David G.; Winn, Joshua N.; Welsh, William F.; Uddin, Kamal; Tenenbaum, Peter; Still, M.; Seager, Sara; Quinn, Samuel N.; Mullally, F.; Miller, Neil; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Lucas, Phillip; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Knutson, Heather; Kinemuchi, K.; Johnson, John A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew; Horch, Elliott; Holman, Matthew J.; Henze, Christopher E.; Haas, Michael R.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Ford, Eric B.; Fischer, Debra A.; Everett, Mark; Endl, Michael; Demory, Brice-Oliver; Deming, Drake; Charbonneau, David; Caldwell, Douglas; Buchhave, Lars; Brown, Timothy M.; Batalha, Natalie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....7C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....6G</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Mission Stellar and Instrument Noise Properties</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; Chaplin, William J.; Dunham, Edward W.; Argabright, Vic S.; Borucki, William J.; Basri, Gibor; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buzasi, Derek L.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Elsworth, Yvonne P.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Miglio, Andrea; van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Welsh, William F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 6 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....6G</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
