<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752....7H</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra of Terrestrial Exoplanet Surfaces</title>
			<authors>Hu, Renyu; Ehlmann, Bethany L.; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752....7H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745..120B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-22b: A 2.4 Earth-radius Planet in the Habitable Zone of a Sun-like Star</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Batalha, Natalie; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason; Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Kaltenegger, Lisa; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Steffen, Jason H.; Mullally, Fergal; Still, Martin; Tarter, Jill; Ballard, Sarah; Buchhave, Lars A.; Carter, Josh; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Demory, Brice-Olivier; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Dressing, Courtney; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fischer, Debra; Haas, Michael R.; Henze, Christopher; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Johnson, John Asher; Klaus, Todd; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Barclay, Thomas; Li, Jie; Meibom, Sren; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Robertson, Paul; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Welsh, William F.; Basu, Sarbani; Chaplin, William; Miglio, Andrea; Kawaler, Steven D.; Arentoft, Torben; Stello, Dennis; Metcalfe, Travis S.; Verner, Graham A.; Karoff, Christoffer; Lundkvist, Mia; Lund, Mikkel N.; Handberg, Rasmus; Elsworth, Yvonne; Hekker, Saskia; Huber, Daniel; Bedding, Timothy R.; Rapin, William</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 2, article id. 120 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745..120B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.486..375B</bibcode>
			<title>An abundance of small exoplanets around stars with a wide range of metallicities</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Johansen, Anders; Bizzarro, Martin; Torres, Guillermo; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brugamyer, Erik; Caldwell, Caroline; Bryson, Stephen T.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Ford, Eric B.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Hansen, Terese; Isaacson, Howard; Laird, John B.; Lucas, Philip W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Morse, Jon A.; Robertson, Paul; Shporer, Avi; Stefanik, Robert P.; Still, Martin; Quinn, Samuel N.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 486, Issue 7403, pp. 375-377 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.486..375B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...72D</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation between the Eclipse Depths of Kepler Gas Giant Candidates and the Metallicities of Their Parent Stars</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 72 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...72D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..114F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. IV. Confirmation of Four Multiple-planet Systems by Simple Physical Models</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Rowe, Jason F.; Carter, Joshua A.; Moorhead, Althea V.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fischer, Debra; Fressin, Francois; Geary, John; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Lissauer, Jack J.; Lucas, Philip; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Mazeh, Tsevi; McCauliff, Sean; Quinn, Samuel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 114 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750..114F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745..120B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-22b: A 2.4 Earth-radius Planet in the Habitable Zone of a Sun-like Star</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Batalha, Natalie; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason; Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Kaltenegger, Lisa; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Steffen, Jason H.; Mullally, Fergal; Still, Martin; Tarter, Jill; Ballard, Sarah; Buchhave, Lars A.; Carter, Josh; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Demory, Brice-Olivier; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Dressing, Courtney; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fischer, Debra; Haas, Michael R.; Henze, Christopher; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Johnson, John Asher; Klaus, Todd; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Barclay, Thomas; Li, Jie; Meibom, Sren; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Robertson, Paul; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Welsh, William F.; Basu, Sarbani; Chaplin, William; Miglio, Andrea; Kawaler, Steven D.; Arentoft, Torben; Stello, Dennis; Metcalfe, Travis S.; Verner, Graham A.; Karoff, Christoffer; Lundkvist, Mia; Lund, Mikkel N.; Handberg, Rasmus; Elsworth, Yvonne; Hekker, Saskia; Huber, Daniel; Bedding, Timothy R.; Rapin, William</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 2, article id. 120 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745..120B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, Sren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
