<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..114F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. IV. Confirmation of Four Multiple-planet Systems by Simple Physical Models</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Rowe, Jason F.; Carter, Joshua A.; Moorhead, Althea V.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fischer, Debra; Fressin, Francois; Geary, John; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Lissauer, Jack J.; Lucas, Philip; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Mazeh, Tsevi; McCauliff, Sean; Quinn, Samuel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 114 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...750..114F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..113F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. II. Confirmation of Two Multiplanet Systems via a Non-parametric Correlation Analysis</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Steffen, Jason H.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fressin, Francois; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Moorhead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Rowe, Jason F.; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Burke, Christopher J.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Charbonneau, David; Clarke, Bruce D.; Cochran, William D.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Everett, Mark E.; Fischer, Debra A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ron L.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Haas, Michael R.; Horch, Elliott; Howell, Steve B.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Isaacson, Howard; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCauliff, Sean; Mullally, Fergal R.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa; Shporer, Avi; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Wohler, Bill; the Kepler Science Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 113 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...750..113F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...536L...9T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of transit timing variations in excess of one hour in the Kepler multi-planet candidate system KOI 806 with the GTC</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Palle, E.; Parviainen, H.; Deeg, H. J.; Zapatero Osorio, M. R.; Cabrera-Lavers, A.; Belmonte, J. A.; Rodriguez, P. M.; Murgas, F.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 536, id.L9</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...536L...9T</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..114F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. IV. Confirmation of Four Multiple-planet Systems by Simple Physical Models</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Rowe, Jason F.; Carter, Joshua A.; Moorhead, Althea V.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fischer, Debra; Fressin, Francois; Geary, John; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Lissauer, Jack J.; Lucas, Philip; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Mazeh, Tsevi; McCauliff, Sean; Quinn, Samuel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 114 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...750..114F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...536L...9T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of transit timing variations in excess of one hour in the Kepler multi-planet candidate system KOI 806 with the GTC</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Palle, E.; Parviainen, H.; Deeg, H. J.; Zapatero Osorio, M. R.; Cabrera-Lavers, A.; Belmonte, J. A.; Rodriguez, P. M.; Murgas, F.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 536, id.L9</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...536L...9T</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
