<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...81F</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Infrared Observations and Independent Validation of the Transiting Super-Earth CoRoT-7 b</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Pont, Frederic; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Mazeh, Tsevi; Aigrain, Suzanne; Fridlund, Malcolm; Henze, Christopher E.; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 81 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...745...81F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749...15G</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-20: A Sun-like Star with Three Sub-Neptune Exoplanets and Two Earth-size Candidates</title>
			<authors>Gautier, Thomas N., III; Charbonneau, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Francois; Rogers, Leslie A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ciardi, David R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Howell, Steve B.; Horch, Elliott P.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Borucki, William J.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Silverio, Kathryn; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Still, Martin; Stumpe, Martin C.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 1, article id. 15 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...749...15G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..62O</bibcode>
			<title>Transit-timing measurements with the model-independent barycenter method: application to the LHS 6343 system</title>
			<authors>Oshagh, M.; Bou, G.; Haghighipour, N.; Montalto, M.; Figueira, P.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A62</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012A%26A...540A..62O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...536L...9T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of transit timing variations in excess of one hour in the Kepler multi-planet candidate system KOI 806 with the GTC</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Palle, E.; Parviainen, H.; Deeg, H. J.; Zapatero Osorio, M. R.; Cabrera-Lavers, A.; Belmonte, J. A.; Rodriguez, P. M.; Murgas, F.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 536, id.L9</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...536L...9T</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
