<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.480..496C</bibcode>
			<title>A compact system of small planets around a former red-giant star</title>
			<authors>Charpinet, S.; Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.; Green, E. M.; van Grootel, V.; Randall, S. K.; Silvotti, R.; Baran, A. S.; &#216;stensen, R. H.; Kawaler, S. D.; Telting, J. H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 480, Issue 7378, pp. 496-499 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.480..496C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....7C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-18b, c, and d: A System of Three Planets Confirmed by Transit Timing Variations, Light Curve Validation, Warm-Spitzer Photometry, and Radial Velocity Measurements</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran&#231; ois; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steve B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Borucki, William. J.; Koch, David G.; Winn, Joshua N.; Welsh, William F.; Uddin, Kamal; Tenenbaum, Peter; Still, M.; Seager, Sara; Quinn, Samuel N.; Mullally, F.; Miller, Neil; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Lucas, Phillip; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Knutson, Heather; Kinemuchi, K.; Johnson, John A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew; Horch, Elliott; Holman, Matthew J.; Henze, Christopher E.; Haas, Michael R.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Ford, Eric B.; Fischer, Debra A.; Everett, Mark; Endl, Michael; Demory, Brice-Oliver; Deming, Drake; Charbonneau, David; Caldwell, Douglas; Buchhave, Lars; Brown, Timothy M.; Batalha, Natalie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....7C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....5F</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-10 c: a 2.2 Earth Radius Transiting Planet in a Multiple System</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Torres, Guillermo; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Charbonneau, David; Batalha, Natalie M.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Allen, Christopher; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Deming, Drake; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Knutson, Heather; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Uddin, Kamal</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 5 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....5F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....2F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. I. Statistical Analysis of the First Four Months</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rowe, Jason F.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Carter, Joshua A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Steffen, Jason H.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCauliff, Sean; Mullally, Fergal R.; Quintana, Elisa; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....2F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...741L..30R</bibcode>
			<title>The Orbital Phases and Secondary Transits of Kepler-10b. A Physical Interpretation Based on the Lava-ocean Planet Model</title>
			<authors>Rouan, D.; Deeg, H. J.; Demangeon, O.; Samuel, B.; Cavarroc, C.; Fegley, B.; L&#233;ger, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 741, Issue 2, article id. L30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...741L..30R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534A..26V</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic characterization of the atmospheres of potentially habitable planets: GL 581 d as a model case study</title>
			<authors>von Paris, P.; Cabrera, J.; Godolt, M.; Grenfell, J. L.; Hedelt, P.; Rauer, H.; Schreier, F.; Stracke, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.A26</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534A..26V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..177S</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Exoplanet Candidate Host Stars Are Preferentially Metal Rich</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.; Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 177 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..177S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A.136H</bibcode>
			<title>Venus transit 2004: Illustrating the capability of exoplanet transmission spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Hedelt, P.; Alonso, R.; Brown, T.; Collados Vera, M.; Rauer, H.; Schleicher, H.; Schmidt, W.; Schreier, F.; Titz, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A136</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A.136H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A.114D</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a transit of the super-Earth 55 Cancri e with warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Demory, B.-O.; Gillon, M.; Deming, D.; Valencia, D.; Seager, S.; Benneke, B.; Lovis, C.; Cubillos, P.; Harrington, J.; Stevenson, K. B.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A114</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A.114D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737L..18W</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth Transiting a Naked-eye Star</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Dawson, Rebekah I.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Holman, Matthew J.; Kallinger, Thomas; Kuschnig, Rainer; Sasselov, Dimitar; Dragomir, Diana; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Rucinski, Slavek; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 737, Issue 1, article id. L18 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737L..18W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A...1S</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal phase curves of nontransiting terrestrial exoplanets. I. Characterizing atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Selsis, F.; Wordsworth, R. D.; Forget, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A1</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A...1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...27B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler's First Rocky Planet: Kepler-10b</title>
			<authors>Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Ciardi, David; Dunham, Edward W.; Fressin, Francois; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Torres, Guillermo; Basri, Gibor S.; Brown, Timothy M.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie; Clarke, Bruce; Cochran, William D.; Dupree, Andrea; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fischer, Debra; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Girouard, Forrest R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Johnson, John; Isaacson, Howard; Klaus, Todd C.; Machalek, Pavel; Moorehead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Twicken, Joseph; Quinn, Samuel; VanCleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Welsh, William F.; Devore, Edna; Gould, Alan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 27 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...27B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...24R</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: Beyond the stars</title>
			<authors>Reich, Eugenie Samuel</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 24-26 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...24R</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...75H</bibcode>
			<title>The Mass of CoRoT-7b</title>
			<authors>Hatzes, Artie P.; Fridlund, Malcolm; Nachmani, Gil; Mazeh, Tsevi; Valencia, Diana; H&#233;brard, Guillaume; Carone, Ludmila; P&#228;tzold, Martin; Udry, Stephane; Bouchy, Francois; Deleuil, Magali; Moutou, Claire; Barge, Pierre; Bord&#233; , Pascal; Deeg, Hans; Tingley, Brandon; Dvorak, Rudolf; Gandolfi, Davide; Ferraz-Mello, Sylvio; Wuchterl, G&#252;nther; Guenther, Eike; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike; Erikson, Anders; Cabrera, Juan; Csizmadia, Szilard; L&#233;ger, Alain; Lammer, Helmut; Weingrill, J&#246;rg; Queloz, Didier; Alonso, Roi; Rouan, Daniel; Schneider, Jean</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...75H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...41K</bibcode>
			<title>Climate Instability on Tidally Locked Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Kite, Edwin S.; Gaidos, Eric; Manga, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...41K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....8L</bibcode>
			<title>Architecture and Dynamics of Kepler's Candidate Multiple Transiting Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Steffen, Jason H.; Ford, Eric B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Shporer, Avi; Holman, Matthew J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David; Dunham, Edward W.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Howell, Steve B.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Morehead, Robert C.; Sasselov, Dimitar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 8 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....8L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....7C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-18b, c, and d: A System of Three Planets Confirmed by Transit Timing Variations, Light Curve Validation, Warm-Spitzer Photometry, and Radial Velocity Measurements</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran&#231; ois; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steve B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Borucki, William. J.; Koch, David G.; Winn, Joshua N.; Welsh, William F.; Uddin, Kamal; Tenenbaum, Peter; Still, M.; Seager, Sara; Quinn, Samuel N.; Mullally, F.; Miller, Neil; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Lucas, Phillip; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Knutson, Heather; Kinemuchi, K.; Johnson, John A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew; Horch, Elliott; Holman, Matthew J.; Henze, Christopher E.; Haas, Michael R.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Ford, Eric B.; Fischer, Debra A.; Everett, Mark; Endl, Michael; Demory, Brice-Oliver; Deming, Drake; Charbonneau, David; Caldwell, Douglas; Buchhave, Lars; Brown, Timothy M.; Batalha, Natalie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....7C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....5F</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-10 c: a 2.2 Earth Radius Transiting Planet in a Multiple System</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Torres, Guillermo; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Charbonneau, David; Batalha, Natalie M.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Allen, Christopher; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Deming, Drake; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Knutson, Heather; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Uddin, Kamal</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 5 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....5F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....2F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. I. Statistical Analysis of the First Four Months</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rowe, Jason F.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Carter, Joshua A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Steffen, Jason H.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCauliff, Sean; Mullally, Fergal R.; Quintana, Elisa; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....2F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...741L..30R</bibcode>
			<title>The Orbital Phases and Secondary Transits of Kepler-10b. A Physical Interpretation Based on the Lava-ocean Planet Model</title>
			<authors>Rouan, D.; Deeg, H. J.; Demangeon, O.; Samuel, B.; Cavarroc, C.; Fegley, B.; L&#233;ger, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 741, Issue 2, article id. L30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...741L..30R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..170M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Low False Positive Probabilities of Kepler Planet Candidates</title>
			<authors>Morton, Timothy D.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 170 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..170M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...27B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler's First Rocky Planet: Kepler-10b</title>
			<authors>Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Ciardi, David; Dunham, Edward W.; Fressin, Francois; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Torres, Guillermo; Basri, Gibor S.; Brown, Timothy M.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie; Clarke, Bruce; Cochran, William D.; Dupree, Andrea; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fischer, Debra; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Girouard, Forrest R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Johnson, John; Isaacson, Howard; Klaus, Todd C.; Machalek, Pavel; Moorehead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Twicken, Joseph; Quinn, Samuel; VanCleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Welsh, William F.; Devore, Edna; Gould, Alan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 27 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...27B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
