<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746..123H</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-21b: A 1.6 R Earth Planet Transiting the Bright Oscillating F Subgiant Star HD 179070</title>
			<authors>Howell, Steve B.; Rowe, Jason F.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Ciardi, David R.; Chaplin, William J.; Metcalfe, Travis S.; Monteiro, Mario J. P. F. G.; Appourchaux, Thierry; Basu, Sarbani; Creevey, Orlagh L.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Quirion, Pierre-Olivier; Stello, Denis; Kjeldsen, Hans; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Elsworth, Yvonne; Garca, Rafael A.; Houdek, Gnter; Karoff, Christoffer; Molenda-Zakowicz, Joanna; Thompson, Michael J.; Verner, Graham A.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Francois; Crepp, Justin R.; Adams, Elisabeth; Dupree, Andrea; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Dressing, Courtney D.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Everett, Mark; Horch, Elliott; Batalha, Natalie M.; Dunham, Edward W.; Szkody, Paula; Silva, David R.; Mighell, Ken; Holberg, Jay; Ballot, Jerme; Bedding, Timothy R.; Bruntt, Hans; Campante, Tiago L.; Handberg, Rasmus; Hekker, Saskia; Huber, Daniel; Mathur, Savita; Mosser, Benoit; Rgulo, Clara; White, Timothy R.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Jenkins, Jon M.; McCaulif, Sean; Fanelli, Michael N.; Kulesa, Craig; McCarthy, Don; Henze, Christopher E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 2, article id. 123 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...746..123H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.486..375B</bibcode>
			<title>An abundance of small exoplanets around stars with a wide range of metallicities</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Johansen, Anders; Bizzarro, Martin; Torres, Guillermo; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brugamyer, Erik; Caldwell, Caroline; Bryson, Stephen T.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Ford, Eric B.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Hansen, Terese; Isaacson, Howard; Laird, John B.; Lucas, Philip W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Morse, Jon A.; Robertson, Paul; Shporer, Avi; Stefanik, Robert P.; Still, Martin; Quinn, Samuel N.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 486, Issue 7403, pp. 375-377 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.486..375B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749..152M</bibcode>
			<title>A Uniform Asteroseismic Analysis of 22 Solar-type Stars Observed by Kepler</title>
			<authors>Mathur, S.; Metcalfe, T. S.; Woitaszek, M.; Bruntt, H.; Verner, G. A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Creevey, O. L.; Dogan, G.; Basu, S.; Karoff, C.; Stello, D.; Appourchaux, T.; Campante, T. L.; Chaplin, W. J.; Garca, R. A.; Bedding, T. R.; Benomar, O.; Bonanno, A.; Deheuvels, S.; Elsworth, Y.; Gaulme, P.; Guzik, J. A.; Handberg, R.; Hekker, S.; Herzberg, W.; Monteiro, M. J. P. F. G.; Piau, L.; Quirion, P.-O.; Rgulo, C.; Roth, M.; Salabert, D.; Serenelli, A.; Thompson, M. J.; Trampedach, R.; White, T. R.; Ballot, J.; Brando, I. M.; Molenda-Zakowicz, J.; Kjeldsen, H.; Twicken, J. D.; Uddin, K.; Wohler, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 2, article id. 152 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...749..152M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746..123H</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-21b: A 1.6 R Earth Planet Transiting the Bright Oscillating F Subgiant Star HD 179070</title>
			<authors>Howell, Steve B.; Rowe, Jason F.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Ciardi, David R.; Chaplin, William J.; Metcalfe, Travis S.; Monteiro, Mario J. P. F. G.; Appourchaux, Thierry; Basu, Sarbani; Creevey, Orlagh L.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Quirion, Pierre-Olivier; Stello, Denis; Kjeldsen, Hans; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Elsworth, Yvonne; Garca, Rafael A.; Houdek, Gnter; Karoff, Christoffer; Molenda-Zakowicz, Joanna; Thompson, Michael J.; Verner, Graham A.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Francois; Crepp, Justin R.; Adams, Elisabeth; Dupree, Andrea; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Dressing, Courtney D.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Everett, Mark; Horch, Elliott; Batalha, Natalie M.; Dunham, Edward W.; Szkody, Paula; Silva, David R.; Mighell, Ken; Holberg, Jay; Ballot, Jerme; Bedding, Timothy R.; Bruntt, Hans; Campante, Tiago L.; Handberg, Rasmus; Hekker, Saskia; Huber, Daniel; Mathur, Savita; Mosser, Benoit; Rgulo, Clara; White, Timothy R.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Jenkins, Jon M.; McCaulif, Sean; Fanelli, Michael N.; Kulesa, Craig; McCarthy, Don; Henze, Christopher E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 2, article id. 123 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...746..123H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, Sren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501..941H</bibcode>
			<title>The Geneva-Copenhagen survey of the solar neighbourhood. III. Improved distances, ages, and kinematics</title>
			<authors>Holmberg, J.; Nordstrm, B.; Andersen, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 3, 2009, pp.941-947</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501..941H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AstL...32..759G</bibcode>
			<title>Pulkovo Compilation of Radial Velocities for 35 495 Hipparcos stars in a common system</title>
			<authors>Gontcharov, G. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Letters, Vol. 32, Issue 11, p.759-771</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AstL...32..759G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...418..989N</bibcode>
			<title>The Geneva-Copenhagen survey of the Solar neighbourhood. Ages, metallicities, and kinematic properties of &amp;tilde14 000 F and G dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Nordstrm, B.; Mayor, M.; Andersen, J.; Holmberg, J.; Pont, F.; J rgensen, B. R.; Olsen, E. H.; Udry, S.; Mowlavi, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.418, p.989-1019 (2004)</journal>
			<date>5/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...418..989N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;AS..114..269D</bibcode>
			<title>Vitesses radiales. Catalogue WEB: Wilson Evans Batten. Subtittle: Radial velocities: The Wilson-Evans-Batten catalogue.</title>
			<authors>Duflot, M.; Figon, P.; Meyssonnier, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.114, p.269</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26AS..114..269D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1950ApJ...112...48M</bibcode>
			<title>Radial Velocities, Spectral Types, and Luminosity Classes of 820 Stars.</title>
			<authors>Moore, J. H.; Paddock, G. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, vol. 112, p.48</journal>
			<date>7/1950</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1950ApJ...112...48M</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
