<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737L..18W</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth Transiting a Naked-eye Star</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Dawson, Rebekah I.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Holman, Matthew J.; Kallinger, Thomas; Kuschnig, Rainer; Sasselov, Dimitar; Dragomir, Diana; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Rucinski, Slavek; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 737, Issue 1, article id. L18 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737L..18W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...24R</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: Beyond the stars</title>
			<authors>Reich, Eugenie Samuel</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 24-26 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...24R</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...739...31L</bibcode>
			<title>Theory of Secular Chaos and Mercury's Orbit</title>
			<authors>Lithwick, Yoram; Wu, Yanqin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 739, Issue 1, article id. 31 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...739...31L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..177S</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Exoplanet Candidate Host Stars Are Preferentially Metal Rich</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.; Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 177 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..177S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738...59R</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and Structure of Low-density exo-Neptunes</title>
			<authors>Rogers, Leslie A.; Bodenheimer, Peter; Lissauer, Jack J.; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738...59R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737L..18W</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth Transiting a Naked-eye Star</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Dawson, Rebekah I.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Holman, Matthew J.; Kallinger, Thomas; Kuschnig, Rainer; Sasselov, Dimitar; Dragomir, Diana; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Rucinski, Slavek; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 737, Issue 1, article id. L18 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737L..18W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..24N</bibcode>
			<title>TASTE II. A new observational study of transit time variations in HAT-P-13b</title>
			<authors>Nascimbeni, V.; Piotto, G.; Bedin, L. R.; Damasso, M.; Malavolta, L.; Borsato, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A24</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..24N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..24L</bibcode>
			<title>A First Comparison of Kepler Planet Candidates in Single and Multiple Systems</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Wohler, Bill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..24L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...24R</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: Beyond the stars</title>
			<authors>Reich, Eugenie Samuel</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 24-26 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...24R</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
