<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....3B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-14b: A Massive Hot Jupiter Transiting an F Star in a Close Visual Binary</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Carter, Joshua A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Charbonneau, David B.; Ciardi, David R.; Kulesa, Craig; Dupree, Andrea K.; Fischer, Debra A.; Fressin, Franois; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCarthy, Donald W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Deming, Drake; Dunham, Edward W.; Everett, Mark; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Geary, John C.; Girouard, Forrest R.; Haas, Michael R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Horch, Elliott; Klaus, Todd C.; Knutson, Heather A.; Koch, David G.; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Lissauer, Jack J.; Machalek, Pavel; Mullally, Fergal; Still, Martin D.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Seager, Sara; Thompson, Susan E.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 3 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJS..197....3B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749...15G</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-20: A Sun-like Star with Three Sub-Neptune Exoplanets and Two Earth-size Candidates</title>
			<authors>Gautier, Thomas N., III; Charbonneau, David; Rowe, Jason F.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Francois; Rogers, Leslie A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ciardi, David R.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Howell, Steve B.; Horch, Elliott P.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Borucki, William J.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Silverio, Kathryn; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Still, Martin; Stumpe, Martin C.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 1, article id. 15 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...749...15G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....3B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-14b: A Massive Hot Jupiter Transiting an F Star in a Close Visual Binary</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, Lars A.; Latham, David W.; Carter, Joshua A.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Charbonneau, David B.; Ciardi, David R.; Kulesa, Craig; Dupree, Andrea K.; Fischer, Debra A.; Fressin, Franois; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCarthy, Donald W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Deming, Drake; Dunham, Edward W.; Everett, Mark; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Geary, John C.; Girouard, Forrest R.; Haas, Michael R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Horch, Elliott; Klaus, Todd C.; Knutson, Heather A.; Koch, David G.; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Lissauer, Jack J.; Machalek, Pavel; Mullally, Fergal; Still, Martin D.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Seager, Sara; Thompson, Susan E.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 3 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJS..197....3B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
