<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....144...34H</bibcode>
			<title>The Proposed Quadruple System SZ Herculis: Revised LITE Model and Orbital Stability Study</title>
			<authors>Hinse, Tobias Cornelius; Gozdziewski, Krzysztof; Lee, Jae Woo; Haghighipour, Nader; Lee, Chung-Uk</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 144, Issue 2, article id. 34 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....144...34H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754L..16P</bibcode>
			<title>How Not to Build Tatooine: The Difficulty of In Situ Formation of Circumbinary Planets Kepler 16b, Kepler 34b, and Kepler 35b</title>
			<authors>Paardekooper, Sijme-Jan; Leinhardt, Zo M.; Thbault, Philippe; Baruteau, Clment</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 754, Issue 1, article id. L16 (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754L..16P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...71M</bibcode>
			<title>Circumbinary Planet Formation in the Kepler-16 System. I. N-body Simulations</title>
			<authors>Meschiari, Stefano</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 71 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...71M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751L..31B</bibcode>
			<title>The SDSS-HET Survey of Kepler Eclipsing Binaries: Spectroscopic Dynamical Masses of the Kepler-16 Circumbinary Planet Hosts</title>
			<authors>Bender, Chad F.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Deshpande, Rohit; Wright, Jason T.; Roy, Arpita; Terrien, Ryan C.; Sigurdsson, Steinn; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Schneider, Donald P.; Fleming, Scott W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. L31 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...751L..31B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..475W</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting circumbinary planets Kepler-34 b and Kepler-35 b</title>
			<authors>Welsh, William F.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Bloemen, Steven; Brugamyer, Erik; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Caroline; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howard, Andrew W.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Klaus, Todd C.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Mazeh, Tsevi; Quintana, Elisa V.; Robertson, Paul; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Windmiller, Gur; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 481, Issue 7382, pp. 475-479 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..475W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..448S</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: A new class of planet</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 481, Issue 7382, pp. 448-449 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..448S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...755...17Y</bibcode>
			<title>Circumbinary Chaos: Using Pluto's Newest Moon to Constrain the Masses of Nix and Hydra</title>
			<authors>Youdin, Andrew N.; Kratter, Kaitlin M.; Kenyon, Scott J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 755, Issue 1, article id. 17 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...755...17Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754L..16P</bibcode>
			<title>How Not to Build Tatooine: The Difficulty of In Situ Formation of Circumbinary Planets Kepler 16b, Kepler 34b, and Kepler 35b</title>
			<authors>Paardekooper, Sijme-Jan; Leinhardt, Zo M.; Thbault, Philippe; Baruteau, Clment</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 754, Issue 1, article id. L16 (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754L..16P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...72D</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation between the Eclipse Depths of Kepler Gas Giant Candidates and the Metallicities of Their Parent Stars</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 72 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...72D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...542A..92R</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planets in stellar multiple systems</title>
			<authors>Roell, T.; Neuhuser, R.; Seifahrt, A.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 542, id.A92</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...542A..92R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..475W</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting circumbinary planets Kepler-34 b and Kepler-35 b</title>
			<authors>Welsh, William F.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Short, Donald R.; Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Doyle, Laurance R.; Barclay, Thomas; Batalha, Natalie; Bloemen, Steven; Brugamyer, Erik; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Caroline; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howard, Andrew W.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Klaus, Todd C.; Latham, David W.; Li, Jie; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Mazeh, Tsevi; Quintana, Elisa V.; Robertson, Paul; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Windmiller, Gur; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 481, Issue 7382, pp. 475-479 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..475W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Sci...337.1511O</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-47: A transiting circumbinary multiplanet system.</title>
			<authors>Orosz, J. A.; Welsh, W. F.; Carter, J. A.; Fabrycky, D. C.; Cochran, W. D.; Endl, M.; Ford, E. B.; Haghighipour, N.; MacQueen, P.; Mazeh, T.; Sanchis-Ojeda, R.; Short, D. R.; Torres, G.; Agol, E.; Buchhave, L. A.; Doyle, L. R.; Isaacson, H.; Lissauer, J. J.; Marcy, G. W.; Shporer, A.; Windmiller, G.; Barclay, T.; Boss, A. P.; Clarke, B. D.; Fortney, J.; Geary, J. C.; Holman, M. J.; Huber, D.; Jenkins, J. M.; Kinemuchi, K.; Kruse, E.; Ragozzine, D.; Sasselov, D.; Still, M.; Tenenbaum, P.; Uddin, K.; Winn, J. N.; Koch, D. G.; Borucki, W. J.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Vol. 337, p. 1511-1514 (2012)</journal>
			<date>0/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Sci...337.1511O</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
