<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....7C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-18b, c, and d: A System of Three Planets Confirmed by Transit Timing Variations, Light Curve Validation, Warm-Spitzer Photometry, and Radial Velocity Measurements</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran&#231; ois; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steve B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Borucki, William. J.; Koch, David G.; Winn, Joshua N.; Welsh, William F.; Uddin, Kamal; Tenenbaum, Peter; Still, M.; Seager, Sara; Quinn, Samuel N.; Mullally, F.; Miller, Neil; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Lucas, Phillip; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Knutson, Heather; Kinemuchi, K.; Johnson, John A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew; Horch, Elliott; Holman, Matthew J.; Henze, Christopher E.; Haas, Michael R.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Ford, Eric B.; Fischer, Debra A.; Everett, Mark; Endl, Michael; Demory, Brice-Oliver; Deming, Drake; Charbonneau, David; Caldwell, Douglas; Buchhave, Lars; Brown, Timothy M.; Batalha, Natalie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....7C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....2F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. I. Statistical Analysis of the First Four Months</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rowe, Jason F.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Carter, Joshua A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Steffen, Jason H.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCauliff, Sean; Mullally, Fergal R.; Quintana, Elisa; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....2F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A.136H</bibcode>
			<title>Venus transit 2004: Illustrating the capability of exoplanet transmission spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Hedelt, P.; Alonso, R.; Brown, T.; Collados Vera, M.; Rauer, H.; Schleicher, H.; Schmidt, W.; Schreier, F.; Titz, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A136</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A.136H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737L..18W</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth Transiting a Naked-eye Star</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Dawson, Rebekah I.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Holman, Matthew J.; Kallinger, Thomas; Kuschnig, Rainer; Sasselov, Dimitar; Dragomir, Diana; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Rucinski, Slavek; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 737, Issue 1, article id. L18 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737L..18W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...24R</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: Beyond the stars</title>
			<authors>Reich, Eugenie Samuel</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 24-26 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...24R</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...10B</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Misalignment of KOI-13.01 from Its Gravity-darkened Kepler Transit Lightcurve</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.; Linscott, Ethan; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...10B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....9F</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Atmospheric Characterization of Giant Planet Kepler-12b: An Inflated Radius Outlier</title>
			<authors>Fortney, Jonathan J.; Demory, Brice-Olivier; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Rowe, Jason; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Buchhave, Lars A.; Ciardi, David; Gautier, Thomas N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Nutzman, Philip; Jenkins, Jon M.; Howard, Andrew; Charbonneau, David; Knutson, Heather A.; Howell, Steve B.; Everett, Mark; Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Deming, Drake; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Latham, David W.; Miller, Neil; Seager, Sara; Fischer, Debra A.; Koch, David; Lissauer, Jack J.; Haas, Michael R.; Still, Martin; Lucas, Philip; Gillon, Michael; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 9 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....9F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....8L</bibcode>
			<title>Architecture and Dynamics of Kepler's Candidate Multiple Transiting Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Steffen, Jason H.; Ford, Eric B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Shporer, Avi; Holman, Matthew J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David; Dunham, Edward W.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Howell, Steve B.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Morehead, Robert C.; Sasselov, Dimitar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 8 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....8L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....7C</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-18b, c, and d: A System of Three Planets Confirmed by Transit Timing Variations, Light Curve Validation, Warm-Spitzer Photometry, and Radial Velocity Measurements</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran&#231; ois; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Brugamyer, Erik J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Carter, Joshua A.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steve B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Borucki, William. J.; Koch, David G.; Winn, Joshua N.; Welsh, William F.; Uddin, Kamal; Tenenbaum, Peter; Still, M.; Seager, Sara; Quinn, Samuel N.; Mullally, F.; Miller, Neil; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Lucas, Phillip; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Knutson, Heather; Kinemuchi, K.; Johnson, John A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew; Horch, Elliott; Holman, Matthew J.; Henze, Christopher E.; Haas, Michael R.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Ford, Eric B.; Fischer, Debra A.; Everett, Mark; Endl, Michael; Demory, Brice-Oliver; Deming, Drake; Charbonneau, David; Caldwell, Douglas; Buchhave, Lars; Brown, Timothy M.; Batalha, Natalie</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....7C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....5F</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-10 c: a 2.2 Earth Radius Transiting Planet in a Multiple System</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Torres, Guillermo; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Charbonneau, David; Batalha, Natalie M.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Allen, Christopher; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Deming, Drake; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Henze, Christopher E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kinemuchi, Karen; Knutson, Heather; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Uddin, Kamal</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 5 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....5F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....2F</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Observations from Kepler. I. Statistical Analysis of the First Four Months</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rowe, Jason F.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Carter, Joshua A.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Ragozzine, Darin; Steffen, Jason H.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Steve; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; McCauliff, Sean; Mullally, Fergal R.; Quintana, Elisa; Still, Martin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....2F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417L..16G</bibcode>
			<title>Potential biases in the detection of planetary systems with large transit timing variations</title>
			<authors>Garc&#237;a-Melendo, E.; L&#243;pez-Morales, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 417, Issue 1, pp. L16-L20.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417L..16G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740...61K</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Phase Variations of the 55 Cancri System</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Gelino, Dawn M.; Ciardi, David R.; Dragomir, Diana; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 740, Issue 2, article id. 61 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740...61K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...739...31L</bibcode>
			<title>Theory of Secular Chaos and Mercury's Orbit</title>
			<authors>Lithwick, Yoram; Wu, Yanqin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 739, Issue 1, article id. 31 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...739...31L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..177S</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Exoplanet Candidate Host Stars Are Preferentially Metal Rich</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.; Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 177 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..177S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738...59R</bibcode>
			<title>Formation and Structure of Low-density exo-Neptunes</title>
			<authors>Rogers, Leslie A.; Bodenheimer, Peter; Lissauer, Jack J.; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738...59R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...737L..18W</bibcode>
			<title>A Super-Earth Transiting a Naked-eye Star</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Dawson, Rebekah I.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Holman, Matthew J.; Kallinger, Thomas; Kuschnig, Rainer; Sasselov, Dimitar; Dragomir, Diana; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Rucinski, Slavek; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 737, Issue 1, article id. L18 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...737L..18W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..24N</bibcode>
			<title>TASTE II. A new observational study of transit time variations in HAT-P-13b</title>
			<authors>Nascimbeni, V.; Piotto, G.; Bedin, L. R.; Damasso, M.; Malavolta, L.; Borsato, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A24</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..24N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AN....332..547N</bibcode>
			<title>The Young Exoplanet Transit Initiative (YETI)</title>
			<authors>Neuh&#228;user, R.; Errmann, R.; Berndt, A.; Maciejewski, G.; Takahashi, H.; Chen, W. P.; Dimitrov, D. P.; Pribulla, T.; Nikogossian, E. H.; Jensen, E. L. N.; Marschall, L.; Wu, Z.-Y.; Kellerer, A.; Walter, F. M.; Brice&#241;o, C.; Chini, R.; Fernandez, M.; Raetz, St.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Quinn, S. N.; Niedzielski, A.; Bukowiecki, L.; Nowak, G.; Tomov, T.; Tachihara, K.; Hu, S. C.-L.; Hung, L. W.; Kjurkchieva, D. P.; Radeva, V. S.; Mihov, B. M.; Slavcheva-Mihova, L.; Bozhinova, I. N.; Budaj, J.; Vanko, M.; Kundra, E.; Hamb&#225;lek, L.; Krushevska, V.; Movsessian, T.; Harutyunyan, H.; Downes, J. J.; Hernandez, J.; Hoffmeister, V. H.; Cohen, D. H.; Abel, I.; Ahmad, R.; Chapman, S.; Eckert, S.; Goodman, J.; Guerard, A.; Kim, H. M.; Koontharana, A.; Sokol, J.; Trinh, J.; Wang, Y.; Zhou, X.; Redmer, R.; Kramm, U.; Nettelmann, N.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, J.; Moualla, M.; Ginski, C.; Marka, C.; Adam, C.; Seeliger, M.; Baar, S.; Roell, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Trepl, L.; Eisenbei&#223;, T.; Fiedler, S.; Tetzlaff, N.; Schmidt, E.; Hohle, M. M.; Kitze, M.; Chakrova, N.; Gr&#228;fe, C.; Schreyer, K.; Hambaryan, V. V.; Broeg, C. H.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Pandey, A. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.332, Issue 6, p.547</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AN....332..547N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..24L</bibcode>
			<title>A First Comparison of Kepler Planet Candidates in Single and Multiple Systems</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Wohler, Bill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..24L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...24R</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: Beyond the stars</title>
			<authors>Reich, Eugenie Samuel</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 24-26 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...24R</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
