<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>The Heavy-element Masses of Extrasolar Giant Planets, Revealed</title>
			<authors>Miller, Neil; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.413L..43P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variations in the HAT-P-13 planetary system</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; S&#225;rneczky, Kriszti&#225;n; Szab&#243;, Gyula M.; Szing, Attila; Kiss, L&#225;szl&#243; L.; Mezo, Gy&#246;rgy; Reg&#225;ly, Zsolt</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 413, Issue 1, pp. L43-L46.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.413L..43P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...93W</bibcode>
			<title>The California Planet Survey. III. A Possible 2:1 Resonance in the Exoplanetary Triple System HD 37124</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Isaacson, H.; Fischer, D. A.; Spronck, J.; Anderson, J.; Valenti, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. 93 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...93W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...24R</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: Beyond the stars</title>
			<authors>Reich, Eugenie Samuel</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 24-26 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...24R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727L..44S</bibcode>
			<title>A Short-period Censor of Sub-Jupiter Mass Exoplanets with Low Density</title>
			<authors>Szab&#243;, Gy. M.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. L44 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727L..44S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...24T</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling Kepler Transit Light Curves as False Positives: Rejection of Blend Scenarios for Kepler-9, and Validation of Kepler-9 d, A Super-earth-size Planet in a Multiple System</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David R.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Monet, David G.; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...24T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...52H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-18b and HAT-P-19b: Two Low-density Saturn-mass Planets Transiting Metal-rich K Stars</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Sato, B.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Howard, A. W.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; F&#252;resz, G.; Perumpilly, G.; B&#233;ky, B.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Csubry, Z.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id. 52 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...52H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...330...51H</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-9: A System of Multiple Planets Transiting a Sun-Like Star, Confirmed by Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Ford, Eric B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Cochran, William D.; Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Buchhave, Lars A.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Charbonneau, David; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Howell, Steve B.; Ciardi, David R.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra; F&#252;r&#233;sz, G&#225;bor; Hartman, Joel D.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John A.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Moorhead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Orosz, Jerome A.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 330, Issue 6000, pp. 51- (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...330...51H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...330...47L</bibcode>
			<title>A dance of extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, G.</authors>
			<journal>Science, 330, 47-48 (2010)</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...330...47L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..177S</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Exoplanet Candidate Host Stars Are Preferentially Metal Rich</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.; Laughlin, Gregory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 177 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..177S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..40F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-39b: a highly inflated Saturn-mass planet orbiting a late G-type star</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Anderson, D. R.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Boisse, I.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..40F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A...3H</bibcode>
			<title>The multiple planets transiting Kepler-9. I. Inferring stellar properties and planetary compositions</title>
			<authors>Havel, M.; Guillot, T.; Valencia, D.; Crida, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A3</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A...3H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...530A..41B</bibcode>
			<title>Evolution of inclined planets in three-dimensional radiative discs</title>
			<authors>Bitsch, B.; Kley, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 530, id.A41</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...530A..41B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.413L..43P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variations in the HAT-P-13 planetary system</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; S&#225;rneczky, Kriszti&#225;n; Szab&#243;, Gyula M.; Szing, Attila; Kiss, L&#225;szl&#243; L.; Mezo, Gy&#246;rgy; Reg&#225;ly, Zsolt</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 413, Issue 1, pp. L43-L46.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.413L..43P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...53H</bibcode>
			<title>Five New Transit Epochs of the Exoplanet OGLE-TR-111b</title>
			<authors>Hoyer, S.; Rojo, P.; L&#243;pez-Morales, M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Chambers, J.; Minniti, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 53 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...53H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..24L</bibcode>
			<title>A First Comparison of Kepler Planet Candidates in Single and Multiple Systems</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David R.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah A.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Shporer, Avi; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Wohler, Bill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..24L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...41B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in Five of the Exoplanetary Systems Studied by the NASA EPOXI Mission</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...41B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.412.2799F</bibcode>
			<title>Evolution of spin direction of accreting magnetic protostars and spin-orbit misalignment in exoplanetary systems - II. Warped discs</title>
			<authors>Foucart, Francois; Lai, Dong</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 412, Issue 4, pp. 2799-2815.</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.412.2799F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...93W</bibcode>
			<title>The California Planet Survey. III. A Possible 2:1 Resonance in the Exoplanetary Triple System HD 37124</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Isaacson, H.; Fischer, D. A.; Spronck, J.; Anderson, J.; Valenti, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. 93 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...93W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...27B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler's First Rocky Planet: Kepler-10b</title>
			<authors>Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Ciardi, David; Dunham, Edward W.; Fressin, Francois; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Torres, Guillermo; Basri, Gibor S.; Brown, Timothy M.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie; Clarke, Bruce; Cochran, William D.; Dupree, Andrea; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fischer, Debra; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Girouard, Forrest R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Johnson, John; Isaacson, Howard; Klaus, Todd C.; Machalek, Pavel; Moorehead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Twicken, Joseph; Quinn, Samuel; VanCleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Welsh, William F.; Devore, Edna; Gould, Alan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 27 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...27B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AcA....61...25M</bibcode>
			<title>Refining Parameters of the XO-5 Planetary System with High-Precision Transit Photometry</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Seeliger, M.; Adam, Ch.; Raetz, St.; Neuh&#228;user, R.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, vol 61, no 1, p. 25-35</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AcA....61...25M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63..287F</bibcode>
			<title>Measurements of Transit Timing Variations for WASP-5b</title>
			<authors>Fukui, Akihiko; Narita, Norio; Tristram, Paul J.; Sumi, Takahiro; Abe, Fumio; Itow, Yoshitaka; Sullivan, Denis J.; Bond, Ian A.; Hirano, Teruyuki; Tamura, Motohide; Bennett, David P.; Furusawa, Kei; Hayashi, Fumiya; Hearnshaw, John B.; Hosaka, Shun; Kamiya, Koki; Kobara, Shuhei; Korpela, Aarno; Kilmartin, Pam M.; Lin, Wei; Ling, Cho Hong; Makita, Shota; Masuda, Kimiaki; Matsubara, Yutaka; Miyake, Noriyuki; Muraki, Yasushi; Nagaya, Maiko; Nishimoto, Kenta; Ohnishi, Kouji; Omori, Kengo; Perrott, Yvette; Rattenbury, Nicholas; Saito, Toshiharu; Skuljan, Ljiljana; Suzuki, Daisuke; Sweatman, Winston L.; Wada, Kohei</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.1, pp.287--300</journal>
			<date>2/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63..287F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...53L</bibcode>
			<title>A closely packed system of low-mass, low-density planets transiting Kepler-11</title>
			<authors>Lissauer, Jack J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Borucki, William J.; Fressin, Francois; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Orosz, Jerome A.; Rowe, Jason F.; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Carter, Joshua A.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Cochran, William D.; Desert, Jean-Michel; Dunham, Edward W.; Fanelli, Michael N.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lopez, Eric; McCauliff, Sean; Miller, Neil; Morehead, Robert C.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sasselov, Dimitar; Short, Donald R.; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 53-58 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...53L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.470...24R</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: Beyond the stars</title>
			<authors>Reich, Eugenie Samuel</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 470, Issue 7332, pp. 24-26 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.470...24R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..125A</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Variation Analysis of OGLE-TR-132b with Seven New Transits</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; L&#243;pez-Morales, M.; Elliot, J. L.; Seager, S.; Osip, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 125 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..125A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...74V</bibcode>
			<title>Quantifying the Challenges of Detecting Unseen Planetary Companions with Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Payne, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...74V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...63W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Orientations of Exoplanets: HAT-P-4b is Prograde and HAT-P-14b is Retrograde</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Hartman, Joel D.; Holman, Matthew J.; Albrecht, Simon; Crepp, Justin R.; Morton, Timothy D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 63 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...63W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...24T</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling Kepler Transit Light Curves as False Positives: Rejection of Blend Scenarios for Kepler-9, and Validation of Kepler-9 d, A Super-earth-size Planet in a Multiple System</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David R.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ford, Eric B.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David G.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Monet, David G.; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...24T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...52H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-18b and HAT-P-19b: Two Low-density Saturn-mass Planets Transiting Metal-rich K Stars</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Sato, B.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Howard, A. W.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; F&#252;resz, G.; Perumpilly, G.; B&#233;ky, B.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Csubry, Z.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id. 52 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...52H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1226S</bibcode>
			<title>Five Kepler Target Stars That Show Multiple Transiting Exoplanet Candidates</title>
			<authors>Steffen, Jason H.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Haas, Michael J.; Holman, Matthew J.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Jenkins, Jon M.; Koch, David; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Moorhead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Marcy, Geoffrey; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Ragozzine, Darin; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Seager, Sara; Torres, Guillermo; Welsh, William F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 1, pp. 1226-1241 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1226S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...523A..84S</bibcode>
			<title>A multi-site campaign to detect the transit of the second planet in HAT-P-13</title>
			<authors>Szab&#243;, Gy. M.; Kiss, L. L.; Benko, J. M.; Mezo, Gy.; Nuspl, J.; Reg&#225;ly, Zs.; S&#225;rneczky, K.; Simon, A. E.; Leto, G.; Zanmar Sanchez, R.; Ngeow, C.-C.; Kov&#225;ri, Zs.; Szab&#243;, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 523, id.A84</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...523A..84S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...330...51H</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-9: A System of Multiple Planets Transiting a Sun-Like Star, Confirmed by Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Ford, Eric B.; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Cochran, William D.; Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Buchhave, Lars A.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Charbonneau, David; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Haas, Michael R.; Howell, Steve B.; Ciardi, David R.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra; F&#252;r&#233;sz, G&#225;bor; Hartman, Joel D.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John A.; MacQueen, Phillip J.; Moorhead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Orosz, Jerome A.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 330, Issue 6000, pp. 51- (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...330...51H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...330...47L</bibcode>
			<title>A dance of extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, G.</authors>
			<journal>Science, 330, 47-48 (2010)</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...330...47L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
