<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.480..496C</bibcode>
			<title>A compact system of small planets around a former red-giant star</title>
			<authors>Charpinet, S.; Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.; Green, E. M.; van Grootel, V.; Randall, S. K.; Silvotti, R.; Baran, A. S.; &#216;stensen, R. H.; Kawaler, S. D.; Telting, J. H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 480, Issue 7378, pp. 496-499 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.480..496C</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.480..496C</bibcode>
			<title>A compact system of small planets around a former red-giant star</title>
			<authors>Charpinet, S.; Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.; Green, E. M.; van Grootel, V.; Randall, S. K.; Silvotti, R.; Baran, A. S.; &#216;stensen, R. H.; Kawaler, S. D.; Telting, J. H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 480, Issue 7378, pp. 496-499 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.480..496C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.480..460K</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary science: The ultimate fate of planets</title>
			<authors>Kempton, Eliza M. R.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 480, Issue 7378, pp. 460-461 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.480..460K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734...59G</bibcode>
			<title>The Unusual Variable Hot B Subdwarf LS IV-14&#176;116</title>
			<authors>Green, E. M.; Guvenen, B.; O'Malley, C. J.; O'Connell, C. J.; Baringer, B. P.; Villareal, A. S.; Carleton, T. M.; Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.; Charpinet, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734...59G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...530A...3C</bibcode>
			<title>Deep asteroseismic sounding of the compact hot B subdwarf pulsator KIC02697388 from Kepler time series photometry</title>
			<authors>Charpinet, S.; van Grootel, V.; Fontaine, G.; Green, E. M.; Brassard, P.; Randall, S. K.; Silvotti, R.; &#216;stensen, R. H.; Kjeldsen, H.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Kawaler, S. D.; Clarke, B. D.; Li, J.; Wohler, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 530, id.A3</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...530A...3C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.409.1496R</bibcode>
			<title>First Kepler results on compact pulsators - III. Subdwarf B stars with V1093 Her and hybrid (DW Lyn) type pulsations</title>
			<authors>Reed, M. D.; Kawaler, S. D.; &#216;stensen, R. H.; Bloemen, S.; Baran, A.; Telting, J. H.; Silvotti, R.; Charpinet, S.; Quint, A. C.; Handler, G.; Gilliland, R. L.; Borucki, W. J.; Koch, D. G.; Kjeldsen, H.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 409, Issue 4, pp. 1496-1508.</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.409.1496R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.409.1470O</bibcode>
			<title>First Kepler results on compact pulsators - I. Survey target selection and the first pulsators</title>
			<authors>&#216;stensen, R. H.; Silvotti, R.; Charpinet, S.; Oreiro, R.; Handler, G.; Green, E. M.; Bloemen, S.; Heber, U.; G&#228;nsicke, B. T.; Marsh, T. R.; Kurtz, D. W.; Telting, J. H.; Reed, M. D.; Kawaler, S. D.; Aerts, C.; Rodr&#237;guez-L&#243;pez, C.; Vuckovic, M.; Ottosen, T. A.; Liimets, T.; Quint, A. C.; van Grootel, V.; Randall, S. K.; Gilliland, R. L.; Kjeldsen, H.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Borucki, W. J.; Koch, D.; Quintana, E. V.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 409, Issue 4, pp. 1470-1486.</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.409.1470O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...524A..63V</bibcode>
			<title>Structural and core parameters of the hot B subdwarf KPD 0629-0016 from CoRoT g-mode asteroseismology</title>
			<authors>van Grootel, V.; Charpinet, S.; Fontaine, G.; Green, E. M.; Brassard, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 524, id.A63</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...524A..63V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L..97V</bibcode>
			<title>Early Asteroseismic Results from Kepler: Structural and Core Parameters of the Hot B Subdwarf KPD 1943+4058 as Inferred from g-mode Oscillations</title>
			<authors>Van Grootel, V.; Charpinet, S.; Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.; Green, E. M.; Randall, S. K.; Silvotti, R.; &#216;stensen, R. H.; Kjeldsen, H.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Borucki, W. J.; Koch, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L97-L101 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L..97V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJ...450..851V</bibcode>
			<title>Studies of Hot B Subdwarfs. XI. A Redetermination of the Density of Hot, Hydrogen-rich Subdwarfs in the Galactic Plane</title>
			<authors>Villeneuve, B.; Wesemael, F.; Fontaine, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.450, p.851</journal>
			<date>9/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJ...450..851V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994AJ....107.1565A</bibcode>
			<title>Studies of hot B subdwarfs. 9: Cousins BVRI photometry and the binary fraction of hot, hydrogen-rich subdwarfs in the Palomar-Green survey</title>
			<authors>Allard, F.; Wesemael, F.; Fontaine, G.; Bergeron, P.; Lamontagne, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, vol. 107, no. 4, p. 1565-1576</journal>
			<date>4/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994AJ....107.1565A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992AJ....104..203W</bibcode>
			<title>Studies of hot B subdwarfs. VIII - Stromgren photometry of hot, hydrogen-rich subdwarf candidates in the Palomar-Green and Kitt Peak-Downes surveys</title>
			<authors>Wesemael, F.; Fontaine, G.; Bergeron, P.; Lamontagne, R.; Green, R. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 104, no. 1, July 1992, p. 203-215. Research supported by NSERC, FCAR, and Killam Fellowship.</journal>
			<date>7/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992AJ....104..203W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988SAAOC..12....1K</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of spectroscopically identified hot subdwarf stars.</title>
			<authors>Kilkenny, D.; Heber, U.; Drilling, J. S.</authors>
			<journal>South African Astronomical Observatory Circular, No. 12, 80 pp.</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988SAAOC..12....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986ApJS...61..569D</bibcode>
			<title>The KPD survey for galactic plane ultraviolet-excess objects Space densities of white dwarfs and subdwarfs</title>
			<authors>Downes, R. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 61, July 1986, p. 569-584.</journal>
			<date>7/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986ApJS...61..569D</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
