<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.1512M</bibcode>
			<title>A massive exoplanet candidate around KOI-13: independent confirmation by ellipsoidal variations</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Hodgkin, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 2, pp. 1512-1517.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012MNRAS.422.1512M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.421L.122S</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-orbit resonance, transit duration variation and possible secular perturbations in KOI-13</title>
			<authors>Szab, Gy. M.; Pl, A.; Derekas, A.; Simon, A. E.; Szalai, T.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 421, Issue 1, pp. L122-L126.</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012MNRAS.421L.122S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Sci...336.1133N</bibcode>
			<title>The detection and characterization of a nontransiting planet by transit timing variations.</title>
			<authors>Nesvorny, D.; Kipping, D. M.; Buchhave, L. A.; Bakos, G. A.; Hartman, J.; Schmitt, A. R.</authors>
			<journal>Science, 336, 1133-1136 (2012)</journal>
			<date>0/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012Sci...336.1133N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..195S</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of KOI-13.01 Using the Photometric Orbit</title>
			<authors>Shporer, Avi; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Seader, Shawn E.; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Still, Martin D.; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Welsh, William F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 6, article id. 195 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....142..195S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L...4S</bibcode>
			<title>Asymmetric Transit Curves as Indication of Orbital Obliquity: Clues from the Late-type Dwarf Companion in KOI-13</title>
			<authors>Szab, Gy. M.; Szab, R.; Benko, J. M.; Lehmann, H.; Mezo, Gy.; Simon, A. E.; Kovri, Zs.; Hodosn, G.; Regly, Zs.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. L4 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...736L...4S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...19H</bibcode>
			<title>Speckle Camera Observations for the NASA Kepler Mission Follow-up Program</title>
			<authors>Howell, Steve B.; Everett, Mark E.; Sherry, William; Horch, Elliott; Ciardi, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....142...19H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
