<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..56M</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler KOI-13.01 - Detection of beaming and ellipsoidal modulations pointing to a massive hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Nachmani, G.; Sokol, G.; Faigler, S.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A56</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..56M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..195S</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of KOI-13.01 Using the Photometric Orbit</title>
			<authors>Shporer, Avi; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Seader, Shawn E.; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Still, Martin D.; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Welsh, William F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 6, article id. 195 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142..195S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L...4S</bibcode>
			<title>Asymmetric Transit Curves as Indication of Orbital Obliquity: Clues from the Late-type Dwarf Companion in KOI-13</title>
			<authors>Szab, Gy. M.; Szab, R.; Benko, J. M.; Lehmann, H.; Mezo, Gy.; Simon, A. E.; Kovri, Zs.; Hodosn, G.; Regly, Zs.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. L4 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L...4S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Sci...336.1133N</bibcode>
			<title>The Detection and Characterization of a Nontransiting Planet by Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Nesvorn, David; Kipping, David M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Bakos, Gspr .; Hartman, Joel; Schmitt, Allan R.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 336, Issue 6085, pp. 1133- (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Sci...336.1133N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.1512M</bibcode>
			<title>A massive exoplanet candidate around KOI-13: independent confirmation by ellipsoidal variations</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Hodgkin, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 2, pp. 1512-1517.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.1512M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..56M</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler KOI-13.01 - Detection of beaming and ellipsoidal modulations pointing to a massive hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Nachmani, G.; Sokol, G.; Faigler, S.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A56</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..56M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.421L.122S</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-orbit resonance, transit duration variation and possible secular perturbations in KOI-13</title>
			<authors>Szab, Gy. M.; Pl, A.; Derekas, A.; Simon, A. E.; Szalai, T.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 421, Issue 1, pp. L122-L126.</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.421L.122S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..195S</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of KOI-13.01 Using the Photometric Orbit</title>
			<authors>Shporer, Avi; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sanderfer, Dwight T.; Seader, Shawn E.; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Still, Martin D.; Thompson, Susan E.; Twicken, Joseph D.; Welsh, William F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 6, article id. 195 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142..195S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L...4S</bibcode>
			<title>Asymmetric Transit Curves as Indication of Orbital Obliquity: Clues from the Late-type Dwarf Companion in KOI-13</title>
			<authors>Szab, Gy. M.; Szab, R.; Benko, J. M.; Lehmann, H.; Mezo, Gy.; Simon, A. E.; Kovri, Zs.; Hodosn, G.; Regly, Zs.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. L4 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L...4S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, Sren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...19H</bibcode>
			<title>Speckle Camera Observations for the NASA Kepler Mission Follow-up Program</title>
			<authors>Howell, Steve B.; Everett, Mark E.; Sherry, William; Horch, Elliott; Ciardi, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142...19H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
