<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.2024J</bibcode>
			<title>The coronal X-ray-age relation and its implications for the evaporation of exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Alan P.; Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 3, pp. 2024-2043.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.2024J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...538A..96B</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. V. The three hot Jupiters KOI-135b, KOI-204b, and KOI-203b (alias Kepler-17b)</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Hbrard, G.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; Deleuil, M.; Almenara, J.; Bouchy, F.; Daz, R. F.; Moutou, C.; Vanhuysse, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 538, id.A96</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...538A..96B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..83B</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. III. KOI-423b: an 18 MJup transiting companion around an F7IV star</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Moutou, C.; Deleuil, M.; D az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H brard, G.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A83</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..83B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..63S</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. II. KOI-428b: a hot Jupiter transiting a subgiant F-star</title>
			<authors>Santerne, A.; Daz, R. F.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Moutou, C.; Hbrard, G.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A63</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..63S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..83B</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. III. KOI-423b: an 18 MJup transiting companion around an F7IV star</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Moutou, C.; Deleuil, M.; D az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H brard, G.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A83</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..83B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736L...4S</bibcode>
			<title>Asymmetric Transit Curves as Indication of Orbital Obliquity: Clues from the Late-type Dwarf Companion in KOI-13</title>
			<authors>Szab, Gy. M.; Szab, R.; Benko, J. M.; Lehmann, H.; Mezo, Gy.; Simon, A. E.; Kovri, Zs.; Hodosn, G.; Regly, Zs.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. L4 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736L...4S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, Sren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..63S</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. II. KOI-428b: a hot Jupiter transiting a subgiant F-star</title>
			<authors>Santerne, A.; Daz, R. F.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Moutou, C.; Hbrard, G.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A63</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..63S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..117B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Kepler Planetary Candidates Based on the First Data Set</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Boss, Alan; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Monet, David G.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Tarter, Jill; Charbonneau, David; Doyle, Laurance; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Bryson, Stephen T.; Buchhave, Lars; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ciardi, David; Clarke, Bruce D.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Li, Jie; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, Sren; Prsa, Andrej; Quintana, Elisa V.; Rowe, Jason; Sherry, William; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Wu, Hayley</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 117 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..117B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
