<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742L...5A</bibcode>
			<title>A Closer Look at the LkCa 15 Protoplanetary Disk</title>
			<authors>Andrews, Sean M.; Rosenfeld, Katherine A.; Wilner, David J.; Bremer, Michael</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. L5 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742L...5A</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745..119N</bibcode>
			<title>Close Companions to Young Stars. I. A Large Spectroscopic Survey in Chamaeleon I and Taurus-Auriga</title>
			<authors>Nguyen, Duy Cuong; Brandeker, Alexis; van Kerkwijk, Marten H.; Jayawardhana, Ray</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 2, article id. 119 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745..119N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...19K</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Multiplicity in Disk Evolution and Planet Formation</title>
			<authors>Kraus, Adam L.; Ireland, Michael J.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Martinache, Frantz</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...19K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745....5K</bibcode>
			<title>LkCa 15: A Young Exoplanet Caught at Formation?</title>
			<authors>Kraus, Adam L.; Ireland, Michael J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 5 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745....5K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..121Y</bibcode>
			<title>A Far-ultraviolet Atlas of Low-resolution Hubble Space Telescope Spectra of T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Yang, Hao; Herczeg, Gregory J.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Brown, Alexander; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Ingleby, Laura; Calvet, Nuria; Bergin, Edwin; Valenti, Jeff A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 121 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744..121Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..120E</bibcode>
			<title>Mapping the Shores of the Brown Dwarf Desert. III. Young Moving Groups</title>
			<authors>Evans, T. M.; Ireland, M. J.; Kraus, A. L.; Martinache, F.; Stewart, P.; Tuthill, P. G.; Lacour, S.; Carpenter, J. M.; Hillenbrand, L. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 120 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744..120E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A..60C</bibcode>
			<title>Chemistry in disks. VI. CN and HCN in protoplanetary disks</title>
			<authors>