<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740...43S</bibcode>
			<title>Dust Grain Evolution in Spatially Resolved T Tauri Binaries</title>
			<authors>Skemer, Andrew J.; Close, Laird M.; Greene, Thomas P.; Hinz, Philip M.; Hoffmann, William F.; Males, Jared R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 740, Issue 1, article id. 43 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740...43S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..196....4R</bibcode>
			<title>New Young Star Candidates in the Taurus-Auriga Region as Selected from the Wide-Field Infrared Survey Explorer</title>
			<authors>Rebull, L. M.; Koenig, X. P.; Padgett, D. L.; Terebey, S.; McGehee, P. M.; Hillenbrand, L. A.; Knapp, G. R.; Leisawitz, D.; Liu, W.; Noriega-Crespo, A.; Ressler, M. E.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Fajardo-Acosta, S.; Mainzer, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 196, Issue 1, article id. 4 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..196....4R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738..131D</bibcode>
			<title>Transitional Disks as Signposts of Young, Multiplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.; Salyk, Colette</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 2, article id. 131 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738..131D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..195....3F</bibcode>
			<title>The Spitzer Infrared Spectrograph Survey of T Tauri Stars in Taurus</title>
			<authors>Furlan, E.; Luhman, K. L.; Espaillat, C.; D'Alessio, P.; Adame, L.; Manoj, P.; Kim, K. H.; Watson, Dan M.; Forrest, W. J.; McClure, M. K.; Calvet, N.; Sargent, B. A.; Green, J. D.; Fischer, W. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 195, Issue 1, article id. 3 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..195....3F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..80K</bibcode>
			<title>Stirring up the dust: a dynamical model for halo-like dust clouds in transitional disks</title>
			<authors>Krijt, S.; Dominik, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A80</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..80K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734...98O</bibcode>
			<title>Disk Imaging Survey of Chemistry with SMA. II. Southern Sky Protoplanetary Disk Data and Full Sample Statistics</title>
			<authors>&#214;berg, Karin I.; Qi, Chunhua; Fogel, Jeffrey K. J.; Bergin, Edwin A.; Andrews, Sean M.; Espaillat, Catherine; Wilner, David J.; Pascucci, Ilaria; Kastner, Joel H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 2, article id. 98 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734...98O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734...51O</bibcode>
			<title>On the Evolution of Dust Mineralogy, from Protoplanetary Disks to Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Oliveira, Isa; Olofsson, Johan; Pontoppidan, Klaus M.; van Dishoeck, Ewine F.; Augereau, Jean-Charles; Mer&#237;n, Bruno</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 1, article id. 51 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734...51O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...42A</bibcode>
			<title>Resolved Images of Large Cavities in Protoplanetary Transition Disks</title>
			<authors>Andrews, Sean M.; Wilner, David J.; Espaillat, Catherine; Hughes, A. M.; Dullemond, C. P.; McClure, M. K.; Qi, Chunhua; Brown, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 42 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...42A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...24C</bibcode>
			<title>The Transitional Protoplanetary Disk Frequency as a Function of Age: Disk Evolution In the Coronet Cluster, Taurus, and Other 1-8 Myr Old Regions</title>
			<authors>Currie, Thayne; Sicilia-Aguilar, Aurora</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 24 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...24C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.105G</bibcode>
			<title>A dual-frequency sub-arcsecond study of proto-planetary disks at mm wavelengths: first evidence for radial variations of the dust properties</title>
			<authors>Guilloteau, S.; Dutrey, A.; Pi&#233;tu, V.; Boehler, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A105</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.105G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...731....8K</bibcode>
			<title>Mapping the Shores of the Brown Dwarf Desert. II. Multiple Star Formation in Taurus-Auriga</title>
			<authors>Kraus, Adam L.; Ireland, Michael J.; Martinache, Frantz; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 731, Issue 1, article id. 8 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...731....8K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..127I</bibcode>
			<title>Evolution of X-ray and Far-ultraviolet Disk-dispersing Radiation Fields</title>
			<authors>Ingleby, Laura; Calvet, Nuria; Hern&#225;ndez, Jesus; Brice&#241;o, Cesar; Espaillat, Catherine; Miller, Jon; Bergin, Edwin; Hartmann, Lee</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 4, article id. 127 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..127I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..193...11M</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Infrared Spectrograph Survey of Young Stars in the Chamaeleon I Star-Forming Region</title>
			<authors>Manoj, P.; Kim, K. H.; Furlan, E.; McClure, M. K.; Luhman, K. L.; Watson, Dan M.; Espaillat, C.; Calvet, N.; Najita, J. R.; D'Alessio, P.; Adame, L.; Sargent, B. A.; Forrest, W. J.; Bohac, C.; Green, J. D.; Arnold, L. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 193, Issue 1, article id. 11 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..193...11M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...47Z</bibcode>
			<title>Transitional and Pre-transitional Disks: Gap Opening by Multiple Planets?</title>
			<authors>Zhu, Zhaohuan; Nelson, Richard P.; Hartmann, Lee; Espaillat, Catherine; Calvet, Nuria</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 47 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...47Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASP..123..138V</bibcode>
			<title>Water in Star-forming Regions with the Herschel Space Observatory (WISH). I. Overview of Key Program and First Results</title>
			<authors>van Dishoeck, E. F.; Kristensen, L. E.; Benz, A. O.; Bergin, E. A.; Caselli, P.; Cernicharo, J.; Herpin, F.; Hogerheijde, M. R.; Johnstone, D.; Liseau, R.; Nisini, B.; Shipman, R.; Tafalla, M.; van der Tak, F.; Wyrowski, F.; Aikawa, Y.; Bachiller, R.; Baudry, A.; Benedettini, M.; Bjerkeli, P.; Blake, G. A.; Bontemps, S.; Braine, J.; Brinch, C.; Bruderer, S.; Chavarr&#237;a, L.; Codella, C.; Daniel, F.; de Graauw, Th.; Deul, E.; di Giorgio, A. M.; Dominik, C.; Doty, S. D.; Dubernet, M. L.; Encrenaz, P.; Feuchtgruber, H.; Fich, M.; Frieswijk, W.; Fuente, A.; Giannini, T.; Goicoechea, J. R.; Helmich, F. P.; Herczeg, G. J.; Jacq, T.; J&#248;rgensen, J. K.; Karska, A.; Kaufman, M. J.; Keto, E.; Larsson, B.; Lefloch, B.; Lis, D.; Marseille, M.; McCoey, C.; Melnick, G.; Neufeld, D.; Olberg, M.; Pagani, L.; Panic, O.; Parise, B.; Pearson, J. C.; Plume, R.; Risacher, C.; Salter, D.; Santiago-Garc&#237;a, J.; Saraceno, P.; St&#228;uber, P.; van Kempen, T. A.; Visser, R.; Viti, S.; Walmsley, M.; Wampfler, S. F.; Yildiz, U. A.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 123, issue 900, pp.138-170</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASP..123..138V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728...96A</bibcode>
			<title>Radial Structure in the TW Hya Circumstellar Disk</title>
			<authors>Akeson, R. L.; Millan-Gabet, R.; Ciardi, D. R.; Boden, A. F.; Sargent, A. I.; Monnier, J. D.; McAlister, H.; ten Brummelaar, T.; Sturmann, J.; Sturmann, L.; Turner, N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 96 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728...96A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728...49E</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer IRS Study of Infrared Variability in Transitional and Pre-transitional Disks Around T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Espaillat, C.; Furlan, E.; D'Alessio, P.; Sargent, B.; Nagel, E.; Calvet, N.; Watson, Dan M.; Muzerolle, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 1, article id. 49 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728...49E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...76V</bibcode>
			<title>Impact of Grain Evolution on the Chemical Structure of Protoplanetary Disks</title>
			<authors>Vasyunin, A. I.; Wiebe, D. S.; Birnstiel, T.; Zhukovska, S.; Henning, T.; Dullemond, C. P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 76 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...76V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727....2P</bibcode>
			<title>Surface Layer Accretion in Transitional and Conventional Disks: From Polycyclic Aromatic Hydrocarbons to Planets</title>
			<authors>Perez-Becker, Daniel; Chiang, Eugene</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727....2P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...29F</bibcode>
			<title>Chemistry of a Protoplanetary Disk with Grain Settling and Lyalpha Radiation</title>
			<authors>Fogel, Jeffrey K. J.; Bethell, Thomas J.; Bergin, Edwin A.; Calvet, Nuria; Semenov, Dmitry</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id. 29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...29F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.2485K</bibcode>
			<title>A Chandra Observation of the Obscured Star-forming Complex W40</title>
			<authors>Kuhn, Michael A.; Getman, Konstantin V.; Feigelson, Eric D.; Reipurth, Bo; Rodney, Steven A.; Garmire, Gordon P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 2485-2506 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.2485K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1735I</bibcode>
			<title>Millimeter Imaging of MWC 758: Probing the Disk Structure and Kinematics</title>
			<authors>Isella, Andrea; Natta, Antonella; Wilner, David; Carpenter, John M.; Testi, Leonardo</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1735-1741 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1735I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...524L...1B</bibcode>
			<title>Dissecting the Moth: discovery of an off-centered ring in the HD 61005 debris disk with high-resolution imaging</title>
			<authors>Buenzli, E.; Thalmann, C.; Vigan, A.; Boccaletti, A.; Chauvin, G.; Augereau, J. C.; Meyer, M. R.; M&#233;nard, F.; Desidera, S.; Messina, S.; Henning, T.; Carson, J.; Montagnier, G.; Beuzit, J. L.; Bonavita, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Lagrange, A. M.; Mesa, D.; Mouillet, D.; Quanz, S. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 524, id.L1</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...524L...1B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...524A..19F</bibcode>
			<title>Molecular content of the circumstellar disk in AB Aurigae. First detection of SO in a circumstellar disk</title>
			<authors>Fuente, A.; Cernicharo, J.; Ag&#250;ndez, M.; Bern&#233;, O.; Goicoechea, J. R.; Alonso-Albi, T.; Marcelino, N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 524, id.A19</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...524A..19F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A...2B</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for the sub-stellar companions in the LkCa15 proto-planetary disk</title>
			<authors>Bonavita, M.; Chauvin, G.; Boccaletti, A.; Pietu, V.; Baudoz, P.; Beuzit, J. L.; Dutrey, A.; Guilloteau, S.; Lagrange, A. M.; Mouillet, D.; Niccolini, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A2</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...522A...2B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722.1607W</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical Processes in Protoplanetary Disks</title>
			<authors>Walsh, Catherine; Millar, T. J.; Nomura, Hideko</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 2, pp. 1607-1623 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722.1607W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722.1226H</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Observations of the lambda Orionis Cluster. II. Disks Around Solar-type and Low-mass Stars</title>
			<authors>Hern&#225;ndez, Jes&#250;s; Morales-Calderon, Maria; Calvet, Nuria; Hartmann, L.; Muzerolle, J.; Gutermuth, R.; Luhman, K. L.; Stauffer, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 2, pp. 1226-1239 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722.1226H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720..480O</bibcode>
			<title>The Disk Imaging Survey of Chemistry with SMA. I. Taurus Protoplanetary Disk Data</title>
			<authors>&#214;berg, Karin I.; Qi, Chunhua; Fogel, Jeffrey K. J.; Bergin, Edwin A.; Andrews, Sean M.; Espaillat, Catherine; van Kempen, Tim A.; Wilner, David J.; Pascucci, Ilaria</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 1, pp. 480-493 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720..480O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140..887H</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and Composition of Two Transitional Circumstellar Disks in Corona Australis</title>
			<authors>Hughes, A. M.; Andrews, S. M.; Wilner, D. J.; Meyer, M. R.; Carpenter, J. M.; Qi, C.; Hales, A. S.; Casassus, S.; Hogerheijde, M. R.; Mamajek, E. E.; Wolf, S.; Henning, T.; Silverstone, M. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 3, pp. 887-896 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140..887H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A.110P</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of warm molecular gas and kinematics in the disc around HD 100546</title>
			<authors>Panic, O.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Hogerheijde, M. R.; Belloche, A.; G&#252;sten, R.; Boland, W.; Baryshev, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A110</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A.110P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L..87T</bibcode>
			<title>Imaging of a Transitional Disk Gap in Reflected Light: Indications of Planet Formation Around the Young Solar Analog LkCa 15</title>
			<authors>Thalmann, C.; Grady, C. A.; Goto, M.; Wisniewski, J. P.; Janson, M.; Henning, T.; Fukagawa, M.; Honda, M.; Mulders, G. D.; Min, M.; Moro-Mart&#237;n, A.; McElwain, M. W.; Hodapp, K. W.; Carson, J.; Abe, L.; Brandner, W.; Egner, S.; Feldt, M.; Fukue, T.; Golota, T.; Guyon, O.; Hashimoto, J.; Hayano, Y.; Hayashi, M.; Hayashi, S.; Ishii, M.; Kandori, R.; Knapp, G. R.; Kudo, T.; Kusakabe, N.; Kuzuhara, M.; Matsuo, T.; Miyama, S.; Morino, J.-I.; Nishimura, T.; Pyo, T.-S.; Serabyn, E.; Shibai, H.; Suto, H.; Suzuki, R.; Takami, M.; Takato, N.; Terada, H.; Tomono, D.; Turner, E. L.; Watanabe, M.; Yamada, T.; Takami, H.; Usuda, T.; Tamura, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L87-L91 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L..87T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717..693Q</bibcode>
			<title>A Large, Massive, Rotating Disk Around an Isolated Young Stellar Object</title>
			<authors>Quanz, Sascha P.; Beuther, Henrik; Steinacker, J&#252;rgen; Linz, Hendrik; Birkmann, Stephan M.; Krause, Oliver; Henning, Thomas; Zhang, Qizhou</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. 693-707 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717..693Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717..441E</bibcode>
			<title>Unveiling the Structure of Pre-transitional Disks</title>
			<authors>Espaillat, C.; D'Alessio, P.; Hern&#225;ndez, J.; Nagel, E.; Luhman, K. L.; Watson, D. M.; Calvet, N.; Muzerolle, J.; McClure, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 1, pp. 441-457 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717..441E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717...93A</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Star-Disk Interaction among the Strongest X-ray Flaring Stars in the Orion Nebula Cluster</title>
			<authors>Aarnio, Alicia N.; Stassun, Keivan G.; Matt, Sean P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 1, pp. 93-106 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717...93A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..188...75M</bibcode>
			<title>The Evolutionary State of the Pre-main Sequence Population in Ophiuchus: A Large Infrared Spectrograph Survey</title>
			<authors>McClure, M. K.; Furlan, E.; Manoj, P.; Luhman, K. L.; Watson, D. M.; Forrest, W. J.; Espaillat, C.; Calvet, N.; D'Alessio, P.; Sargent, B.; Tobin, J. J.; Chiang, Hsin-Fang</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 188, Issue 1, pp. 75-122 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..188...75M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714.1511H</bibcode>
			<title>Chemistry in Disks. III. Photochemistry and X-ray Driven Chemistry Probed by the Ethynyl Radical (CCH) in DM Tau, LkCa 15, and MWC 480</title>
			<authors>Henning, Th.; Semenov, D.; Guilloteau, St.; Dutrey, A.; Hersant, F.; Wakelam, V.; Chapillon, E.; Launhardt, R.; Pi&#233;tu, V.; Schreyer, K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 2, pp. 1511-1520 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714.1511H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..925C</bibcode>
			<title>The Nature of Transition Circumstellar Disks. I. The Ophiuchus Molecular Cloud</title>
			<authors>Cieza, Lucas A.; Schreiber, Matthias R.; Romero, Gisela A.; Mora, Marcelo D.; Merin, Bruno; Swift, Jonathan J.; Orellana, Mariana; Williams, Jonathan P.; Harvey, Paul M.; Evans, Neal J., II</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 2, article id. 925-941 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..925C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..274N</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Spectroscopy of the Transition Object TW Hya</title>
			<authors>Najita, Joan R.; Carr, John S.; Strom, Stephen E.; Watson, Dan M.; Pascucci, Ilaria; Hollenbach, David; Gorti, Uma; Keller, Luke</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 274-286 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..274N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711.1280S</bibcode>
			<title>ISM Dust Grains and N-band Spectral Variability in the Spatially Resolved Subarcsecond Binary UY Aur</title>
			<authors>Skemer, Andrew J.; Close, Laird M.; Hinz, Philip M.; Hoffmann, William F.; Greene, Thomas P.; Males, Jared R.; Beck, Tracy L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 2, pp. 1280-1290 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711.1280S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..11M</bibcode>
			<title>Full two-dimensional radiative transfer modelling of the transitional disk LkCa 15</title>
			<authors>Mulders, G. D.; Dominik, C.; Min, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A11</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..11M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARep...54..163A</bibcode>
			<title>A search for Keplerian periods in the brightness variations of T Tauri and Ae Herbig stars</title>
			<authors>Artemenko, S. A.; Grankin, K. N.; Petrov, P. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Reports, Volume 54, Issue 2, pp.163-172</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARep...54..163A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..186..259R</bibcode>
			<title>The Taurus Spitzer Survey: New Candidate Taurus Members Selected Using Sensitive Mid-Infrared Photometry</title>
			<authors>Rebull, L. M.; Padgett, D. L.; McCabe, C.-E.; Hillenbrand, L. A.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Noriega-Crespo, A.; Carey, S. J.; Brooke, T.; Huard, T.; Terebey, S.; Audard, M.; Monin, J.-L.; Fukagawa, M.; G&#252;del, M.; Knapp, G. R.; Menard, F.; Allen, L. E.; Angione, J. R.; Baldovin-Saavedra, C.; Bouvier, J.; Briggs, K.; Dougados, C.; Evans, N. J.; Flagey, N.; Guieu, S.; Grosso, N.; Glauser, A. M.; Harvey, P.; Hines, D.; Latter, W. B.; Skinner, S. L.; Strom, S.; Tromp, J.; Wolf, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 186, Issue 2, pp. 259-307 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..186..259R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1786Y</bibcode>
			<title>High-Velocity Jets and Slowly Rotating Envelope in B335</title>
			<authors>Yen, Hsi-Wei; Takakuwa, Shigehisa; Ohashi, Nagayoshi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1786-1799 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1786Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710..265P</bibcode>
			<title>Ruling Out Stellar Companions and Resolving the Innermost Regions of Transitional Disks with the Keck Interferometer</title>
			<authors>Pott, Jorg-Uwe; Perrin, Marshall D.; Furlan, Elise; Ghez, Andrea M.; Herbst, Tom M.; Metchev, Stanimir</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 265-278 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710..265P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJS..186..111L</bibcode>
			<title>The Disk Population of the Taurus Star-Forming Region</title>
			<authors>Luhman, K. L.; Allen, P. R.; Espaillat, C.; Hartmann, L.; Calvet, N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 186, Issue 1, pp. 111-174 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJS..186..111L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..185..289R</bibcode>
			<title>The Infrared Telescope Facility (IRTF) Spectral Library: Cool Stars</title>
			<authors>Rayner, John T.; Cushing, Michael C.; Vacca, William D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 185, Issue 2, pp. 289-432 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..185..289R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704L..15M</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for Dynamical Changes in a Transitional Protoplanetary Disk with Mid-Infrared Variability</title>
			<authors>Muzerolle, James; Flaherty, Kevin; Balog, Zoltan; Furlan, Elise; Smith, Paul S.; Allen, Lori; Calvet, Nuria; D'Alessio, Paola; Megeath, S. Thomas; Muench, August; Rieke, George H.; Sherry, William H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 704, Issue 1, pp. L15-L19 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704L..15M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704.1482P</bibcode>
			<title>A New Raytracer for Modeling AU-Scale Imaging of Lines from Protoplanetary Disks</title>
			<authors>Pontoppidan, Klaus M.; Meijerink, Rowin; Dullemond, Cornelis P.; Blake, Geoffrey A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 2, pp. 1482-1494 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704.1482P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704..531K</bibcode>
			<title>The Coevality of Young Binary Systems</title>
			<authors>Kraus, Adam L.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 1, pp. 531-547 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704..531K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704..496B</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for Dust Clearing Through Resolved Submillimeter Imaging</title>
			<authors>Brown, J. M.; Blake, G. A.; Qi, C.; Dullemond, C. P.; Wilner, D. J.; Williams, J. P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 1, pp. 496-502 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704..496B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703L.137I</bibcode>
			<title>Far-Ultraviolet H2 Emission from Circumstellar Disks</title>
			<authors>Ingleby, Laura; Calvet, Nuria; Bergin, Edwin; Yerasi, Ashwin; Espaillat, Catherine; Herczeg, Gregory; Roueff, Evelyne; Abgrall, Herv&#233;; Hern&#225;ndez, Jesus; Brice&#241;o, C&#233;sar; Pascucci, Ilaria; Miller, Jon; Fogel, Jeffrey; Hartmann, Lee; Meyer, Michael; Carpenter, John; Crockett, Nathan; McClure, Melissa</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. L137-L141 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703L.137I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.1964F</bibcode>
			<title>Disk Evolution in the Three Nearby Star-forming Regions of Taurus, Chamaeleon, and Ophiuchus</title>
			<authors>Furlan, E.; Watson, Dan M.; McClure, M. K.; Manoj, P.; Espaillat, C.; D'Alessio, P.; Calvet, N.; Kim, K. H.; Sargent, B. A.; Forrest, W. J.; Hartmann, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. 1964-1983 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.1964F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.1511K</bibcode>
			<title>Unusually Wide Binaries: Are They Wide or Unusual?</title>
			<authors>Kraus, Adam L.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. 1511-1530 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.1511K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...505..695F</bibcode>
			<title>Results from DROXO. II. [Ne II] and X-ray emission from rho Ophiuchi young stellar objects</title>
			<authors>Flaccomio, E.; Stelzer, B.; Sciortino, S.; Micela, G.; Pillitteri, I.; Testi, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 505, Issue 2, 2009, pp.695-706</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...505..695F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..698S</bibcode>
			<title>A Millimeter-wave Interferometric Study of Dust and CO Disks Around Late Spectral Type Stars in Taurus-Auriga</title>
			<authors>Schaefer, G. H.; Dutrey, A.; Guilloteau, S.; Simon, M.; White, R. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 698-709 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..698S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..260I</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and Evolution of Pre-main-sequence Circumstellar Disks</title>
			<authors>Isella, Andrea; Carpenter, John M.; Sargent, Anneila I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 260-282 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..260I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700.1017K</bibcode>
			<title>Mid-Infrared Spectra of Transitional Disks in the Chamaeleon I Cloud</title>
			<authors>Kim, K. H.; Watson, Dan M.; Manoj, P.; Furlan, E.; Najita, J.; Forrest, W. J.; Sargent, B.; Espaillat, C.; Calvet, N.; Luhman, K. L.; McClure, M. K.; Green, J. D.; Harrold, Samuel T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 1017-1025 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700.1017K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..330S</bibcode>
			<title>High-resolution 5 mum Spectroscopy of Transitional Disks</title>
			<authors>Salyk, C.; Blake, G. A.; Boogert, A. C. A.; Brown, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 330-347 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..330S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501.1013S</bibcode>
			<title>Variability of the transitional T Tauri star T Chamaeleontis</title>
			<authors>Schisano, E.; Covino, E.; Alcal&#225;, J. M.; Esposito, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Guenther, E. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 3, 2009, pp.1013-1030</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501.1013S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..182..477S</bibcode>
			<title>Dust Processing and Grain Growth in Protoplanetary Disks in the Taurus-Auriga Star-Forming Region</title>
			<authors>Sargent, B. A.; Forrest, W. J.; Tayrien, C.; McClure, M. K.; Watson, Dan M.; Sloan, G. C.; Li, A.; Manoj, P.; Bohac, C. J.; Furlan, E.; Kim, K. H.; Green, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 182, Issue 2, pp. 477-508 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..182..477S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698..131H</bibcode>
			<title>A Spatially Resolved Inner Hole in the Disk Around GM Aurigae</title>
			<authors>Hughes, A. Meredith; Andrews, Sean M.; Espaillat, Catherine; Wilner, David J.; Calvet, Nuria; D'Alessio, Paola; Qi, Chunhua; Williams, Jonathan P.; Hogerheijde, Michiel R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 1, pp. 131-142 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698..131H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009RMxAC..35...33D</bibcode>
			<title>Transitional disks around young low mass stars</title>
			<authors>D'Alessio, P.</authors>
			<journal>XII Latin American IAU Regional Meeting (Eds. G. Magris, G. Bruzual, &amp; L. Carigi) Revista Mexicana de Astronom&#237;a y Astrof&#237;sica (Serie de Conferencias) Vol. 35, pp. 33-38 (2009) (http://www.astroscu.unam.mx/~rmaa/)</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009RMxAC..35...33D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696L..84C</bibcode>
			<title>Primordial Circumstellar Disks in Binary Systems: Evidence for Reduced Lifetimes</title>
			<authors>Cieza, Lucas A.; Padgett, Deborah L.; Allen, Lori E.; McCabe, Caer E.; Brooke, Timothy Y.; Carey, Sean J.; Chapman, Nicholas L.; Fukagawa, Misato; Huard, Tracy L.; Noriga-Crespo, Alberto; Peterson, Dawn E.; Rebull, Luisa M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 696, Issue 1, pp. L84-L88 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696L..84C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696..143P</bibcode>
			<title>The Different Evolution of Gas and Dust in Disks around Sun-Like and Cool Stars</title>
			<authors>Pascucci, I.; Apai, D.; Luhman, K.; Henning, Th.; Bouwman, J.; Meyer, M. R.; Lahuis, F.; Natta, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 1, pp. 143-159 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696..143P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...695.1648N</bibcode>
			<title>Disk Braking in young Stars: Probing Rotation in Chamaeleon i and Taurus-Auriga</title>
			<authors>Nguyen, Duy Cuong; Jayawardhana, Ray; van Kerkwijk, Marten H.; Brandeker, Alexis; Scholz, Alexander; Damjanov, Ivana</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 695, Issue 2, pp. 1648-1656 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...695.1648N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJS..180...84W</bibcode>
			<title>Crystalline Silicates and Dust Processing in the Protoplanetary Disks of the Taurus Young Cluster</title>
			<authors>Watson, Dan M.; Leisenring, Jarron M.; Furlan, Elise; Bohac, C. J.; Sargent, B.; Forrest, W. J.; Calvet, Nuria; Hartmann, Lee; Nordhaus, Jason T.; Green, Joel D.; Kim, K. H.; Sloan, G. C.; Chen, C. H.; Keller, L. D.; d'Alessio, Paola; Najita, J.; Uchida, Keven I.; Houck, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 180, Issue 1, pp. 84-101 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJS..180...84W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...494..147L</bibcode>
			<title>Rotating molecular outflows: the young T Tauri star in CB 26</title>
			<authors>Launhardt, R.; Pavlyuchenkov, Ya.; Gueth, F.; Chen, X.; Dutrey, A.; Guilloteau, S.; Henning, Th.; Pi&#233;tu, V.; Schreyer, K.; Semenov, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 494, Issue 1, 2009, pp.147-156</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...494..147L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493L..49H</bibcode>
			<title>Cold CO in circumstellar disks. On the effects of photodesorption and vertical mixing</title>
			<authors>Hersant, F.; Wakelam, V.; Dutrey, A.; Guilloteau, S.; Herbst, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 3, 2009, pp.L49-L52</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493L..49H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689L.145E</bibcode>
			<title>A Slowly Accreting ~10 Myr-old Transitional Disk in Orion OB1a</title>
			<authors>Espaillat, C.; Muzerolle, J.; Hern&#225;ndez, J.; Brice&#241;o, C.; Calvet, N.; D'Alessio, P.; McClure, M.; Watson, D. M.; Hartmann, L.; Sargent, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 2, pp. L145-L148.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689L.145E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689..513T</bibcode>
			<title>A Tale of Two Herbig Ae Stars, MWC 275 and AB Aurigae: Comprehensive Models for Spectral Energy Distribution and Interferometry</title>
			<authors>Tannirkulam, A.; Monnier, J. D.; Harries, T. J.; Millan-Gabet, R.; Zhu, Z.; Pedretti, E.; Ireland, M.; Tuthill, P.; ten Brummelaar, T.; McAlister, H.; Farrington, C.; Goldfinger, P. J.; Sturmann, J.; Sturmann, L.; Turner, N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 1, pp. 513-531.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689..513T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...688.1326B</bibcode>
			<title>The TEXES Survey for H2 Emission from Protoplanetary Disks</title>
			<authors>Bitner, Martin A.; Richter, Matthew J.; Lacy, John H.; Herczeg, Gregory J.; Greathouse, Thomas K.; Jaffe, Daniel T.; Salyk, Colette; Blake, Geoffrey A.; Hollenbach, David J.; Doppmann, Greg W.; Najita, Joan R.; Currie, Thayne</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 688, Issue 2, pp. 1326-1344.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...688.1326B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...491..821S</bibcode>
			<title>Chemistry in disks. II. Poor molecular content of the AB Aurigae disk</title>
			<authors>Schreyer, K.; Guilloteau, S.; Semenov, D.; Bacmann, A.; Chapillon, E.; Dutrey, A.; Gueth, F.; Henning, T.; Hersant, F.; Launhardt, R.; Pety, J.; Pi&#233;tu, V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 491, Issue 3, 2008, pp.821-827</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...491..821S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1168N</bibcode>
			<title>CO Fundamental Emission from V836 Tauri</title>
			<authors>Najita, Joan R.; Crockett, Nathan; Carr, John S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1168-1179.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1168N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...491..219P</bibcode>
			<title>Gas and dust mass in the disc around the Herbig Ae star HD 169142</title>
			<authors>Panic, O.; Hogerheijde, M. R.; Wilner, D.; Qi, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 491, Issue 1, 2008, pp.219-227</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...491..219P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...490L..15D</bibcode>
			<title>Cavities in inner disks: the GM Aurigae case</title>
			<authors>Dutrey, A.; Guilloteau, S.; Pi&#233;tu, V.; Chapillon, E.; Gueth, F.; Henning, T.; Launhardt, R.; Pavlyuchenkov, Y.; Schreyer, K.; Semenov, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 490, Issue 2, 2008, pp.L15-L18</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...490L..15D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1195H</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer View of Protoplanetary Disks in the gamma Velorum Cluster</title>
			<authors>Hern&#225;ndez, Jes&#250;s; Hartmann, Lee; Calvet, Nuria; Jeffries, R. D.; Gutermuth, R.; Muzerolle, J.; Stauffer, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1195-1208.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1195H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488..565C</bibcode>
			<title>Disks around CQ Tauri and MWC 758: dense PDR or gas dispersal?</title>
			<authors>Chapillon, E.; Guilloteau, S.; Dutrey, A.; Pi&#233;tu, V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.565-578</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488..565C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488..235G</bibcode>
			<title>Spatially resolved H2 emission from the disk around T Tau N</title>
			<authors>Gustafsson, M.; Labadie, L.; Herbst, T. M.; Kasper, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 1, 2008, pp.235-244</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488..235G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...487..965S</bibcode>
			<title>An assessment of Li abundances in weak-lined and classical T Tauri stars of the Taurus-Auriga association</title>
			<authors>Sestito, P.; Palla, F.; Randich, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 487, Issue 3, 2008, pp.965-973</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...487..965S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682L.125E</bibcode>
			<title>Confirmation of a Gapped Primordial Disk around LkCa 15</title>
			<authors>Espaillat, Catherine; Calvet, Nuria; Luhman, Kevin L.; Muzerolle, James; D'Alessio, Paola</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. L125-L128.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682L.125E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...486..245C</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the nature of embedded young stellar objects through silicate, ice and millimeter observations</title>
			<authors>Crapsi, A.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Hogerheijde, M. R.; Pontoppidan, K. M.; Dullemond, C. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 486, Issue 1, 2008, pp.245-254</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...486..245C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...486..239K</bibcode>
			<title>Molecules in the circumstellar disk orbiting BP Piscium</title>
			<authors>Kastner, J. H.; Zuckerman, B.; Forveille, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 486, Issue 1, 2008, pp.239-244</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...486..239K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678L..59I</bibcode>
			<title>The Disk Around CoKu Tauri/4: Circumbinary, Not Transitional</title>
			<authors>Ireland, M. J.; Kraus, A. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 1, pp. L59-L62.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678L..59I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1119H</bibcode>
			<title>Gas and Dust Emission at the Outer Edge of Protoplanetary Disks</title>
			<authors>Hughes, A. M.; Wilner, D. J.; Qi, C.; Hogerheijde, M. R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1119-1126.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1119H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1088B</bibcode>
			<title>Quiescent H2 Emission From Pre-Main-Sequence Stars in Chamaeleon I</title>
			<authors>Bary, Jeffrey S.; Weintraub, David A.; Shukla, Sonali J.; Leisenring, Jarron M.; Kastner, Joel H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1088-1098.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1088B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1070S</bibcode>
			<title>Variability of Disk Emission in Pre-Main-Sequence and Related Stars. I. HD 31648 and HD 163296: Isolated Herbig Ae Stars Driving Herbig-Haro Flows</title>
			<authors>Sitko, Michael L.; Carpenter, William J.; Kimes, Robin L.; Wilde, J. Leon; Lynch, David K.; Russell, Ray W.; Rudy, Richard J.; Mazuk, Stephan M.; Venturini, Catherine C.; Puetter, Richard C.; Grady, Carol A.; Polomski, Elisha F.; Wisnewski, John P.; Brafford, Suellen M.; Hammel, H. B.; Perry, R. Brad</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1070-1087.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1070S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJS..175..277D</bibcode>
			<title>The SCUBA Legacy Catalogues: Submillimeter-Continuum Objects Detected by SCUBA</title>
			<authors>Di Francesco, James; Johnstone, Doug; Kirk, Helen; MacKenzie, Todd; Ledwosinska, Elizabeth</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 175, Issue 1, pp. 277-295.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJS..175..277D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673L.195S</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical and Thermal Structure of Protoplanetary Disks as Observed with ALMA</title>
			<authors>Semenov, D.; Pavlyuchenkov, Ya.; Henning, Th.; Wolf, S.; Launhardt, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 2, pp. L195-L198.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673L.195S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...478L..31G</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the circumbinary dust disk surrounding HH 30</title>
			<authors>Guilloteau, S.; Dutrey, A.; Pety, J.; Gueth, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 478, Issue 2, February I 2008, pp.L31-L34</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...478L..31G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673L..63P</bibcode>
			<title>The Inner Radius of T Tauri Disks Estimated from Near-Infrared Interferometry: The Importance of Scattered Light</title>
			<authors>Pinte, C.; M&#233;nard, F.; Berger, J. P.; Benisty, M.; Malbet, F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. L63-L66.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673L..63P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..477P</bibcode>
			<title>Medium-Separation Binaries Do Not Affect the First Steps of Planet Formation</title>
			<authors>Pascucci, I.; Apai, D.; Hardegree-Ullman, E. E.; Kim, J. S.; Meyer, M. R.; Bouwman, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 477-486.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..477P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...477..839C</bibcode>
			<title>A search for mid-infrared molecular hydrogen emission from protoplanetary disks</title>
			<authors>Carmona, A.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Henning, Th.; Pavlyuchenkov, Ya.; Dullemond, C. P.; Goto, M.; Thi, W. F.; Bouwman, J.; Waters, L. B. F. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 477, Issue 3, 2008, pp.839-852</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...477..839C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...670L.135E</bibcode>
			<title>On the Diversity of the Taurus Transitional Disks: UX Tauri A and LkCa 15</title>
			<authors>Espaillat, C.; Calvet, N.; D'Alessio, P.; Hern&#225;ndez, J.; Qi, C.; Hartmann, L.; Furlan, E.; Watson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 670, Issue 2, pp. L135-L138.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...670L.135E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...476..853C</bibcode>
			<title>A search for near-infrared molecular hydrogen emission in the CTTS LkHalpha 264 and the debris disk 49 Ceti</title>
			<authors>Carmona, A.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Henning, Th.; Goto, M.; Fedele, D.; Stecklum, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 476, Issue 2, December III 2007, pp.853-862</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...476..853C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...473L..21B</bibcode>
			<title>The evolution of stars in the Taurus-Auriga T association</title>
			<authors>Bertout, C.; Siess, L.; Cabrit, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 473, Issue 3, October III 2007, pp.L21-L24</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...473L..21B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379.1658R</bibcode>
			<title>Molecular hydrogen emission from discs in the eta Chamaeleontis cluster</title>
			<authors>Ramsay Howat, S. K.; Greaves, J. S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 379, Issue 4, pp. 1658-1664.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379.1658R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664..964H</bibcode>
			<title>ASTE Submillimeter Observations of a Young Stellar Object Condensation in Cederblad 110</title>
			<authors>Hiramatsu, Masaaki; Hayakawa, Takahiro; Tatematsu, Ken'ichi; Kamegai, Kazuhisa; Onishi, Toshikazu; Mizuno, Akira; Yamaguchi, Nobuyuki; Hasegawa, Tetsuo</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 2, pp. 964-974.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664..964H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...469..213I</bibcode>
			<title>Millimeter imaging of HD 163296: probing the disk structure and kinematics</title>
			<authors>Isella, A.; Testi, L.; Natta, A.; Neri, R.; Wilner, D.; Qi, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 469, Issue 1, July I 2007, pp.213-222</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...469..213I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.378..369N</bibcode>
			<title>Demographics of transition objects</title>
			<authors>Najita, Joan R.; Strom, Stephen E.; Muzerolle, James</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 378, Issue 1, pp. 369-378.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.378..369N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662..413K</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Mass and Environment in Multiple-Star Formation: A 2MASS Survey of Wide Multiplicity in Three Young Associations</title>
			<authors>Kraus, Adam L.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 1, pp. 413-430.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662..413K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.377.1324C</bibcode>
			<title>Cavity opening by a giant planet in a protoplanetary disc and effects on planetary migration</title>
			<authors>Crida, A.; Morbidelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 377, Issue 3, pp. 1324-1336.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.377.1324C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..469K</bibcode>
			<title>H I 21 cm Emission as a Tracer of Gas During the Evolution from Protoplanetary to Debris Disks</title>
			<authors>Kamp, I.; Freudling, W.; Chengalur, Jayaram N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 469-478.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..469K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..441W</bibcode>
			<title>The Chemistry of Multiply Deuterated Molecules in Protoplanetary Disks. I. The Outer Disk</title>
			<authors>Willacy, K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 441-460.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..441W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...467..163P</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the structure of protoplanetary disks: a comparative study of DM Tau, LkCa 15, and MWC 480</title>
			<authors>Pi&#233;tu, V.; Dutrey, A.; Guilloteau, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 467, Issue 1, May III 2007, pp.163-178</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...467..163P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007RMxAA..43..155L</bibcode>
			<title>Mass determination for T Tauri stars from JHK Photometry</title>
			<authors>L&#243;pez-Chico, T.; Salas, L.</authors>
			<journal>Revista Mexicana de Astronom&#237;a y Astrof&#237;sica Vol. 43, pp. 155-171 (2007) (http://www.astroscu.unam.mx/~rmaa/)</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007RMxAA..43..155L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJS..169..328R</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting Spectral Energy Distributions from Young Stellar Objects. II. Fitting Observed SEDs Using a Large Grid of Precomputed Models</title>
			<authors>Robitaille, Thomas P.; Whitney, Barbara A.; Indebetouw, Remy; Wood, Kenneth</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 169, Issue 2, pp. 328-352.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJS..169..328R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658..462V</bibcode>
			<title>Relation between the Luminosity of Young Stellar Objects and Their Circumstellar Environment</title>
			<authors>Vinkovic, Dejan; Jurkic, Tomislav</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 1, pp. 462-479.</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658..462V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...464..615D</bibcode>
			<title>Chemistry in disks. I. Deep search for N2H+ in the protoplanetary disks around LkCa 15, MWC 480, and DM Tauri</title>
			<authors>Dutrey, A.; Henning, T.; Guilloteau, S.; Semenov, D.; Pi&#233;tu, V.; Schreyer, K.; Bacmann, A.; Launhardt, R.; Pety, J.; Gueth, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 464, Issue 2, March III 2007, pp.615-623</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...464..615D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...462..977K</bibcode>
			<title>The photophoretic sweeping of dust in transient protoplanetary disks</title>
			<authors>Krauss, O.; Wurm, G.; Mousis, O.; Petit, J.-M.; Horner, J.; Alibert, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 462, Issue 3, February II 2007, pp.977-987</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...462..977K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....132.2469K</bibcode>
			<title>Mid-Infrared Observations of T Tauri Stars: Probing the Star-Disk Connection in Rotational Evolution</title>
			<authors>Kundurthy, Praveen; Meyer, Michael R.; Robberto, Massimo; Beckwith, Steven V. W.; Herbst, Tom</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 132, Issue 6, pp. 2469-2477.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....132.2469K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460L..43P</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the inner dust disks surrounding LkCa 15 and MWC 480 at mm wavelengths</title>
			<authors>Pi&#233;tu, V.; Dutrey, A.; Guilloteau, S.; Chapillon, E.; Pety, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 3, December IV 2006, pp.L43-L47</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460L..43P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460..499B</bibcode>
			<title>A kinematic study of the Taurus-Auriga T association</title>
			<authors>Bertout, C.; Genova, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 2, December III 2006, pp.499-518</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460..499B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...456..535S</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of the dust evolution in the circumstellar disks of T Tauri stars</title>
			<authors>Schegerer, A.; Wolf, S.; Voshchinnikov, N. V.; Przygodda, F.; Kessler-Silacci, J. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 456, Issue 2, September III 2006, pp.535-548</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...456..535S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJS..165..568F</bibcode>
			<title>A Survey and Analysis of Spitzer Infrared Spectrograph Spectra of T Tauri Stars in Taurus</title>
			<authors>Furlan, E.; Hartmann, L.; Calvet, N.; D'Alessio, P.; Franco-Hern&#225;ndez, R.; Forrest, W. J.; Watson, D. M.; Uchida, K. I.; Sargent, B.; Green, J. D.; Keller, L. D.; Herter, T. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 165, Issue 2, pp. 568-605.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJS..165..568F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...647.1426N</bibcode>
			<title>Molecular Line Emission from Gravitationally Unstable Protoplanetary Disks</title>
			<authors>Narayanan, Desika; Kulesa, Craig A.; Boss, Alan; Walker, Christopher K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 647, Issue 2, pp. 1426-1436.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...647.1426N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJS..165..256H</bibcode>
			<title>The Origins of Fluorescent H2 Emission From T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Herczeg, Gregory J.; Linsky, Jeffrey L.; Walter, Frederick M.; Gahm, G&#246; sta F.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 165, Issue 1, pp. 256-282.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJS..165..256H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...645.1283P</bibcode>
			<title>The SPITZER c2d Survey of Weak-Line T Tauri Stars. I. Initial Results</title>
			<authors>Padgett, Deborah L.; Cieza, Lucas; Stapelfeldt, Karl R.; Evans, Neal J., II; Koerner, David; Sargent, Anneila; Fukagawa, Misato; van Dishoeck, Ewine F.; Augereau, Jean-Charles; Allen, Lori; Blake, Geoff; Brooke, Tim; Chapman, Nicholas; Harvey, Paul; Porras, Alicia; Lai, Shih-Ping; Mundy, Lee; Myers, Philip C.; Spiesman, William; Wahhaj, Zahed</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 645, Issue 2, pp. 1283-1296.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...645.1283P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644L..71S</bibcode>
			<title>Silicate Emission Profiles from Low-Mass Protostellar Disks in the Orion Nebula: Evidence for Growth and Thermal Processing of Grains</title>
			<authors>Shuping, R. Y.; Kassis, Marc; Morris, Mark; Smith, Nathan; Bally, John</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 1, pp. L71-L74.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644L..71S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644.1202W</bibcode>
			<title>Turbulence-driven Diffusion in Protoplanetary Disks: Chemical Effects in the Outer Regions</title>
			<authors>Willacy, Karen; Langer, William; Allen, Mark; Bryden, Geoffrey</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 2, pp. 1202-1213.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644.1202W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...452..897C</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal stripping and disk kinematics in the RW Aurigae system</title>
			<authors>Cabrit, S.; Pety, J.; Pesenti, N.; Dougados, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 452, Issue 3, June IV 2006, pp.897-906</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...452..897C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...639..275K</bibcode>
			<title>c2d Spitzer IRS Spectra of Disks around T Tauri Stars. I. Silicate Emission and Grain Growth</title>
			<authors>Kessler-Silacci, Jacqueline; Augereau, Jean-Charles; Dullemond, Cornelis P.; Geers, Vincent; Lahuis, Fred; Evans, Neal J., II; van Dishoeck, Ewine F.; Blake, Geoffrey A.; Boogert, A. C. Adwin; Brown, Joanna; J&#248;rgensen, Jes K.; Knez, Claudia; Pontoppidan, Klaus M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 639, Issue 1, pp. 275-291.</journal>
			<date>3/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...639..275K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...636..932M</bibcode>
			<title>Investigating Disk Evolution: A High Spatial Resolution Mid-Infrared Survey of T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>McCabe, C.; Ghez, A. M.; Prato, L.; Duch&#234;ne, G.; Fisher, R. S.; Telesco, C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 636, Issue 2, pp. 932-951.</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...636..932M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...446..211R</bibcode>
			<title>Large dust particles in disks around T Tauri stars</title>
			<authors>Rodmann, J.; Henning, Th.; Chandler, C. J.; Mundy, L. G.; Wilner, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 446, Issue 1, January IV 2006, pp.211-221</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...446..211R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...635.1173A</bibcode>
			<title>Keck Interferometer Observations of Classical and Weak-line T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Akeson, R. L.; Boden, A. F.; Monnier, J. D.; Millan-Gabet, R.; Beichman, C.; Beletic, J.; Calvet, N.; Hartmann, L.; Hillenbrand, L.; Koresko, C.; Sargent, A.; Tannirkulam, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 635, Issue 2, pp. 1173-1181.</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...635.1173A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...635..422C</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for J- and H-Band Excess in Classical T Tauri Stars and the Implications for Disk Structure and Estimated Ages</title>
			<authors>Cieza, Lucas A.; Kessler-Silacci, Jacqueline E.; Jaffe, Daniel T.; Harvey, Paul M.; Evans, Neal J., II</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 635, Issue 1, pp. 422-441.</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...635..422C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...443..945P</bibcode>
			<title>Sub-arcsec imaging of the AB Aur molecular disk and envelope at millimeter wavelengths: a non Keplerian disk</title>
			<authors>Pi&#233;tu, V.; Guilloteau, S.; Dutrey, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 443, Issue 3, December I 2005, pp.945-954</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...443..945P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...632..973J</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Inner 200 AU of Low-Mass Protostars with the Submillimeter Array: Dust and Organic Molecules in NGC 1333 IRAS 2A</title>
			<authors>J&#248;rgensen, Jes K.; Bourke, Tyler L.; Myers, Philip C.; Sch&#246;ier, Fredrik L.; van Dishoeck, Ewine F.; Wilner, David J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 632, Issue 2, pp. 973-981.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...632..973J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...631.1134A</bibcode>
			<title>Circumstellar Dust Disks in Taurus-Auriga: The Submillimeter Perspective</title>
			<authors>Andrews, Sean M.; Williams, Jonathan P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 631, Issue 2, pp. 1134-1160.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...631.1134A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...438..769D</bibcode>
			<title>Pre-main sequence star Proper Motion Catalogue</title>
			<authors>Ducourant, C.; Teixeira, R.; P&#233;ri&#233;, J. P.; Lecampion, J. F.; Guibert, J.; Sartori, M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 438, Issue 2, August I 2005, pp.769-778</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...438..769D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005AJ....129.2294M</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Substellar Companions around 15 Weak-Lined T Tauri Stars with the Planetary Camera 2 of the Hubble Space Telescope</title>
			<authors>Massarotti, Alessandro; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo; Brown, Robert A.; Oppenheimer, Benjamin D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 129, Issue 5, pp. 2294-2307.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005AJ....129.2294M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622..404K</bibcode>
			<title>8-13 mum Spectroscopy of Young Stellar Objects: Evolution of the Silicate Feature</title>
			<authors>Kessler-Silacci, Jacqueline E.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Blake, Geoffrey A.; Meyer, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 1, pp. 404-429.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622..404K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...620..347S</bibcode>
			<title>Search for 17 mum H2 Pure Rotational Emission from Circumstellar Disks</title>
			<authors>Sako, S.; Yamashita, T.; Kataza, H.; Miyata, T.; Okamoto, Y. K.; Honda, M.; Fujiyoshi, T.; Onaka, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 620, Issue 1, pp. 347-354.</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...620..347S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005AJ....129..935C</bibcode>
			<title>Disk Evolution in the Orion OB1 Association</title>
			<authors>Calvet, Nuria; Brice&#241;o, Cesar; Hern&#225;ndez, Jesus; Hoyer, Sergio; Hartmann, Lee; Sicilia-Aguilar, Aurora; Megeath, S. T.; D'Alessio, Paola</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 129, Issue 2, pp. 935-946.</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005AJ....129..935C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Sci...307...68G</bibcode>
			<title>Disks Around Stars and the Growth of Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Greaves, Jane S.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 307, Issue 5706, pp. 68-71 (2005).</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Sci...307...68G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...429..531H</bibcode>
			<title>Turbulence in circumstellar disks</title>
			<authors>Hersant, F.; Dubrulle, B.; Hur&#233;, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.429, p.531-542 (2005)</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...429..531H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...614L.133B</bibcode>
			<title>A New Probe of the Planet-forming Region in T Tauri Disks</title>
			<authors>Bergin, Edwin; Calvet, Nuria; Sitko, Michael L.; Abgrall, Herve; D'Alessio, Paola; Herczeg, Gregory J.; Roueff, Evelyne; Qi, Chunhua; Lynch, David K.; Russell, Ray W.; Brafford, Suellen M.; Perry, R. Brad</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 614, Issue 2, pp. L133-L136.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...614L.133B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...425..973M</bibcode>
			<title>On the alignment of Classical T Tauri stars with the magnetic  field in the Taurus-Auriga molecular cloud</title>
			<authors>M&#233;nard, F.; Duch&#234;ne, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.425, p.973-980 (2004)</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...425..973M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...425..955T</bibcode>
			<title>Organic molecules in protoplanetary disks around T Tauri and Herbig Ae stars</title>
			<authors>Thi, W.-F.; van Zadelhoff, G.-J.; van Dishoeck, E. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.425, p.955-972 (2004)</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...425..955T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.351L..99G</bibcode>
			<title>Dense gas discs around T Tauri stars</title>
			<authors>Greaves, J. S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 351, Issue 4, pp. L99-L104.</journal>
			<date>7/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.351L..99G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...607L..51C</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of H2D+: Measuring the Midplane Degree of Ionization in the Disks of DM Tauri and TW Hydrae</title>
			<authors>Ceccarelli, C.; Dominik, C.; Lefloch, B.; Caselli, P.; Caux, E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 607, Issue 1, pp. L51-L54.</journal>
			<date>5/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...607L..51C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...604..741H</bibcode>
			<title>An Assessment of Dynamical Mass Constraints on Pre-Main-Sequence Evolutionary Tracks</title>
			<authors>Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; White, Russel J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 604, Issue 2, pp. 741-757.</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...604..741H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...418..185S</bibcode>
			<title>On the origin of H2CO abundance enhancements in low-mass protostars</title>
			<authors>Sch&#246;ier, F. L.; J&#248;rgensen, J. K.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Blake, G. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.418, p.185-202 (2004)</journal>
			<date>4/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...418..185S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.348.1301U</bibcode>
			<title>Multisite observations of SU Aurigae</title>
			<authors>Unruh, Y. C.; Donati, J.-F.; Oliveira, J. M.; Collier Cameron, A.; Catala, C.; Henrichs, H. F.; Johns-Krull, C. M.; Foing, B.; Hao, J.; Cao, H.; Landstreet, J. D.; Stempels, H. C.; de Jong, J. A.; Telting, J.; Walton, N.; Ehrenfreund, P.; Hatzes, A. P.; Neff, J. E.; B&#246;hm, T.; Simon, T.; Kaper, L.; Strassmeier, K. G.; Granzer, Th.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 348, Issue 3, pp. 1301-1320.</journal>
			<date>3/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.348.1301U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...416..213T</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a warm molecular wind in DG Tauri</title>
			<authors>Takami, M.; Chrysostomou, A.; Ray, T. P.; Davis, C.; Dent, W. R. F.; Bailey, J.; Tamura, M.; Terada, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.416, p.213-219 (2004)</journal>
			<date>3/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...416..213T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003PASJ...55L..77I</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Molecular Hydrogen Emission Associated with LkHalpha 264</title>
			<authors>Itoh, Yoichi; Sugitani, Koji; Ogura, Katsuo; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.55, No.6, pp. L77-L81</journal>
			<date>12/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003PASJ...55L..77I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...597..986Q</bibcode>
			<title>Continuum and CO/HCO+ Emission from the Disk Around the T Tauri Star LkCa 15</title>
			<authors>Qi, Chunhua; Kessler, Jacqueline E.; Koerner, David W.; Sargent, Anneila I.; Blake, Geoffrey A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 597, Issue 2, pp. 986-997.</journal>
			<date>11/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...597..986Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...596..597W</bibcode>
			<title>Disks around the Young Stars TW Hydrae and HD 100546 Imaged at 3.4 Millimeters with the Australia Telescope Compact Array</title>
			<authors>Wilner, D. J.; Bourke, T. L.; Wright, C. M.; J&#248;rgensen, J. K.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Wong, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 596, Issue 1, pp. 597-602.</journal>
			<date>10/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...596..597W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003RMxAC..18...38J</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetic Accretion Onto T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, C. M.; Valenti, J. A.; Gafford, A. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Eight Texas-Mexico Conference on Astrophysics (Eds. M. Reyes-Ruiz &amp; E. V&#225;zquez-Semadeni) Revista Mexicana de Astronom&#237;a y Astrof&#237;sica (Serie de Conferencias) Vol. 18, pp. 38-44 (2003) (http://www.astroscu.unam.mx/~rmaa/)</journal>
			<date>9/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003RMxAC..18...38J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...593.1093L</bibcode>
			<title>A Census of the Young Cluster IC 348</title>
			<authors>Luhman, K. L.; Stauffer, John R.; Muench, A. A.; Rieke, G. H.; Lada, E. A.; Bouvier, J.; Lada, C. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 593, Issue 2, pp. 1093-1115.</journal>
			<date>8/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...593.1093L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...591L.159B</bibcode>
			<title>The Effects of UV Continuum and Lyalpha Radiation on the Chemical Equilibrium of T Tauri Disks</title>
			<authors>Bergin, Edwin; Calvet, Nuria; D'Alessio, Paola; Herczeg, Gregory J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 591, Issue 2, pp. L159-L162.</journal>
			<date>7/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...591L.159B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...589..931N</bibcode>
			<title>Gas in the Terrestrial Planet Region of Disks: CO Fundamental Emission from T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Najita, Joan; Carr, John S.; Mathieu, Robert D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 589, Issue 2, pp. 931-952.</journal>
			<date>6/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...589..931N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...586.1136B</bibcode>
			<title>Detections of Rovibrational H2 Emission from the Disks of T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Bary, Jeffrey S.; Weintraub, David A.; Kastner, Joel H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 586, Issue 2, pp. 1136-1147.</journal>
			<date>4/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...586.1136B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...585..398H</bibcode>
			<title>Comments on Inferences of Star Formation Histories and Birth Lines</title>
			<authors>Hartmann, Lee</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 585, Issue 1, pp. 398-405.</journal>
			<date>3/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...585..398H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003PASJ...55...11A</bibcode>
			<title>Interferometric Observations of Formaldehyde in the Protoplanetary Disk around LkCa 15</title>
			<authors>Aikawa, Yuri; Momose, Munetake; Thi, Wing-Fai; van Zadelhoff, Gerd-Jan; Qi, Chunhua; Blake, Geoffrey A.; van Dishoeck, Ewine F.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.55, No.1, pp.11-15</journal>
			<date>2/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003PASJ...55...11A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...581.1194P</bibcode>
			<title>Star Formation in Space and Time: Taurus-Auriga</title>
			<authors>Palla, Francesco; Stahler, Steven W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 581, Issue 2, pp. 1194-1203.</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...581.1194P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...581..357K</bibcode>
			<title>Investigation of the Physical Properties of Protoplanetary Disks around T Tauri Stars by a 1 Arcsecond Imaging Survey: Evolution and Diversity of the Disks in Their Accretion Stage</title>
			<authors>Kitamura, Yoshimi; Momose, Munetake; Yokogawa, Sozo; Kawabe, Ryohei; Tamura, Motohide; Ida, Shigeru</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 581, Issue 1, pp. 357-380.</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...581..357K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...578..914H</bibcode>
			<title>Flows, Fragmentation, and Star Formation. I. Low-Mass Stars in Taurus</title>
			<authors>Hartmann, Lee</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 578, Issue 2, pp. 914-924.</journal>
			<date>10/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...578..914H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...576L..73B</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Molecular Hydrogen Orbiting a ``Naked'' T Tauri Star</title>
			<authors>Bary, Jeffrey S.; Weintraub, David A.; Kastner, Joel H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 576, Issue 1, pp. L73-L76.</journal>
			<date>9/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...576L..73B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...573..685J</bibcode>
			<title>New Tests of Magnetospheric Accretion in T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Gafford, April D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 573, Issue 2, pp. 685-698.</journal>
			<date>7/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...573..685J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...570..785K</bibcode>
			<title>Hubble Space Telescope/WFPC2 Images of the GG Tauri Circumbinary Disk</title>
			<authors>Krist, John E.; Stapelfeldt, Karl R.; Watson, Alan M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 570, Issue 2, pp. 785-792.</journal>
			<date>5/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...570..785K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...386..622A</bibcode>
			<title>Warm molecular layers in protoplanetary disks</title>
			<authors>Aikawa, Y.; van Zadelhoff, G. J.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Herbst, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.386, p.622-632 (2002)</journal>
			<date>5/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...386..622A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...561.1074T</bibcode>
			<title>H2 and CO Emission from Disks around T Tauri and Herbig Ae Pre-Main-Sequence Stars and from Debris Disks around Young Stars: Warm and Cold Circumstellar Gas</title>
			<authors>Thi, W. F.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Blake, G. A.; van Zadelhoff, G. J.; Horn, J.; Becklin, E. E.; Mannings, V.; Sargent, A. I.; van den Ancker, M. E.; Natta, A.; Kessler, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 561, Issue 2, pp. 1074-1094.</journal>
			<date>11/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...561.1074T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...561..880N</bibcode>
			<title>X-Ray Desorption of Molecules from Grains in Protoplanetary Disks</title>
			<authors>Najita, Joan; Bergin, Edwin A.; Ullom, J. N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 561, Issue 2, pp. 880-889.</journal>
			<date>11/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...561..880N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...377..566V</bibcode>
			<title>Submillimeter lines from circumstellar disks around pre-main sequence stars</title>
			<authors>van Zadelhoff, G.-J.; van Dishoeck, E. F.; Thi, W.-F.; Blake, G. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.377, p.566-580 (2001)</journal>
			<date>10/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...377..566V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...556..265W</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Constraints on the Formation and Evolution of Binary Stars</title>
			<authors>White, R. J.; Ghez, A. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 556, Issue 1, pp. 265-295.</journal>
			<date>7/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...556..265W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...371.1107A</bibcode>
			<title>Two-dimensional distributions and column densities of gaseous molecules in protoplanetary disks. II. Deuterated species and UV shielding by ambient clouds</title>
			<authors>Aikawa, Y.; Herbst, E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.371, p.1107-1117 (2001)</journal>
			<date>6/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...371.1107A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...369..971K</bibcode>
			<title>X-ray emission of multiple T Tauri stars in Taurus</title>
			<authors>K&#246;nig, B.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Stelzer, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.369, p.971-980 (2001)</journal>
			<date>4/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...369..971K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001ApJ...547.1077C</bibcode>
			<title>Spectral Energy Distributions of Passive T Tauri and Herbig Ae Disks: Grain Mineralogy, Parameter Dependences, and Comparison with Infrared Space Observatory LWS Observations</title>
			<authors>Chiang, E. I.; Joung, M. K.; Creech-Eakman, M. J.; Qi, C.; Kessler, J. E.; Blake, G. A.; van Dishoeck, E. F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 547, Issue 2, pp. 1077-1089.</journal>
			<date>2/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001ApJ...547.1077C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000MNRAS.319..457C</bibcode>
			<title>A comparison of the rotational properties of T Tauri stars in Orion and Taurus</title>
			<authors>Clarke, C. J.; Bouvier, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 319, Issue 2, pp. 457-466.</journal>
			<date>12/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000MNRAS.319..457C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000ApJ...545.1034S</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical Masses of T Tauri Stars and Calibration of Pre-Main-Sequence Evolution</title>
			<authors>Simon, M.; Dutrey, A.; Guilloteau, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 545, Issue 2, pp. 1034-1043.</journal>
			<date>12/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000ApJ...545.1034S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000AAS...197.1014B</bibcode>
			<title>Detections of Ro-vibrational H2 Emission from T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Bary, J. S.; Weintraub, D. A.; Kastner, J. H.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 197th AAS Meeting, #10.14; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 32, p.1414</journal>
			<date>12/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000AAS...197.1014B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000MNRAS.317...55S</bibcode>
			<title>The PSCz catalogue</title>
			<authors>Saunders, W.; Sutherland, W. J.; Maddox, S. J.; Keeble, O.; Oliver, S. J.; Rowan-Robinson, M.; McMahon, R. G.; Efstathiou, G. P.; Tadros, H.; White, S. D. M.; Frenk, C. S.; Carrami&#241;ana, A.; Hawkins, M. R. S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 317, Issue 1, pp. 55-63.</journal>
			<date>9/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000MNRAS.317...55S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000A&amp;A...355..165D</bibcode>
			<title>A search for extended disks around weak-lined T Tauri stars</title>
			<authors>Duvert, G.; Guilloteau, S.; M&#233;nard, F.; Simon, M.; Dutrey, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.355, p.165-170 (2000)</journal>
			<date>3/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000A%26A...355..165D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999ApJ...527..893D</bibcode>
			<title>Accretion Disks around Young Objects. II. Tests of Well-mixed Models with ISM Dust</title>
			<authors>D'Alessio, Paola; Calvet, Nuria; Hartmann, Lee; Lizano, Susana; Cant&#243;, Jorge</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 527, Issue 2, pp. 893-909.</journal>
			<date>12/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999ApJ...527..893D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999ApJ...516..900J</bibcode>
			<title>Measuring the Magnetic Field on the Classical T Tauri Star BP Tauri</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Koresko, Christopher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 516, Issue 2, pp. 900-915.</journal>
			<date>5/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999ApJ...516..900J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...342..480S</bibcode>
			<title>Physics of accretion onto young stars. III. Comparisons with observations</title>
			<authors>Siess, L.; Forestini, M.; Bertout, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.342, p.480-491 (1999)</journal>
			<date>2/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...342..480S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999ApJ...510L.127S</bibcode>
			<title>A Physical Limit to the Magnetic Fields of T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Safier, Pedro N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 510, Issue 2, pp. L127-L130.</journal>
			<date>1/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999ApJ...510L.127S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...341..768G</bibcode>
			<title>Measurements of magnetic field strength on T Tauri stars</title>
			<authors>Guenther, Eike W.; Lehmann, Holger; Emerson, James P.; Staude, J&#252;rgen</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.341, p.768-783 (1999)</journal>
			<date>1/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...341..768G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999ARA&amp;A..37..363F</bibcode>
			<title>High-Energy Processes in Young Stellar Objects</title>
			<authors>Feigelson, Eric D.; Montmerle, Thierry</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, Vol. 37, pp. 363-408.</journal>
			<date>0/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999ARA%26A..37..363F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998Ap&amp;SS.263..231M</bibcode>
			<title>Chromospheric Activity of Weak-Lined T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Montes, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science, v. 263, Issue 1/4, p. 231-234 (1998).</journal>
			<date>6/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998Ap%26SS.263..231M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998AJ....115.2491K</bibcode>
			<title>Optical Spectroscopy of Embedded Young Stars in the Taurus-Auriga Molecular Cloud</title>
			<authors>Kenyon, Scott J.; Brown, David I.; Tout, Christopher A.; Berlind, Perry</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 115, Issue 6, pp. 2491-2503.</journal>
			<date>6/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998AJ....115.2491K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1997A&amp;A...325..613F</bibcode>
			<title>New proper motions of pre-main sequence stars in Taurus-Auriga</title>
			<authors>Frink, S.; R&#246;ser, S.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Sterzik, M. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astron. Astrophys. 325, 613-622</journal>
			<date>9/1997</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1997A%26A...325..613F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996ApJ...471..847P</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Parameters and Iron Abundances of Low-Mass Pre-Main-Sequence Stars in Nearby Star Formation Regions</title>
			<authors>Padgett, Deborah L.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal v.471, p.847</journal>
			<date>11/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996ApJ...471..847P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AJ....112.2159B</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Observations of YY Orionis: New Insight Into the Accretion Process</title>
			<authors>Bertout, Claude; Harder, Stephan; Malbet, Fabian; Mennessier, Catherine; Regev, Oded</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.112, p.2159</journal>
			<date>11/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AJ....112.2159B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1996AJ....111.2066W</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Protoplanetary Disks Around Naked T Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Wolk, Scott J.; Walter, Frederick M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal v.111, p.2066</journal>
			<date>5/1996</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1996AJ....111.2066W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995AZh....72..894G</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric study of the properties of SPOT rotational modulation in weak line T Tauri stars</title>
			<authors>Grankin, K. N.; Ibragimov, M. A.; Kondrat'ev, V. B.; Mel'Nikov, S. Yu.; Shevchenko, V. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomicheskij Zhurnal, vol. 72, p. 894</journal>
			<date>12/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995AZh....72..894G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ARep...39..799G</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric study of the properties of spot rotational modulation in weak line T Tauri stars</title>
			<authors>Grankin, K. N.; Ibragimov, M. A.; Kondrat'ev, V. B.; Mel'Nikov, S. Yu.; Shevchenko, V. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Reports, Volume 39, Issue 6, November 1995, pp.799-807</journal>
			<date>11/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ARep...39..799G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJS..101..117K</bibcode>
			<title>Pre-Main-Sequence Evolution in the Taurus-Auriga Molecular Cloud</title>
			<authors>Kenyon, Scott J.; Hartmann, Lee</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement v.101, p.117</journal>
			<date>11/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJS..101..117K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;A...299..347C</bibcode>
			<title>A search for IRAS galaxies behind the Taurus molecular clouds.</title>
			<authors>Chamaraux, P.; Kazes, I.; Saito, M.; Yamada, T.; Takata, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.299, p.347</journal>
			<date>7/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26A...299..347C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;A...299...89B</bibcode>
			<title>COYOTES II: SPOT properties and the origin of photometric period variations in T Tauri stars.</title>
			<authors>Bouvier, J.; Covino, E.; Kovo, O.; Martin, E. L.; Matthews, J. M.; Terranegra, L.; Beck, S. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.299, p.89</journal>
			<date>7/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26A...299...89B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;A...297..391N</bibcode>
			<title>ROSAT survey observation of T Tauri stars in Taurus.</title>
			<authors>Neuhaeuser, R.; Sterzik, M. F.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Wichmann, R.; Krautter, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.297, p.391</journal>
			<date>5/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26A...297..391N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995MNRAS.272..763G</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation of T Tauri stars: accretion discs and stellar dynamos</title>
			<authors>Ghosh, Pranab</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 272, Issue 4, pp. 763-771.</journal>
			<date>2/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995MNRAS.272..763G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995IBVS.4140....1K</bibcode>
			<title>The 72nd Name-List of Variable Stars</title>
			<authors>Kazarovets, E. V.; Samus, N. N.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4140, 1.</journal>
			<date>1/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995IBVS.4140....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJ...439..288O</bibcode>
			<title>Millimeter-wave continuum measurements of young stars</title>
			<authors>Osterloh, M.; Beckwith, S. V. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 439, no. 1, p. 288-302</journal>
			<date>1/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJ...439..288O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995A&amp;AS..109..177W</bibcode>
			<title>Radio continuum emission from stars: a catalogue update.</title>
			<authors>Wendker, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astron. Astrophys. Suppl. 109, 177-179 (1995)</journal>
			<date>1/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995A%26AS..109..177W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994A&amp;A...287..523S</bibcode>
			<title>T Tauri stars as differential rotators</title>
			<authors>Smith, Michael D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 287, no. 2, p. 523-534</journal>
			<date>7/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994A%26A...287..523S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994A&amp;A...282..503M</bibcode>
			<title>Pre-main sequence lithium burning. 1: Weak T Tauri stars</title>
			<authors>Martin, E. L.; Rebolo, R.; Magazzu, A.; Pavlenko, Ya. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 282, no. 2, p. 503-517</journal>
			<date>2/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994A%26A...282..503M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;AS..101..485B</bibcode>
			<title>COYOTES - Part One - Multisite UBVRI Photometry of 24 Pre Main Sequence Stars of the Taurus-Auriga Cloud</title>
			<authors>Bouvier, J.; Cabrit, S.; Fernandez, M.; Martin, E. L.; Matthews, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>ASTRON. AND ASTROPHYS. SUPPL. V.101, NO. 3/NOVI, P. 485, 1993</journal>
			<date>11/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26AS..101..485B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;A...278..129L</bibcode>
			<title>A systematic approach for young binaries in Taurus</title>
			<authors>Leinert, Ch.; Zinnecker, H.; Weitzel, N.; Christou, J.; Ridgway, S. T.; Jameson, R.; Haas, M.; Lenzen, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 278, no. 1, p. 129-149</journal>
			<date>10/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26A...278..129L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;A...272..176B</bibcode>
			<title>Coyotes-I - the Photometric Variability and Rotational Evolution of T-Tauri Stars</title>
			<authors>Bouvier, J.; Cabrit, S.; Fernandez, M.; Martin, E. L.; Matthews, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>ASTRONOMY AND ASTROPHYSICS V.272, NO. 1/MAYI, P. 176, 1993</journal>
			<date>5/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26A...272..176B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993IBVS.3823....1G</bibcode>
			<title>Periodic Light Variations in Ten Weak Emission T Tauri Stars in Taurus-Auriga Complex</title>
			<authors>Grankin, K. N.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 3823, 1.</journal>
			<date>1/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993IBVS.3823....1G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJS...82..247H</bibcode>
			<title>Emission-line studies of young stars. I - The T Tauri stars. II - The Herbig Ae/Be stars</title>
			<authors>Hamann, Fred; Persson, S. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 82, no. 1, Sept. 1992, p. 247-283, 285-309. Research supported by NSF.</journal>
			<date>9/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJS...82..247H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJ...394..628H</bibcode>
			<title>Emission-line studies of young stars. III - Correlations with the infrared excess</title>
			<authors>Hamann, Fred; Persson, S. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 394, no. 2, Aug. 1, 1992, p. 628-642. Research supported by NSF.</journal>
			<date>8/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJ...394..628H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992ApJS...78..239W</bibcode>
			<title>A catalog of co-added IRAS fluxes of Orion population stars</title>
			<authors>Weaver, Wm. B.; Jones, Gordon</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 78, Jan. 1992, p. 239-266. Research supported by Mericos Foundation and Research Corp.</journal>
			<date>1/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992ApJS...78..239W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990AJ....100.1610O</bibcode>
			<title>A radio survey of weak T Tauri stars in Taurus-Auriga</title>
			<authors>O'Neal, Douglas; Feigelson, Eric D.; Mathieu, Robert D.; Myers, Philip C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 100, Nov. 1990, p. 1610-1617. Research supported by TRW, Inc. and Sun Microsystems, Inc.</journal>
			<date>11/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990AJ....100.1610O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990ApJS...74..575W</bibcode>
			<title>A catalog of pre-main-sequence emission-line stars with IRAS source associations</title>
			<authors>Weintraub, David A.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 74, Oct. 1990, p. 575-594.</journal>
			<date>10/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990ApJS...74..575W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989AJ.....97.1451S</bibcode>
			<title>Circumstellar material associated with solar-type pre-main-sequence stars - A possible constraint on the timescale for planet building</title>
			<authors>Strom, Karen M.; Strom, Stephen E.; Edwards, Suzan; Cabrit, Sylvie; Skrutskie, Michael F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 97, May 1989, p. 1451-1470. Research supported by NSF and NASA.</journal>
			<date>5/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989AJ.....97.1451S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988cels.book.....H</bibcode>
			<title>Third Catalog of Emission-Line Stars of the Orion Population : 3 : 1988</title>
			<authors>Herbig, G. H.; Bell, K. Robbin</authors>
			<journal>Third catalog of emission-line stars of the Orion population., by G.H. gerbig and K.R. Bell.  Lick Observatory Bulletin #1111, Santa Cruz: Lick Observatory, Jun 1988, 90 p.</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988cels.book.....H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987AJ.....93..907H</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation and kinematics of the premain-sequence stars in Taurus-Auriga with CA II emission</title>
			<authors>Hartmann, Lee W.; Soderblom, David R.; Stauffer, John R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 93, April 1987, p. 907-912. Research supported by the Smithsonian Institution.</journal>
			<date>4/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987AJ.....93..907H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986AJ.....91..575H</bibcode>
			<title>A spectroscopic survey of the Taurus-Auriga dark clouds for pre-main-sequence stars having CA II H, K emission</title>
			<authors>Herbig, G. H.; Vrba, F. J.; Rydgren, A. E.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 91, March 1986, p. 575-582.</journal>
			<date>3/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986AJ.....91..575H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
