<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754...73B</bibcode>
			<title>MOA 2010-BLG-477Lb: Constraining the Mass of a Microlensing Planet from Microlensing Parallax, Orbital Motion, and Detection of Blended Light</title>
			<authors>Bachelet, E.; Shin, I.-G.; Han, C.; Fouqu, P.; Gould, A.; Menzies, J. W.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Dong, Subo; Heyrovsk, D.; Marquette, J.-B.; Marshall, J.; Skowron, J.; Street, R. A.; Sumi, T.; Udalski, A.; Abe, L.; Agabi, K.; Albrow, M. D.; Allen, W.; Bertin, E.; Bos, M.; Bramich, D. M.; Chavez, J.; Christie, G. W.; Cole, A. A.; Crouzet, N.; Dieters, S.; Dominik, M.; Drummond, J.; Greenhill, J.; Guillot, T.; Henderson, C. B.; Hessman, F. V.; Horne, K.; Hundertmark, M.; Johnson, J. A.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kandori, R.; Liebig, C.; Mkarnia, D.; McCormick, J.; Moorhouse, D.; Nagayama, T.; Nataf, D.; Natusch, T.; Nishiyama, S.; Rivet, J.-P.; Sahu, K. C.; Shvartzvald, Y.; Thornley, G.; Tomczak, A. R.; Tsapras, Y.; Yee, J. C.; Batista, V.; Bennett, C. S.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Cassan, A.; Corrales, E.; Coutures, C.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Kubas, D.; Martin, R.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; The PLANET Collaboration; de Almeida, L. Andrade; DePoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Hung, L.-W.; Jablonski, F.; Kaspi, S.; Klein, N.; Lee, C.-U.; Lee, Y.; Koo, J.-R.; Maoz, D.; Mu oz, J. A.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Shporer, A.; muCollaboration, The FUN; Abe, F.; Botzler, C. S.; Chote, P.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Harris, P.; Itow, Y.; Kobara, S.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Ohmori, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Saito, To.; Sullivan, D. J.; Suzuki, D.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Wada, K.; Yock, P. C. M.; The MOA Collaboration; Szyman ski, M. K.; Soszynski, I.; Kubiak, M.; Poleski, R.; Ulaczyk, K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Wyrzykowski, L.; The OGLE Collaboration; Kains, N.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I. A.; The RoboNet Collaboration; Alsubai, K. A.; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dodds, P.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Gerner, T.; Hardis, S.; Harpse, K.; Hinse, T. C.; Kerins, E.; Mancini, L.; Mathiasen, M.; Penny, M. T.; Proft, S.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Schfer, S.; Schnebeck, F.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Wambsganss, J.; MiNDSTEp Consortium, The</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 754, Issue 1, article id. 73 (2012).</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754...73B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
