<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..167C</bibcode>
			<title>One or more bound planets per Milky Way star from microlensing observations.</title>
			<authors>Cassan, A.; Kubas, D.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Dominik, M.; Horne, K.; Greenhill, J.; Wambsganss, J.; Menzies, J.; Williams, A.; Jorgensen, U.; Udalski, A.; Bennett, D. P.; Albrow, M. D.; Batista, V.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Cole, A.; Coutures, C.; Cook, H.; Dieters, S.; Prester, D. D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouque, P.; Hill, K.; Kains, N.; Kane, S.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Vinter, C.; Warren, D.; Watson, B.; Zub, M.; Sumi, T.; Szymanski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Poleski, R.; Soszynski, I.; Ulaczyk, K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Wyrzykowski, L.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, 481, 167-169 (2012)</journal>
			<date>0/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..167C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411....2D</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary mass function and planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Dominik, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. 2-8.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411....2D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..120M</bibcode>
			<title>A Sub-Saturn Mass Planet, MOA-2009-BLG-319Lb</title>
			<authors>Miyake, N.; Sumi, T.; Dong, Subo; Street, R.; Mancini, L.; Gould, A.; Bennett, D. P.; Tsapras, Y.; Yee, J. C.; Albrow, M. D.; Bond, I. A.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Browne, P.; Han, C.; Snodgrass, C.; Finet, F.; Furusawa, K.; Harps&#248;e, K.; Allen, W.; Hundertmark, M.; Freeman, M.; Suzuki, D.; Abe, F.; Botzler, C. S.; Douchin, D.; Fukui, A.; Hayashi, F.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Muraki, Y.; Nagayama, T.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Wada, K.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Bolt, G.; Bos, M.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Drummond, J.; Gal-Yam, A.; Gaudi, B. S.; Gorbikov, E.; Higgins, D.; Hwang, K.-H.; Janczak, J.; Kaspi, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Koo, J.-R.; Kozlowski, S.; Lee, Y.; Mallia, F.; Maury, A.; Maoz, D.; McCormick, J.; Monard, L. A. G.; Moorhouse, D.; Mu&#241;oz, J. A.; Natusch, T.; Ofek, E. O.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Santallo, R.; Shporer, A.; Spector, O.; Thornley, G.; muFUN Collaboration; Allan, A.; Bramich, D. M.; Horne, K.; Kains, N.; Steele, I.; RoboNet Collaboration; Bozza, V.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dominik, M.; Dreizler, S.; Glitrup, M.; Hessman, F. V.; Hinse, T. C.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Maier, G.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Skottfelt, J.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Wambsganss, J.; Zimmer, F.; MiNDSTEp Consortium; Batista, V.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Brillant, S.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Corrales, E.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Greenhill, J.; Kubas, D.; Menzies, J.; PLANET Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 120 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..120M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1073G</bibcode>
			<title>Frequency of Solar-like Systems and of Ice and Gas Giants Beyond the Snow Line from High-magnification Microlensing Events in 2005-2008</title>
			<authors>Gould, A.; Dong, Subo; Gaudi, B. S.; Udalski, A.; Bond, I. A.; Greenhill, J.; Street, R. A.; Dominik, M.; Sumi, T.; Szymanski, M. K.; Han, C.; Allen, W.; Bolt, G.; Bos, M.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Drummond, J.; Eastman, J. D.; Gal-Yam, A.; Higgins, D.; Janczak, J.; Kaspi, S.; Kozlowski, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Maury, A.; Maoz, D.; McCormick, J.; Monard, L. A. G.; Moorhouse, D.; Morgan, N.; Natusch, T.; Ofek, E. O.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Santallo, R.; Shporer, A.; Spector, O.; Thornley, G.; Yee, J. C.; mu FUN Collaboration; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; Poleski, R.; OGLE Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Botzler, C. S.; Douchin, D.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Philpott, L.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; von Seggern, E.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Albrow, M.; Batista, V.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J.; Calitz, J. J.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Cook, K.; Coutures, C.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Hill, K.; Hoffman, M.; Jablonski, F.; Kane, S. R.; Kains, N.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Martioli, E.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pedretti, E.; Pollard, K.; Sahu, K. C.; Vinter, C.; Wambsganss, J.; Watson, R.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; PLANET Collaboration; Allan, A.; Bode, M. F.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Clay, N.; Fraser, S.; Hawkins, E.; Horne, K.; Kerins, E.; Lister, T. A.; Mottram, C.; Saunders, E. S.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I. A.; Tsapras, Y.; RoboNet Collaboration; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Anguita, T.; Bozza, V.; Calchi Novati, S.; Harps&#248;e, K.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Kj&#230;rgaard, P.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Masi, G.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Th&#246;ne, C. C.; MiNDSTEp Consortium</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1073-1089 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1073G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..68L</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of extrasolar moons as gravitational microlenses</title>
			<authors>Liebig, C.; Wambsganss, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A68</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..68L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...518A..51F</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE 2008-BLG-290: an accurate measurement of the limb darkening of a galactic bulge K Giant spatially resolved by microlensing</title>
			<authors>Fouqu&#233;, P.; Heyrovsk&#253;, D.; Dong, S.; Gould, A.; Udalski, A.; Albrow, M. D.; Batista, V.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Bramich, D. M.; Calchi Novati, S.; Cassan, A.; Coutures, C.; Dieters, S.; Dominik, M.; Dominis Prester, D.; Greenhill, J.; Horne, K.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Kozlowski, S.; Kubas, D.; Lee, C.-H.; Marquette, J.-B.; Mathiasen, M.; Menzies, J.; Monard, L. A. G.; Nishiyama, S.; Papadakis, I.; Street, R.; Sumi, T.; Williams, A.; Yee, J. C.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Cole, A.; Cook, K. H.; Donatowicz, J.; Kains, N.; Kane, S. R.; Martin, R.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Tsapras, Y.; Wambsganss, J.; Depoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Han, C.; Lee, C.-U.; Park, B.-G.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Abe, F.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Gilmore, A. C.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A. V.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sato, S.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D.; Sweatman, W.; Tristram, P. J.; Allan, A.; Bode, M. F.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Clay, N.; Fraser, S. N.; Hawkins, E.; Kerins, E.; Lister, T. A.; Mottram, C. J.; Saunders, E. S.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I. A.; Anguita, T.; Bozza, V.; Harps&#248;e, K.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Kj&#230; rgaard, P.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Masi, G.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Th&#246;ne, C. C.; Riffeser, A.; Seitz, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 518, id.A51</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...518A..51F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1408B</bibcode>
			<title>An Efficient Method for Modeling High-magnification Planetary Microlensing Events</title>
			<authors>Bennett, David P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1408-1422 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1408B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..865C</bibcode>
			<title>Properties of Microlensing Central Perturbations by Planets in Binary Stellar Systems under the Strong Finite-Source Effect</title>
			<authors>Chung, Sun-Ju; Park, Byeong-Gon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 865-870 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..865C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..837B</bibcode>
			<title>Masses and Orbital Constraints for the OGLE-2006-BLG-109Lb,c Jupiter/Saturn Analog Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Bennett, D. P.; Rhie, S. H.; Nikolaev, S.; Gaudi, B. S.; Udalski, A.; Gould, A.; Christie, G. W.; Maoz, D.; Dong, S.; McCormick, J.; Szymanski, M. K.; Tristram, P. J.; Macintosh, B.; Cook, K. H.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; The OGLE Collaboration; DePoy, D. L.; Han, C.; Kaspi, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; The muFUN Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bond, I. A.; Botzler, C. S.; Fukui, A.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Korpela, A. V.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Lin, W.; Ling, J.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Motomura, M.; Muraki, Y.; Nakamura, S.; Okumura, T.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Saito, To.; Sato, S.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Sweatman, W. L.; Yock, P. C. M.; The MOA Collaboration; Albrow, M.; Allan, A.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Coutures, C.; Dominik, M.; Dieters, S.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Greenhill, J.; Horne, K.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Tsapras, Y.; PLANET, From the; RoboNet Collaborations; Chaboyer, B.; Crocker, A.; Frank, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 837-855 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..837B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..731J</bibcode>
			<title>Sub-Saturn Planet MOA-2008-BLG-310Lb: Likely to be in the Galactic Bulge</title>
			<authors>Janczak, Julia; Fukui, A.; Dong, Subo; Monard, L. A. G.; Kozlowski, Szymon; Gould, A.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Kubas, Daniel; Marquette, J. B.; Sumi, T.; Bond, I. A.; Bennett, D. P.; Abe, F.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Korpela, A. V.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nagayama, T.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Saito, To.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; The MOA Collaboration; An, Jin H.; Christie, G. W.; Chung, Sun-Ju; DePoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Han, C.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; The muFUN Collaboration; Anguita, T.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dominik, M.; J&#248; rgensen, U. G.; Masi, G.; Mathiasen, M.; The MiNDSTEp Collaboration; Batista, V.; Brillant, S.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Corrales, E.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Greenhill, J.; The PLANET Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 2, pp. 731-743 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..731J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1641S</bibcode>
			<title>A Cold Neptune-Mass Planet OGLE-2007-BLG-368Lb: Cold Neptunes Are Common</title>
			<authors>Sumi, T.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Udalski, A.; Batista, V.; Dominik, M.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Kubas, D.; Gould, A.; Macintosh, B.; Cook, K.; Dong, S.; Skuljan, L.; Cassan, A.; Abe, F.; Botzler, C. S.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nagayama, T.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; The MOA Collaboration; Beaulieu, J. P.; Cole, A.; Coutures, Ch.; Duran, M. F.; Greenhill, J.; Jablonski, F.; Marboeuf, U.; Martioli, E.; Pedretti, E.; Pejcha, O.; Rojo, P.; Albrow, M. D.; Brillant, S.; Bode, M.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Calitz, H.; Corrales, E.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Hill, K.; Hoffman, M.; Horne, K.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Kains, N.; Kane, S.; Marquette, J. B.; Martin, R.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Street, R.; Tsapras, Y.; Wambsganss, J.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; The PLANET Collaboration; Szymanski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; The OGLE Collaboration; Allen, W.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Han, C.; Janczak, J.; Lee, C.-U.; McCormick, J.; Mallia, F.; Monard, B.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Santallo, R.; The muFUN Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1641-1653 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1641S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508..467B</bibcode>
			<title>Mass measurement of a single unseen star and planetary detection efficiency for OGLE 2007-BLG-050</title>
			<authors>Batista, V.; Dong, S.; Gould, A.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Cassan, A.; Christie, G. W.; Han, C.; Udalski, A.; Allen, W.; Depoy, D. L.; Gal-Yam, A.; Gaudi, B. S.; Johnson, B.; Kaspi, S.; Lee, C. U.; Maoz, D.; McCormick, J.; McGreer, I.; Monard, B.; Natusch, T.; Ofek, E.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Shporer, A.; mu FUN Collaboration; Albrow, M. D.; Bennett, D. P.; Brillant, S.; Bode, M.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Calitz, H.; Cole, A.; Cook, K. H.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Dominik, M.; Prester, D. D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Greenhill, J.; Hoffman, M.; Horne, K.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Kains, N.; Kane, S.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J. B.; Martin, R.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Tsapras, Y.; Wambsganss, J.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; PLANET/Robonet Collaboration; Wyrzykowski, L.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Ogle Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bond, I. A.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Holderness, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, T.; Sako, T.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D.; Sumi, T.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; The Moa Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 1, 2009, pp.467-478</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508..467B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1826D</bibcode>
			<title>Microlensing Event MOA-2007-BLG-400: Exhuming the Buried Signature of a Cool, Jovian-Mass Planet</title>
			<authors>Dong, Subo; Bond, I. A.; Gould, A.; Kozlowski, Szymon; Miyake, N.; Gaudi, B. S.; Bennett, D. P.; Abe, F.; Gilmore, A. C.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sato, S.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Sweatman, W.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; The MOA Collaboration; Bolt, G.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Han, C.; Janczak, J.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; McCormick, J.; Monard, B.; Maury, A.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Santallo, R.; Stanek, K. Z.; The muFUN Collaboration; Udalski, A.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; The OGLE Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1826-1837 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1826D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693.1835H</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Lensing Signals of High-Magnification Events Under the Severe Finite-Source Effect</title>
			<authors>Han, Cheongho; Kim, Doeon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 2, pp. 1835-1839 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693.1835H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691..452H</bibcode>
			<title>Microlensing Zone of Planets Detectable Through the Channel of High-Magnification Events</title>
			<authors>Han, Cheongho</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 1, pp. 452-457 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691..452H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689.1084K</bibcode>
			<title>Limits of Binaries That Can Be Characterized by Gravitational Microlensing</title>
			<authors>Kim, Doeon; Ryu, Yoon-Hyun; Park, Byeong-Gon; Chang, Heon-Young; Hwang, Kyu-Ha; Chung, Sun-Ju; Lee, Chung-Uk; Han, Cheongho</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 2, pp. 1084-1088.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689.1084K</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
