<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.102B</bibcode>
			<title>MOA-2009-BLG-387Lb: a massive planet orbiting an M dwarf</title>
			<authors>Batista, V.; Gould, A.; Dieters, S.; Dong, S.; Bond, I.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Maoz, D.; Monard, B.; Christie, G. W.; McCormick, J.; Albrow, M. D.; Horne, K.; Tsapras, Y.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Calchi Novati, S.; Skottfelt, J.; Caldwell, J.; Kozl owski, S.; Kubas, D.; Gaudi, B. S.; Han, C.; Bennett, D. P.; An, J.; MOA Collaboration; Abe, F.; Botzler, C. S.; Douchin, D.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, B. S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; von Seggern, E.; Yock, P. C. M.; PLANET Collaboration; Brillant, S.; Calitz, J. J.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Cook, K.; Coutures, C.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Greenhill, J.; Hoffman, M.; Jablonski, F.; Kane, S. R.; Kains, N.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Martioli, E.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pedretti, E.; Pollard, K.; Sahu, K. C.; Vinter, C.; Wambsganss, J.; Watson, R.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; FUN Collaboration; Allen, W.; Bolt, G.; Bos, M.; DePoy, D. L.; Drummond, J.; Eastman, J. D.; Gal-Yam, A.; Gorbikov, E.; Higgins, D.; Janczak, J.; Kaspi, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Maury, A.; Monard, L. A. G.; Moorhouse, D.; Morgan, N.; Natusch, T.; Ofek, E. O.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Santallo, R.; Shporer, A.; Spector, O.; Thornley, G.; Yee, J. C.; MiNDSTEp Consortium; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Dominik, M.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Glitrup, M.; Grundahl, F.; Harpse, K.; Hessman, F. V.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Maier, G.; Mancini, L.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Zimmer, F.; RoboNet Collaboration; Allan, A.; Bramich, D. M.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I. A.; Street, R. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A102</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.102B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
