<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1073G</bibcode>
			<title>Frequency of Solar-like Systems and of Ice and Gas Giants Beyond the Snow Line from High-magnification Microlensing Events in 2005-2008</title>
			<authors>Gould, A.; Dong, Subo; Gaudi, B. S.; Udalski, A.; Bond, I. A.; Greenhill, J.; Street, R. A.; Dominik, M.; Sumi, T.; Szymanski, M. K.; Han, C.; Allen, W.; Bolt, G.; Bos, M.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Drummond, J.; Eastman, J. D.; Gal-Yam, A.; Higgins, D.; Janczak, J.; Kaspi, S.; Kozlowski, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Maury, A.; Maoz, D.; McCormick, J.; Monard, L. A. G.; Moorhouse, D.; Morgan, N.; Natusch, T.; Ofek, E. O.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Santallo, R.; Shporer, A.; Spector, O.; Thornley, G.; Yee, J. C.; mu FUN Collaboration; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; Poleski, R.; OGLE Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Botzler, C. S.; Douchin, D.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Philpott, L.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; von Seggern, E.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Albrow, M.; Batista, V.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J.; Calitz, J. J.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Cook, K.; Coutures, C.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Hill, K.; Hoffman, M.; Jablonski, F.; Kane, S. R.; Kains, N.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Martioli, E.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pedretti, E.; Pollard, K.; Sahu, K. C.; Vinter, C.; Wambsganss, J.; Watson, R.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; PLANET Collaboration; Allan, A.; Bode, M. F.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Clay, N.; Fraser, S.; Hawkins, E.; Horne, K.; Kerins, E.; Lister, T. A.; Mottram, C.; Saunders, E. S.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I. A.; Tsapras, Y.; RoboNet Collaboration; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Anguita, T.; Bozza, V.; Calchi Novati, S.; Harps&#248;e, K.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Kj&#230;rgaard, P.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Masi, G.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Th&#246;ne, C. C.; MiNDSTEp Consortium</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1073-1089 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1073G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..837B</bibcode>
			<title>Masses and Orbital Constraints for the OGLE-2006-BLG-109Lb,c Jupiter/Saturn Analog Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Bennett, D. P.; Rhie, S. H.; Nikolaev, S.; Gaudi, B. S.; Udalski, A.; Gould, A.; Christie, G. W.; Maoz, D.; Dong, S.; McCormick, J.; Szymanski, M. K.; Tristram, P. J.; Macintosh, B.; Cook, K. H.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; The OGLE Collaboration; DePoy, D. L.; Han, C.; Kaspi, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; The muFUN Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bond, I. A.; Botzler, C. S.; Fukui, A.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Korpela, A. V.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Lin, W.; Ling, J.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Motomura, M.; Muraki, Y.; Nakamura, S.; Okumura, T.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Saito, To.; Sato, S.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Sweatman, W. L.; Yock, P. C. M.; The MOA Collaboration; Albrow, M.; Allan, A.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Coutures, C.; Dominik, M.; Dieters, S.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Greenhill, J.; Horne, K.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Tsapras, Y.; PLANET, From the; RoboNet Collaborations; Chaboyer, B.; Crocker, A.; Frank, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 837-855 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..837B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..713J</bibcode>
			<title>The Effect of Differential Limb Magnification on Abundance Analysis of Microlensed Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Johnson, Jennifer A.; Dong, Subo; Gould, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 713-720 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..713J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..731J</bibcode>
			<title>Sub-Saturn Planet MOA-2008-BLG-310Lb: Likely to be in the Galactic Bulge</title>
			<authors>Janczak, Julia; Fukui, A.; Dong, Subo; Monard, L. A. G.; Kozlowski, Szymon; Gould, A.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Kubas, Daniel; Marquette, J. B.; Sumi, T.; Bond, I. A.; Bennett, D. P.; Abe, F.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Korpela, A. V.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nagayama, T.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Saito, To.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; The MOA Collaboration; An, Jin H.; Christie, G. W.; Chung, Sun-Ju; DePoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Han, C.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; The muFUN Collaboration; Anguita, T.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dominik, M.; J&#248; rgensen, U. G.; Masi, G.; Mathiasen, M.; The MiNDSTEp Collaboration; Batista, V.; Brillant, S.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Corrales, E.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Greenhill, J.; The PLANET Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 2, pp. 731-743 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..731J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1800G</bibcode>
			<title>A Second Method to Photometrically Align Multi-Site Microlensing Light Curves: Source Color in Planetary Event MOA-2007-BLG-192</title>
			<authors>Gould, Andrew; Dong, Subo; Bennett, David P.; Bond, Ian A.; Udalski, Andrzej; Kozlowski, Szymon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1800-1805 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1800G</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
