<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...741...22M</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Mass Measurements of a Cold, 10 Earth Mass Planet and Its Host Star</title>
			<authors>Muraki, Y.; Han, C.; Bennett, D. P.; Suzuki, D.; Monard, L. A. G.; Street, R.; Jorgensen, U. G.; Kundurthy, P.; Skowron, J.; Becker, A. C.; Albrow, M. D.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Heyrovsk&#253;, D.; Barry, R. K.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Wellnitz, D. D.; Bond, I. A.; Sumi, T.; Dong, S.; Gaudi, B. S.; Bramich, D. M.; Dominik, M.; Abe, F.; Botzler, C. S.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hayashi, F.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Korpela, A. V.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Saito, To.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Wada, K.; Yock, P. C. M.; (The MOA Collaboration; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Gorbikov, E.; Gould, A.; Kaspi, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Maoz, D.; McCormick, J.; Moorhouse, D.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Shporer, A.; Thornley, G.; Yee, J. C.; (The mu FUN Collaboration; Allan, A.; Browne, P.; Horne, K.; Kains, N.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Tsapras, Y.; (The RoboNet Collaboration; Batista, V.; Bennett, C. S.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Corrales, R.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Greenhill, J.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Menzies, J.; Sahu, K. C.; Waldman, I.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; (The PLANET Collaboration; Bourhrous, H.; Matsuoka, Y.; Nagayama, T.; Oi, N.; Randriamanakoto, Z.; Observers, (IRSF; Bozza, V.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Glitrup, M.; Harps&#248;e, K.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Liebig, C.; Maier, G.; Mancini, L.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Skottfelt, J.; Surdej, J.; Southworth, J.; Wambsganss, J.; Zimmer, F.; MiNDSTEp Consortium, (The; Udalski, A.; Poleski, R.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; Szymanski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; (The OGLE Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 741, Issue 1, article id. 22 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...741...22M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.413.1244H</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE-2009-BLG-023/MOA-2009-BLG-028: characterization of a binary microlensing event based on survey data</title>
			<authors>Hwang, K.-H.; Han, C.; Udalski, A.; Sumi, T.; Gould, A.; OGLE Collaboration; Jaroszynski, M.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; MOA Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Botzler, C. S.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 413, Issue 2, pp. 1244-1250.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.413.1244H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717..435H</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the Physical Lens Parameters of the Binary Gravitational Microlensing Event MOA-2009-BLG-016</title>
			<authors>Hwang, K.-H.; Han, C.; Bond, I. A.; Miyake, N.; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Botzler, C. S.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hayashi, F.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Muraki, Y.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Suzuki, D.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Wada, K.; Yock, P. C. M.; The MOA Collaboration; Depoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Gould, A.; Lee, C.-U.; Pogge, R. W.; The mu FUN Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 1, pp. 435-440 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717..435H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690.1772P</bibcode>
			<title>Extended-Source Effect and Chromaticity in Two-Point-Mass Microlensing</title>
			<authors>Pejcha, Ondrej; Heyrovsk&#253;, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 2, pp. 1772-1796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690.1772P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689.1084K</bibcode>
			<title>Limits of Binaries That Can Be Characterized by Gravitational Microlensing</title>
			<authors>Kim, Doeon; Ryu, Yoon-Hyun; Park, Byeong-Gon; Chang, Heon-Young; Hwang, Kyu-Ha; Chung, Sun-Ju; Lee, Chung-Uk; Han, Cheongho</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 2, pp. 1084-1088.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689.1084K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684..663B</bibcode>
			<title>A Low-Mass Planet with a Possible Sub-Stellar-Mass Host in Microlensing Event MOA-2007-BLG-192</title>
			<authors>Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Udalski, A.; Sumi, T.; Abe, F.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Holderness, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Korpela, A. V.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Okumura, T.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Saito, To.; Sato, S.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; Batista, V.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Brillant, S.; Cassan, A.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Kervella, P.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 1, pp. 663-683.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684..663B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
