<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewA...17..325C</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric observations and orbital period variations of HS 0705 + 6700 and NY Vir</title>
			<authors>amurdan, C. M.; Zengin amurdan, D.; Ibanoglu, C.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 17, Issue 3, p. 325-330.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012NewA...17..325C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..12F</bibcode>
			<title>A preliminary look at the empirical mass distribution of hot B subdwarf stars</title>
			<authors>Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.; Charpinet, S.; Green, E. M.; Randall, S. K.; van Grootel, V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A12</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..12F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745L..23Q</bibcode>
			<title>Circumbinary Planets Orbiting the Rapidly Pulsating Subdwarf B-type Binary NY Vir</title>
			<authors>Qian, S.-B.; Zhu, L.-Y.; Dai, Z.-B.; Fernndez-Lajs, E.; Xiang, F.-Y.; He, J.-J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 745, Issue 2, article id. L23 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745L..23Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.480..496C</bibcode>
			<title>A compact system of small planets around a former red-giant star</title>
			<authors>Charpinet, S.; Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.; Green, E. M.; van Grootel, V.; Randall, S. K.; Silvotti, R.; Baran, A. S.; stensen, R. H.; Kawaler, S. D.; Telting, J. H.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 480, Issue 7378, pp. 496-499 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011Natur.480..496C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740L..47P</bibcode>
			<title>Exploring B4: A Pulsating sdB Star, in a Binary, in the Open Cluster NGC 6791</title>
			<authors>Pablo, Herbert; Kawaler, Steven D.; Green, Elizabeth M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 740, Issue 2, article id. L47 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740L..47P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.2871B</bibcode>
			<title>First Kepler results on compact pulsators - VII. Pulsating subdwarf B stars detected in the second half of the survey phase</title>
			<authors>Baran, A. S.; Kawaler, S. D.; Reed, M. D.; Quint, A. C.; O'Toole, S. J.;  stensen, R. H.; Telting, J. H.; Silvotti, R.; Charpinet, S.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Still, M.; Hall, J. R.; Uddin, K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 4, pp. 2871-2884.</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.2871B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011JAVSO..39...94S</bibcode>
			<title>Recent Minima of 144 Eclipsing Binary Stars</title>
			<authors>Samolyk, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Journal of the American Association of Variable Star Observers, vol. 39, nr. 1, p. 94</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011JAVSO..39...94S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734...59G</bibcode>
			<title>The Unusual Variable Hot B Subdwarf LS IV-14116</title>
			<authors>Green, E. M.; Guvenen, B.; O'Malley, C. J.; O'Connell, C. J.; Baringer, B. P.; Villareal, A. S.; Carleton, T. M.; Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.; Charpinet, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734...59G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...530A..28G</bibcode>
			<title>The MUCHFUSS project - searching for hot subdwarf binaries with massive unseen companions. Survey, target selection and atmospheric parameters</title>
			<authors>Geier, S.; Hirsch, H.; Tillich, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Bentley, S. J.;  stensen, R. H.; Heber, U.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Marsh, T. R.; Napiwotzki, R.; Barlow, B. N.; O'Toole, S. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 530, id.A28</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...530A..28G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..90N</bibcode>
			<title>Short period eclipsing binary candidates identified using SuperWASP</title>
			<authors>Norton, A. J.; Payne, S. G.; Evans, T.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.; Anderson, D. R.; Barros, S. C. C.; Butters, O. W.; Collier Cameron, A.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, B.; Faedi, F.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Horne, K. D.; Kane, S. R.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Parley, N.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Smalley, B.; Southworth, J.; Street, R. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A90</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..90N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.412..487K</bibcode>
			<title>The orbital periods of AA Dor and NY Vir</title>
			<authors>Kilkenny, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 412, Issue 1, pp. 487-491.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.412..487K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.2277D</bibcode>
			<title>On the alpha formalism for the common envelope interaction</title>
			<authors>De Marco, Orsola; Passy, Jean-Claude; Moe, Maxwell; Herwig, Falk; Mac Low, Mordecai-Mark; Paxton, Bill</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 4, pp. 2277-2292.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.2277D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1792B</bibcode>
			<title>Connecting planets around horizontal branch stars with known exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Bear, Ealeal; Soker, Noam</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 3, pp. 1792-1802.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1792B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.409.1509K</bibcode>
			<title>First Kepler results on compact pulsators - V. Slowly pulsating subdwarf B stars in short-period binaries</title>
			<authors>Kawaler, S. D.; Reed, M. D.; stensen, R. H.; Bloemen, S.; Kurtz, D. W.; Quint, A. C.; Silvotti, R.; Baran, A. S.; Green, E. M.; Charpinet, S.; Telting, J.; Aerts, C.; Handler, G.; Kjeldsen, H.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Borucki, W. J.; Koch, D. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 409, Issue 4, pp. 1509-1517.</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.409.1509K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.409.1470O</bibcode>
			<title>First Kepler results on compact pulsators - I. Survey target selection and the first pulsators</title>
			<authors>stensen, R. H.; Silvotti, R.; Charpinet, S.; Oreiro, R.; Handler, G.; Green, E. M.; Bloemen, S.; Heber, U.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Marsh, T. R.; Kurtz, D. W.; Telting, J. H.; Reed, M. D.; Kawaler, S. D.; Aerts, C.; Rodrguez-Lpez, C.; Vuckovic, M.; Ottosen, T. A.; Liimets, T.; Quint, A. C.; van Grootel, V.; Randall, S. K.; Gilliland, R. L.; Kjeldsen, H.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Borucki, W. J.; Koch, D.; Quintana, E. V.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 409, Issue 4, pp. 1470-1486.</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.409.1470O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408L..51O</bibcode>
			<title>2M1938+4603: a rich, multimode pulsating sdB star with an eclipsing dM companion observed with Kepler</title>
			<authors>stensen, R. H.; Green, E. M.; Bloemen, S.; Marsh, T. R.; Laird, J. B.; Morris, M.; Moriyama, E.; Oreiro, R.; Reed, M. D.; Kawaler, S. D.; Aerts, C.; Vuckovic, M.; Degroote, P.; Telting, J. H.; Kjeldsen, H.; Gilliland, R. L.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Borucki, W. J.; Koch, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 408, Issue 1, pp. L51-L55.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408L..51O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..86Z</bibcode>
			<title>Post-common-envelope binaries from SDSS. IX: Constraining the common-envelope efficiency</title>
			<authors>Zorotovic, M.; Schreiber, M. R.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Nebot Gmez-Morn, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A86</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..86Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A..25G</bibcode>
			<title>Hot subdwarf stars in close-up view. I. Rotational properties of subdwarf B stars in close binary systems and nature of their unseen companions</title>
			<authors>Geier, S.; Heber, U.; Podsiadlowski, Ph.; Edelmann, H.; Napiwotzki, R.; Kupfer, T.; Mller, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A25</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A..25G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010NewA...15..483B</bibcode>
			<title>Spinning-up the envelope before entering a common envelope phase</title>
			<authors>Bear, Ealeal; Soker, Noam</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 15, Issue 5, p. 483-490.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010NewA...15..483B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...513A...6O</bibcode>
			<title>A survey for pulsating subdwarf B stars with the Nordic Optical Telescope</title>
			<authors>stensen, R. H.; Oreiro, R.; Solheim, J.-E.; Heber, U.; Silvotti, R.; Gonzlez-Prez, J. M.; Ulla, A.; Prez Hernndez, F.; Rodrguez-Lpez, C.; Telting, J. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 513, id.A6</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...513A...6O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403..179D</bibcode>
			<title>A comprehensive population synthesis study of post-common envelope binaries</title>
			<authors>Davis, P. J.; Kolb, U.; Willems, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 1, pp. 179-195.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403..179D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401...23R</bibcode>
			<title>The rapidly pulsating sdO star, SDSS J160043.6+074802.9</title>
			<authors>Rodrguez-Lpez, C.; Lynas-Gray, A. E.; Kilkenny, D.; MacDonald, J.; Moya, A.; Koen, C.; Woudt, P. A.; Wium, D. J.; Oruru, B.; Zietsman, E.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 1, pp. 23-34.</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401...23R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708..253F</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling the System Parameters of 2M 1533+3759: A New Longer Period Low-Mass Eclipsing sdB+dM Binary</title>
			<authors>For, B.-Q.; Green, E. M.; Fontaine, G.; Drechsel, H.; Shaw, J. S.; Dittmann, J. A.; Fay, A. G.; Francoeur, M.; Laird, J.; Moriyama, E.; Morris, M.; Rodrguez-L pez, C.; Sierchio, J. M.; Story, S. M.; Strom, A.; Wang, C.; Adams, S. M.; Bolin, D. E.; Eskew, M.; Chayer, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 1, pp. 253-267 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...708..253F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508..869H</bibcode>
			<title>Impact of helium diffusion and helium-flash-induced carbon production on gravity-mode pulsations in subdwarf B stars</title>
			<authors>Hu, Haili; Nelemans, G.; Aerts, C.; Dupret, M.-A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 2, 2009, pp.869-876</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508..869H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..911R</bibcode>
			<title>Observations and asteroseismological analysis of the rapid subdwarf B pulsator EC 09582-1137</title>
			<authors>Randall, S. K.; van Grootel, V.; Fontaine, G.; Charpinet, S.; Brassard, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 2, 2009, pp.911-921</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..911R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...505..239V</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the line-profile variations of subdwarf B pulsators: the case of PG 1336-018 (NY Virginis)</title>
			<authors>Vuckovic, M.; stensen, R. H.; Aerts, C.; Telting, J. H.; Heber, U.; Oreiro, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 505, Issue 1, 2009, pp.239-248</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...505..239V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ARA&amp;A..47..211H</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Subdwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Heber, Ulrich</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, vol. 47, Issue 1, pp.211-251</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ARA%26A..47..211H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..737M</bibcode>
			<title>A lack of close binaries among hot horizontal branch stars in globular clusters. M 80 and NGC 5986</title>
			<authors>Moni Bidin, C.; Moehler, S.; Piotto, G.; Momany, Y.; Recio-Blanco, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 3, 2009, pp.737-751</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..737M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009CoAst.159...75O</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology and Evolution of EHB stars</title>
			<authors>stensen, R. H.</authors>
			<journal>"Communications in Asteroseismology, Vol. 159, p. 75-87. Proceedings of "JENAM 2008 Symposium No 4: Asteroseismology and Stellar Evolution", held on September 8-12 2008, edited by Sonja Schuh and Gerald Handler."</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009CoAst.159...75O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493..595C</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the driving region in hot subdwarf stars through nonadiabatic asteroseismology: the principle of the method</title>
			<authors>Charpinet, S.; Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 2, 2009, pp.595-600</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493..595C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...492..815T</bibcode>
			<title>Time-resolved high-resolution spectroscopy of the bright pulsating subdwarf B star Balloon 090100001</title>
			<authors>Telting, J. H.; Geier, S.; stensen, R. H.; Heber, U.; Glowienka, L.; Nielsen, T.; Oreiro, R.; Frandsen, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 492, Issue 3, 2008, pp.815-821</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...492..815T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...490..243H</bibcode>
			<title>A seismic approach to testing different formation channels of subdwarf B stars</title>
			<authors>Hu, Haili; Dupret, M.-A.; Aerts, C.; Nelemans, G.; Kawaler, S. D.; Miglio, A.; Montalban, J.; Scuflaire, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 490, Issue 1, 2008, pp.243-252</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...490..243H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...489..377C</bibcode>
			<title>Testing the forward modeling approach in asteroseismology. II. Structure and internal dynamics of the hot B subdwarf component in the close eclipsing binary system PG 1336-018</title>
			<authors>Charpinet, S.; van Grootel, V.; Reese, D.; Fontaine, G.; Green, E. M.; Brassard, P.; Chayer, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 489, Issue 1, 2008, pp.377-394</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...489..377C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008BAVSR..57...45G</bibcode>
			<title>Aus dem IBVS 5780, 5786, 5789, 5781, 5784, 5791, 5795, 5796, 5788, 5790, 5797, 5798 and 5800.</title>
			<authors>Grimm, W.</authors>
			<journal>BAV Rundbrief, 57, 45-48 (2008)</journal>
			<date>0/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008BAVSR..57...45G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;ARv..14..217C</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology and interferometry</title>
			<authors>Cunha, M. S.; Aerts, C.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Baglin, A.; Bigot, L.; Brown, T. M.; Catala, C.; Creevey, O. L.; Domiciano de Souza, A.; Eggenberger, P.; Garcia, P. J. V.; Grundahl, F.; Kervella, P.; Kurtz, D. W.; Mathias, P.; Miglio, A.; Monteiro, M. J. P. F. G.; Perrin, G.; Pijpers, F. P.; Pourbaix, D.; Quirrenbach, A.; Rousselet-Perraut, K.; Teixeira, T. C.; Thvenin, F.; Thompson, M. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomy and Astrophysics Review, Volume 14, Issue 3-4, pp. 217-360</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26ARv..14..217C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007IBVS.5802....1H</bibcode>
			<title>Photoelectric Minima of Selected Eclipsing Binaries and Maxima of Pulsating Stars</title>
			<authors>Hubscher, Joachim</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 5802, 1.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007IBVS.5802....1H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007IBVS.5800....1W</bibcode>
			<title>NSVS 14256825: A New HW Vir Type System</title>
			<authors>Wils, Patrick; di Scala, Giorgio; Otero, Sebastian A.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 5800, 1.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007IBVS.5800....1W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...473..569H</bibcode>
			<title>An evolutionary study of the pulsating subdwarf B eclipsing binary PG 1336-018 (NY Virginis)</title>
			<authors>Hu, Haili; Nelemans, G.; stensen, R.; Aerts, C.; Vuckovic, M.; Groot, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 473, Issue 2, October II 2007, pp.569-577</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...473..569H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...471..605V</bibcode>
			<title>The binary properties of the pulsating subdwarf B eclipsing binary PG 1336-018 (NY Virginis)</title>
			<authors>Vuckovic, M.; Aerts, C.; stensen, R.; Nelemans, G.; Hu, Haili; Jeffery, C. S.; Dhillon, V. S.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 471, Issue 2, August IV 2007, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...471..605V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.378.1049R</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the pulsations of subdwarf B stars: HS 0039+4302, HS 0444+0458 and an examination of the group properties of resolved pulsators</title>
			<authors>Reed, M. D.; Terndrup, D. M.; Zhou, A.-Y.; Unterborn, C. T.; An, D.; Eggen, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 378, Issue 3, pp. 1049-1063.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.378.1049R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006IBVS.5731....1H</bibcode>
			<title>Photoelectric Minima of Selected Eclipsing Binaries and Maxima of Pulsating Stars</title>
			<authors>Hubscher, J.; Paschke, A.; Walter, F.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 5731, 1.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006IBVS.5731....1H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...456.1069S</bibcode>
			<title>The new pre-cataclysmic binary PG 2200+085</title>
			<authors>Shimansky, V.; Sakhibullin, N. A.; Bikmaev, I.; Ritter, H.; Suleimanov, V.; Borisov, N.; Galeev, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 456, Issue 3, September IV 2006, pp.1069-1075</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...456.1069S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.367.1317A</bibcode>
			<title>High-speed colourimetry of the subdwarf B star SDSSJ171722.08+58055.8 with ULTRACAM*</title>
			<authors>Aerts, C.; Jeffery, C. S.; Fontaine, G.; Dhillon, V. S.; Marsh, T. R.; Groot, P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 367, Issue 3, pp. 1317-1322.</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.367.1317A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.367..179Z</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the pulsations of the subdwarf B star KPD 2109 + 4401</title>
			<authors>Zhou, A.-Y.; Reed, M. D.; Harms, S.; Terndrup, D. M.; An, D.; Zola, S.; Gazeas, K. D.; Niarchos, P. G.; Ogloza, W.; Baran, A.; Wolf, G. W.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 367, Issue 1, pp. 179-185.</journal>
			<date>3/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.367..179Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...446..785M</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of eclipsing variables</title>
			<authors>Malkov, O. Yu.; Oblak, E.; Snegireva, E. A.; Torra, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 446, Issue 2, February I 2006, pp.785-789</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...446..785M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MmSAI..77..417R</bibcode>
			<title>The observational search for tidally tipped pulsation axes in subdwarf B stars .</title>
			<authors>Reed, M. D.; Whole Earth Telescope Xcov 21 and 23 Collaborations</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ Astronomica Italiana, v.77, p.417 (2006)</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MmSAI..77..417R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006BSAO...59...34V</bibcode>
			<title>Precatalysmic binary systems.</title>
			<authors>Voichanskaya, N. F.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the Special Astrophysical Observatory, 59, 34-51 (2006)</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006BSAO...59...34V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006BaltA..15..279W</bibcode>
			<title>Follow-Up Observations of Known EC 14026-TYPE Pulsators</title>
			<authors>Wolf, G. W.; Reed, M. D.; Zhou, A.-Y.; Terndrup, D. M.; Harms, S. L.; An, D.; Chen, C.-W.; Lin, H.-C.; Zola, S.; Baran, A.; Ogloza, W.; Siwak, M.; Gazeas, K. D.; Niarchos, P. G.; Kilkenny, D.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, Vol. 15, p. 279-282</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006BaltA..15..279W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006BaltA..15..255K</bibcode>
			<title>Four Rapidly Pulsating Sdb Stars Revisited</title>
			<authors>Kilkenny, D.; Kotze, J. P.; Jurua, E.; Brownstone, M.; Babiker, H. A.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, Vol. 15, p. 255-258</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006BaltA..15..255K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006BaltA..15..207M</bibcode>
			<title>Helium, Carbon and Silicon Abundances in the HW VIR Eclipsing Binary Subdwarf-B Primary</title>
			<authors>Mortimore, A. N.; Lynas-Gray, A. E.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, Vol. 15, p. 207-210</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006BaltA..15..207M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...634..602R</bibcode>
			<title>Pulsating Stars in Close Binaries. I. Investigations of Eclipse Mapping and Oblique Pulsations</title>
			<authors>Reed, M. D.; Brondel, B. J.; Kawaler, S. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 634, Issue 1, pp. 602-615.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...634..602R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...440..667O</bibcode>
			<title>The MultiSite Spectroscopic Telescope campaign: 2 m spectroscopy of the V361 Hya variable PG 1605+072</title>
			<authors>O'Toole, S. J.; Heber, U.; Jeffery, C. S.; Dreizler, S.; Schuh, S. L.; Woolf, V. M.; Falter, S.; Green, E. M.; For, B.-Q.; Hyde, E. A.; Kjeldsen, H.; Mauch, T.; White, B. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 440, Issue 2, September III 2005, pp.667-674</journal>
			<date>9/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...440..667O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005JApA...26..301S</bibcode>
			<title>Results from the Whole Earth Telescope - Indian Contributions</title>
			<authors>Seetha, S.; Ashoka, B. N.; Marar, T. M. K.</authors>
			<journal>Journal of Astrophysics and Astronomy, Vol. 26, Issue 2-3, p. 301</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005JApA...26..301S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.359..648M</bibcode>
			<title>Six detached white-dwarf close binaries</title>
			<authors>Morales-Rueda, L.; Marsh, T. R.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Nelemans, G.; Karl, C.; Napiwotzki, R.; Moran, C. K. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 359, Issue 2, pp. 648-662.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.359..648M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005PASP..117..311T</bibcode>
			<title>Astrophysics in 2004</title>
			<authors>Trimble, Virginia; Aschwanden, Markus</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 117, Issue 830, pp. 311-394.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005PASP..117..311T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.356..753N</bibcode>
			<title>Reconstructing the evolution of white dwarf binaries: further evidence for an alternative algorithm for the outcome of the common-envelope phase in close binaries</title>
			<authors>Nelemans, G.; Tout, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 356, Issue 2, pp. 753-764.</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.356..753N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...426..213P</bibcode>
			<title>Amplitude variations in the sdBV star PG 1605+072: Another beating time scale?</title>
			<authors>Pereira, T. M. D.; Lopes, I. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.426, p.213-217 (2004)</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...426..213P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004NewA....9..565K</bibcode>
			<title>Two new EC14026 stars: PG 0048+091 and PG 0154+182</title>
			<authors>Koen, C.; O'Donoghue, D.; Kilkenny, D.; Pollacco, D. L.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 9, Issue 7, p. 565-572.</journal>
			<date>9/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004NewA....9..565K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...422.1053O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a companion to the pulsating sdB Feige 48</title>
			<authors>O'Toole, S. J.; Heber, U.; Benjamin, R. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.422, p.1053-1058 (2004)</journal>
			<date>8/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...422.1053O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004PASP..116..506R</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Main-Sequence Companions to Subdwarf B Stars Using the Two Micron All Sky Survey</title>
			<authors>Reed, M. D.; Stiening, Rae</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 116, Issue 820, pp. 506-515.</journal>
			<date>6/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004PASP..116..506R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AcA....54..207K</bibcode>
			<title>Up-to-Date Linear Elements of Eclipsing Binaries</title>
			<authors>Kreiner, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, v.54, pp.207-210, (2004).</journal>
			<date>6/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AcA....54..207K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...420..251H</bibcode>
			<title>HS 2333+3927: A new sdB+dM binary with a large reflection effect</title>
			<authors>Heber, U.; Drechsel, H.; stensen, R.; Karl, C.; Napiwotzki, R.; Altmann, M.; Cordes, O.; Solheim, J.-E.; Voss, B.; Koester, D.; Folkes, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.420, p.251-264 (2004)</journal>
			<date>6/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...420..251H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...414.1043I</bibcode>
			<title>High-speed photometry of the pre-cataclysmic binary HW Virginis and its orbital period change</title>
			<authors>Ibanoglu, C.; akirli, .; Tas, G.; Evren, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.414, p.1043-1048 (2004)</journal>
			<date>2/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...414.1043I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003MNRAS.345..834K</bibcode>
			<title>A Whole Earth Telescope campaign on the pulsating subdwarf B binary system PG 1336-018 (NY Vir)</title>
			<authors>Kilkenny, D.; Reed, M. D.; O'Donoghue, D.; Kawaler, S. D.; Mukadam, A.; Kleinman, S. J.; Nitta, A.; Metcalfe, T. S.; Provencal, J. L.; Watson, T. K.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sullivan, T.; Shobbrook, R.; Jiang, X. J.; Joshi, S.; Ashoka, B. N.; Seetha, S.; Leibowitz, E.; Ibbetson, P.; Mendelson, H.; Meistas, E.; Kalytis, R.; Alisauskas, D.; Martinez, P.; van Wyk, F.; Stobie, R. S.; Marang, F.; Zola, S.; Krzesinski, J.; Ogloza, W.; Moskalik, P.; Silvotti, R.; Piccioni, A.; Vauclair, G.; Dolez, N.; Chevreton, M.; Dreizler, S.; Schuh, S. L.; Deetjen, J. L.; Solheim, J.-E.; Gonzalez Perez, J. M.; Ulla, A.; stensen, R.; Manteiga, M.; Suarez, O.; Burleigh, M.; Kepler, S. O.; Kanaan, A.; Giovannini, O.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 345, Issue 3, pp. 834-846.</journal>
			<date>11/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003MNRAS.345..834K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003MNRAS.344..644H</bibcode>
			<title>New VIC photometry of the sdOB binary AA Dor and an improved photometric model</title>
			<authors>Hilditch, R. W.; Kilkenny, D.; Lynas-Gray, A. E.; Hill, G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notice of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 344, Issue 2, pp. 644-650.</journal>
			<date>9/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003MNRAS.344..644H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...406..305S</bibcode>
			<title>The age, life expectancy, and space density   of Post Common Envelope Binaries</title>
			<authors>Schreiber, M. R.; Gnsicke, B. T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.406, p.305-321 (2003)</journal>
			<date>7/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...406..305S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...583L..31G</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of A New Class of Pulsating Stars: Gravity-Mode Pulsators among Subdwarf B Stars</title>
			<authors>Green, E. M.; Fontaine, G.; Reed, M. D.; Callerame, K.; Seitenzahl, I. R.; White, B. A.; Hyde, E. A.; stensen, R.; Cordes, O.; Brassard, P.; Falter, S.; Jeffery, E. J.; Dreizler, S.; Schuh, S. L.; Giovanni, M.; Edelmann, H.; Rigby, J.; Bronowska, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 583, Issue 1, pp. L31-L34.</journal>
			<date>1/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...583L..31G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003BaltA..12..578J</bibcode>
			<title>Moletai Observatory as a Part of the Whole Earth Telescope</title>
			<authors>Janulis, R.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, Vol. 12, p. 578-583</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003BaltA..12..578J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003BaltA..12..287B</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of Pulsating sdB Stars Observed at Catania Astrophysical Observatory</title>
			<authors>Bonanno, A.; Frasca, A.; Lanza, A. F.; Ventura, R.; Mignemi, B.; Silvotti, R.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.12, p.287-294.</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003BaltA..12..287B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003BaltA..12..211S</bibcode>
			<title>On the quality of WET time.</title>
			<authors>Solheim, J.-E.; Sullivan, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.12, p.211-219.</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003BaltA..12..211S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003BaltA..12..193R</bibcode>
			<title>Whole earth telescope headquarters standard data formats.</title>
			<authors>Riddle, R. L.; Kawaler, S. D.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.12, p.193-204.</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003BaltA..12..193R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003BaltA..12..183R</bibcode>
			<title>XQED: The Next Generation of WET Light Curve Reduction and Analysis Software</title>
			<authors>Riddle, R. L.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.12, p.183-191.</journal>
			<date>0/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003BaltA..12..183R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002A&amp;A...389..180S</bibcode>
			<title>The temporal spectrum of the sdB pulsating star HS 2201+2610 at 2 ms resolution</title>
			<authors>Silvotti, R.; Janulis, R.; Schuh, S. L.; Charpinet, S.; Oswalt, T.; Silvestri, N.; Gonzalez Perez, J. M.; Kalytis, R.; Meistas, E.; Alisauskas, D.; Marinoni, S.; Jiang, X. J.; Reed, M. D.; Riddle, R. L.; Bernabei, S.; Heber, U.; Brnbantner, O.; Cordes, O.; Dreizler, S.; Goehler, E.; stensen, R.; Bochanski, J.; Carlson, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.389, p.180-190 (2002)</journal>
			<date>7/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002A%26A...389..180S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.333..231M</bibcode>
			<title>Photometry of four binary subdwarf B stars and the nature of their unseen companion stars</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Marsh, T. R.; Heber, U.; Morales-Rueda, L.; North, R. C.; Lawson, W. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 333, Issue 1, pp. 231-240.</journal>
			<date>6/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.333..231M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002MNRAS.331..399K</bibcode>
			<title>A multisite campaign on the pulsating subdwarf B star PG 1047+003</title>
			<authors>Kilkenny, D.; Billres, M.; Stobie, R. S.; Fontaine, G.; Shobbrook, R. R.; O'Donoghue, D.; Brassard, P.; Sullivan, D. J.; Burleigh, M. R.; Barstow, M. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 331, Issue 2, pp. 399-406.</journal>
			<date>3/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002MNRAS.331..399K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001AN....322..387C</bibcode>
			<title>The pulsations in subdwarf B stars</title>
			<authors>Charpinet, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, vol. 322, no. 5/6, p. 387-393</journal>
			<date>12/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001AN....322..387C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...379..893D</bibcode>
			<title>HS 0705+6700: A new eclipsing sdB binary</title>
			<authors>Drechsel, H.; Heber, U.; Napiwotzki, R.; stensen, R.; Solheim, J.-E.; Johannessen, F.; Schuh, S. L.; Deetjen, J.; Zola, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.379, p.893-904 (2001)</journal>
			<date>12/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...379..893D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...378..466O</bibcode>
			<title>Four new subdwarf B pulsators</title>
			<authors>stensen, R.; Heber, U.; Silvotti, R.; Solheim, J.-E.; Dreizler, S.; Edelmann, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.378, p.466-476 (2001)</journal>
			<date>11/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...378..466O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001MNRAS.326.1391M</bibcode>
			<title>The binary fraction of extreme horizontal branch stars</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. f. L.; Heber, U.; Marsh, T. R.; North, R. C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 326, Issue 4, pp. 1391-1402.</journal>
			<date>10/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001MNRAS.326.1391M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001JRASC..95..209C</bibcode>
			<title>Thorie et Modlisation des toiles Sous-Naines de Type B Pulsantes: Confrontation avec les Observations</title>
			<authors>Charpinet, Stphane</authors>
			<journal>Journal of the Royal Astronomical Society of Canada, Vol. 95, p.209</journal>
			<date>10/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001JRASC..95..209C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001PASP..113..775C</bibcode>
			<title>A Theoretical Exploration of the Pulsational Stability of Subdwarf B Stars</title>
			<authors>Charpinet, Stphane; Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 113, Issue 785, pp. 775-788.</journal>
			<date>7/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001PASP..113..775C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001A&amp;A...368..994A</bibcode>
			<title>Physical parameters of sdB stars from spectral energy distributions</title>
			<authors>Aznar Cuadrado, R.; Jeffery, C. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.368, p.994-1005 (2001)</journal>
			<date>3/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001A%26A...368..994A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000AAS...197.4602R</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving pulsations across the surface of a pulsating subdwarf B star.</title>
			<authors>Reed, M. D.; Kawaler, S. D.; Whole Earth Telescope (Xcov 17) Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society, 197th AAS Meeting, #46.02; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 32, p.1477</journal>
			<date>12/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000AAS...197.4602R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000MNRAS.318..974J</bibcode>
			<title>Radial velocities of pulsating subdwarf B stars: KPD 2109+4401 and PB 8783</title>
			<authors>Jeffery, C. Simon; Pollacco, Don</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 318, Issue 4, pp. 974-982.</journal>
			<date>11/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000MNRAS.318..974J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000MNRAS.317..861S</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation, planets, and the `second parameter' of the horizontal branch</title>
			<authors>Soker, Noam; Harpaz, Amos</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 317, Issue 4, pp. 861-866.</journal>
			<date>10/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000MNRAS.317..861S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000NewAR..44....3W</bibcode>
			<title>Cataclysmic variables: some lacunae</title>
			<authors>Warner, B.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 44, Issue 1-2, p. 3-8.</journal>
			<date>4/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000NewAR..44....3W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000ApJ...533..984S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Formation of Helium Double Degenerate Stars and Pre-Cataclysmic Variables</title>
			<authors>Sandquist, Eric L.; Taam, Ronald E.; Burkert, Andreas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 533, Issue 2, pp. 984-997.</journal>
			<date>4/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000ApJ...533..984S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000IBVS.4870....1K</bibcode>
			<title>The 75th Name-List of Variable Stars</title>
			<authors>Kazarovets, E. V.; Samus, N. N.; Durlevich, O. V.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 4870, 1.</journal>
			<date>3/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000IBVS.4870....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000Obs...120...48K</bibcode>
			<title>On the orbital periods of three close binaries with hot subdwarf primaries</title>
			<authors>Kilkenny, D.; Keuris, S.; Marang, F.; Roberts, G.; van Wyk, F.; Ogloza, W.</authors>
			<journal>The Observatory, Vol. 120, p. 48-59 (2000)</journal>
			<date>2/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000Obs...120...48K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000MNRAS.311..877M</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital periods of the binary sdB stars PG0940+068 and PG 1247+554</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Moran, C. K. J.; Marsh, T. R.; Gatti, A. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 311, Issue 4, pp. 877-880.</journal>
			<date>2/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000MNRAS.311..877M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000MmSAI..71.1109S</bibcode>
			<title>The TT1 three channel photometer and the wet project.</title>
			<authors>Silvotti, R.; Vittone, A.; de Martino, D.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societa Astronomica Italiana, 71, 1109-1112 (2000)</journal>
			<date>0/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000MmSAI..71.1109S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000BaltA...9..411O</bibcode>
			<title>Results from the Tromso CCD Photometry Project]</title>
			<authors>Ostensen, R.; Solheim, J.-E.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.9, p.411-424.</journal>
			<date>0/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000BaltA...9..411O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000BaltA...9..395S</bibcode>
			<title>CCD Photometry of Variable Subdwarfs and White Dwarfs at Calar Alto Observatory</title>
			<authors>Schuh, Sonja; Dreizler, Stefan; Deetjen, Jochen L.; Heber, Uli; Geckeler, Ralf D.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.9, p.395-402.</journal>
			<date>0/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000BaltA...9..395S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000BaltA...9..197Z</bibcode>
			<title>Reflection Effect in PG 1336-018</title>
			<authors>Zola, S.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.9, p.197-204.</journal>
			<date>0/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000BaltA...9..197Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000BaltA...9..183R</bibcode>
			<title>Preliminary Results from XCOV 17: PG 1336-018</title>
			<authors>Reed, M. D.; Kilkenny, D.; Kawaler, S. D.; Mukadam, A.; Kleinman, S. J.; Nitta-Kleinman, A.; Provencal, J. L.; Watson, T.; Sullivan, D.; Sullivan, T.; Shobbrook, B.; Jiang, X. J.; Ashoka, B. N.; Seetha, S.; Leibowitz, E.; Ibbetson, P.; Mendelson, H.; Meistas, E. G.; Kalytis, R.; Alisauskas, D.; O'Donoghue, D.; Martinez, P.; van Wyk, F.; Stobie, R.; Marang, F.; Zola, S.; Krzesinski, J.; Ogloza, W.; Moskalik, P.; Silvotti, R.; Piccioni, A.; Vauclair, G.; Dolez, N.; Rene-Fremy, J.; Chevreton, M.; Ulla, A.; Dreizler, S.; Schuh, S.; Deetjen, J.; Solheim, J. E.; Perez, J.; Suarez, O.; Manteiga, M.; Burleigh, M.; Barstow, M.; Kepler, S. O.; Kanaan, A.; Giovannini, O.; Metcalfe, T.; Ostensen, R.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.9, p.183-195.</journal>
			<date>0/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000BaltA...9..183R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000BaltA...9..113D</bibcode>
			<title>Time-Resolved Spectroscopy of BPM 37093 and PG 1336-018</title>
			<authors>Dreizler, Stefan; Koester, Detlev; Heber, Uli</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.9, p.113-118.</journal>
			<date>0/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000BaltA...9..113D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000BaltA...9....3K</bibcode>
			<title>The State and Fugure of WET as an Instrument</title>
			<authors>Kleinman, S. J.; O'Donoghue, D.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.9, p.3-12.</journal>
			<date>0/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000BaltA...9....3K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999MNRAS.310..773O</bibcode>
			<title>Confirmation of eclipses in KPD 0422+5421, a binary containing a white dwarf and a subdwarf B star</title>
			<authors>Orosz, Jerome A.; Wade, Richard A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 310, Issue 3, pp. 773-783.</journal>
			<date>12/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999MNRAS.310..773O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999MNRAS.306..213K</bibcode>
			<title>The EC 14026 stars - XIII. EC 05217-3914 and KUV 0442+1416</title>
			<authors>Koen, C.; O'Donoghue, D.; Kilkenny, D.; Stobie, R. S.; Saffer, R. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 306, Issue 1, pp. 213-222.</journal>
			<date>6/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999MNRAS.306..213K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999MNRAS.305...28K</bibcode>
			<title>The EC 14026 stars - XII. PG 1219+534, PG 0911+456: successes and new challenges for the Fe driving mechanism</title>
			<authors>Koen, C.; O'Donoghue, D.; Pollacco, D. L.; Charpinet, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 305, Issue 1, pp. 28-38.</journal>
			<date>5/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999MNRAS.305...28K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999AGAb...15..106D</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of Variable [pre-] White Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Dreizler, S.; Schuh, S.; Deetjen, J.; Heber, U.; Edelmann, H.; Koester, D.</authors>
			<journal>AG Abstract Services, vol. 15.  Abstracts of Contributed Talks and Posters presented at the Annual Scientific Meeting of the Astronomische Gesellschaft, in Goettingen, 20-25 September 1999.</journal>
			<date>0/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999AGAb...15..106D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998MNRAS.300.1105K</bibcode>
			<title>The EC 14026 stars - XI. Feige 48: a link in its class</title>
			<authors>Koen, C.; O'Donoghue, D.; Pollacco, D. L.; Nitta, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 300, Issue 4, pp. 1105-1110.</journal>
			<date>11/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998MNRAS.300.1105K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998MNRAS.300..567K</bibcode>
			<title>The EC 14026 stars - IX. KPD 2109+4401</title>
			<authors>Koen, Chris</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 300, Issue 2, pp. 567-572.</journal>
			<date>10/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998MNRAS.300..567K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998MNRAS.296..329K</bibcode>
			<title>The EC 14026 stars - VIII. PG 1336-018: a pulsating sdB star in an HWVir-type eclipsing binary</title>
			<authors>Kilkenny, D.; O'Donoghue, D.; Koen, C.; Lynas-Gray, A. E.; van Wyk, F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 296, Issue 2, pp. 329-338.</journal>
			<date>5/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998MNRAS.296..329K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998BaltA...7..313O</bibcode>
			<title>The EC 14026 Stars</title>
			<authors>O'Donoghue, D.; Koen, C.; Kilkenny, D.; Stobie, R. S.; Lynas-Gray, A. E.; Kawaler, S. D.</authors>
			<journal>Baltic Astronomy, v.7, p.313-317.</journal>
			<date>3/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998BaltA...7..313O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998ApJ...494L..75B</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of p-Mode Pulsations in the Hot Subdwarf B Star KPD 2109+4401</title>
			<authors>Billeres, M.; Fontaine, G.; Brassard, P.; Charpinet, S.; Liebert, James; Saffer, R. A.; Bergeron, P.; Vauclair, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Letters v.494, p.L75</journal>
			<date>2/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998ApJ...494L..75B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992MNRAS.258..521H</bibcode>
			<title>Low-dispersion spectroscopy of blue stars from the UK Schmidt Telescope UBVRI survey</title>
			<authors>Holmgren, D. E.; McCausland, R. J. H.; Dufton, P. L.; Keenan, F. P.; Kilkenny, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society (ISSN 0035-8711), vol. 258, no. 3, p. 521-526.</journal>
			<date>10/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992MNRAS.258..521H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1992AJ....104..203W</bibcode>
			<title>Studies of hot B subdwarfs. VIII - Stromgren photometry of hot, hydrogen-rich subdwarf candidates in the Palomar-Green and Kitt Peak-Downes surveys</title>
			<authors>Wesemael, F.; Fontaine, G.; Bergeron, P.; Lamontagne, R.; Green, R. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 104, no. 1, July 1992, p. 203-215. Research supported by NSERC, FCAR, and Killam Fellowship.</journal>
			<date>7/1992</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1992AJ....104..203W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988SAAOC..12....1K</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of spectroscopically identified hot subdwarf stars.</title>
			<authors>Kilkenny, D.; Heber, U.; Drilling, J. S.</authors>
			<journal>South African Astronomical Observatory Circular, No. 12, 80 pp.</journal>
			<date>0/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988SAAOC..12....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986ApJS...61..305G</bibcode>
			<title>The Palomar-Green catalog of ultraviolet-excess stellar objects</title>
			<authors>Green, R. F.; Schmidt, M.; Liebert, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 61, June 1986, p. 305-352. Research supported by the California Institute of Technology.</journal>
			<date>6/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986ApJS...61..305G</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
