<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.2087H</bibcode>
			<title>A metric and optimization scheme for microlens planet searches</title>
			<authors>Horne, Keith; Snodgrass, Colin; Tsapras, Yianni</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 4, pp. 2087-2102.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.2087H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..623P</bibcode>
			<title>An ultracool Star's Candidate Planet</title>
			<authors>Pravdo, Steven H.; Shaklan, Stuart B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 623-632 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..623P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1826D</bibcode>
			<title>Microlensing Event MOA-2007-BLG-400: Exhuming the Buried Signature of a Cool, Jovian-Mass Planet</title>
			<authors>Dong, Subo; Bond, I. A.; Gould, A.; Kozlowski, Szymon; Miyake, N.; Gaudi, B. S.; Bennett, D. P.; Abe, F.; Gilmore, A. C.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sato, S.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Sweatman, W.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; The MOA Collaboration; Bolt, G.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Han, C.; Janczak, J.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; McCormick, J.; Monard, B.; Maury, A.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Santallo, R.; Stanek, K. Z.; The muFUN Collaboration; Udalski, A.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; The OGLE Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1826-1837 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1826D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...695..970D</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE-2005-BLG-071Lb, the Most Massive M Dwarf Planetary Companion?</title>
			<authors>Dong, Subo; Gould, Andrew; Udalski, Andrzej; Anderson, Jay; Christie, G. W.; Gaudi, B. S.; OGLE Collaboration; Jaroszynski, M.; Kubiak, M.; Szyman ski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; muFUN Collaboration; DePoy, D. L.; Fox, D. B.; Gal-Yam, A.; Han, C.; L&#233; pine, S.; McCormick, J.; Ofek, E.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; MOA Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Britton, T. R.; Gilmore, A. C.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Motomura, M.; Muraki, Y.; Nakamura, S.; Ohnishi, K.; Okada, C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sasaki, M.; Sullivan, D.; Sumi, T.; Tristram, P. J.; Yanagisawa, T.; Yock, P. C. M.; Yoshoika, T.; PLANET/Robo Net Collaborations; Albrow, M. D.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Brillant, S.; Calitz, H.; Cassan, A.; Cook, K. H.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Prester, D. Dominis; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu&#233;, P.; Greenhill, J.; Hill, K.; Hoffman, M.; Horne, K.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Kane, S.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J. B.; Martin, R.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Vinter, C.; Wambsganss, J.; Williams, A.; Bode, M.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Doublier, Vanessa; Foellmi, Cedric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 695, Issue 2, pp. 970-987 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...695..970D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691..452H</bibcode>
			<title>Microlensing Zone of Planets Detectable Through the Channel of High-Magnification Events</title>
			<authors>Han, Cheongho</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 1, pp. 452-457 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691..452H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690..743B</bibcode>
			<title>A Jupiter-Like Planet Orbiting the Nearby M dwarf GJ 832</title>
			<authors>Bailey, Jeremy; Butler, R. Paul; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, Hugh R. A.; O'Toole, Simon; Carter, Brad D.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 1, pp. 743-747 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690..743B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AN....330....4T</bibcode>
			<title>RoboNet-II: Follow-up observations of microlensing events with a robotic network of telescopes</title>
			<authors>Tsapras, Y.; Street, R.; Horne, K.; Snodgrass, C.; Dominik, M.; Allan, A.; Steele, I.; Bramich, D. M.; Saunders, E. S.; Rattenbury, N.; Mottram, C.; Fraser, S.; Clay, N.; Burgdorf, M.; Bode, M.; Lister, T. A.; Hawkins, E.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Fouqu&#233; , P.; Albrow, M.; Menzies, J.; Cassan, A.; Dominis-Prester, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.330, Issue 1, p.4</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AN....330....4T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689.1084K</bibcode>
			<title>Limits of Binaries That Can Be Characterized by Gravitational Microlensing</title>
			<authors>Kim, Doeon; Ryu, Yoon-Hyun; Park, Byeong-Gon; Chang, Heon-Young; Hwang, Kyu-Ha; Chung, Sun-Ju; Lee, Chung-Uk; Han, Cheongho</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 2, pp. 1084-1088.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689.1084K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689...53H</bibcode>
			<title>A Characteristic Planetary Feature in Double-Peaked, High-Magnification Microlensing Events</title>
			<authors>Han, Cheongho; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 1, pp. 53-58.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689...53H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...491..587C</bibcode>
			<title>An alternative parameterisation for binary-lens caustic-crossing events</title>
			<authors>Cassan, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 491, Issue 2, 2008, pp.587-595</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...491..587C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681.1593G</bibcode>
			<title>Hexadecapole Approximation in Planetary Microlensing</title>
			<authors>Gould, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 2, pp. 1593-1598.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681.1593G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...474..293B</bibcode>
			<title>The HARPS search for southern extra-solar planets. X. A m sin i = 11 M_&amp;oplus; planet around the nearby spotted M dwarf GJ 674</title>
			<authors>Bonfils, X.; Mayor, M.; Delfosse, X.; Forveille, T.; Gillon, M.; Perrier, C.; Udry, S.; Bouchy, F.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Bertaux, J.-L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 474, Issue 1, October IV 2007, pp.293-299</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...474..293B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..823M</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of Earth-like Planets During and After Giant Planet Migration</title>
			<authors>Mandell, Avi M.; Raymond, Sean N.; Sigurdsson, Steinn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 823-844.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..823M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...466..157S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic and light curve characterization of bulge microlensing events</title>
			<authors>Soto, M.; Minniti, D.; Rejkuba, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 466, Issue 1, April IV 2007, pp.157-164</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...466..157S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007LAstr.121...17C</bibcode>
			<title>Des planetes extra-solaires revelees par effet de microlentille gravitationnelle.</title>
			<authors>Cassan, A.</authors>
			<journal>L'astronomie, 121, 17-22 (2007)</journal>
			<date>0/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007LAstr.121...17C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...647L.171B</bibcode>
			<title>Identification of the OGLE-2003-BLG-235/MOA-2003-BLG-53 Planetary Host Star</title>
			<authors>Bennett, David P.; Anderson, Jay; Bond, Ian A.; Udalski, Andrzej; Gould, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 647, Issue 2, pp. L171-L174.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...647L.171B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644L..37G</bibcode>
			<title>Microlens OGLE-2005-BLG-169 Implies That Cool Neptune-like Planets Are Common</title>
			<authors>Gould, A.; Udalski, A.; An, D.; Bennett, D. P.; Zhou, A.-Y.; Dong, S.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Gaudi, B. S.; Yock, P. C. M.; Bond, I. A.; Christie, G. W.; Horne, K.; Anderson, J.; Stanek, K. Z.; DePoy, D. L.; Han, C.; McCormick, J.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Poindexter, S. D.; Soszynski, I.; Szymanski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; Paczynski, B.; Bramich, D. M.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I. A.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Bode, M. F.; Botzler, C. S.; Mao, S.; Swaving, S. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 1, pp. L37-L40.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644L..37G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...628L.109U</bibcode>
			<title>A Jovian-Mass Planet in Microlensing Event OGLE-2005-BLG-071</title>
			<authors>Udalski, A.; Jaroszynski, M.; Paczynski, B.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Soszynski, I.; Pietrzynski, G.; Ulaczyk, K.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Dong, S.; Gal-Yam, A.; Gaudi, B. S.; Gould, A.; Han, C.; L&#233;pine, S.; McCormick, J.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Muraki, Y.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Bramich, D. M.; Dieters, S. W.; Greenhill, J.; Hill, K.; Horne, K.; Kubas, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 628, Issue 2, pp. L109-L112.</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...628L.109U</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
