<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewAR..56...25B</bibcode>
			<title>The first extrasolar planet detected via gravitational microlensing</title>
			<authors>Bond, Ian A.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 56, Issue 1, p. 25-32.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012NewAR..56...25B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1641S</bibcode>
			<title>A Cold Neptune-Mass Planet OGLE-2007-BLG-368Lb: Cold Neptunes Are Common</title>
			<authors>Sumi, T.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Udalski, A.; Batista, V.; Dominik, M.; Fouqu, P.; Kubas, D.; Gould, A.; Macintosh, B.; Cook, K.; Dong, S.; Skuljan, L.; Cassan, A.; Abe, F.; Botzler, C. S.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nagayama, T.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Beaulieu, J. P.; Cole, A.; Coutures, Ch.; Duran, M. F.; Greenhill, J.; Jablonski, F.; Marboeuf, U.; Martioli, E.; Pedretti, E.; Pejcha, O.; Rojo, P.; Albrow, M. D.; Brillant, S.; Bode, M.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Calitz, H.; Corrales, E.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Hill, K.; Hoffman, M.; Horne, K.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kains, N.; Kane, S.; Marquette, J. B.; Martin, R.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Street, R.; Tsapras, Y.; Wambsganss, J.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; PLANET Collaboration; Szymanski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; OGLE Collaboration; Allen, W.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Han, C.; Janczak, J.; Lee, C.-U.; McCormick, J.; Mallia, F.; Monard, B.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Santallo, R.; muFUN Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1641-1653 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1641S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
