<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A.116D</bibcode>
			<title>Prospecting transit duration variations in extrasolar planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Damiani, C.; Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A116</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...535A.116D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414..108B</bibcode>
			<title>On the use of the Virtual Observatory to select calibrators for phase-referenced astrometry of exoplanet-host stars</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonneau, D.; Mourard, D.; Lafrasse, S.; Mella, G.; Duvert, G.; Chelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. 108-115.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.414..108B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A..50L</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining tidal dissipation in F-type main-sequence stars: the case of CoRoT-11</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Damiani, C.; Gandolfi, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A50</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...529A..50L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A..29L</bibcode>
			<title>New parameters and transit timing studies for OGLE2-TR-L9 b</title>
			<authors>Lendl, M.; Afonso, C.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Nikolov, N.; Henning, Th.; Swain, M.; Greiner, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A29</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...522A..29L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721L.153J</bibcode>
			<title>A Hot Jupiter Orbiting the 1.7 M sun Subgiant HD 102956</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Bowler, Brendan P.; Howard, Andrew W.; Henry, Gregory W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Brewer, John Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Morton, Timothy D.; Crepp, Justin R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. L153-L157 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...721L.153J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407..507C</bibcode>
			<title>Line-profile tomography of exoplanet transits - II. A gas-giant planet transiting a rapidly rotating A5 star</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Guenther, E.; Smalley, B.; McDonald, I.; Hebb, L.; Andersen, J.; Augusteijn, Th.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Cochran, W. D.; Endl, M.; Fossey, S. J.; Hartmann, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Telting, J.; Waldmann, I. P.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 1, pp. 507-514.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.407..507C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707..167S</bibcode>
			<title>Physical Properties of the 0.94-Day Period Transiting Planetary System WASP-18</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Dominik, M.; Glitrup, M.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Mathiasen, M.; Anderson, D. R.; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Burgdorf, M.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Harpse, K.; Hessman, F.; Hundertmark, M.; Maier, G.; Mancini, L.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Skottfelt, J.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.; Zimmer, F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, article id. 167-172 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...707..167S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...497..545S</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE2-TR-L9b: an exoplanet transiting a rapidly rotating F3 star</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.; Koppenhoefer, J.; van der Burg, R. F. J.; Dreizler, S.; Greiner, J.; de Hoon, M. D. J.; Husser, T. O.; Krhler, T.; Saglia, R. P.; Vuijsje, F. N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 497, Issue 2, 2009, pp.545-550</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009A%26A...497..545S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...476.1357S</bibcode>
			<title>A search for transiting extrasolar planet candidates in the OGLE-II microlens database of the galactic plane</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.; van der Burg, R. F. J.; de Hoon, M. D. J.; Vuijsje, F. N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 476, Issue 3, December IV 2007, pp.1357-1363</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2007A%26A...476.1357S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
