<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721.1829A</bibcode>
			<title>Six High-precision Transits of OGLE-TR-113b</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; L&#243;pez-Morales, M.; Elliot, J. L.; Seager, S.; Osip, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. 1829-1834 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...721.1829A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010NewA...15..433M</bibcode>
			<title>VISTA Variables in the Via Lactea (VVV): The public ESO near-IR variability survey of the Milky Way</title>
			<authors>Minniti, D.; Lucas, P. W.; Emerson, J. P.; Saito, R. K.; Hempel, M.; Pietrukowicz, P.; Ahumada, A. V.; Alonso, M. V.; Alonso-Garcia, J.; Arias, J. I.; Bandyopadhyay, R. M.; Barb&#225;, R. H.; Barbuy, B.; Bedin, L. R.; Bica, E.; Borissova, J.; Bronfman, L.; Carraro, G.; Catelan, M.; Clari&#225;, J. J.; Cross, N.; de Grijs, R.; D&#233;k&#225;ny, I.; Drew, J. E.; Fari&#241;a, C.; Feinstein, C.; Fern&#225;ndez Laj&#250;s, E.; Gamen, R. C.; Geisler, D.; Gieren, W.; Goldman, B.; Gonzalez, O. A.; Gunthardt, G.; Gurovich, S.; Hambly, N. C.; Irwin, M. J.; Ivanov, V. D.; Jord&#225;n, A.; Kerins, E.; Kinemuchi, K.; Kurtev, R.; L&#243;pez-Corredoira, M.; Maccarone, T.; Masetti, N.; Merlo, D.; Messineo, M.; Mirabel, I. F.; Monaco, L.; Morelli, L.; Padilla, N.; Palma, T.; Parisi, M. C.; Pignata, G.; Rejkuba, M.; Roman-Lopes, A.; Sale, S. E.; Schreiber, M. R.; Schr&#246;der, A. C.; Smith, M.; Sodr&#233;, L., Jr.; Soto, M.; Tamura, M.; Tappert, C.; Thompson, M. A.; Toledo, I.; Zoccali, M.; Pietrzynski, G.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 15, Issue 5, p. 433-443.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010NewA...15..433M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..111M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission and Tidal Heating of the Heavy and Eccentric Planet XO-3b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; Greene, Tom; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Deming, Drake L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 111-118 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..111M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A...4P</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude photometry for transiting extrasolar planetary candidates . V. Follow-up of 30 OGLE transits. New candidates</title>
			<authors>Pietrukowicz, P.; Minniti, D.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Fern&#225;ndez, J. M.; Zoccali, M.; Gieren, W.; Pietrzynski, G.; Ru&#237;z, M. T.; Udalski, A.; Szeifert, T.; Hempel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A4</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A...4P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...503..651P</bibcode>
			<title>Deep census of variable stars in a VLT/VIMOS field in Carina</title>
			<authors>Pietrukowicz, P.; Minniti, D.; Fern&#225;ndez, J. M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Ru&#237;z, M. T.; Gieren, W.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Zoccali, M.; Hempel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 503, Issue 2, 2009, pp.651-662</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...503..651P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AJ....137.4368B</bibcode>
			<title>The Lupus Transit Survey for Hot Jupiters: Results and Lessons</title>
			<authors>Bayliss, Daniel D. R.; Weldrake, David T. F.; Sackett, Penny D.; Tingley, Brandon W.; Lewis, Karen M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 137, Issue 5, pp. 4368-4376 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AJ....137.4368B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...487..749P</bibcode>
			<title>A transiting planet among 23 new near-threshold candidates from the OGLE survey - OGLE-TR-182</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Tamuz, O.; Udalski, A.; Mazeh, T.; Bouchy, F.; Melo, C.; Naef, D.; Santos, N. C.; Moutou, C.; Diaz, R. F.; Gieren, W.; Gillon, M.; Hoyer, S.; Kubiak, M.; Mayor, M.; Minniti, D.; Pietrzynski, G.; Queloz, D.; Ramirez, S.; Ruiz, M. T.; Shporer, A.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Szymanski, M. K.; Udry, S.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Zoccali, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 487, Issue 2, 2008, pp.749-754</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...487..749P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1345H</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude Photometry for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Candidates. IV. Solution to the Puzzle of the Extremely Red OGLE-TR-82 Primary</title>
			<authors>Hoyer, Sergio; Ram&#237;rez Alegr&#237;a, Sebasti&#225;n; Ivanov, Valentin D.; Minniti, Dante; Pietrzynski, Grzegorz; Ru&#237;z, Mar&#237;a Teresa; Gieren, Wolfgang; Udalski, Andrzej; Zoccali, Manuela; Carrasco, Eleazar Rodrigo; D&#237;az, Rodrigo F.; Fern&#225;ndez, Jos&#233; Miguel; Gallardo, Jos&#233;; Rejkuba, Marina; P&#233;rez, Felipe</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1345-1353.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1345H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..729F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting and predicting the yield of transit surveys: giant planets in the OGLE fields</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Morello, V.; Pont, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 2, November IV 2007, pp.729-746</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..729F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379L..11S</bibcode>
			<title>A method for the direct determination of the surface gravities of transiting extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Wheatley, Peter J.; Sams, Giles</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 379, Issue 1, pp. L11-L15.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379L..11S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASP..119..616K</bibcode>
			<title>A Ground-based Search for Thermal Emission from the Exoplanet TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Richardson, L. Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 119, Issue 856, pp. 616-622.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASP..119..616K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.378..148D</bibcode>
			<title>3.8-mum photometry during the secondary eclipse of the extrasolar planet HD209458b</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Richardson, L. Jeremy; Harrington, Joseph</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 378, Issue 1, pp. 148-152.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.378..148D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...661..502B</bibcode>
			<title>Possible Solutions to the Radius Anomalies of Transiting Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Hubbard, W. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 661, Issue 1, pp. 502-514.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...661..502B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..850D</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude Photometry for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Candidates. II. Transits of OGLE-TR-113-b in the Optical and Near-IR</title>
			<authors>D&#237;az, Rodrigo F.; Ram&#237;rez, Sebasti&#225;n; Fern&#225;ndez, Jos&#233; Miguel; Gallardo, Jos&#233;; Gieren, Wolfgang; Ivanov, Valentin D.; Mauas, Pablo; Minniti, Dante; Pietrzynski, Grzegorz; P&#233;rez, Felipe; Ru&#237;z, Mar&#237;a Teresa; Udalski, Andrzej; Zoccali, Manuela</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 850-857.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..850D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..823M</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of Earth-like Planets During and After Giant Planet Migration</title>
			<authors>Mandell, Avi M.; Raymond, Sean N.; Sigurdsson, Steinn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 823-844.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..823M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...466..743G</bibcode>
			<title>The transiting planet OGLE-TR-132b revisited with new spectroscopy and deconvolution photometry,</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Pont, F.; Moutou, C.; Santos, N. C.; Bouchy, F.; Hartman, J. D.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Magain, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 466, Issue 2, May I 2007, pp.743-748</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...466..743G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...465.1069P</bibcode>
			<title>The "666" collaboration on OGLE transits. I. Accurate radius of the planets OGLE-TR-10b and OGLE-TR-56b with VLT deconvolution photometry</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Moutou, C.; Gillon, M.; Udalski, A.; Bouchy, F.; Fernandes, J. M.; Gieren, W.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Minniti, D.; Melo, C.; Naef, D.; Pietrzynski, G.; Queloz, D.; Ruiz, M. T.; Santos, N. C.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 465, Issue 3, April III 2007, pp.1069-1074</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...465.1069P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...464.1133C</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting companions to extrasolar planets using mutual events</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Schneider, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 464, Issue 3, March IV 2007, pp.1133-1138</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...464.1133C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.375..307S</bibcode>
			<title>K-band transit and secondary eclipse photometry of exoplanet OGLE-TR-113b</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.; Covino, E.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 375, Issue 1, pp. 307-312.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.375..307S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460..251M</bibcode>
			<title>On the age of stars harboring transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Melo, C.; Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 1, December II 2006, pp.251-256</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460..251M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...459..249G</bibcode>
			<title>High accuracy transit photometry of the planet OGLE-TR-113b with a new deconvolution-based method</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Pont, F.; Moutou, C.; Bouchy, F.; Courbin, F.; Sohy, S.; Magain, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 459, Issue 1, November III 2006, pp.249-255</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...459..249G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...458..997S</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical abundances for the transiting planet host stars OGLE-TR-10, 56, 111, 113, 132, and TrES-1. Abundances in different galactic populations</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Ecuvillon, A.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Ribeiro, J. P.; Jorge, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 458, Issue 3, November II 2006, pp.997-1005</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...458..997S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650..394A</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Structure and Radius Evolution of Irradiated Gas Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Arras, Phil; Bildsten, Lars</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 1, pp. 394-407.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650..394A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1010J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of Known Exoplanetary Systems Based on Measured Stellar Properties</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick; Underwood, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1019.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1010J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...647..587F</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude Optical Photometry for the Transiting Planetary Candidate OGLE-TR-109</title>
			<authors>Fern&#225;ndez, Jos&#233; Miguel; Minniti, Dante; Pietrzynski, Grzegorz; Gieren, Wolfgang; Ru&#237;z, Mar&#237;a Teresa; Zoccali, Manuela; Udalski, Andrzej; Szeifert, Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 647, Issue 1, pp. 587-593.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...647..587F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...453L..21G</bibcode>
			<title>A correlation between the heavy element content of transiting extrasolar planets and the metallicity of their parent stars</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Iro, N.; Melo, C.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 453, Issue 2, July II 2006, pp.L21-L24</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...453L..21G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006RMxAC..26..156R</bibcode>
			<title>Milli-magnitude IR Transit Detection: OGLE-TR-113</title>
			<authors>Ram&#237;rez-Alegr&#237;a, S.; Minniti, D.; Fern&#225;ndez, J. M.; Ruiz, M. T.; Gieren, W.; Pietrzynski, G.; Zoccali, M.; Ivanov, V.</authors>
			<journal>XI IAU Regional Latin American Meeting of Astronomy (Eds. L. Infante &amp; M. Rubio) Revista Mexicana de Astronom&#237;a y Astrof&#237;sica (Serie de Conferencias) Vol. 26, pp. 156</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006RMxAC..26..156R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...642..488S</bibcode>
			<title>Search for Planetary Candidates within the OGLE Stars</title>
			<authors>Silva, Adriana V. R.; Cruz, Patricia C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 642, Issue 1, pp. 488-494.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...642..488S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...450..825S</bibcode>
			<title>High resolution spectroscopy of stars with transiting planets. The cases of OGLE-TR-10, 56, 111, 113, and TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Melo, C.; Israelian, G.; Bouchy, F.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Guillot, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 450, Issue 2, May I 2006, pp.825-831</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...450..825S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AcA....56....1G</bibcode>
			<title>Frequency of Hot Jupiters and Very Hot Jupiters from the OGLE-III Transit Surveys toward the Galactic Bulge and Carina</title>
			<authors>Gould, A.; Dorsher, S.; Gaudi, B. S.; Udalski, A.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, v.56, pp.1-50, (2006).</journal>
			<date>3/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AcA....56....1G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.364...29P</bibcode>
			<title>A link between the semimajor axis of extrasolar gas giant planets and stellar metallicity</title>
			<authors>Pinotti, R.; Arany-Prado, L.; Lyra, W.; Porto de Mello, G. F.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 364, Issue 1, pp. 29-36.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.364...29P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Sci...310..251S</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Planets: Constraints for Planet Formation Models</title>
			<authors>Santos, Nuno C.; Benz, Willy; Mayor, Michel</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 310, Issue 5746, pp. 251-255 (2005).</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Sci...310..251S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...438.1123P</bibcode>
			<title>Doppler follow-up of OGLE planetary transit candidates in Carina</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Bouchy, F.; Melo, C.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 438, Issue 3, August II 2005, pp.1123-1140</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...438.1123P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...627.1011T</bibcode>
			<title>A Photometric Diagnostic to Aid in the Identification of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Tingley, Brandon; Sackett, Penny D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 627, Issue 2, pp. 1011-1018.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...627.1011T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Msngr.120...19P</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting Extra-solar Planets, follow the FLAMES ...</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frederic; Bouchy, Francois; Queloz, Didier; Melo, Claudio; Santos, Nuno; Udry, Stephane; Mayor, Michel; Moutou, Claire</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger (ISSN0722-6691), No.120, p. 19-21 (June 2005)</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Msngr.120...19P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...625.1004M</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Hot Massive Extrasolar Planets around Nearby Young Stars with the Adaptive Optics System NACO</title>
			<authors>Masciadri, E.; Mundt, R.; Henning, Th.; Alvarez, C.; Barrado y Navascu&#233;s, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 625, Issue 2, pp. 1004-1018.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...625.1004M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...624..463G</bibcode>
			<title>A Map of the Universe</title>
			<authors>Gott, J. Richard, III; Juric, Mario; Schlegel, David; Hoyle, Fiona; Vogeley, Michael; Tegmark, Max; Bahcall, Neta; Brinkmann, Jon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 624, Issue 2, pp. 463-484.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...624..463G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...623L..45L</bibcode>
			<title>A Dynamical Method for Measuring the Masses of Stars with Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Loeb, Abraham</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 623, Issue 1, pp. L45-L48.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...623L..45L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...623..472G</bibcode>
			<title>On the Period Distribution of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. Scott; Seager, S.; Mallen-Ornelas, Gabriela</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 623, Issue 1, pp. 472-481.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...623..472G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622.1118O</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect and Analytic Radial Velocity Curves for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Ohta, Yasuhiro; Taruya, Atsushi; Suto, Yasushi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 2, pp. 1118-1135.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622.1118O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...621.1061M</bibcode>
			<title>The Challenge of Wide-Field Transit Surveys: The Case of GSC 01944-02289</title>
			<authors>Mandushev, Georgi; Torres, Guillermo; Latham, David W.; Charbonneau, David; Alonso, Roi; White, Russel J.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Dunham, Edward W.; Brown, Timothy M.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 621, Issue 2, pp. 1061-1071.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...621.1061M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...431.1105B</bibcode>
			<title>Doppler follow-up of OGLE transiting companions in the Galactic bulge</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Melo, C.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 431, Issue 3, March I 2005, pp.1105-1121</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...431.1105B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.356.1053S</bibcode>
			<title>Magnetospheric radio emission from extrasolar giant planets: the role of the host stars</title>
			<authors>Stevens, Ian R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 356, Issue 3, pp. 1053-1063.</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.356.1053S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.356..955M</bibcode>
			<title>An intriguing correlation between the masses and periods of the transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, Tsevi; Zucker, Shay; Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 356, Issue 3, pp. 955-957.</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.356..955M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...619..558T</bibcode>
			<title>Testing Blend Scenarios for Extrasolar Transiting Planet Candidates. II. OGLE-TR-56</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Konacki, Maciej; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Jha, Saurabh</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 619, Issue 1, pp. 558-569.</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...619..558T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...616.1193B</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Detectability of Ring Systems around Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 616, Issue 2, pp. 1193-1203.</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...616.1193B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AcA....54..313U</bibcode>
			<title>The Optical Gravitational Lensing Experiment. Planetary and Low-Luminosity Object Transits in the Fields of Galactic Disk. Results of the 2003 OGLE Observing Campaigns</title>
			<authors>Udalski, A.; Szymanski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Zebrun, K.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, v.54, pp. 313-345, (2004).</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AcA....54..313U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...427.1075P</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal interactions of close-in extrasolar planets: The OGLE cases</title>
			<authors>P&#228;tzold, M.; Carone, L.; Rauer, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.427, p.1075-1080 (2004)</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...427.1075P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004PASP..116.1072D</bibcode>
			<title>PSST: The Planet Search Survey Telescope</title>
			<authors>Dunham, Edward W.; Mandushev, Georgi I.; Taylor, Brian W.; Oetiker, Brian</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 116, Issue 825, pp. 1072-1080.</journal>
			<date>11/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004PASP..116.1072D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.354.1194S</bibcode>
			<title>On the possible correlation between the orbital periods of extrasolar planets and the metallicity of the host stars</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 354, Issue 4, pp. 1194-1200.</journal>
			<date>11/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.354.1194S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...614L..81M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of a Neptune-Mass Planet in the rho1 Cancri System Using the Hobby-Eberly Telescope</title>
			<authors>McArthur, Barbara E.; Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Benedict, G. Fritz; Fischer, Debra A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Naef, Dominique; Mayor, Michel; Queloz, Diedre; Udry, Stephane; Harrison, Thomas E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 614, Issue 1, pp. L81-L84.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...614L..81M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...614..979T</bibcode>
			<title>Testing Blend Scenarios for Extrasolar Transiting Planet Candidates. I. OGLE-TR-33: A False Positive</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Konacki, Maciej; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Jha, Saurabh</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 614, Issue 2, pp. 979-989.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...614..979T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...613L.153A</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-1: The Transiting Planet of a Bright K0 V Star</title>
			<authors>Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Torres, Guillermo; Latham, David W.; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Mandushev, Georgi; Belmonte, Juan A.; Charbonneau, David; Deeg, Hans J.; Dunham, Edward W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Stefanik, Robert P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 613, Issue 2, pp. L153-L156.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...613L.153A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...426L..15P</bibcode>
			<title>The ``missing link'': A 4-day period  transiting exoplanet around OGLE-TR-111</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Bouchy, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Melo, C.; Mayor, M.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.426, p.L15-L18 (2004)</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...426L..15P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...424..727P</bibcode>
			<title>SB9: The ninth catalogue of spectroscopic binary orbits</title>
			<authors>Pourbaix, D.; Tokovinin, A. A.; Batten, A. H.; Fekel, F. C.; Hartkopf, W. I.; Levato, H.; Morrell, N. I.; Torres, G.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.424, p.727-732 (2004)</journal>
			<date>9/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...424..727P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...610L..53B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Radii of Transiting Giant Planets: The Case of OGLE-TR-56b</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Hubbard, W. B.; Sudarsky, D.; Fortney, J. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 610, Issue 1, pp. L53-L56.</journal>
			<date>7/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...610L..53B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...609L..37K</bibcode>
			<title>The Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planet around the Star OGLE-TR-113</title>
			<authors>Konacki, Maciej; Torres, Guillermo; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Pietrzyn ski, Grzegorz; Udalski, Andrzej; Jha, Saurabh; Ruiz, Maria Teresa; Gieren, Wolfgang; Minniti, Dante</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 609, Issue 1, pp. L37-L40.</journal>
			<date>7/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...609L..37K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004A&amp;A...421L..13B</bibcode>
			<title>Two new ``very hot Jupiters'' among the OGLE transiting candidates</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Santos, N. C.; Melo, C.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.421, p.L13-L16 (2004)</journal>
			<date>7/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004A%26A...421L..13B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004Msngr.116...32M</bibcode>
			<title>Two New Very Hot Jupiters in the FLAMES spotlight</title>
			<authors>Melo, C.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger (ISSN0722-6691), No.116, p. 32-34 (June 2004)</journal>
			<date>6/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004Msngr.116...32M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...592.1217S</bibcode>
			<title>Ellipsoidal Variability in the OGLE Planetary Transit Candidates</title>
			<authors>Sirko, E.; Paczynski, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 592, Issue 2, pp. 1217-1224.</journal>
			<date>8/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...592.1217S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002AcA....52..317U</bibcode>
			<title>The Optical Gravitational Lensing Experiment. Planetary and Low-Luminosity Object Transits in the Carina Fields of the Galactic Disk</title>
			<authors>Udalski, A.; Szewczyk, O.; Zebrun, K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Szymanski, M.; Kubiak, M.; Soszynski, I.; Wyrzykowski, L.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, Vol. 52, p. 317-359</journal>
			<date>12/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002AcA....52..317U</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
