<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.413.1244H</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE-2009-BLG-023/MOA-2009-BLG-028: characterization of a binary microlensing event based on survey data</title>
			<authors>Hwang, K.-H.; Han, C.; Udalski, A.; Sumi, T.; Gould, A.; OGLE Collaboration; Jaroszynski, M.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; MOA Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Botzler, C. S.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 413, Issue 2, pp. 1244-1250.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.413.1244H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...93W</bibcode>
			<title>The California Planet Survey. III. A Possible 2:1 Resonance in the Exoplanetary Triple System HD 37124</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Isaacson, H.; Fischer, D. A.; Spronck, J.; Anderson, J.; Valenti, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. 93 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...93W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.412..607P</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of orbital motion in stellar binary and planetary microlenses</title>
			<authors>Penny, Matthew T.; Mao, Shude; Kerins, Eamonn</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 412, Issue 1, pp. 607-626.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.412..607P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411....2D</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary mass function and planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Dominik, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. 2-8.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411....2D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727..108W</bibcode>
			<title>Forming Habitable Planets Around Dwarf Stars: Application to OGLE-06-109L</title>
			<authors>Wang, Su; Zhou, Ji-Lin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 108 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727..108W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727L...5J</bibcode>
			<title>Forming Close-in Earth-like Planets Via a Collision-merger Mechanism in Late-stage Planet Formation</title>
			<authors>Ji, Jianghui; Jin, Sheng; Tinney, C. G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. L5 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727L...5J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1073G</bibcode>
			<title>Frequency of Solar-like Systems and of Ice and Gas Giants Beyond the Snow Line from High-magnification Microlensing Events in 2005-2008</title>
			<authors>