<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.413.1244H</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE-2009-BLG-023/MOA-2009-BLG-028: characterization of a binary microlensing event based on survey data</title>
			<authors>Hwang, K.-H.; Han, C.; Udalski, A.; Sumi, T.; Gould, A.; OGLE Collaboration; Jaroszynski, M.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; MOA Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Botzler, C. S.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 413, Issue 2, pp. 1244-1250.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.413.1244H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730...93W</bibcode>
			<title>The California Planet Survey. III. A Possible 2:1 Resonance in the Exoplanetary Triple System HD 37124</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Isaacson, H.; Fischer, D. A.; Spronck, J.; Anderson, J.; Valenti, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 730, Issue 2, article id. 93 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730...93W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.412..607P</bibcode>
			<title>Detectability of orbital motion in stellar binary and planetary microlenses</title>
			<authors>Penny, Matthew T.; Mao, Shude; Kerins, Eamonn</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 412, Issue 1, pp. 607-626.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.412..607P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411....2D</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary mass function and planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Dominik, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. 2-8.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411....2D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727..108W</bibcode>
			<title>Forming Habitable Planets Around Dwarf Stars: Application to OGLE-06-109L</title>
			<authors>Wang, Su; Zhou, Ji-Lin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 108 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727..108W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727L...5J</bibcode>
			<title>Forming Close-in Earth-like Planets Via a Collision-merger Mechanism in Late-stage Planet Formation</title>
			<authors>Ji, Jianghui; Jin, Sheng; Tinney, C. G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. L5 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727L...5J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1073G</bibcode>
			<title>Frequency of Solar-like Systems and of Ice and Gas Giants Beyond the Snow Line from High-magnification Microlensing Events in 2005-2008</title>
			<authors>Gould, A.; Dong, Subo; Gaudi, B. S.; Udalski, A.; Bond, I. A.; Greenhill, J.; Street, R. A.; Dominik, M.; Sumi, T.; Szymanski, M. K.; Han, C.; Allen, W.; Bolt, G.; Bos, M.; Christie, G. W.; DePoy, D. L.; Drummond, J.; Eastman, J. D.; Gal-Yam, A.; Higgins, D.; Janczak, J.; Kaspi, S.; Kozlowski, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Maury, A.; Maoz, D.; McCormick, J.; Monard, L. A. G.; Moorhouse, D.; Morgan, N.; Natusch, T.; Ofek, E. O.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Santallo, R.; Shporer, A.; Spector, O.; Thornley, G.; Yee, J. C.; mu FUN Collaboration; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; Poleski, R.; OGLE Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Botzler, C. S.; Douchin, D.; Freeman, M.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Philpott, L.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; von Seggern, E.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Albrow, M.; Batista, V.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Brillant, S.; Caldwell, J.; Calitz, J. J.; Cassan, A.; Cole, A.; Cook, K.; Coutures, C.; Dieters, S.; Dominis Prester, D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu, P.; Hill, K.; Hoffman, M.; Jablonski, F.; Kane, S. R.; Kains, N.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J.-B.; Martin, R.; Martioli, E.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pedretti, E.; Pollard, K.; Sahu, K. C.; Vinter, C.; Wambsganss, J.; Watson, R.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; PLANET Collaboration; Allan, A.; Bode, M. F.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Clay, N.; Fraser, S.; Hawkins, E.; Horne, K.; Kerins, E.; Lister, T. A.; Mottram, C.; Saunders, E. S.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I. A.; Tsapras, Y.; RoboNet Collaboration; Jrgensen, U. G.; Anguita, T.; Bozza, V.; Calchi Novati, S.; Harpse, K.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Kjrgaard, P.; Liebig, C.; Mancini, L.; Masi, G.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Southworth, J.; Surdej, J.; Thne, C. C.; MiNDSTEp Consortium</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1073-1089 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1073G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AcA....60..197J</bibcode>
			<title>Binary Lenses in OGLE-III EWS Database. Seasons 2006-2008</title>
			<authors>Jaroszyski, M.; Skowron, J.; Udalski, A.; Kubiak, M.; Szymaski, M. K.; Pietrzyski, G.; Soszyski, I.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; Poleski, R.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, vol 60, no 3, p. 197-231</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AcA....60..197J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717..435H</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the Physical Lens Parameters of the Binary Gravitational Microlensing Event MOA-2009-BLG-016</title>
			<authors>Hwang, K.-H.; Han, C.; Bond, I. A.; Miyake, N.; Abe, F.; Bennett, D. P.; Botzler, C. S.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hayashi, F.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Hosaka, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Makita, S.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Muraki, Y.; Nishimoto, K.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, To.; Sako, T.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Suzuki, D.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Wada, K.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Depoy, D. L.; Gaudi, B. S.; Gould, A.; Lee, C.-U.; Pogge, R. W.; mu FUN Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 1, pp. 435-440 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717..435H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1408B</bibcode>
			<title>An Efficient Method for Modeling High-magnification Planetary Microlensing Events</title>
			<authors>Bennett, David P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1408-1422 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1408B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..837B</bibcode>
			<title>Masses and Orbital Constraints for the OGLE-2006-BLG-109Lb,c Jupiter/Saturn Analog Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Bennett, D. P.; Rhie, S. H.; Nikolaev, S.; Gaudi, B. S.; Udalski, A.; Gould, A.; Christie, G. W.; Maoz, D.; Dong, S.; McCormick, J.; Szymanski, M. K.; Tristram, P. J.; Macintosh, B.; Cook, K. H.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; OGLE Collaboration; DePoy, D. L.; Han, C.; Kaspi, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Natusch, T.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; muFUN Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bond, I. A.; Botzler, C. S.; Fukui, A.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Korpela, A. V.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Lin, W.; Ling, J.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Motomura, M.; Muraki, Y.; Nakamura, S.; Okumura, T.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Saito, To.; Sato, S.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Sweatman, W. L.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Albrow, M.; Allan, A.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Coutures, C.; Dominik, M.; Dieters, S.; Fouqu, P.; Greenhill, J.; Horne, K.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Tsapras, Y.; PLANET, From the; RoboNet Collaborations; Chaboyer, B.; Crocker, A.; Frank, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 837-855 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..837B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508..467B</bibcode>
			<title>Mass measurement of a single unseen star and planetary detection efficiency for OGLE 2007-BLG-050</title>
			<authors>Batista, V.; Dong, S.; Gould, A.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Cassan, A.; Christie, G. W.; Han, C.; Udalski, A.; Allen, W.; Depoy, D. L.; Gal-Yam, A.; Gaudi, B. S.; Johnson, B.; Kaspi, S.; Lee, C. U.; Maoz, D.; McCormick, J.; McGreer, I.; Monard, B.; Natusch, T.; Ofek, E.; Park, B.-G.; Pogge, R. W.; Polishook, D.; Shporer, A.; mu FUN Collaboration; Albrow, M. D.; Bennett, D. P.; Brillant, S.; Bode, M.; Bramich, D. M.; Burgdorf, M.; Caldwell, J. A. R.; Calitz, H.; Cole, A.; Cook, K. H.; Coutures, Ch.; Dieters, S.; Dominik, M.; Prester, D. D.; Donatowicz, J.; Fouqu, P.; Greenhill, J.; Hoffman, M.; Horne, K.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Kains, N.; Kane, S.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J. B.; Martin, R.; Meintjes, P.; Menzies, J.; Pollard, K. R.; Sahu, K. C.; Snodgrass, C.; Steele, I.; Tsapras, Y.; Wambsganss, J.; Williams, A.; Zub, M.; PLANET/Robonet Collaboration; Wyrzykowski, L.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Ogle Collaboration; Abe, F.; Bond, I. A.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Holderness, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Korpela, A.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Ohnishi, K.; Okumura, T.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N.; Saito, T.; Sako, T.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D.; Sumi, T.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 1, 2009, pp.467-478</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508..467B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..772W</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamics and Eccentricity Formation of Planets in OGLE-06-109L System</title>
			<authors>Wang, Su; Zhao, Gang; Zhou, Ji-Lin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 772-784 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..772W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AcA....59..255N</bibcode>
			<title>Finding the Brightest Galactic Bulge Microlensing Events with a Small Aperture Telescope and Image Subtraction</title>
			<authors>Nataf, D. M.; Stanek, K. Z.; Bakos, G. A.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, vol 59, no 3, p. 255-272</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AcA....59..255N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.2087H</bibcode>
			<title>A metric and optimization scheme for microlens planet searches</title>
			<authors>Horne, Keith; Snodgrass, Colin; Tsapras, Yianni</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 4, pp. 2087-2102.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.2087H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.395.1204M</bibcode>
			<title>On the habitability of the OGLE-2006-BLG-109L planetary system</title>
			<authors>Migaszewski, Cezary; Gozdziewski, Krzysztof; Hinse, Tobias C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 395, Issue 3, pp. 1204-1212.</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.395.1204M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693.1084W</bibcode>
			<title>Ten New and Updated Multiplanet Systems and a Survey of Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Wright, J. T.; Upadhyay, S.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Ford, Eric B.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 2, pp. 1084-1099 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693.1084W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690.1772P</bibcode>
			<title>Extended-Source Effect and Chromaticity in Two-Point-Mass Microlensing</title>
			<authors>Pejcha, Ondrej; Heyrovsk, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 2, pp. 1772-1796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690.1772P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AN....330....4T</bibcode>
			<title>RoboNet-II: Follow-up observations of microlensing events with a robotic network of telescopes</title>
			<authors>Tsapras, Y.; Street, R.; Horne, K.; Snodgrass, C.; Dominik, M.; Allan, A.; Steele, I.; Bramich, D. M.; Saunders, E. S.; Rattenbury, N.; Mottram, C.; Fraser, S.; Clay, N.; Burgdorf, M.; Bode, M.; Lister, T. A.; Hawkins, E.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Fouqu , P.; Albrow, M.; Menzies, J.; Cassan, A.; Dominis-Prester, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.330, Issue 1, p.4</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AN....330....4T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684..663B</bibcode>
			<title>A Low-Mass Planet with a Possible Sub-Stellar-Mass Host in Microlensing Event MOA-2007-BLG-192</title>
			<authors>Bennett, D. P.; Bond, I. A.; Udalski, A.; Sumi, T.; Abe, F.; Fukui, A.; Furusawa, K.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Holderness, S.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Korpela, A. V.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Lin, W.; Ling, C. H.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Miyake, N.; Muraki, Y.; Nagaya, M.; Okumura, T.; Ohnishi, K.; Perrott, Y. C.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Saito, To.; Sato, S.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sweatman, W. L.; Tristram, P. J.; Yock, P. C. M.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.; Ulaczyk, K.; Batista, V.; Beaulieu, J. P.; Brillant, S.; Cassan, A.; Fouqu, P.; Kervella, P.; Kubas, D.; Marquette, J. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 1, pp. 663-683.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684..663B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...683L..67M</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for the Habitability of OGLE-2006-BLG-109L</title>
			<authors>Malhotra, Renu; Minton, David A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 683, Issue 1, pp. L67-L70.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...683L..67M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008Sci...319..927G</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Jupiter/Saturn Analog with Gravitational Microlensing</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. S.; Bennett, D. P.; Udalski, A.; Gould, A.; Christie, G. W.; Maoz, D.; Dong, S.; McCormick, J.; Szymanski, M. K.; Tristram, P. J.; Nikolaev, S.; Paczynski, B.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.; OGLE Collaboration; DePoy, D. L.; Han, C.; Kaspi, S.; Lee, C.-U.; Mallia, F.; Natusch, T.; Pogge, R. W.; Park, B.-G.; mu-Fun Collabortion; Abe, F.; Bond, I. A.; Botzler, C. S.; Fukui, A.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Itow, Y.; Kamiya, K.; Korpela, A. V.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Lin, W.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Motomura, M.; Muraki, Y.; Nakamura, S.; Okumura, T.; Ohnishi, K.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Saito, To.; Sato, S.; Skuljan, L.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Sweatman, W. L.; Yock, P. C. M.; MOA Collaboration; Albrow, M. D.; Allan, A.; Beaulieu, J.-P.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Cook, K. H.; Coutures, C.; Dominik, M.; Dieters, S.; Fouqu, P.; Greenhill, J.; Horne, K.; Steele, I.; Tsapras, Y.; Planet Collaboration; Robonet Collaborations; Chaboyer, B.; Crocker, A.; Frank, S.; Macintosh, B.</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 319, Issue 5865, pp. 927- (2008).</journal>
			<date>0/2008 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008Sci...319..927G</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
