<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...543A.138B</bibcode>
			<title>The quest for companions to post-common envelope binaries. III. A reexamination of HW Virginis</title>
			<authors>Beuermann, K.; Dreizler, S.; Hessman, F. V.; Deller, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 543, id.A138</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...543A.138B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422L..24Q</bibcode>
			<title>A circumbinary planet in orbit around the short-period white dwarf eclipsing binary RR Cae</title>
			<authors>Qian, S.-B.; Liu, L.; Zhu, L.-Y.; Dai, Z.-B.; Fernndez Lajs, E.; Baume, G. L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 422, Issue 1, pp. 24-27.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422L..24Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJS..199...29G</bibcode>
			<title>Know Your Neighborhood: A Detailed Model Atmosphere Analysis of Nearby White Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Giammichele, N.; Bergeron, P.; Dufour, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 199, Issue 2, article id. 29 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJS..199...29G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...68H</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Constraints on the Degenerate Mass-Radius Relation</title>
			<authors>Holberg, J. B.; Oswalt, T. D.; Barstow, M. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 3, article id. 68 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143...68H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.419..817P</bibcode>
			<title>Post-common envelope binaries from SDSS - XV. Accurate stellar parameters for a cool 0.4 M&amp;sun; white dwarf and a 0.16 M&amp;sun; M dwarf in a 3 h eclipsing binary</title>
			<authors>Pyrzas, S.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Brady, S.; Parsons, S. G.; Marsh, T. R.; Koester, D.; Breedt, E.; Copperwheat, C. M.; Nebot Gmez-Morn, A.; Rebassa-Mansergas, A.; Schreiber, M. R.; Zorotovic, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 419, Issue 1, pp. 817-826.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.419..817P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...536A..43N</bibcode>
			<title>Post common envelope binaries from SDSS. XII. The orbital period distribution</title>
			<authors>Nebot Gmez-Morn, A.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Schreiber, M. R.; Rebassa-Mansergas, A.; Schwope, A. D.; Southworth, J.; Aungwerojwit, A.; Bothe, M.; Davis, P. J.; Kolb, U.; Mller, M.; Papadaki, C.; Pyrzas, S.; Rabitz, A.; Rodrguez-Gil, P.; Schmidtobreick, L.; Schwarz, R.; Tappert, C.; Toloza, O.; Vogel, J.; Zorotovic, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 536, id.A43</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...536A..43N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...536A..42Z</bibcode>
			<title>Post common envelope binaries from SDSS. XI. The white dwarf mass distributions of CVs and pre-CVs</title>
			<authors>Zorotovic, M.; Schreiber, M. R.; Gnsicke, B. T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 536, id.A42</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...536A..42Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...739..101Z</bibcode>
			<title>An Aluminum/Calcium-rich, Iron-poor, White Dwarf Star: Evidence for an Extrasolar Planetary Lithosphere?</title>
			<authors>Zuckerman, B.; Koester, D.; Dufour, P.; Melis, Carl; Klein, B.; Jura, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 739, Issue 2, article id. 101 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...739..101Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A.129T</bibcode>
			<title>Accretion in the detached post-common-envelope binary LTT 560</title>
			<authors>Tappert, C.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Schmidtobreick, L.; Ribeiro, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A129</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A.129T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A.113T</bibcode>
			<title>Multiple emission line components in detached post-common-envelope binaries</title>
			<authors>Tappert, C.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Rebassa-Mansergas, A.; Schmidtobreick, L.; Schreiber, M. R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A113</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A.113T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..194...28K</bibcode>
			<title>The Evolution of Cataclysmic Variables as Revealed by Their Donor Stars</title>
			<authors>Knigge, Christian; Baraffe, Isabelle; Patterson, Joseph</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 194, Issue 2, article id. 28 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..194...28K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..166H</bibcode>
			<title>A Photometric Variability Survey of Field K and M Dwarf Stars with HATNet</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Noyes, R. W.; Sipocz, B.; Kovcs, G.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.; Pl, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 5, article id. 166 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..166H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.2277D</bibcode>
			<title>On the alpha formalism for the common envelope interaction</title>
			<authors>De Marco, Orsola; Passy, Jean-Claude; Moe, Maxwell; Herwig, Falk; Mac Low, Mordecai-Mark; Paxton, Bill</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 4, pp. 2277-2292.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.2277D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728...16H</bibcode>
			<title>Infrared Spectroscopic Observations of the Secondary Stars of Short-period Sub-gap Cataclysmic Variables</title>
			<authors>Hamilton, Ryan T.; Harrison, Thomas E.; Tappert, Claus; Howell, Steve B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 1, article id. 16 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728...16H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...525A..85E</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. I. Detection of the low-mass white dwarf KOI 74b</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Bouchy, F.; Perrier, C.; Hbrard, G.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; Arnold, L.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Daz, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lovis, C.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Santos, N. C.; Santerne, A.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 525, id.A85</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...525A..85E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.1433B</bibcode>
			<title>Hard X-ray Emission Associated with White Dwarfs. III.</title>
			<authors>Bilkov, Jana; Chu, You-Hua; Gruendl, Robert A.; Maddox, Larry A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 5, pp. 1433-1443 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.1433B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..86Z</bibcode>
			<title>Post-common-envelope binaries from SDSS. IX: Constraining the common-envelope efficiency</title>
			<authors>Zorotovic, M.; Schreiber, M. R.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Nebot Gmez-Morn, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A86</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..86Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403..179D</bibcode>
			<title>A comprehensive population synthesis study of post-common envelope binaries</title>
			<authors>Davis, P. J.; Kolb, U.; Willems, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 1, pp. 179-195.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403..179D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705..693S</bibcode>
			<title>Helium Core White Dwarfs in Cataclysmic Variables</title>
			<authors>Shen, Ken J.; Idan, Irit; Bildsten, Lars</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 705, Issue 1, pp. 693-703 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705..693S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AJ....137.4547S</bibcode>
			<title>The Solar Neighborhood. XXI. Parallax Results from the CTIOPI 0.9 m Program: 20 New Members of the 25 Parsec White Dwarf Sample</title>
			<authors>Subasavage, John P.; Jao, Wei-Chun; Henry, Todd J.; Bergeron, P.; Dufour, P.; Ianna, Philip A.; Costa, Edgardo; Mndez, Ren A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 137, Issue 6, pp. 4547-4560 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AJ....137.4547S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..978P</bibcode>
			<title>Post-common-envelope binaries from SDSS - V. Four eclipsing white dwarf main-sequence binaries</title>
			<authors>Pyrzas, S.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Marsh, T. R.; Aungwerojwit, A.; Rebassa-Mansergas, A.; Rodrguez-Gil, P.; Southworth, J.; Schreiber, M. R.; Nebot Gomez-Moran, A.; Koester, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 2, pp. 978-994.</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..978P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.391..802A</bibcode>
			<title>Two-colour photometry of the binary planetary nebula nuclei UU Sagitte and V477 Lyrae: oversized secondaries in post-common-envelope binaries</title>
			<authors>Afsar, M.; Ibanoglu, C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 391, Issue 2, pp. 802-814.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.391..802A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1253D</bibcode>
			<title>T-Lyr1-17236: A Long-Period Low-Mass Eclipsing Binary</title>
			<authors>Devor, Jonathan; Charbonneau, David; Torres, Guillermo; Blake, Cullen H.; White, Russel J.; Rabus, Markus; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi; Bakos, Gaspar .; Fursz, Gbor; Szentgyorgyi, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1253-1263.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1253D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389.1563D</bibcode>
			<title>How many cataclysmic variables are crossing the period gap? A test for the disruption of magnetic braking</title>
			<authors>Davis, P. J.; Kolb, U.; Willems, B.; Gnsicke, B. T.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 4, pp. 1563-1576.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389.1563D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AJ....135.1225H</bibcode>
			<title>A New Look at the Local White Dwarf Population</title>
			<authors>Holberg, J. B.; Sion, E. M.; Oswalt, T.; McCook, G. P.; Foran, S.; Subasavage, John P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 135, Issue 4, pp. 1225-1238 (2008).</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AJ....135.1225H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.382.1377R</bibcode>
			<title>Post-common-envelope binaries from SDSS - I. 101 white dwarf main-sequence binaries with multiple Sloan Digital Sky Survey spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Rebassa-Mansergas, A.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Rodrguez-Gil, P.; Schreiber, M. R.; Koester, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 382, Issue 4, pp. 1377-1393.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.382.1377R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..575T</bibcode>
			<title>K-band spectroscopy of pre-cataclysmic variables</title>
			<authors>Tappert, C.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Schmidtobreick, L.; Mennickent, R. E.; Navarrete, F. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 2, November IV 2007, pp.575-583</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..575T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...474..205T</bibcode>
			<title>The pre-cataclysmic variable, LTT 560</title>
			<authors>Tappert, C.; Gnsicke, B. T.; Schmidtobreick, L.; Aungwerojwit, A.; Mennickent, R. E.; Koester, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 474, Issue 1, October IV 2007, pp.205-211</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...474..205T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AJ....134...26H</bibcode>
			<title>Cool Companions to White Dwarf Stars from the Two Micron All Sky Survey All Sky Data Release</title>
			<authors>Hoard, D. W.; Wachter, S.; Sturch, Laura K.; Widhalm, Allison M.; Weiler, Kevin P.; Pretorius, Magaretha L.; Wellhouse, Joseph W.; Gibiansky, Maxsim</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 134, Issue 1, pp. 26-42.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AJ....134...26H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...466.1031V</bibcode>
			<title>DE Canum Venaticorum: a bright, eclipsing red dwarf-white dwarf binary</title>
			<authors>van den Besselaar, E. J. M.; Greimel, R.; Morales-Rueda, L.; Nelemans, G.; Thorstensen, J. R.; Marsh, T. R.; Dhillon, V. S.; Robb, R. M.; Balam, D. D.; Guenther, E. W.; Kemp, J.; Augusteijn, T.; Groot, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 466, Issue 3, May II 2007, pp.1031-1041</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...466.1031V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.376..919M</bibcode>
			<title>The mass and radius of the M-dwarf in the short-period eclipsing binary RR Caeli</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; O'Donoghue, D.; Morales-Rueda, L.; Napiwotzki, R.; Smalley, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 376, Issue 2, pp. 919-928.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.376..919M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...654..499K</bibcode>
			<title>Spectropolarimetric Survey of Hydrogen-rich White Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Kawka, A.; Vennes, S.; Schmidt, G. D.; Wickramasinghe, D. T.; Koch, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 654, Issue 1, pp. 499-520.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...654..499K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652..636D</bibcode>
			<title>Measuring M Dwarf Winds with DAZ White Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Debes, John H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 1, pp. 636-642.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652..636D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...456.1069S</bibcode>
			<title>The new pre-cataclysmic binary PG 2200+085</title>
			<authors>Shimansky, V.; Sakhibullin, N. A.; Bikmaev, I.; Ritter, H.; Suleimanov, V.; Borisov, N.; Galeev, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 456, Issue 3, September IV 2006, pp.1069-1075</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...456.1069S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...446..785M</bibcode>
			<title>A catalogue of eclipsing variables</title>
			<authors>Malkov, O. Yu.; Oblak, E.; Snegireva, E. A.; Torra, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 446, Issue 2, February I 2006, pp.785-789</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...446..785M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006BSAO...59...34V</bibcode>
			<title>Precatalysmic binary systems.</title>
			<authors>Voichanskaya, N. F.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the Special Astrophysical Observatory, 59, 34-51 (2006)</journal>
			<date>0/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006BSAO...59...34V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005PASP..117..676R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the LHS Catalog. II. Faint Proper-Motion Stars</title>
			<authors>Reid, I. Neill; Gizis, John E.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 117, Issue 833, pp. 676-698.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005PASP..117..676R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.359..648M</bibcode>
			<title>Six detached white-dwarf close binaries</title>
			<authors>Morales-Rueda, L.; Marsh, T. R.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Nelemans, G.; Karl, C.; Napiwotzki, R.; Moran, C. K. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 359, Issue 2, pp. 648-662.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.359..648M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.356..753N</bibcode>
			<title>Reconstructing the evolution of white dwarf binaries: further evidence for an alternative algorithm for the outcome of the common-envelope phase in close binaries</title>
			<authors>Nelemans, G.; Tout, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 356, Issue 2, pp. 753-764.</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.356..753N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004MNRAS.354..727S</bibcode>
			<title>A population model of the solar neighbourhood thin disc white dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Schrder, K.-P.; Pauli, E.-M.; Napiwotzki, R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 354, Issue 3, pp. 727-736.</journal>
			<date>11/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004MNRAS.354..727S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AJ....127..477C</bibcode>
			<title>Hard X-Ray Emission Associated with White Dwarfs. II.</title>
			<authors>Chu, You-Hua; Guerrero, Martn A.; Gruendl, Robert A.; Webbink, Ronald F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 127, Issue 1, pp. 477-480.</journal>
			<date>1/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AJ....127..477C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003ApJ...596..477Z</bibcode>
			<title>Metal Lines in DA White Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Zuckerman, B.; Koester, D.; Reid, I. N.; Hnsch, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 596, Issue 1, pp. 477-495.</journal>
			<date>10/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003ApJ...596..477Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2003A&amp;A...406..305S</bibcode>
			<title>The age, life expectancy, and space density   of Post Common Envelope Binaries</title>
			<authors>Schreiber, M. R.; Gnsicke, B. T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.406, p.305-321 (2003)</journal>
			<date>7/2003</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2003A%26A...406..305S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJS..141..187B</bibcode>
			<title>Revised Coordinates and Proper Motions of the Stars in the Luyten Half-Second Catalog</title>
			<authors>Bakos, Gspr .; Sahu, Kailash C.; Nmeth, Pter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 141, Issue 1, pp. 187-193.</journal>
			<date>7/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJS..141..187B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ARep...46..406S</bibcode>
			<title>The Spectrum of EG UMa</title>
			<authors>Shimanskii, V. V.; Borisov, N. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Reports, Volume 46, Issue 5, May 2002, pp. 406-416</journal>
			<date>5/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ARep...46..406S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2002ApJ...571..512H</bibcode>
			<title>A Determination of the Local Density of White Dwarf Stars</title>
			<authors>Holberg, J. B.; Oswalt, Terry D.; Sion, E. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 571, Issue 1, pp. 512-518.</journal>
			<date>5/2002</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2002ApJ...571..512H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2001MNRAS.324..547M</bibcode>
			<title>Gravitational lensing in eclipsing binary stars</title>
			<authors>Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 324, Issue 3, pp. 547-552.</journal>
			<date>6/2001</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2001MNRAS.324..547M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000AJ....120.1113H</bibcode>
			<title>Post-Common-Envelope Binary Stars and the Precataclysmic Binary PG 1114+187</title>
			<authors>Hillwig, Todd C.; Honeycutt, R. Kent; Robertson, Jeff W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 120, Issue 2, pp. 1113-1119.</journal>
			<date>8/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000AJ....120.1113H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000PASP..112..434T</bibcode>
			<title>Astrophysics in 1999</title>
			<authors>Trimble, Virginia; Aschwanden, Markus J.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 112, Issue 770, pp. 434-503.</journal>
			<date>4/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000PASP..112..434T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000NewAR..44..119M</bibcode>
			<title>Detached white-dwarf close-binary stars - CV's extended family</title>
			<authors>Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 44, Issue 1-2, p. 119-124.</journal>
			<date>4/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000NewAR..44..119M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2000PASP..112..237B</bibcode>
			<title>V893 Scorpii: The Brightest Eclipsing Cataclysmic Variable below the Period Gap</title>
			<authors>Bruch, Albert; Steiner, J. E.; Gneiding, C. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 112, Issue 768, pp. 237-250.</journal>
			<date>2/2000</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2000PASP..112..237B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;A...351..573B</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopy and photometry of the pre-cataclysmic binary PG1026+002</title>
			<authors>Bruch, Albert; Diaz, Marcos P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, v.351, p.573-581 (1999)</journal>
			<date>11/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26A...351..573B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999PASP..111.1258T</bibcode>
			<title>Ionization of the Local Interstellar Medium</title>
			<authors>Tat, Hong H.; Terzian, Yervant</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 111, Issue 764, pp. 1258-1268.</journal>
			<date>10/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999PASP..111.1258T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999AJ....117.3031B</bibcode>
			<title>The Precataclysmic Binary RR Caeli Revisited: Spectroscopy and Light-Curve Synthesis</title>
			<authors>Bruch, Albert</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 117, Issue 6, pp. 3031-3040.</journal>
			<date>6/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999AJ....117.3031B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999ApJS..121....1M</bibcode>
			<title>A Catalog of Spectroscopically Identified White Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>McCook, George P.; Sion, Edward M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 121, Issue 1, pp. 1-130.</journal>
			<date>3/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999ApJS..121....1M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1999A&amp;AS..135..319H</bibcode>
			<title>The ROSAT all-sky survey catalogue of the nearby stars</title>
			<authors>Hnsch, M.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Sterzik, M. F.; Voges, W.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.135, p.319-338</journal>
			<date>3/1999</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1999A%26AS..135..319H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998ApJ...505L.143Z</bibcode>
			<title>Metals in Cool DA White Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Zuckerman, B.; Reid, I. Neill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 505, Issue 2, pp. L143-L146.</journal>
			<date>10/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998ApJ...505L.143Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998AJ....116..908B</bibcode>
			<title>The Eclipsing Precataclysmic Binary RR Caeli</title>
			<authors>Bruch, Albert; Diaz, Marcos P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 116, Issue 2, pp. 908-916.</journal>
			<date>8/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998AJ....116..908B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1998A&amp;AS..129...83R</bibcode>
			<title>Catalogue of cataclysmic binaries, low-mass X-ray binaries and related objects (Sixth edition)</title>
			<authors>Ritter, H.; Kolb, U.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics Supplement, v.129, p.83-85</journal>
			<date>4/1998</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1998A%26AS..129...83R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1995ApJ...443..735B</bibcode>
			<title>Temperatures, gravities, and masses for a sample of bright DA white dwarfs and the initial-to-final mass relation</title>
			<authors>Bragaglia, Angela; Renzini, Alvio; Bergeron, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1 (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 443, no. 2, p. 735-752</journal>
			<date>4/1995</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1995ApJ...443..735B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1994MNRAS.267..840H</bibcode>
			<title>ROSAT Extreme Ultraviolet / EUV Luminosity Functions of Nearby Late Type Stars</title>
			<authors>Hodgkin, S. T.; Pye, J. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Vol. 267, NO. 4/APR15, P. 840, 1994</journal>
			<date>4/1994</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1994MNRAS.267..840H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1993A&amp;A...267..397D</bibcode>
			<title>On the formation rate and space density of close white dwarf main sequence star binaries</title>
			<authors>de Kool, M.; Ritter, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 267, no. 2, p. 397-409.</journal>
			<date>1/1993</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1993A%26A...267..397D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1990ApJ...365L..13B</bibcode>
			<title>Double Degenerates among DA white dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Bragaglia, Angela; Greggio, Laura; Renzini, Alvio; D'Odorico, Sandro</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 2 - Letters (ISSN 0004-637X), vol. 365, Dec. 10, 1990, p. L13-L17. Research supported by the Ministero dell'Universita e della Ricerca Scientifica e Tecnologica.</journal>
			<date>12/1990</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1990ApJ...365L..13B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1989IBVS.3323....1K</bibcode>
			<title>The 69th Name-List of Variable Stars</title>
			<authors>Kholopov, P. N.; Samus, N. N.; Kazarovets, B. V.; Frolov, M. S.; Kireeva, N. N.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 3323, 1.</journal>
			<date>4/1989</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1989IBVS.3323....1K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988AJ.....96..251S</bibcode>
			<title>Kinematical tests of white dwarf formation channels and evolution</title>
			<authors>Sion, Edward M.; Fritz, Matthew L.; McMullin, Joseph P.; Lallo, Matthew D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 96, July 1988, p. 251-274.</journal>
			<date>7/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988AJ.....96..251S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1988Msngr..52...35B</bibcode>
			<title>Searching for double degenerates.</title>
			<authors>Bragaglia, A.; Greggio, L.; Renzini, A.; D'Odorico, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger, vol. 52, p. 35-39</journal>
			<date>6/1988</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1988Msngr..52...35B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987ApJS...65..603M</bibcode>
			<title>A catalog of spectroscopically identified white dwarfs</title>
			<authors>McCook, George P.; Sion, Edward M.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 65, Dec. 1987, p. 603-671.</journal>
			<date>12/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987ApJS...65..603M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1987AJ.....93..379E</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of proper-motion stars. III - Stars brighter than visual magnitude 15.1, south of declination +30 deg, and with annual proper motion between 0.5 and 0.7 arcsec</title>
			<authors>Eggen, Olin J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal (ISSN 0004-6256), vol. 93, Feb. 1987, p. 379-392.</journal>
			<date>2/1987</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1987AJ.....93..379E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1986A&amp;A...169..139R</bibcode>
			<title>Precataclysmic binaries</title>
			<authors>Ritter, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics (ISSN 0004-6361), vol. 169, no. 1-2, Nov. 1986, p. 139-148.</journal>
			<date>11/1986</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1986A%26A...169..139R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1985PASP...97.1029E</bibcode>
			<title>The colors and luminosities of white dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications (ISSN 0004-6280), vol. 97, Nov. 1985, p. 1029-1049.</journal>
			<date>11/1985</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1985PASP...97.1029E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1984IAUC.4014....4K</bibcode>
			<title>Lft 349</title>
			<authors>Krzeminski, W.</authors>
			<journal>IAU Circ., 4014, 4 (1984).  Edited by Marsden, B. G.</journal>
			<date>11/1984</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1984IAUC.4014....4K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983ApJS...53..335P</bibcode>
			<title>An infrared search for very low mass stars - JHK photometry and results for composite systems</title>
			<authors>Probst, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series (ISSN 0067-0049), vol. 53, Oct. 1983, p. 335-349.</journal>
			<date>10/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983ApJS...53..335P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1983Ap&amp;SS..96....1G</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric parameters and mass distribution of DA-white dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Guseinov, O. Kh.; Novruzova, Kh. I.; Rustamov, Iu. S.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysics and Space Science (ISSN 0004-640X), vol. 96, no. 1, Oct. 1983, p. 1-23.</journal>
			<date>10/1983</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1983Ap%26SS..96....1G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1982ApJ...252L..69P</bibcode>
			<title>The luminosity function of very low mass stars</title>
			<authors>Probst, R. G.; Oconnell, R. W.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 2 - Letters to the Editor, vol. 252, Jan. 15, 1982, p. L69-L72.</journal>
			<date>1/1982</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1982ApJ...252L..69P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979AJ.....84.1384W</bibcode>
			<title>Photometry of white dwarfs on the UVBY system</title>
			<authors>Wegner, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Journal, vol. 84, Sept. 1979, p. 1384-1394.  Research supported by the A. J. Cannon Fund, Unidel Foundation, and NSF.</journal>
			<date>9/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979AJ.....84.1384W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1979ApJ...227..232B</bibcode>
			<title>Subdwarfs. II - The missing halo-population K subdwarfs</title>
			<authors>Bessell, M. S.; Wickramasinghe, D. T.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, Part 1, vol. 227, Jan. 1, 1979, p. 232-243.</journal>
			<date>1/1979</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1979ApJ...227..232B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1975MNRAS.171..637W</bibcode>
			<title>A spectroscopic survey of Southern Hemisphere white dwarfs. V - Data for fifteen additional stars and the nature of the W219 group</title>
			<authors>Wegner, G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, vol. 171, June 1975, p. 637-646.</journal>
			<date>6/1975</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1975MNRAS.171..637W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1974PASP...86..742R</bibcode>
			<title>A photometric and spectroscopic survey of large proper-motion stars</title>
			<authors>Rodgers, A. W.; Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Publications, vol. 86, Oct. 1974, p. 742-766.</journal>
			<date>10/1974</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1974PASP...86..742R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1969ApJ...157..287E</bibcode>
			<title>Subluminous stars. III. Luminosity calibration for subluminous stars and the space density of the blue subluminous stars south of declination - 45 degres</title>
			<authors>Eggen, O. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astrophysical Journal, 157, 287</journal>
			<date>7/1969</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1969ApJ...157..287E</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
