<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...81F</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Infrared Observations and Independent Validation of the Transiting Super-Earth CoRoT-7 b</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Pont, Frederic; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Mazeh, Tsevi; Aigrain, Suzanne; Fridlund, Malcolm; Henze, Christopher E.; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 81 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...81F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012PABei..30...48Z</bibcode>
			<title>A Statistical survey of orbital parameters of extra-solar planets system.</title>
			<authors>Zhao, J.; Zhao, G.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 30, 48-63 (2012)</journal>
			<date>0/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012PABei..30...48Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...69H</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Modeling of the Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect for Transiting Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Suto, Yasushi; Winn, Joshua N.; Taruya, Atsushi; Narita, Norio; Albrecht, Simon; Sato, Bun'ei</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 69 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...69H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A...7M</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of new high-precision transit light curves of WASP-10 b: starspot occultations, small planetary radius, and high metallicity</title>
			<authors>