<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..14E</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT-SRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Erikson, A.; Santerne, A.; Renner, S.; Barge, P.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; Rgulo, C.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..14E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...81F</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Infrared Observations and Independent Validation of the Transiting Super-Earth CoRoT-7 b</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Pont, Frederic; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Mazeh, Tsevi; Aigrain, Suzanne; Fridlund, Malcolm; Henze, Christopher E.; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 81 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...81F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A.147H</bibcode>
			<title>Optimizing exoplanet transit searches around low-mass stars with inclination constraints</title>
			<authors>Herrero, E.; Ribas, I.; Jordi, C.; Guinan, E. F.; Engle, S. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 537, id.A147</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...537A.147H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012PABei..30...48Z</bibcode>
			<title>A Statistical survey of orbital parameters of extra-solar planets system.</title>
			<authors>Zhao, J.; Zhao, G.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 30, 48-63 (2012)</journal>
			<date>0/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012PABei..30...48Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...69H</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Modeling of the Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect for Transiting Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Suto, Yasushi; Winn, Joshua N.; Taruya, Atsushi; Narita, Norio; Albrecht, Simon; Sato, Bun'ei</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 69 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...69H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A...7M</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of new high-precision transit light curves of WASP-10 b: starspot occultations, small planetary radius, and high metallicity</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Raetz, St.; Nettelmann, N.; Seeliger, M.; Adam, C.; Nowak, G.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A7</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...535A...7M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ChA&amp;A..35..409Z</bibcode>
			<title>Observation and Research of the Transits of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Zhang, Ji-Cheng; Cao, Chen; Song, Nan; Wang, Fei-Ge; Zhang, Xiao-Tong</authors>
			<journal>Chinese Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 35, Issue 4, p. 409-420.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ChA%26A..35..409Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740L..10N</bibcode>
			<title>Using Star Spots to Measure the Spin-orbit Alignment of Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 740, Issue 1, article id. L10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740L..10N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Broadband Transmission Spectroscopy of the Super-Earth GJ 1214b Suggests a Low Mean Molecular Weight Atmosphere</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Miller-Ricci Kempton, Eliza; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman; Neilson, Hilding</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. 78 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...12B</bibcode>
			<title>The GJ1214 Super-Earth System: Stellar Variability, New Transits, and a Search for Additional Planets</title>
			<authors>Berta, Zachory K.; Charbonneau, David; Bean, Jacob; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Nutzman, Philip; Falco, Emilio E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 12 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...12B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AN....332..547N</bibcode>
			<title>The Young Exoplanet Transit Initiative (YETI)</title>
			<authors>Neuhuser, R.; Errmann, R.; Berndt, A.; Maciejewski, G.; Takahashi, H.; Chen, W. P.; Dimitrov, D. P.; Pribulla, T.; Nikogossian, E. H.; Jensen, E. L. N.; Marschall, L.; Wu, Z.-Y.; Kellerer, A.; Walter, F. M.; Briceo, C.; Chini, R.; Fernandez, M.; Raetz, St.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Quinn, S. N.; Niedzielski, A.; Bukowiecki, L.; Nowak, G.; Tomov, T.; Tachihara, K.; Hu, S. C.-L.; Hung, L. W.; Kjurkchieva, D. P.; Radeva, V. S.; Mihov, B. M.; Slavcheva-Mihova, L.; Bozhinova, I. N.; Budaj, J.; Vanko, M.; Kundra, E.; Hamblek, L.; Krushevska, V.; Movsessian, T.; Harutyunyan, H.; Downes, J. J.; Hernandez, J.; Hoffmeister, V. H.; Cohen, D. H.; Abel, I.; Ahmad, R.; Chapman, S.; Eckert, S.; Goodman, J.; Guerard, A.; Kim, H. M.; Koontharana, A.; Sokol, J.; Trinh, J.; Wang, Y.; Zhou, X.; Redmer, R.; Kramm, U.; Nettelmann, N.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, J.; Moualla, M.; Ginski, C.; Marka, C.; Adam, C.; Seeliger, M.; Baar, S.; Roell, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Trepl, L.; Eisenbei, T.; Fiedler, S.; Tetzlaff, N.; Schmidt, E.; Hohle, M. M.; Kitze, M.; Chakrova, N.; Grfe, C.; Schreyer, K.; Hambaryan, V. V.; Broeg, C. H.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Pandey, A. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.332, Issue 6, p.547</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AN....332..547N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734..109B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-27b: A Hot Jupiter Transiting a G Star on a 3 Day Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bky, B.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Jordn, A.; Arriagada, P.; Bayliss, D.; Kiss, L. L.; Kovcs, Gza; Quinn, S. N.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 2, article id. 109 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734..109B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733..127S</bibcode>
			<title>Starspots and Spin-orbit Alignment in the WASP-4 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Carter, Joshua A.; Osip, David J.; Fuentes, Cesar I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. 127 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733..127S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733..116B</bibcode>
			<title>Hat-P-28b and Hat-P-29b: Two Sub-Jupiter Mass Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, L. A.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J. D.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Andersen, J.; Kovcs, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Shporer, A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Bky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Fursz, G.; Quinn, S. N.; Stefanik, R. P.; Szklenr, T.; Berlind, P.; Calkins, M. L.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...53H</bibcode>
			<title>Five New Transit Epochs of the Exoplanet OGLE-TR-111b</title>
			<authors>Hoyer, S.; Rojo, P.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Daz, R. F.; Chambers, J.; Minniti, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 53 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...53H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...41M</bibcode>
			<title>High Metallicity and Non-equilibrium Chemistry in the Dayside Atmosphere of hot-Neptune GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...41M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...74V</bibcode>
			<title>Quantifying the Challenges of Detecting Unseen Planetary Companions with Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Payne, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...74V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...63W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Orientations of Exoplanets: HAT-P-4b is Prograde and HAT-P-14b is Retrograde</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Bakos, Gspr .; Hartman, Joel D.; Holman, Matthew J.; Albrecht, Simon; Crepp, Justin R.; Morton, Timothy D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 63 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...63W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...23B</bibcode>
			<title>Secondary Eclipse Photometry of WASP-4b with Warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Beerer, Ingrid M.; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Agol, Eric; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Deming, Drake; Desert, Jean-Michel; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 23 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 29, 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; Sgransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1938L</bibcode>
			<title>Forming Planetesimals by Gravitational Instability. II. How Dust Settles to its Marginally Stable State</title>
			<authors>Lee, Aaron T.; Chiang, Eugene; Asay-Davis, Xylar; Barranco, Joseph</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1938-1954 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1938L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1606W</bibcode>
			<title>Estimating the masses of extra-solar planets</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Littlefair, S. P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Dhillon, V. S.; Simpson, E. K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1606-1622.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1606W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2625M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation in exoplanet WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuhuser, R.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Ginski, Ch.; Adam, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2625-2631.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2625M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722L..75S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Transits of Limb-brightened Lines: Tentative Si IV Absorption by HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Schlawin, E.; Agol, E.; Walkowicz, L. M.; Covey, K.; Lloyd, J. P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. L75-L79 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722L..75S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..60M</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit timing variations induced by stellar binarity. The light travel time effect</title>
			<authors>Montalto, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A60</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..60M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Dsert, J.-M.; Daz, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..64L</bibcode>
			<title>Is tidal heating sufficient to explain bloated exoplanets? Consistent calculations accounting for finite initial eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Chabrier, G.; Baraffe, I.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A64</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..64L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...515A.111S</bibcode>
			<title>The PASTEL catalogue of stellar parameters</title>
			<authors>Soubiran, C.; Le Campion, J.-F.; Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Caillo, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 515, id.A111</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...515A.111S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714..462S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Apparent Orbital Inclination Change of the Extrasolar Transiting Planet TrES-2b</title>
			<authors>Scuderi, Louis J.; Dittmann, Jason A.; Males, Jared R.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Close, Laird M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 462-468 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714..462S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714...13A</bibcode>
			<title>Lack of Transit Timing Variations of OGLE-TR-111b: A Re-Analysis with Six New Epochs</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Elliot, J. L.; Seager, S.; Osip, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 13-24 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714...13A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...514A..39H</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary eclipse mapping of CoRoT-2a. Evolution, differential rotation, and spot migration</title>
			<authors>Huber, K. F.; Czesla, S.; Wolter, U.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 514, id.A39</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...514A..39H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.2111H</bibcode>
			<title>Tight constraints on the existence of additional planets around HD 189733&amp;dagger</title>
			<authors>Hrudkov, M.; Skillen, I.; Benn, C. R.; Gibson, N. P.; Pollacco, D.; Nesvorn, D.; Augusteijn, T.; Tulloch, S. M.; Joshi, Y. C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 4, pp. 2111-2119.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.2111H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010NewA...15..297P</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Transit Database. Reduction and processing of the photometric data of exoplanet transits</title>
			<authors>Poddan, Stanislav; Brt, Lubos; Pejcha, Ondrej</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 15, Issue 3, p. 297-301.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010NewA...15..297P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..374F</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Mandushev, Georgi; Spiegel, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 374-379 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..374F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1551O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Planetary Emission from the Exoplanet Tres-2 Using Spitzer/IRAC</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Harrington, Joseph; Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1551-1556 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1551O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710...97C</bibcode>
			<title>Studying the Atmosphere of the Exoplanet HAT-P-7b Via Secondary Eclipse Measurements with EPOXI, Spitzer, and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Holman, Matthew J.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Deming, Drake; A'Hearn, Michael F.; EPOXI Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 97-104 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710...97C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709.1396F</bibcode>
			<title>Transmission Spectra of Three-Dimensional Hot Jupiter Model Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Shabram, M.; Showman, A. P.; Lian, Y.; Freedman, R. S.; Marley, M. S.; Lewis, N. K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 2, pp. 1396-1406 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709.1396F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508.1011R</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing analysis of the exoplanets TrES-1 and TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Rabus, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Alonso, R.; Belmonte, J. A.; Almenara, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 2, 2009, pp.1011-1020</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508.1011R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..877B</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting the Wind-Driven Shapes of Extrasolar Giant Planets from Transit Photometry</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.; Cooper, Curtis S.; Showman, Adam P.; Hubbard, William B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 877-884 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..877B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..481C</bibcode>
			<title>High cadence near infrared timing observations of extrasolar planets. I. GJ 436b and XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Cceres, C.; Ivanov, V. D.; Minniti, D.; Naef, D.; Melo, C.; Mason, E.; Selman, F.; Pietrzynski, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.481-486</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..481C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..369B</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the transit times of CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Bean, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.369-375</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..369B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.1086C</bibcode>
			<title>Benefits of Ground-Based Photometric Follow-Up for Transiting Extrasolar Planets Discovered with Kepler and CoRoT</title>
			<authors>Coln, Knicole D.; Ford, Eric B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 1086-1095 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.1086C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..769K</bibcode>
			<title>The 8 mum Phase Variation of the Hot Saturn HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Showman, Adam P.; Agol, Eric; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 769-784 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..769K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..752L</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-16b: A New Jupiter-Like Planet Transiting a Southern Solar Analog</title>
			<authors>Lister, T. A.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Smalley, B. S.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Wilson, D. M.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, R.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Kane, S. R.; Mayor, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 752-756 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..752L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..561W</bibcode>
			<title>Transit mapping of a starspot on CoRoT-2. Probing a stellar surface with planetary transits</title>
			<authors>Wolter, U.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Huber, K. F.; Czesla, S.; Mller, H. M.; Guenther, E. W.; Hatzes, A. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.561-564</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..561W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701L..20Z</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Sulfur Photochemistry on Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Zahnle, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.; Lodders, K.; Fortney, J. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. L20-L24 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701L..20Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.1616A</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting Transits of Planetary Companions to Giant Stars</title>
			<authors>Assef, R. J.; Gaudi, B. S.; Stanek, K. Z.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 1616-1626 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.1616A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..756D</bibcode>
			<title>A Tentative Detection of a Starspot During Consecutive Transits of an Extrasolar Planet from the Ground: No Evidence of a Double Transiting Planet System Around TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, Jason A.; Close, Laird M.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Fenwick, Mike</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 756-763 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..756D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..514M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission of XO-2b: Evidence for a Weak Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 514-520 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..514M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1797K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon - II</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1797-1804.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1797K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...500L..51L</bibcode>
			<title>GMRT radio observations of the transiting extrasolar planet HD 189733 b at 244 and 614 MHz</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Sirothia, S. K.; Gopal-Krishna; Zarka, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 500, Issue 3, 2009, pp.L51-L54</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...500L..51L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009RMxAC..35...13S</bibcode>
			<title>Starspot detection from planetary transits observed by CoRoT</title>
			<authors>Silva-Vlio, A.</authors>
			<journal>XII Latin American IAU Regional Meeting (Eds. G. Magris, G. Bruzual, &amp; L. Carigi) Revista Mexicana de Astronoma y Astrofsica (Serie de Conferencias) Vol. 35, pp. 13-18 (2009) (http://www.astroscu.unam.mx/~rmaa/)</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009RMxAC..35...13S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1230F</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Spin-Orbit Alignment: Results from the Ensemble of Rossiter-McLaughlin Observations</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1230-1240 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1230F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AN....330..475R</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit observations at the University Observatory Jena: XO-1b and TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Raetz, St.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Roell, T.; Eisenbeiss, T.; Hohle, M. M.; Tetzlaff, N.; Vanko, M.; Seifahrt, A.; Broeg, Ch.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.330, Issue 5, p.475</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AN....330..475R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..567D</bibcode>
			<title>Binarity of transit host stars. Implications for planetary parameters</title>
			<authors>Daemgen, S.; Hormuth, F.; Brandner, W.; Bergfors, C.; Janson, M.; Hippler, S.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 2, 2009, pp.567-574</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..567D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691.1145S</bibcode>
			<title>A New Spectroscopic and Photometric Analysis of the Transiting Planet Systems TrES-3 and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Korzennik, Sylvain G.; Holman, Matthew J.; Latham, David W.; Laird, John B.; Fernandez, Jos; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward; Everett, Mark E.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Belmonte, Juan A.; Deeg, Hans J.; Brown, Timothy N.; Hidas, Mrton G.; Baliber, Nairn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 2, pp. 1145-1158 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691.1145S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392..181K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 1, pp. 181-189.</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392..181K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691..866K</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of A Temperature Inversion in the Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Burrows, Adam; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 1, pp. 866-874 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...494..391R</bibcode>
			<title>A cool starspot or a second transiting planet in the TrES-1 system?</title>
			<authors>Rabus, M.; Alonso, R.; Belmonte, J. A.; Deeg, H. J.; Gilliland, R. L.; Almenara, J. M.; Brown, T. M.; Charbonneau, D.; Mandushev, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 494, Issue 1, 2009, pp.391-397</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...494..391R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493L..35D</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based K-band detection of thermal emission from the exoplanet TrES-3b</title>
			<authors>de Mooij, E. J. W.; Snellen, I. A. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 2, 2009, pp.L35-L38</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493L..35D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJS..179..484H</bibcode>
			<title>On the Absorption and Redistribution of Energy in Irradiated Planets</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 179, Issue 2, pp. 484-508.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJS..179..484H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origins of Eccentric Close-In Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Takeda, Genya; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. L29-L32.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1302B</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting the Yields of Photometric Surveys for Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1302-1330.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1302B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..649J</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Angle of Exoplanet HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.; Narita, Norio; Enya, Keigo; Williams, Peter K. G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Sato, Bun'ei; Ohta, Yasuhiro; Taruya, Atsushi; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Bakos, Gaspar; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide; Yamada, Toru; Yoshii, Yuzuru; Hidas, Marton</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 649-657.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..649J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..621F</bibcode>
			<title>Origins of Eccentric Extrasolar Planets: Testing the Planet-Planet Scattering Model</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 621-636.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..621F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..580C</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical Outcomes of Planet-Planet Scattering</title>
			<authors>Chatterjee, Sourav; Ford, Eric B.; Matsumura, Soko; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 580-602.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..580C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389..257H</bibcode>
			<title>Reflected light from 3D exoplanetary atmospheres and simulation of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Hood, Ben; Wood, Kenneth; Seager, Sara; Collier Cameron, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 1, pp. 257-269.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389..257H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389..191P</bibcode>
			<title>Periastron precession measurements in transiting extrasolar planetary systems at the level of general relativity</title>
			<authors>Pl, Andrs; Kocsis, Bence</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 1, pp. 191-198.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389..191P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684.1427M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission of Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Burrows, Adam; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 2, pp. 1427-1432.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684.1427M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488..763H</bibcode>
			<title>Misaligned spin-orbit in the XO-3 planetary system?</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Loeillet, B.; Rabus, M.; Bonfils, X.; Moutou, C.; Boisse, I.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488..763H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1277B</bibcode>
			<title>Optical Albedo Theory of Strongly Irradiated Giant Planets: The Case of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Ibgui, L.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1277-1282.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1277B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682L..49D</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Period Variations in Extrasolar Transiting Planet OGLE-TR-111b</title>
			<authors>Daz, Rodrigo F.; Rojo, Patricio; Melita, Mario; Hoyer, Sergio; Minniti, Dante; Mauas, Pablo J. D.; Ruz, Mara Teresa</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 1, pp. L49-L52.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682L..49D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682..593M</bibcode>
			<title>MOST Space-based Photometry of the Transiting Exoplanet System HD 189733: Precise Timing Measurements for Transits across an Active Star</title>
			<authors>Miller-Ricci, Eliza; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Kuschnig, Rainer; Croll, Bryce; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rucinski, Slavek M.; Walker, Gordon A. H.; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 1, pp. 593-601.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682..593M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682..586M</bibcode>
			<title>MOST Space-based Photometry of the Transiting Exoplanet System HD 209458: Transit Timing to Search for Additional Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller-Ricci, Eliza; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Guenther, David B.; Kuschnig, Rainer; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rucinski, Slavek M.; Walker, Gordon A. H.; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 1, pp. 586-592.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682..586M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681.1631J</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 2, pp. 1631-1638.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681.1631J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008NewAR..52..154S</bibcode>
			<title>Extra-solar planets: Detection methods and results</title>
			<authors>Santos, Nuno C.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 52, Issue 2-5, p. 154-166.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008NewAR..52..154S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678L.129C</bibcode>
			<title>Inverting Phase Functions to Map Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. L129-L132.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678L.129C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1419F</bibcode>
			<title>A Unified Theory for the Atmospheres of the Hot and Very Hot Jupiters: Two Classes of Irradiated Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Lodders, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1419-1435.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1419F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482L..25B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. III. The spectroscopic transit of CoRoT-Exo-2b with SOPHIE and HARPS</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Queloz, D.; Deleuil, M.; Loeillet, B.; Hatzes, A. P.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 3, 2008, pp.L25-L28</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482L..25B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482L..21A</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. II. CoRoT-Exo-2b: a transiting planet around an active G star</title>
			<authors>Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Ollivier, M.; Moutou, C.; Rouan, D.; Deeg, H. J.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Kabath, P.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Shporer, A.; Schneider, J.; Stecklum, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 3, 2008, pp.L21-L24</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482L..21A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...481..529L</bibcode>
			<title>Refined parameters and spectroscopic transit of the super-massive planet HD 147506b</title>
			<authors>Loeillet, B.; Shporer, A.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Mazeh, T.; Beuzit, J. L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; da Silva, R.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Ecuvillon, A.; Forveille, T.; Galland, F.; Gallenne, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Sivan, J. P.; Santos, N. C.; Tsodikovich, Y.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 481, Issue 2, 2008, pp.529-533</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...481..529L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008PASP..120..317N</bibcode>
			<title>Design Considerations for a Ground-Based Transit Search for Habitable Planets Orbiting M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip; Charbonneau, David</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 120, issue 865, pp.317-327</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008PASP..120..317N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...674..482S</bibcode>
			<title>The Mid-Infrared Spectrum of the Transiting Exoplanet HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Swain, M. R.; Bouwman, J.; Akeson, R. L.; Lawler, S.; Beichman, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 674, Issue 1, pp. 482-497.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...674..482S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..513D</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Dynamics of Short-Period Extrasolar Gas Giant Planets. I. Dependence of Nightside Temperature on Opacity</title>
			<authors>Dobbs-Dixon, Ian; Lin, D. N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 513-525.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..513D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008OEJV...95...81P</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting Explanet Light Curve Solution by Phoebe Code</title>
			<authors>Poddany, S.</authors>
			<journal>Open European Journal on Variable Stars, Vol. 95. Proceedings of the 39th Conference on Variable Stars Research, p.81</journal>
			<date>0/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008OEJV...95...81P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008BAVSR..57..199B</bibcode>
			<title>BAV-Veraenderlichenbeobachter-Treffen 2008 in Hartha.</title>
			<authors>Braune, W.</authors>
			<journal>BAV Rundbrief, 57, 199 (2008)</journal>
			<date>0/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008BAVSR..57..199B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008BAVSM.191....1H</bibcode>
			<title>Three New Variable Stars in the Field of the RR Lyrae Star GY Peg.</title>
			<authors>Hambsch, F.-J.; Vandenbroere, J.</authors>
			<journal>Berliner Arbeitsgemeinschaft fr Veraenderliche Sterne - Mitteilungen, 191, 1-6 (2008)</journal>
			<date>0/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008BAVSM.191....1H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671L.173B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-5b: A Jupiter-like Hot Jupiter Transiting a Bright Star</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Shporer, A.; Pl, A.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Mazeh, T.; Ofir, A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Esquerdo, G.; Sipocz, B.; Kovcs, Gbor; Stefanik, R.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 2, pp. L173-L176.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671L.173B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671.2129C</bibcode>
			<title>Looking for Super-Earths in the HD 189733 System: A Search for Transits in MOST Space-based Photometry</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Gladman, Brett; Miller-Ricci, Eliza; Sasselov, Dimitar; Walker, Gordon A. H.; Kuschnig, Rainer; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rucinski, Slavek M.; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 2, pp. 2129-2138.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671.2129C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671..861H</bibcode>
			<title>Two Classes of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. 861-871.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671..861H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...476.1347P</bibcode>
			<title>Hubble Space Telescope time-series photometry of the planetary transit of HD 189733: no moon, no rings, starspots</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Gilliland, R. L.; Moutou, C.; Charbonneau, D.; Bouchy, F.; Brown, T. M.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 476, Issue 3, December IV 2007, pp.1347-1355</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...476.1347P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1324S</bibcode>
			<title>On Constraining a Transiting Exoplanet's Rotation Rate with Its Transit Spectrum</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Haiman, Zoltn; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1335.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1324S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1298F</bibcode>
			<title>Shrinking Binary and Planetary Orbits by Kozai Cycles with Tidal Friction</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel; Tremaine, Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1298-1315.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1298F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..729F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting and predicting the yield of transit surveys: giant planets in the OGLE fields</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Morello, V.; Pont, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 2, November IV 2007, pp.729-746</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..729F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..359G</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting low-frequency radio fluxes of known extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Griemeier, J.-M.; Zarka, P.; Spreeuw, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 1, November III 2007, pp.359-368</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..359G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...668L.171B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectral Models of the Planet HD 209458b with a Thermal Inversion and Water Emission Bands</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Knutson, H. A.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 668, Issue 2, pp. L171-L174.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...668L.171B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...474..301B</bibcode>
			<title>A method to detect H{2} in the atmosphere of transiting extrasolar planets using the EUV spectrum</title>
			<authors>Barthlmy, M.; Lilensten, J.; Parkinson, C. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 474, Issue 1, October IV 2007, pp.301-306</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...474..301B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007OEJV...67....1H</bibcode>
			<title>Two new variable stars in the field of the Transiting Extrasolar planet TRES-1 (GSC 2652-1324)</title>
			<authors>Hambsch, F.-J.</authors>
			<journal>Open European Journal on Variable Stars, vol. 0067, Issue 1, p.1</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007OEJV...67....1H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ARA&amp;A..45..397U</bibcode>
			<title>Statistical Properties of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Udry, Stphane; Santos, Nuno C.</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, vol. 45, Issue 1, pp.397-439</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ARA%26A..45..397U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...666..475M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Planet Taxonomy: A New Statistical Approach</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 666, Issue 1, pp. 475-485.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...666..475M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...472..329E</bibcode>
			<title>Roche lobe effects on the atmospheric loss from ``Hot Jupiters''</title>
			<authors>Erkaev, N. V.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Lammer, H.; Selsis, F.; Langmayr, D.; Jaritz, G. F.; Biernat, H. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 472, Issue 1, September II 2007, pp.329-334</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...472..329E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASJ...59..763N</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Rossiter-Laughlin Effect in the Transiting Exoplanetary System TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Narita, N.; Enya, K.; Sato, B.; Ohta, Y.; Winn, J. N.; Suto, Y.; Taruya, A.; Turner, E. L.; Aoki, W.; Yoshii, M.; Yamada, T.; Tamura, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.59, No.4, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASJ...59..763N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379.1097B</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared spectroscopic search for the close orbiting planet HD 75289b</title>
			<authors>Barnes, J. R.; Leigh, C. J.; Jones, H. R. A.; Barman, Travis S.; Pinfield, D. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Jenkins, J. S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 379, Issue 3, pp. 1097-1107.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379.1097B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379..641C</bibcode>
			<title>Hot nights on extrasolar planets: mid-infrared phase variations of hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Cowan, N. B.; Agol, E.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 379, Issue 2, pp. 641-646.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379..641C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...665..754F</bibcode>
			<title>Cassini States with Dissipation: Why Obliquity Tides Cannot Inflate Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Johnson, Eric T.; Goodman, Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 665, Issue 1, pp. 754-766.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...665..754F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664.1199R</bibcode>
			<title>Toward Eclipse Mapping of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Rauscher, Emily; Menou, Kristen; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Cho, James Y.-K.; Hansen, Bradley M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 2, pp. 1199-1209.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664.1199R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664.1185H</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve (TLC) Project. VI. Three Transits of the Exoplanet TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Fernandez, Jose; Everett, Mark E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 2, pp. 1185-1189.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664.1185H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379L..11S</bibcode>
			<title>A method for the direct determination of the surface gravities of transiting extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Wheatley, Peter J.; Sams, Giles</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 379, Issue 1, pp. L11-L15.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379L..11S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...663L..37O</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-3: A Nearby, Massive, Transiting Hot Jupiter in a 31 Hour Orbit</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Bakos, Gspr .; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Brown, Timothy M.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Kovcs, Gza; Everett, Mark E.; Baliber, Nairn; Hidas, Mrton G.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Deeg, Hans J.; Belmonte, Juan A.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Stefanik, Robert P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 663, Issue 1, pp. L37-L40.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...663L..37O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASP..119..616K</bibcode>
			<title>A Ground-based Search for Thermal Emission from the Exoplanet TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Richardson, L. Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 119, Issue 856, pp. 616-622.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASP..119..616K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007Natur.447..691H</bibcode>
			<title>The hottest planet</title>
			<authors>Harrington, Joseph; Luszcz, Statia; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Richardson, L. Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 447, Issue 7145, pp. 691-693 (2007).</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007Natur.447..691H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.378..148D</bibcode>
			<title>3.8-mum photometry during the secondary eclipse of the extrasolar planet HD209458b</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Richardson, L. Jeremy; Harrington, Joseph</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 378, Issue 1, pp. 148-152.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.378..148D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662L.115R</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiter Variability in Eclipse Depth</title>
			<authors>Rauscher, Emily; Menou, Kristen; Cho, James Y.-K.; Seager, Sara; Hansen, Bradley M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 2, pp. L115-L118.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662L.115R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662..658O</bibcode>
			<title>Outcome of Six Candidate Transiting Planets from a TrES Field in Andromeda</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Latham, David W.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Torres, Guillermo; Everett, Mark E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 1, pp. 658-668.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662..658O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...661..502B</bibcode>
			<title>Possible Solutions to the Radius Anomalies of Transiting Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Hubbard, W. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 661, Issue 1, pp. 502-514.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...661..502B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..850D</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude Photometry for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Candidates. II. Transits of OGLE-TR-113-b in the Optical and Near-IR</title>
			<authors>Daz, Rodrigo F.; Ramrez, Sebastin; Fernndez, Jos Miguel; Gallardo, Jos; Gieren, Wolfgang; Ivanov, Valentin D.; Mauas, Pablo; Minniti, Dante; Pietrzynski, Grzegorz; Prez, Felipe; Ruz, Mara Teresa; Udalski, Andrzej; Zoccali, Manuela</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 850-857.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..850D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..823M</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of Earth-like Planets During and After Giant Planet Migration</title>
			<authors>Mandell, Avi M.; Raymond, Sean N.; Sigurdsson, Steinn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 823-844.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..823M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...659.1661F</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Radii across Five Orders of Magnitude in Mass and Stellar Insolation: Application to Transits</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Marley, M. S.; Barnes, J. W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 659, Issue 2, pp. 1661-1672.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...659.1661F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658L.115G</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer Spectrum of the Exoplanet HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Grillmair, C. J.; Charbonneau, D.; Burrows, A.; Armus, L.; Stauffer, J.; Meadows, V.; Van Cleve, J.; Levine, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. L115-L118.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658L.115G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1328C</bibcode>
			<title>Looking for Giant Earths in the HD 209458 System: A Search for Transits in MOST Space-based Photometry</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Kuschnig, Rainer; Walker, Andrew; Gladman, Brett; Sasselov, Dimitar; Cameron, Chris; Walker, Gordon A. H.; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rucinski, Slavek M.; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1328-1339.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1328C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1322C</bibcode>
			<title>Precise Radius Estimates for the Exoplanets WASP-1b and WASP-2b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Everett, Mark E.; Latham, David W.; Holman, Matthew J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1322-1327.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1322C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AJ....133.1828W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. V. System Parameters and Stellar Rotation Period of HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Henry, Gregory W.; Roussanova, Anna; Enya, Keigo; Yoshii, Yuzuru; Shporer, Avi; Mazeh, Tsevi; Johnson, John Asher; Narita, Norio; Suto, Yasushi</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 133, Issue 4, pp. 1828-1835 (2007).</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AJ....133.1828W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...657.1098W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. III. Tres Transits of TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Roussanova, Anna</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 657, Issue 2, pp. 1098-1106.</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...657.1098W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...464.1133C</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting companions to extrasolar planets using mutual events</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Schneider, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 464, Issue 3, March IV 2007, pp.1133-1138</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...464.1133C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007Natur.445..892R</bibcode>
			<title>A spectrum of an extrasolar planet</title>
			<authors>Richardson, L. Jeremy; Deming, Drake; Horning, Karen; Seager, Sara; Harrington, Joseph</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 445, Issue 7130, pp. 892-895 (2007).</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007Natur.445..892R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.375..307S</bibcode>
			<title>K-band transit and secondary eclipse photometry of exoplanet OGLE-TR-113b</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.; Covino, E.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 375, Issue 1, pp. 307-312.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.375..307S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...656..552B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-1b: A Large-Radius, Low-Density Exoplanet Transiting One Member of a Stellar Binary</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Noyes, R. W.; Kovcs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Torres, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sato, B.; Johnson, J. A.; P l, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Stanek, K. Z.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.; Sipocz, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 656, Issue 1, pp. 552-559.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...656..552B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...655.1103H</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. IV. Five Transits of the Exoplanet OGLE-TR-10b</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Fuentes, Cesar I.; Hartman, Joel D.; Stanek, K. Z.; Torres, Guillermo; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Gaudi, B. Scott; Jones, R. Lynne; Fraser, Wesley</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 655, Issue 2, pp. 1103-1109.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...655.1103H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.374..941A</bibcode>
			<title>A limit on the presence of Earth-mass planets around a Sun-like star</title>
			<authors>Agol, Eric; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 374, Issue 3, pp. 941-948.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.374..941A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...655..564K</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Limb-Darkening to Refine the Properties of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Noyes, Robert W.; Brown, Timothy M.; Gilliland, Ronald L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 655, Issue 1, pp. 564-575.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...655..564K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...655..550G</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for the Characterization and Confirmation of Transiting Exoplanets via the Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. Scott; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 655, Issue 1, pp. 550-563.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...655..550G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...461.1185L</bibcode>
			<title>A diagram to determine the evaporation status of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 461, Issue 3, January III 2007, pp.1185-1193</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...461.1185L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1621P</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy with Small Telescopes</title>
			<authors>Paczynski, Bohdan</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 850, pp. 1621-1625.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1621P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652L.137F</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Constraints on Trojans of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. L137-L140.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652L.137F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652.1715H</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. I. Four Consecutive Transits of the Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Bakos, Gspr A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Hergenrother, Carl; Everett, Mark E.; Pl, Andrs</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. 1715-1723.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652.1715H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460..251M</bibcode>
			<title>On the age of stars harboring transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Melo, C.; Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 1, December II 2006, pp.251-256</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460..251M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.373L..55B</bibcode>
			<title>A near-infrared spectroscopic detection of the brown dwarf in the post common envelope binary WD0137-349</title>
			<authors>Burleigh, M. R.; Hogan, E.; Dobbie, P. D.; Napiwotzki, R.; Maxted, P. F. L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 373, Issue 1, pp. L55-L59.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.373L..55B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.373..231P</bibcode>
			<title>The effect of red noise on planetary transit detection</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Zucker, Shay; Queloz, Didier</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 373, Issue 1, pp. 231-242.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.373..231P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.372.1117C</bibcode>
			<title>The SuperWASP wide-field exoplanetary transit survey: candidates from fields 23 h &lt; RA &lt; 03 h</title>
			<authors>Christian, D. J.; Pollacco, D. L.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Keenan, F. P.; Clarkson, W. I.; Collier Cameron, A.; Kane, S. R.; Lister, T. A.; West, R. G.; Enoch, B.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J.; Ryans, R.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 372, Issue 3, pp. 1117-1128.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.372.1117C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652..746F</bibcode>
			<title>The Influence of Atmospheric Dynamics on the Infrared Spectra and Light Curves of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Cooper, C. S.; Showman, A. P.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 1, pp. 746-757.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652..746F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...651L..61O</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-2: The First Transiting Planet in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Brown, Timothy M.; Trauger, John T.; Belmonte, Juan A.; Rabus, Markus; Almenara, Jos M.; Alonso, Roi; Deeg, Hans J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Falco, Emilio E.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Roussanova, Anna; Stefanik, Robert P.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 651, Issue 1, pp. L61-L64.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...651L..61O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...458..997S</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical abundances for the transiting planet host stars OGLE-TR-10, 56, 111, 113, 132, and TrES-1. Abundances in different galactic populations</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Ecuvillon, A.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Ribeiro, J. P.; Jorge, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 458, Issue 3, November II 2006, pp.997-1005</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...458..997S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006Sci...314..623H</bibcode>
			<title>The Phase-Dependent Infrared Brightness of the Extrasolar Planet upsilo Andromedae b</title>
			<authors>Harrington, Joseph; Hansen, Brad M.; Luszcz, Statia H.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Menou, Kristen; Cho, James Y.-K.; Richardson, L. Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 314, Issue 5799, pp. 623-626 (2006).</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006Sci...314..623H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1407P</bibcode>
			<title>The WASP Project and the SuperWASP Cameras</title>
			<authors>Pollacco, D. L.; Skillen, I.; Collier Cameron, A.; Christian, D. J.; Hellier, C.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Street, R. A.; West, R. G.; Anderson, D.; Clarkson, W. I.; Deeg, H.; Enoch, B.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hodgkin, S.; Horne, K.; Kane, S. R.; Keenan, F. P.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J.; Parley, N. R.; Ryans, R. S. I.; Smalley, B.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 848, pp. 1407-1418.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1407P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASJ...58..869U</bibcode>
			<title>An Extrasolar Planet Transit Search with Subaru Suprime-Cam</title>
			<authors>Urakawa, Seitaro; Yamada, Toru; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Itoh, Yoichi; Mukai, Tadashi; Tamura, Motohide; Wang, Yiping</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.58, No.5, pp.869-881</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASJ...58..869U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650.1160B</bibcode>
			<title>Refined Parameters of the Planet Orbiting HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Knutson, H.; Pont, F.; Moutou, C.; Charbonneau, D.; Shporer, A.; Bouchy, F.; Everett, M.; Hergenrother, C.; Latham, D. W.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Noyes, R. W.; Queloz, D.; Pl, A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 2, pp. 1160-1171.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650.1160B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650.1140B</bibcode>
			<title>Theory for the Secondary Eclipse Fluxes, Spectra, Atmospheres, and Light Curves of Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Sudarsky, D.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 2, pp. 1140-1149.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650.1140B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650..394A</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Structure and Radius Evolution of Irradiated Gas Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Arras, Phil; Bildsten, Lars</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 1, pp. 394-407.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650..394A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1048C</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamics and Disequilibrium Carbon Chemistry in Hot Jupiter Atmospheres, with Application to HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Cooper, Curtis S.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1048-1063.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1048C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1020W</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the Surfaces of Extrasolar Planets with Secondary Eclipse Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Williams, Peter K. G.; Charbonneau, David; Cooper, Curtis S.; Showman, Adam P.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1020-1027.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1020W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1010J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of Known Exoplanetary Systems Based on Measured Stellar Properties</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick; Underwood, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1019.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1010J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1302H</bibcode>
			<title>PlanetPol: A Very High Sensitivity Polarimeter</title>
			<authors>Hough, J. H.; Lucas, P. W.; Bailey, J. A.; Tamura, M.; Hirst, E.; Harrison, D.; Bartholomew-Biggs, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 847, pp. 1302-1318.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1302H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ARA&amp;A..44..269W</bibcode>
			<title>First Fruits of the Spitzer Space Telescope: Galactic and Solar System Studies</title>
			<authors>Werner, Michael; Fazio, Giovanni; Rieke, George; Roellig, Thomas L.; Watson, Dan M.</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, vol. 44, Issue 1, pp.269-321</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ARA%26A..44..269W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...648.1228M</bibcode>
			<title>A Transiting Planet of a Sun-like Star</title>
			<authors>McCullough, P. R.; Stys, J. E.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Johns-Krull, C. M.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Bye, B. A.; Dodd, C.; Fleming, S. W.; Pinnick, A.; Bissinger, R.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 648, Issue 2, pp. 1228-1238.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...648.1228M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....132.1267S</bibcode>
			<title>No Detectable H+3 Emission from the Atmospheres of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Shkolnik, Evgenya; Gaidos, Eric; Moskovitz, Nick</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 132, Issue 3, pp. 1267-1274.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....132.1267S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.370.1379J</bibcode>
			<title>Data analysis on the extrasolar planets using robust clustering</title>
			<authors>Jiang, Ing-Guey; Yeh, Li-Chin; Hung, Wen-Liang; Yang, Miin-Shen</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 370, Issue 3, pp. 1379-1392.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.370.1379J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...647.1437M</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer IRAC Search for Substellar Companions of the Debris Disk Star &amp;epsil Eridani</title>
			<authors>Marengo, M.; Megeath, S. T.; Fazio, G. G.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Werner, M. W.; Backman, D. E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 647, Issue 2, pp. 1437-1451.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...647.1437M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118..947T</bibcode>
			<title>Astrophysics in 2005</title>
			<authors>Trimble, Virginia; Aschwanden, Markus J.; Hansen, Carl J.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 845, pp. 947-1047.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118..947T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.369.1267D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of a binary or planetary system during encounters with a third inclined body</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 369, Issue 3, pp. 1267-1280.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.369.1267D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..505B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of Nearby Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. P.; Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Penny, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 505-522.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..505B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...453L..21G</bibcode>
			<title>A correlation between the heavy element content of transiting extrasolar planets and the metallicity of their parent stars</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Iro, N.; Melo, C.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 453, Issue 2, July II 2006, pp.L21-L24</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...453L..21G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644.1237O</bibcode>
			<title>Rejecting Astrophysical False Positives from the TrES Transiting Planet Survey: The Example of GSC 03885-00829</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Torres, Guillermo; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Latham, David W.; Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Creevey, Orlagh L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 2, pp. 1237-1245.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644.1237O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644..560D</bibcode>
			<title>Strong Infrared Emission from the Extrasolar Planet HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Harrington, Joseph; Seager, Sara; Richardson, L. Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 1, pp. 560-564.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644..560D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006NewA...11..490I</bibcode>
			<title>Are we far from testing general relativity with the transitting extrasolar planet HD 209458b `Osiris'?</title>
			<authors>Iorio, L.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 11, Issue 7, p. 490-494.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006NewA...11..490I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...642..495F</bibcode>
			<title>Atmosphere, Interior, and Evolution of the Metal-rich Transiting Planet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Saumon, D.; Marley, M. S.; Lodders, K.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 642, Issue 1, pp. 495-504.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...642..495F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...642..488S</bibcode>
			<title>Search for Planetary Candidates within the OGLE Stars</title>
			<authors>Silva, Adriana V. R.; Cruz, Patricia C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 642, Issue 1, pp. 488-494.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...642..488S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...450..825S</bibcode>
			<title>High resolution spectroscopy of stars with transiting planets. The cases of OGLE-TR-10, 56, 111, 113, and TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Melo, C.; Israelian, G.; Bouchy, F.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Guillot, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 450, Issue 2, May I 2006, pp.825-831</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...450..825S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...641..565S</bibcode>
			<title>The Effect of the Transit of Venus on ACRIM's Total Solar Irradiance Measurements: Implications for Transit Studies of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Schneider, G.; Pasachoff, J. M.; Willson, Richard C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 641, Issue 1, pp. 565-571.</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...641..565S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....131.2274S</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical Composition of the Planet-harboring Star TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Yong, David; Carney, Bruce W.; Laird, John B.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 131, Issue 4, pp. 2274-2289.</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....131.2274S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...638..488B</bibcode>
			<title>High-Contrast Imaging from Space: Speckle Nulling in a Low-Aberration Regime</title>
			<authors>Bord, Pascal J.; Traub, Wesley A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 638, Issue 1, pp. 488-498.</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...638..488B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...637.1102R</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. V. Identifying Very Metal-rich Stars with Low-Resolution Spectra: Finding Planet-Search Targets</title>
			<authors>Robinson, Sarah E.; Strader, Jay; Ammons, S. Mark; Laughlin, Gregory; Fischer, Debra</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 637, Issue 2, pp. 1102-1112.</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...637.1102R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...637.1094F</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. III. Short-Period Planets Orbiting HD 149143 and HD 109749</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Laughlin, Gregory; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Johnson, John A.; Henry, Gregory W.; McCarthy, Chris; Ammons, Mark; Robinson, Sarah; Strader, Jay; Valenti, Jeff A.; McCullough, P. R.; Charbonneau, David; Haislip, Joshua; Knutson, Heather A.; Reichart, Daniel E.; McGee, Padric; Monard, Berto; Wright, Jason T.; Ida, Shigeru; Sato, Bun'ei; Minniti, Dante</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 637, Issue 2, pp. 1094-1101.</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...637.1094F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006RPPh...69..119P</bibcode>
			<title>Planet formation and migration</title>
			<authors>Papaloizou, John C. B.; Terquem, Caroline</authors>
			<journal>Reports on Progress in Physics, Volume 69, Issue 1, pp. 119-180 (2006).</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006RPPh...69..119P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...636..445C</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Photometry of the Core-dominated Planet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; Bakos, Gspr; Falco, Emilio E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Noyes, Robert W.; Csk, Balzs; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 636, Issue 1, pp. 445-452.</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...636..445C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.364.1091K</bibcode>
			<title>Results from the Wide Angle Search for Planets Prototype (WASP0) - III. Planet hunting in the Draco field</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Collier Cameron, Andrew; Horne, Keith; James, David; Lister, T. A.; Pollacco, Don L.; Street, Rachel A.; Tsapras, Yiannis</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 364, Issue 3, pp. 1091-1103.</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.364.1091K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.364..649F</bibcode>
			<title>The effect of condensates on the characterization of transiting planet atmospheres with transmission spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 364, Issue 2, pp. 649-653.</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.364..649F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...634.1385M</bibcode>
			<title>A Moving Cluster Distance to the Exoplanet 2M1207b in the TW Hydrae Association</title>
			<authors>Mamajek, Eric E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 634, Issue 2, pp. 1385-1394.</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...634.1385M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...444L..15B</bibcode>
			<title>ELODIE metallicity-biased search for transiting Hot Jupiters. II. A very hot Jupiter transiting the bright K star HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pont, F.; Iribarne, N.; da Silva, R.; Ilovaisky, S.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 444, Issue 1, December II 2005, pp.L15-L19</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...444L..15B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.364L..96S</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the transit times of TrES-1b</title>
			<authors>Steffen, Jason H.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 364, Issue 1, pp. L96-L100.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.364L..96S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.364..325A</bibcode>
			<title>Candidate extrasolar planet transits discovered in the Microlensing Observations in Astrophysics-I Galactic bulge data</title>
			<authors>Abe, F.; Bond, I. A.; Furuta, Y.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Kurata, Y.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Muraki, Y.; Noda, S.; Okajima, K.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Tristram, P.; Wood, J. N.; Yanagisawa, T.; Yock, P. C. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 364, Issue 1, pp. 325-334.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.364..325A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...633..465S</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. II. A Transiting Hot Saturn around HD 149026 with a Large Dense Core</title>
			<authors>Sato, Bun'ei; Fischer, Debra A.; Henry, Gregory W.; Laughlin, Greg; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Vogt, Steven S.; Bodenheimer, Peter; Ida, Shigeru; Toyota, Eri; Wolf, Aaron; Valenti, Jeff A.; Boyd, Louis J.; Johnson, John A.; Wright, Jason T.; Ammons, Mark; Robinson, Sarah; Strader, Jay; McCarthy, Chris; Tah, K. L.; Minniti, Dante</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 633, Issue 1, pp. 465-473.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...633..465S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...443..609S</bibcode>
			<title>On the ages of exoplanet host stars</title>
			<authors>Saffe, C.; Gmez, M.; Chavero, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 443, Issue 2, November IV 2005, pp.609-626</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...443..609S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...442..731G</bibcode>
			<title>On the potential of extrasolar planet transit surveys</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Courbin, F.; Magain, P.; Borguet, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 442, Issue 2, November I 2005, pp.731-744</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...442..731G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Sci...310..251S</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Planets: Constraints for Planet Formation Models</title>
			<authors>Santos, Nuno C.; Benz, Willy; Mayor, Michel</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 310, Issue 5746, pp. 251-255 (2005).</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Sci...310..251S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005PASP..117.1021S</bibcode>
			<title>Astrometric Methods and Instrumentation to Identify and Characterize Extrasolar Planets: A Review</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 117, Issue 836, pp. 1021-1048.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005PASP..117.1021S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.363..211S</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision K-band photometry of the secondary eclipse of HD 209458</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 363, Issue 1, pp. 211-215.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.363..211S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...632.1132B</bibcode>
			<title>Phase-Dependent Properties of Extrasolar Planet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Barman, Travis S.; Hauschildt, Peter H.; Allard, France</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 632, Issue 2, pp. 1132-1139.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...632.1132B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...632.1122S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Dayside Thermal Emission of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Seager, S.; Richardson, L. J.; Hansen, B. M. S.; Menou, K.; Cho, J. Y.-K.; Deming, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 632, Issue 2, pp. 1122-1131.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...632.1122S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...631.1215W</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of Spin-Orbit Alignment in an Extrasolar Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Noyes, Robert W.; Holman, Matthew J.; Charbonneau, David; Ohta, Yasuhiro; Taruya, Atsushi; Suto, Yasushi; Narita, Norio; Turner, Edwin L.; Johnson, John A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 631, Issue 2, pp. 1215-1226.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...631.1215W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.362..460P</bibcode>
			<title>Fast identification of transits from light-curves</title>
			<authors>Protopapas, Pavlos; Jimenez, Raul; Alcock, Charles</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 362, Issue 2, pp. 460-468.</journal>
			<date>9/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.362..460P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005IBVS.5648....1S</bibcode>
			<title>Erratum: ``A High-Resolution Spectrum of the TrES-1 Parent Star''</title>
			<authors>Strassmeier, Klaus G.; Rice, John B.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 5648, 1.</journal>
			<date>9/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005IBVS.5648....1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005PASP..117..783M</bibcode>
			<title>The XO Project: Searching for Transiting Extrasolar Planet Candidates</title>
			<authors>McCullough, P. R.; Stys, J. E.; Valenti, J. A.; Fleming, S. W.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 117, Issue 834, pp. 783-795.</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005PASP..117..783M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005JAVSO..34...17P</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Transits of the Trans-Atlantic Exoplanet Survey Candidate TrES-1b</title>
			<authors>Price, A.; Bissinger, R.; Laughlin, G. P.; Gary, B. L.; Vanmunster, T.; Henden, A. A.; Starkey, D. R.; Kaiser, D. H.; Holtzman, J. A.; Marschall, L. A.; Michalik, T.; Wellington, T.; Paakkonen, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Journal of the American Association of Variable Star Observers, Vol 34, No. 1, p. 17-22</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005JAVSO..34...17P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...629L.121L</bibcode>
			<title>On the Eccentricity of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Vogt, Steven S.; Fischer, Debra A.; Butler, R. Paul</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 629, Issue 2, pp. L121-L124.</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...629L.121L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...629L..45C</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamic Meteorology at the Photosphere of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Cooper, Curtis S.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 629, Issue 1, pp. L45-L48.</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...629L..45C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...439..771J</bibcode>
			<title>Roche lobe effects on expanded upper atmospheres of short-periodic giant exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jaritz, G. F.; Endler, S.; Langmayr, D.; Lammer, H.; Griemeier, J.-M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Biernat, H. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 439, Issue 2, August IV 2005, pp.771-775</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...439..771J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...438.1123P</bibcode>
			<title>Doppler follow-up of OGLE planetary transit candidates in Carina</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Bouchy, F.; Melo, C.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 438, Issue 3, August II 2005, pp.1123-1140</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...438.1123P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...628L..73G</bibcode>
			<title>On the Size Distribution of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 628, Issue 1, pp. L73-L76.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...628L..73G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...627L..69F</bibcode>
			<title>Comparative Planetary Atmospheres: Models of TrES-1 and HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Marley, M. S.; Lodders, K.; Saumon, D.; Freedman, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 627, Issue 1, pp. L69-L72.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...627L..69F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...627.1011T</bibcode>
			<title>A Photometric Diagnostic to Aid in the Identification of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Tingley, Brandon; Sackett, Penny D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 627, Issue 2, pp. 1011-1018.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...627.1011T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...437.1127S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic metallicities for planet-host stars: Extending the samples</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Bento, J. P.; Almeida, P. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Ecuvillon, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 437, Issue 3, July III 2005, pp.1127-1133</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...437.1127S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Msngr.120...19P</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting Extra-solar Planets, follow the FLAMES ...</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frederic; Bouchy, Francois; Queloz, Didier; Melo, Claudio; Santos, Nuno; Udry, Stephane; Mayor, Michel; Moutou, Claire</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger (ISSN0722-6691), No.120, p. 19-21 (June 2005)</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Msngr.120...19P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...626..523C</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission from an Extrasolar Planet</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Megeath, S. Thomas; Torres, Guillermo; Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Latham, David W.; Mandushev, Georgi; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Sozzetti, Alessandro</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 626, Issue 1, pp. 523-529.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...626..523C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...625L.135B</bibcode>
			<title>A Theoretical Interpretation of the Measurements of the Secondary Eclipses of TrES-1 and HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Sudarsky, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 625, Issue 2, pp. L135-L138.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...625L.135B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...625.1004M</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Hot Massive Extrasolar Planets around Nearby Young Stars with the Adaptive Optics System NACO</title>
			<authors>Masciadri, E.; Mundt, R.; Henning, Th.; Alvarez, C.; Barrado y Navascus, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 625, Issue 2, pp. 1004-1018.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...625.1004M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...436L..47B</bibcode>
			<title>Hot-Jupiters and hot-Neptunes: A common origin?</title>
			<authors>Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T. S.; Selsis, F.; Allard, F.; Hauschildt, P. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 436, Issue 3, June IV 2005, pp.L47-L51</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...436L..47B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.359.1096B</bibcode>
			<title>A survey for planetary transits in the field of NGC 7789</title>
			<authors>Bramich, D. M.; Horne, Keith; Bond, I. A.; Street, R. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hood, B.; Cooke, J.; James, D.; Lister, T. A.; Mitchell, D.; Pearson, K.; Penny, A.; Quirrenbach, A.; Safizadeh, N.; Tsapras, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 359, Issue 3, pp. 1096-1116.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.359.1096B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...624..463G</bibcode>
			<title>A Map of the Universe</title>
			<authors>Gott, J. Richard, III; Juric, Mario; Schlegel, David; Hoyle, Fiona; Vogeley, Michael; Tegmark, Max; Bahcall, Neta; Brinkmann, Jon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 624, Issue 2, pp. 463-484.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...624..463G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...624..372K</bibcode>
			<title>A Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planet around the Star OGLE-TR-10</title>
			<authors>Konacki, Maciej; Torres, Guillermo; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Jha, Saurabh</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 624, Issue 1, pp. 372-377.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...624..372K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...623L..45L</bibcode>
			<title>A Dynamical Method for Measuring the Masses of Stars with Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Loeb, Abraham</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 623, Issue 1, pp. L45-L48.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...623L..45L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...623..472G</bibcode>
			<title>On the Period Distribution of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. Scott; Seager, S.; Mallen-Ornelas, Gabriela</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 623, Issue 1, pp. 472-481.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...623..472G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622.1118O</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect and Analytic Radial Velocity Curves for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Ohta, Yasuhiro; Taruya, Atsushi; Suto, Yasushi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 2, pp. 1118-1135.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622.1118O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622.1091J</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for Habitable ``Earths'' in Known Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Underwood, David R.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 2, pp. 1091-1101.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622.1091J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Natur.434..707S</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary science : A planet that blinks</title>
			<authors>Stapelfeldt, Karl</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 434, Issue 7034, pp. 707-708 (2005).</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Natur.434..707S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...621.1072L</bibcode>
			<title>A Comparison of Observationally Determined Radii with Theoretical Radius Predictions for Short-Period Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Wolf, Aaron; Vanmunster, Tonny; Bodenheimer, Peter; Fischer, Debra; Marcy, Geoff; Butler, Paul; Vogt, Steve</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 621, Issue 2, pp. 1072-1078.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...621.1072L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...621.1061M</bibcode>
			<title>The Challenge of Wide-Field Transit Surveys: The Case of GSC 01944-02289</title>
			<authors>Mandushev, Georgi; Torres, Guillermo; Latham, David W.; Charbonneau, David; Alonso, Roi; White, Russel J.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Dunham, Edward W.; Brown, Timothy M.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 621, Issue 2, pp. 1061-1071.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...621.1061M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...620.1043W</bibcode>
			<title>An Absence of Hot Jupiter Planets in 47 Tucanae: Results of a Wide-Field Transit Search</title>
			<authors>Weldrake, David T. F.; Sackett, Penny D.; Bridges, Terry J.; Freeman, Kenneth C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 620, Issue 2, pp. 1043-1051.</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...620.1043W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.356..955M</bibcode>
			<title>An intriguing correlation between the masses and periods of the transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, Tsevi; Zucker, Shay; Pont, Frdric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 356, Issue 3, pp. 955-957.</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.356..955M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...619..558T</bibcode>
			<title>Testing Blend Scenarios for Extrasolar Transiting Planet Candidates. II. OGLE-TR-56</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Konacki, Maciej; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Jha, Saurabh</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 619, Issue 1, pp. 558-569.</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...619..558T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005IBVS.5599....1D</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of variables.</title>
			<authors>The Editors</authors>
			<journal>IAU Inform. Bull. Var. Stars, 5599, 1-1 (2005)</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005IBVS.5599....1D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005BAVSR..54...39G</bibcode>
			<title>Aus den IBVS.</title>
			<authors>Grimm, W.</authors>
			<journal>BAV Rundbrief, 54, 39-41 (2005)</journal>
			<date>0/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005BAVSR..54...39G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...616L.167S</bibcode>
			<title>High-Resolution Spectroscopy of the Transiting Planet Host Star TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Yong, David; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Latham, David W.; Allende Prieto, Carlos; Brown, Timothy M.; Carney, Bruce W.; Laird, John B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 616, Issue 2, pp. L167-L170.</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...616L.167S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AcA....54..313U</bibcode>
			<title>The Optical Gravitational Lensing Experiment. Planetary and Low-Luminosity Object Transits in the Fields of Galactic Disk. Results of the 2003 OGLE Observing Campaigns</title>
			<authors>Udalski, A.; Szymanski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Zebrun, K.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, v.54, pp. 313-345, (2004).</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AcA....54..313U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AAS...20513513S</bibcode>
			<title>System Parameters of the Transiting Extrasolar Planet TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Serio, A. W.; Kim, J. A.; Reimer, T. W.; Rosenfield, P. A.; Vargas-Alvarez, C. A.; Orosz, J. A.; Welsh, W. F.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society Meeting 205, #135.13; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 36, p.1566</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AAS...20513513S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004IBVS.5566....1S</bibcode>
			<title>A High-Resolution Spectrum of the TrES-1 Parent Star</title>
			<authors>Strassmeier, Klaus G.; Rice, John B.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 5566, 1.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004IBVS.5566....1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...613L.153A</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-1: The Transiting Planet of a Bright K0 V Star</title>
			<authors>Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Torres, Guillermo; Latham, David W.; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Mandushev, Georgi; Belmonte, Juan A.; Charbonneau, David; Deeg, Hans J.; Dunham, Edward W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Stefanik, Robert P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 613, Issue 2, pp. L153-L156.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...613L.153A</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..14E</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit candidates in the CoRoT-SRc01 field</title>
			<authors>Erikson, A.; Santerne, A.; Renner, S.; Barge, P.; Aigrain, S.; Alapini, A.; Almenara, J.-M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Benz, W.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Daz, R. F.; Dvorak, R.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E. W.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ofir, A.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; Rgulo, C.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A14</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..14E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...81F</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Infrared Observations and Independent Validation of the Transiting Super-Earth CoRoT-7 b</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Torres, Guillermo; Pont, Frederic; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Mazeh, Tsevi; Aigrain, Suzanne; Fridlund, Malcolm; Henze, Christopher E.; Guillot, Tristan; Rauer, Heike</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 81 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...81F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A.147H</bibcode>
			<title>Optimizing exoplanet transit searches around low-mass stars with inclination constraints</title>
			<authors>Herrero, E.; Ribas, I.; Jordi, C.; Guinan, E. F.; Engle, S. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 537, id.A147</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...537A.147H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012PABei..30...48Z</bibcode>
			<title>A Statistical survey of orbital parameters of extra-solar planets system.</title>
			<authors>Zhao, J.; Zhao, G.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 30, 48-63 (2012)</journal>
			<date>0/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012PABei..30...48Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...69H</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Modeling of the Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect for Transiting Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Suto, Yasushi; Winn, Joshua N.; Taruya, Atsushi; Narita, Norio; Albrecht, Simon; Sato, Bun'ei</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 69 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...69H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A...7M</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of new high-precision transit light curves of WASP-10 b: starspot occultations, small planetary radius, and high metallicity</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Raetz, St.; Nettelmann, N.; Seeliger, M.; Adam, C.; Nowak, G.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A7</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...535A...7M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ChA&amp;A..35..409Z</bibcode>
			<title>Observation and Research of the Transits of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Zhang, Ji-Cheng; Cao, Chen; Song, Nan; Wang, Fei-Ge; Zhang, Xiao-Tong</authors>
			<journal>Chinese Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 35, Issue 4, p. 409-420.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ChA%26A..35..409Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740L..10N</bibcode>
			<title>Using Star Spots to Measure the Spin-orbit Alignment of Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip A.; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 740, Issue 1, article id. L10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740L..10N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Broadband Transmission Spectroscopy of the Super-Earth GJ 1214b Suggests a Low Mean Molecular Weight Atmosphere</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Miller-Ricci Kempton, Eliza; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman; Neilson, Hilding</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. 78 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...12B</bibcode>
			<title>The GJ1214 Super-Earth System: Stellar Variability, New Transits, and a Search for Additional Planets</title>
			<authors>Berta, Zachory K.; Charbonneau, David; Bean, Jacob; Irwin, Jonathan; Burke, Christopher J.; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Nutzman, Philip; Falco, Emilio E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 12 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...12B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AN....332..547N</bibcode>
			<title>The Young Exoplanet Transit Initiative (YETI)</title>
			<authors>Neuhuser, R.; Errmann, R.; Berndt, A.; Maciejewski, G.; Takahashi, H.; Chen, W. P.; Dimitrov, D. P.; Pribulla, T.; Nikogossian, E. H.; Jensen, E. L. N.; Marschall, L.; Wu, Z.-Y.; Kellerer, A.; Walter, F. M.; Briceo, C.; Chini, R.; Fernandez, M.; Raetz, St.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Quinn, S. N.; Niedzielski, A.; Bukowiecki, L.; Nowak, G.; Tomov, T.; Tachihara, K.; Hu, S. C.-L.; Hung, L. W.; Kjurkchieva, D. P.; Radeva, V. S.; Mihov, B. M.; Slavcheva-Mihova, L.; Bozhinova, I. N.; Budaj, J.; Vanko, M.; Kundra, E.; Hamblek, L.; Krushevska, V.; Movsessian, T.; Harutyunyan, H.; Downes, J. J.; Hernandez, J.; Hoffmeister, V. H.; Cohen, D. H.; Abel, I.; Ahmad, R.; Chapman, S.; Eckert, S.; Goodman, J.; Guerard, A.; Kim, H. M.; Koontharana, A.; Sokol, J.; Trinh, J.; Wang, Y.; Zhou, X.; Redmer, R.; Kramm, U.; Nettelmann, N.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, J.; Moualla, M.; Ginski, C.; Marka, C.; Adam, C.; Seeliger, M.; Baar, S.; Roell, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Trepl, L.; Eisenbei, T.; Fiedler, S.; Tetzlaff, N.; Schmidt, E.; Hohle, M. M.; Kitze, M.; Chakrova, N.; Grfe, C.; Schreyer, K.; Hambaryan, V. V.; Broeg, C. H.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Pandey, A. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.332, Issue 6, p.547</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AN....332..547N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734..109B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-27b: A Hot Jupiter Transiting a G Star on a 3 Day Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bky, B.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Jordn, A.; Arriagada, P.; Bayliss, D.; Kiss, L. L.; Kovcs, Gza; Quinn, S. N.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 2, article id. 109 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734..109B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733..127S</bibcode>
			<title>Starspots and Spin-orbit Alignment in the WASP-4 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Carter, Joshua A.; Osip, David J.; Fuentes, Cesar I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. 127 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733..127S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733..116B</bibcode>
			<title>Hat-P-28b and Hat-P-29b: Two Sub-Jupiter Mass Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, L. A.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J. D.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Andersen, J.; Kovcs, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Shporer, A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Bky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Fursz, G.; Quinn, S. N.; Stefanik, R. P.; Szklenr, T.; Berlind, P.; Calkins, M. L.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...53H</bibcode>
			<title>Five New Transit Epochs of the Exoplanet OGLE-TR-111b</title>
			<authors>Hoyer, S.; Rojo, P.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Daz, R. F.; Chambers, J.; Minniti, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 53 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...53H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...41M</bibcode>
			<title>High Metallicity and Non-equilibrium Chemistry in the Dayside Atmosphere of hot-Neptune GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...41M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...74V</bibcode>
			<title>Quantifying the Challenges of Detecting Unseen Planetary Companions with Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Veras, Dimitri; Ford, Eric B.; Payne, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...74V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...63W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Orientations of Exoplanets: HAT-P-4b is Prograde and HAT-P-14b is Retrograde</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Bakos, Gspr .; Hartman, Joel D.; Holman, Matthew J.; Albrecht, Simon; Crepp, Justin R.; Morton, Timothy D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 63 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...63W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...23B</bibcode>
			<title>Secondary Eclipse Photometry of WASP-4b with Warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Beerer, Ingrid M.; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Agol, Eric; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Deming, Drake; Desert, Jean-Michel; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 23 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 29, 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; Sgransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1938L</bibcode>
			<title>Forming Planetesimals by Gravitational Instability. II. How Dust Settles to its Marginally Stable State</title>
			<authors>Lee, Aaron T.; Chiang, Eugene; Asay-Davis, Xylar; Barranco, Joseph</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1938-1954 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1938L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1606W</bibcode>
			<title>Estimating the masses of extra-solar planets</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Littlefair, S. P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Dhillon, V. S.; Simpson, E. K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1606-1622.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1606W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2625M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation in exoplanet WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuhuser, R.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Ginski, Ch.; Adam, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2625-2631.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2625M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722L..75S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Transits of Limb-brightened Lines: Tentative Si IV Absorption by HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Schlawin, E.; Agol, E.; Walkowicz, L. M.; Covey, K.; Lloyd, J. P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. L75-L79 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722L..75S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..60M</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit timing variations induced by stellar binarity. The light travel time effect</title>
			<authors>Montalto, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A60</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..60M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Dsert, J.-M.; Daz, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..64L</bibcode>
			<title>Is tidal heating sufficient to explain bloated exoplanets? Consistent calculations accounting for finite initial eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Chabrier, G.; Baraffe, I.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A64</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..64L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...515A.111S</bibcode>
			<title>The PASTEL catalogue of stellar parameters</title>
			<authors>Soubiran, C.; Le Campion, J.-F.; Cayrel de Strobel, G.; Caillo, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 515, id.A111</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...515A.111S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714..462S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Apparent Orbital Inclination Change of the Extrasolar Transiting Planet TrES-2b</title>
			<authors>Scuderi, Louis J.; Dittmann, Jason A.; Males, Jared R.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Close, Laird M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 462-468 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714..462S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714...13A</bibcode>
			<title>Lack of Transit Timing Variations of OGLE-TR-111b: A Re-Analysis with Six New Epochs</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Elliot, J. L.; Seager, S.; Osip, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 13-24 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714...13A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...514A..39H</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary eclipse mapping of CoRoT-2a. Evolution, differential rotation, and spot migration</title>
			<authors>Huber, K. F.; Czesla, S.; Wolter, U.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 514, id.A39</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...514A..39H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.2111H</bibcode>
			<title>Tight constraints on the existence of additional planets around HD 189733&amp;dagger</title>
			<authors>Hrudkov, M.; Skillen, I.; Benn, C. R.; Gibson, N. P.; Pollacco, D.; Nesvorn, D.; Augusteijn, T.; Tulloch, S. M.; Joshi, Y. C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 4, pp. 2111-2119.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.2111H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010NewA...15..297P</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Transit Database. Reduction and processing of the photometric data of exoplanet transits</title>
			<authors>Poddan, Stanislav; Brt, Lubos; Pejcha, Ondrej</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 15, Issue 3, p. 297-301.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010NewA...15..297P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..374F</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Mandushev, Georgi; Spiegel, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 374-379 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..374F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1551O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Planetary Emission from the Exoplanet Tres-2 Using Spitzer/IRAC</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Harrington, Joseph; Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1551-1556 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1551O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710...97C</bibcode>
			<title>Studying the Atmosphere of the Exoplanet HAT-P-7b Via Secondary Eclipse Measurements with EPOXI, Spitzer, and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Holman, Matthew J.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Deming, Drake; A'Hearn, Michael F.; EPOXI Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 97-104 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710...97C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709.1396F</bibcode>
			<title>Transmission Spectra of Three-Dimensional Hot Jupiter Model Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Shabram, M.; Showman, A. P.; Lian, Y.; Freedman, R. S.; Marley, M. S.; Lewis, N. K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 2, pp. 1396-1406 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709.1396F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508.1011R</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing analysis of the exoplanets TrES-1 and TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Rabus, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Alonso, R.; Belmonte, J. A.; Almenara, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 2, 2009, pp.1011-1020</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508.1011R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..877B</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting the Wind-Driven Shapes of Extrasolar Giant Planets from Transit Photometry</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.; Cooper, Curtis S.; Showman, Adam P.; Hubbard, William B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 877-884 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..877B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..481C</bibcode>
			<title>High cadence near infrared timing observations of extrasolar planets. I. GJ 436b and XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Cceres, C.; Ivanov, V. D.; Minniti, D.; Naef, D.; Melo, C.; Mason, E.; Selman, F.; Pietrzynski, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.481-486</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..481C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..369B</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the transit times of CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Bean, J. L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.369-375</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..369B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.1086C</bibcode>
			<title>Benefits of Ground-Based Photometric Follow-Up for Transiting Extrasolar Planets Discovered with Kepler and CoRoT</title>
			<authors>Coln, Knicole D.; Ford, Eric B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 1086-1095 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.1086C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..769K</bibcode>
			<title>The 8 mum Phase Variation of the Hot Saturn HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Showman, Adam P.; Agol, Eric; Henry, Gregory W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 769-784 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..769K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..752L</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-16b: A New Jupiter-Like Planet Transiting a Southern Solar Analog</title>
			<authors>Lister, T. A.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Smalley, B. S.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Wilson, D. M.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, R.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Kane, S. R.; Mayor, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 752-756 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..752L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..561W</bibcode>
			<title>Transit mapping of a starspot on CoRoT-2. Probing a stellar surface with planetary transits</title>
			<authors>Wolter, U.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Huber, K. F.; Czesla, S.; Mller, H. M.; Guenther, E. W.; Hatzes, A. P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.561-564</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..561W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701L..20Z</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Sulfur Photochemistry on Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Zahnle, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.; Lodders, K.; Fortney, J. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. L20-L24 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701L..20Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.1616A</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting Transits of Planetary Companions to Giant Stars</title>
			<authors>Assef, R. J.; Gaudi, B. S.; Stanek, K. Z.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 1616-1626 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.1616A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..756D</bibcode>
			<title>A Tentative Detection of a Starspot During Consecutive Transits of an Extrasolar Planet from the Ground: No Evidence of a Double Transiting Planet System Around TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, Jason A.; Close, Laird M.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Fenwick, Mike</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 756-763 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..756D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..514M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission of XO-2b: Evidence for a Weak Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 514-520 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..514M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1797K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon - II</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1797-1804.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1797K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...500L..51L</bibcode>
			<title>GMRT radio observations of the transiting extrasolar planet HD 189733 b at 244 and 614 MHz</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Sirothia, S. K.; Gopal-Krishna; Zarka, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 500, Issue 3, 2009, pp.L51-L54</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...500L..51L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009RMxAC..35...13S</bibcode>
			<title>Starspot detection from planetary transits observed by CoRoT</title>
			<authors>Silva-Vlio, A.</authors>
			<journal>XII Latin American IAU Regional Meeting (Eds. G. Magris, G. Bruzual, &amp; L. Carigi) Revista Mexicana de Astronoma y Astrofsica (Serie de Conferencias) Vol. 35, pp. 13-18 (2009) (http://www.astroscu.unam.mx/~rmaa/)</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009RMxAC..35...13S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1230F</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Spin-Orbit Alignment: Results from the Ensemble of Rossiter-McLaughlin Observations</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1230-1240 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1230F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AN....330..475R</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit observations at the University Observatory Jena: XO-1b and TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Raetz, St.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Roell, T.; Eisenbeiss, T.; Hohle, M. M.; Tetzlaff, N.; Vanko, M.; Seifahrt, A.; Broeg, Ch.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.330, Issue 5, p.475</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AN....330..475R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..567D</bibcode>
			<title>Binarity of transit host stars. Implications for planetary parameters</title>
			<authors>Daemgen, S.; Hormuth, F.; Brandner, W.; Bergfors, C.; Janson, M.; Hippler, S.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 2, 2009, pp.567-574</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..567D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691.1145S</bibcode>
			<title>A New Spectroscopic and Photometric Analysis of the Transiting Planet Systems TrES-3 and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Korzennik, Sylvain G.; Holman, Matthew J.; Latham, David W.; Laird, John B.; Fernandez, Jos; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward; Everett, Mark E.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Belmonte, Juan A.; Deeg, Hans J.; Brown, Timothy N.; Hidas, Mrton G.; Baliber, Nairn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 2, pp. 1145-1158 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691.1145S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392..181K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 1, pp. 181-189.</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392..181K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691..866K</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of A Temperature Inversion in the Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Burrows, Adam; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 1, pp. 866-874 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...494..391R</bibcode>
			<title>A cool starspot or a second transiting planet in the TrES-1 system?</title>
			<authors>Rabus, M.; Alonso, R.; Belmonte, J. A.; Deeg, H. J.; Gilliland, R. L.; Almenara, J. M.; Brown, T. M.; Charbonneau, D.; Mandushev, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 494, Issue 1, 2009, pp.391-397</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...494..391R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493L..35D</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based K-band detection of thermal emission from the exoplanet TrES-3b</title>
			<authors>de Mooij, E. J. W.; Snellen, I. A. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 2, 2009, pp.L35-L38</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493L..35D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJS..179..484H</bibcode>
			<title>On the Absorption and Redistribution of Energy in Irradiated Planets</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 179, Issue 2, pp. 484-508.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJS..179..484H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origins of Eccentric Close-In Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Takeda, Genya; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. L29-L32.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1302B</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting the Yields of Photometric Surveys for Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1302-1330.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1302B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..649J</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Angle of Exoplanet HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.; Narita, Norio; Enya, Keigo; Williams, Peter K. G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Sato, Bun'ei; Ohta, Yasuhiro; Taruya, Atsushi; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Bakos, Gaspar; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide; Yamada, Toru; Yoshii, Yuzuru; Hidas, Marton</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 649-657.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..649J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..621F</bibcode>
			<title>Origins of Eccentric Extrasolar Planets: Testing the Planet-Planet Scattering Model</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 621-636.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..621F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..580C</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical Outcomes of Planet-Planet Scattering</title>
			<authors>Chatterjee, Sourav; Ford, Eric B.; Matsumura, Soko; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 580-602.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..580C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389..257H</bibcode>
			<title>Reflected light from 3D exoplanetary atmospheres and simulation of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Hood, Ben; Wood, Kenneth; Seager, Sara; Collier Cameron, Andrew</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 1, pp. 257-269.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389..257H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389..191P</bibcode>
			<title>Periastron precession measurements in transiting extrasolar planetary systems at the level of general relativity</title>
			<authors>Pl, Andrs; Kocsis, Bence</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 1, pp. 191-198.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389..191P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684.1427M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission of Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Burrows, Adam; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 2, pp. 1427-1432.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684.1427M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488..763H</bibcode>
			<title>Misaligned spin-orbit in the XO-3 planetary system?</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Loeillet, B.; Rabus, M.; Bonfils, X.; Moutou, C.; Boisse, I.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488..763H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1277B</bibcode>
			<title>Optical Albedo Theory of Strongly Irradiated Giant Planets: The Case of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Ibgui, L.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1277-1282.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1277B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682L..49D</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Period Variations in Extrasolar Transiting Planet OGLE-TR-111b</title>
			<authors>Daz, Rodrigo F.; Rojo, Patricio; Melita, Mario; Hoyer, Sergio; Minniti, Dante; Mauas, Pablo J. D.; Ruz, Mara Teresa</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 1, pp. L49-L52.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682L..49D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682..593M</bibcode>
			<title>MOST Space-based Photometry of the Transiting Exoplanet System HD 189733: Precise Timing Measurements for Transits across an Active Star</title>
			<authors>Miller-Ricci, Eliza; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Kuschnig, Rainer; Croll, Bryce; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rucinski, Slavek M.; Walker, Gordon A. H.; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 1, pp. 593-601.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682..593M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682..586M</bibcode>
			<title>MOST Space-based Photometry of the Transiting Exoplanet System HD 209458: Transit Timing to Search for Additional Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller-Ricci, Eliza; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Guenther, David B.; Kuschnig, Rainer; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rucinski, Slavek M.; Walker, Gordon A. H.; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 1, pp. 586-592.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682..586M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681.1631J</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 2, pp. 1631-1638.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681.1631J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008NewAR..52..154S</bibcode>
			<title>Extra-solar planets: Detection methods and results</title>
			<authors>Santos, Nuno C.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 52, Issue 2-5, p. 154-166.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008NewAR..52..154S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678L.129C</bibcode>
			<title>Inverting Phase Functions to Map Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. L129-L132.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678L.129C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1419F</bibcode>
			<title>A Unified Theory for the Atmospheres of the Hot and Very Hot Jupiters: Two Classes of Irradiated Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Lodders, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1419-1435.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1419F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482L..25B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. III. The spectroscopic transit of CoRoT-Exo-2b with SOPHIE and HARPS</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Queloz, D.; Deleuil, M.; Loeillet, B.; Hatzes, A. P.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hbrard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 3, 2008, pp.L25-L28</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482L..25B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482L..21A</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. II. CoRoT-Exo-2b: a transiting planet around an active G star</title>
			<authors>Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Ollivier, M.; Moutou, C.; Rouan, D.; Deeg, H. J.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Kabath, P.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Shporer, A.; Schneider, J.; Stecklum, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 3, 2008, pp.L21-L24</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482L..21A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...481..529L</bibcode>
			<title>Refined parameters and spectroscopic transit of the super-massive planet HD 147506b</title>
			<authors>Loeillet, B.; Shporer, A.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Mazeh, T.; Beuzit, J. L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; da Silva, R.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Ecuvillon, A.; Forveille, T.; Galland, F.; Gallenne, A.; Hbrard, G.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Sivan, J. P.; Santos, N. C.; Tsodikovich, Y.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 481, Issue 2, 2008, pp.529-533</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...481..529L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008PASP..120..317N</bibcode>
			<title>Design Considerations for a Ground-Based Transit Search for Habitable Planets Orbiting M Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Nutzman, Philip; Charbonneau, David</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 120, issue 865, pp.317-327</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008PASP..120..317N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...674..482S</bibcode>
			<title>The Mid-Infrared Spectrum of the Transiting Exoplanet HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Swain, M. R.; Bouwman, J.; Akeson, R. L.; Lawler, S.; Beichman, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 674, Issue 1, pp. 482-497.</journal>
			<date>2/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...674..482S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..513D</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Dynamics of Short-Period Extrasolar Gas Giant Planets. I. Dependence of Nightside Temperature on Opacity</title>
			<authors>Dobbs-Dixon, Ian; Lin, D. N. C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 513-525.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..513D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008OEJV...95...81P</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting Explanet Light Curve Solution by Phoebe Code</title>
			<authors>Poddany, S.</authors>
			<journal>Open European Journal on Variable Stars, Vol. 95. Proceedings of the 39th Conference on Variable Stars Research, p.81</journal>
			<date>0/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008OEJV...95...81P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008BAVSR..57..199B</bibcode>
			<title>BAV-Veraenderlichenbeobachter-Treffen 2008 in Hartha.</title>
			<authors>Braune, W.</authors>
			<journal>BAV Rundbrief, 57, 199 (2008)</journal>
			<date>0/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008BAVSR..57..199B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008BAVSM.191....1H</bibcode>
			<title>Three New Variable Stars in the Field of the RR Lyrae Star GY Peg.</title>
			<authors>Hambsch, F.-J.; Vandenbroere, J.</authors>
			<journal>Berliner Arbeitsgemeinschaft fr Veraenderliche Sterne - Mitteilungen, 191, 1-6 (2008)</journal>
			<date>0/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008BAVSM.191....1H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671L.173B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-5b: A Jupiter-like Hot Jupiter Transiting a Bright Star</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Shporer, A.; Pl, A.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Mazeh, T.; Ofir, A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Esquerdo, G.; Sipocz, B.; Kovcs, Gbor; Stefanik, R.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 2, pp. L173-L176.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671L.173B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671.2129C</bibcode>
			<title>Looking for Super-Earths in the HD 189733 System: A Search for Transits in MOST Space-based Photometry</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Gladman, Brett; Miller-Ricci, Eliza; Sasselov, Dimitar; Walker, Gordon A. H.; Kuschnig, Rainer; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rucinski, Slavek M.; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 2, pp. 2129-2138.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671.2129C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671..861H</bibcode>
			<title>Two Classes of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. 861-871.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671..861H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...476.1347P</bibcode>
			<title>Hubble Space Telescope time-series photometry of the planetary transit of HD 189733: no moon, no rings, starspots</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Gilliland, R. L.; Moutou, C.; Charbonneau, D.; Bouchy, F.; Brown, T. M.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 476, Issue 3, December IV 2007, pp.1347-1355</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...476.1347P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1324S</bibcode>
			<title>On Constraining a Transiting Exoplanet's Rotation Rate with Its Transit Spectrum</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Haiman, Zoltn; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1335.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1324S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...669.1298F</bibcode>
			<title>Shrinking Binary and Planetary Orbits by Kozai Cycles with Tidal Friction</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel; Tremaine, Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 669, Issue 2, pp. 1298-1315.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...669.1298F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..729F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting and predicting the yield of transit surveys: giant planets in the OGLE fields</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Morello, V.; Pont, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 2, November IV 2007, pp.729-746</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..729F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..359G</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting low-frequency radio fluxes of known extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Griemeier, J.-M.; Zarka, P.; Spreeuw, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 1, November III 2007, pp.359-368</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..359G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...668L.171B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectral Models of the Planet HD 209458b with a Thermal Inversion and Water Emission Bands</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Knutson, H. A.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 668, Issue 2, pp. L171-L174.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...668L.171B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...474..301B</bibcode>
			<title>A method to detect H{2} in the atmosphere of transiting extrasolar planets using the EUV spectrum</title>
			<authors>Barthlmy, M.; Lilensten, J.; Parkinson, C. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 474, Issue 1, October IV 2007, pp.301-306</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...474..301B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007OEJV...67....1H</bibcode>
			<title>Two new variable stars in the field of the Transiting Extrasolar planet TRES-1 (GSC 2652-1324)</title>
			<authors>Hambsch, F.-J.</authors>
			<journal>Open European Journal on Variable Stars, vol. 0067, Issue 1, p.1</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007OEJV...67....1H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ARA&amp;A..45..397U</bibcode>
			<title>Statistical Properties of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Udry, Stphane; Santos, Nuno C.</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, vol. 45, Issue 1, pp.397-439</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ARA%26A..45..397U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...666..475M</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Planet Taxonomy: A New Statistical Approach</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 666, Issue 1, pp. 475-485.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...666..475M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...472..329E</bibcode>
			<title>Roche lobe effects on the atmospheric loss from ``Hot Jupiters''</title>
			<authors>Erkaev, N. V.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Lammer, H.; Selsis, F.; Langmayr, D.; Jaritz, G. F.; Biernat, H. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 472, Issue 1, September II 2007, pp.329-334</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...472..329E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASJ...59..763N</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Rossiter-Laughlin Effect in the Transiting Exoplanetary System TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Narita, N.; Enya, K.; Sato, B.; Ohta, Y.; Winn, J. N.; Suto, Y.; Taruya, A.; Turner, E. L.; Aoki, W.; Yoshii, M.; Yamada, T.; Tamura, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.59, No.4, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASJ...59..763N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379.1097B</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared spectroscopic search for the close orbiting planet HD 75289b</title>
			<authors>Barnes, J. R.; Leigh, C. J.; Jones, H. R. A.; Barman, Travis S.; Pinfield, D. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Jenkins, J. S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 379, Issue 3, pp. 1097-1107.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379.1097B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379..641C</bibcode>
			<title>Hot nights on extrasolar planets: mid-infrared phase variations of hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Cowan, N. B.; Agol, E.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 379, Issue 2, pp. 641-646.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379..641C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...665..754F</bibcode>
			<title>Cassini States with Dissipation: Why Obliquity Tides Cannot Inflate Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Johnson, Eric T.; Goodman, Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 665, Issue 1, pp. 754-766.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...665..754F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664.1199R</bibcode>
			<title>Toward Eclipse Mapping of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Rauscher, Emily; Menou, Kristen; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Cho, James Y.-K.; Hansen, Bradley M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 2, pp. 1199-1209.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664.1199R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664.1185H</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve (TLC) Project. VI. Three Transits of the Exoplanet TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Fernandez, Jose; Everett, Mark E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 2, pp. 1185-1189.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664.1185H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379L..11S</bibcode>
			<title>A method for the direct determination of the surface gravities of transiting extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Wheatley, Peter J.; Sams, Giles</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 379, Issue 1, pp. L11-L15.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379L..11S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...663L..37O</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-3: A Nearby, Massive, Transiting Hot Jupiter in a 31 Hour Orbit</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Bakos, Gspr .; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Brown, Timothy M.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Kovcs, Gza; Everett, Mark E.; Baliber, Nairn; Hidas, Mrton G.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Deeg, Hans J.; Belmonte, Juan A.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Stefanik, Robert P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 663, Issue 1, pp. L37-L40.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...663L..37O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASP..119..616K</bibcode>
			<title>A Ground-based Search for Thermal Emission from the Exoplanet TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Richardson, L. Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 119, Issue 856, pp. 616-622.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASP..119..616K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007Natur.447..691H</bibcode>
			<title>The hottest planet</title>
			<authors>Harrington, Joseph; Luszcz, Statia; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Richardson, L. Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 447, Issue 7145, pp. 691-693 (2007).</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007Natur.447..691H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.378..148D</bibcode>
			<title>3.8-mum photometry during the secondary eclipse of the extrasolar planet HD209458b</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Richardson, L. Jeremy; Harrington, Joseph</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 378, Issue 1, pp. 148-152.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.378..148D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662L.115R</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiter Variability in Eclipse Depth</title>
			<authors>Rauscher, Emily; Menou, Kristen; Cho, James Y.-K.; Seager, Sara; Hansen, Bradley M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 2, pp. L115-L118.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662L.115R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662..658O</bibcode>
			<title>Outcome of Six Candidate Transiting Planets from a TrES Field in Andromeda</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Latham, David W.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Torres, Guillermo; Everett, Mark E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 1, pp. 658-668.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662..658O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...661..502B</bibcode>
			<title>Possible Solutions to the Radius Anomalies of Transiting Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Hubbard, W. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 661, Issue 1, pp. 502-514.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...661..502B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..850D</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude Photometry for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Candidates. II. Transits of OGLE-TR-113-b in the Optical and Near-IR</title>
			<authors>Daz, Rodrigo F.; Ramrez, Sebastin; Fernndez, Jos Miguel; Gallardo, Jos; Gieren, Wolfgang; Ivanov, Valentin D.; Mauas, Pablo; Minniti, Dante; Pietrzynski, Grzegorz; Prez, Felipe; Ruz, Mara Teresa; Udalski, Andrzej; Zoccali, Manuela</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 850-857.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..850D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..823M</bibcode>
			<title>Formation of Earth-like Planets During and After Giant Planet Migration</title>
			<authors>Mandell, Avi M.; Raymond, Sean N.; Sigurdsson, Steinn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 823-844.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..823M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...659.1661F</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Radii across Five Orders of Magnitude in Mass and Stellar Insolation: Application to Transits</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Marley, M. S.; Barnes, J. W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 659, Issue 2, pp. 1661-1672.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...659.1661F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658L.115G</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer Spectrum of the Exoplanet HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Grillmair, C. J.; Charbonneau, D.; Burrows, A.; Armus, L.; Stauffer, J.; Meadows, V.; Van Cleve, J.; Levine, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. L115-L118.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658L.115G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1328C</bibcode>
			<title>Looking for Giant Earths in the HD 209458 System: A Search for Transits in MOST Space-based Photometry</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Kuschnig, Rainer; Walker, Andrew; Gladman, Brett; Sasselov, Dimitar; Cameron, Chris; Walker, Gordon A. H.; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rucinski, Slavek M.; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1328-1339.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1328C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1322C</bibcode>
			<title>Precise Radius Estimates for the Exoplanets WASP-1b and WASP-2b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Everett, Mark E.; Latham, David W.; Holman, Matthew J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1322-1327.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1322C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AJ....133.1828W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. V. System Parameters and Stellar Rotation Period of HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Henry, Gregory W.; Roussanova, Anna; Enya, Keigo; Yoshii, Yuzuru; Shporer, Avi; Mazeh, Tsevi; Johnson, John Asher; Narita, Norio; Suto, Yasushi</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 133, Issue 4, pp. 1828-1835 (2007).</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AJ....133.1828W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...657.1098W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. III. Tres Transits of TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Roussanova, Anna</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 657, Issue 2, pp. 1098-1106.</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...657.1098W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...464.1133C</bibcode>
			<title>Detecting companions to extrasolar planets using mutual events</title>
			<authors>Cabrera, J.; Schneider, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 464, Issue 3, March IV 2007, pp.1133-1138</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...464.1133C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007Natur.445..892R</bibcode>
			<title>A spectrum of an extrasolar planet</title>
			<authors>Richardson, L. Jeremy; Deming, Drake; Horning, Karen; Seager, Sara; Harrington, Joseph</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 445, Issue 7130, pp. 892-895 (2007).</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007Natur.445..892R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.375..307S</bibcode>
			<title>K-band transit and secondary eclipse photometry of exoplanet OGLE-TR-113b</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.; Covino, E.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 375, Issue 1, pp. 307-312.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.375..307S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...656..552B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-1b: A Large-Radius, Low-Density Exoplanet Transiting One Member of a Stellar Binary</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Noyes, R. W.; Kovcs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Torres, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sato, B.; Johnson, J. A.; P l, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Stanek, K. Z.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.; Sipocz, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 656, Issue 1, pp. 552-559.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...656..552B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...655.1103H</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. IV. Five Transits of the Exoplanet OGLE-TR-10b</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Fuentes, Cesar I.; Hartman, Joel D.; Stanek, K. Z.; Torres, Guillermo; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Gaudi, B. Scott; Jones, R. Lynne; Fraser, Wesley</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 655, Issue 2, pp. 1103-1109.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...655.1103H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.374..941A</bibcode>
			<title>A limit on the presence of Earth-mass planets around a Sun-like star</title>
			<authors>Agol, Eric; Steffen, Jason H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 374, Issue 3, pp. 941-948.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.374..941A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...655..564K</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Limb-Darkening to Refine the Properties of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Noyes, Robert W.; Brown, Timothy M.; Gilliland, Ronald L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 655, Issue 1, pp. 564-575.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...655..564K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...655..550G</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for the Characterization and Confirmation of Transiting Exoplanets via the Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. Scott; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 655, Issue 1, pp. 550-563.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...655..550G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...461.1185L</bibcode>
			<title>A diagram to determine the evaporation status of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 461, Issue 3, January III 2007, pp.1185-1193</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...461.1185L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1621P</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy with Small Telescopes</title>
			<authors>Paczynski, Bohdan</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 850, pp. 1621-1625.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1621P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652L.137F</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Constraints on Trojans of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. L137-L140.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652L.137F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652.1715H</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. I. Four Consecutive Transits of the Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Bakos, Gspr A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Hergenrother, Carl; Everett, Mark E.; Pl, Andrs</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. 1715-1723.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652.1715H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...460..251M</bibcode>
			<title>On the age of stars harboring transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Melo, C.; Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 460, Issue 1, December II 2006, pp.251-256</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...460..251M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.373L..55B</bibcode>
			<title>A near-infrared spectroscopic detection of the brown dwarf in the post common envelope binary WD0137-349</title>
			<authors>Burleigh, M. R.; Hogan, E.; Dobbie, P. D.; Napiwotzki, R.; Maxted, P. F. L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 373, Issue 1, pp. L55-L59.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.373L..55B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.373..231P</bibcode>
			<title>The effect of red noise on planetary transit detection</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Zucker, Shay; Queloz, Didier</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 373, Issue 1, pp. 231-242.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.373..231P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.372.1117C</bibcode>
			<title>The SuperWASP wide-field exoplanetary transit survey: candidates from fields 23 h &lt; RA &lt; 03 h</title>
			<authors>Christian, D. J.; Pollacco, D. L.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Keenan, F. P.; Clarkson, W. I.; Collier Cameron, A.; Kane, S. R.; Lister, T. A.; West, R. G.; Enoch, B.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J.; Ryans, R.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 372, Issue 3, pp. 1117-1128.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.372.1117C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652..746F</bibcode>
			<title>The Influence of Atmospheric Dynamics on the Infrared Spectra and Light Curves of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Cooper, C. S.; Showman, A. P.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 1, pp. 746-757.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652..746F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...651L..61O</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-2: The First Transiting Planet in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Brown, Timothy M.; Trauger, John T.; Belmonte, Juan A.; Rabus, Markus; Almenara, Jos M.; Alonso, Roi; Deeg, Hans J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Falco, Emilio E.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Roussanova, Anna; Stefanik, Robert P.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 651, Issue 1, pp. L61-L64.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...651L..61O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...458..997S</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical abundances for the transiting planet host stars OGLE-TR-10, 56, 111, 113, 132, and TrES-1. Abundances in different galactic populations</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Ecuvillon, A.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Ribeiro, J. P.; Jorge, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 458, Issue 3, November II 2006, pp.997-1005</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...458..997S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006Sci...314..623H</bibcode>
			<title>The Phase-Dependent Infrared Brightness of the Extrasolar Planet upsilo Andromedae b</title>
			<authors>Harrington, Joseph; Hansen, Brad M.; Luszcz, Statia H.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Menou, Kristen; Cho, James Y.-K.; Richardson, L. Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 314, Issue 5799, pp. 623-626 (2006).</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006Sci...314..623H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1407P</bibcode>
			<title>The WASP Project and the SuperWASP Cameras</title>
			<authors>Pollacco, D. L.; Skillen, I.; Collier Cameron, A.; Christian, D. J.; Hellier, C.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Street, R. A.; West, R. G.; Anderson, D.; Clarkson, W. I.; Deeg, H.; Enoch, B.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hodgkin, S.; Horne, K.; Kane, S. R.; Keenan, F. P.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J.; Parley, N. R.; Ryans, R. S. I.; Smalley, B.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 848, pp. 1407-1418.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1407P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASJ...58..869U</bibcode>
			<title>An Extrasolar Planet Transit Search with Subaru Suprime-Cam</title>
			<authors>Urakawa, Seitaro; Yamada, Toru; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Itoh, Yoichi; Mukai, Tadashi; Tamura, Motohide; Wang, Yiping</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.58, No.5, pp.869-881</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASJ...58..869U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650.1160B</bibcode>
			<title>Refined Parameters of the Planet Orbiting HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Knutson, H.; Pont, F.; Moutou, C.; Charbonneau, D.; Shporer, A.; Bouchy, F.; Everett, M.; Hergenrother, C.; Latham, D. W.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Noyes, R. W.; Queloz, D.; Pl, A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 2, pp. 1160-1171.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650.1160B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650.1140B</bibcode>
			<title>Theory for the Secondary Eclipse Fluxes, Spectra, Atmospheres, and Light Curves of Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Sudarsky, D.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 2, pp. 1140-1149.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650.1140B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...650..394A</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Structure and Radius Evolution of Irradiated Gas Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Arras, Phil; Bildsten, Lars</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 650, Issue 1, pp. 394-407.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...650..394A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1048C</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamics and Disequilibrium Carbon Chemistry in Hot Jupiter Atmospheres, with Application to HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Cooper, Curtis S.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1048-1063.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1048C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1020W</bibcode>
			<title>Resolving the Surfaces of Extrasolar Planets with Secondary Eclipse Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Williams, Peter K. G.; Charbonneau, David; Cooper, Curtis S.; Showman, Adam P.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1020-1027.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1020W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...649.1010J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of Known Exoplanetary Systems Based on Measured Stellar Properties</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick; Underwood, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 649, Issue 2, pp. 1010-1019.</journal>
			<date>10/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...649.1010J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1302H</bibcode>
			<title>PlanetPol: A Very High Sensitivity Polarimeter</title>
			<authors>Hough, J. H.; Lucas, P. W.; Bailey, J. A.; Tamura, M.; Hirst, E.; Harrison, D.; Bartholomew-Biggs, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 847, pp. 1302-1318.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1302H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ARA&amp;A..44..269W</bibcode>
			<title>First Fruits of the Spitzer Space Telescope: Galactic and Solar System Studies</title>
			<authors>Werner, Michael; Fazio, Giovanni; Rieke, George; Roellig, Thomas L.; Watson, Dan M.</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, vol. 44, Issue 1, pp.269-321</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ARA%26A..44..269W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...648.1228M</bibcode>
			<title>A Transiting Planet of a Sun-like Star</title>
			<authors>McCullough, P. R.; Stys, J. E.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Johns-Krull, C. M.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Bye, B. A.; Dodd, C.; Fleming, S. W.; Pinnick, A.; Bissinger, R.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 648, Issue 2, pp. 1228-1238.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...648.1228M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....132.1267S</bibcode>
			<title>No Detectable H+3 Emission from the Atmospheres of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Shkolnik, Evgenya; Gaidos, Eric; Moskovitz, Nick</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 132, Issue 3, pp. 1267-1274.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....132.1267S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.370.1379J</bibcode>
			<title>Data analysis on the extrasolar planets using robust clustering</title>
			<authors>Jiang, Ing-Guey; Yeh, Li-Chin; Hung, Wen-Liang; Yang, Miin-Shen</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 370, Issue 3, pp. 1379-1392.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.370.1379J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...647.1437M</bibcode>
			<title>A Spitzer IRAC Search for Substellar Companions of the Debris Disk Star &amp;epsil Eridani</title>
			<authors>Marengo, M.; Megeath, S. T.; Fazio, G. G.; Stapelfeldt, K. R.; Werner, M. W.; Backman, D. E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 647, Issue 2, pp. 1437-1451.</journal>
			<date>8/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...647.1437M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118..947T</bibcode>
			<title>Astrophysics in 2005</title>
			<authors>Trimble, Virginia; Aschwanden, Markus J.; Hansen, Carl J.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 845, pp. 947-1047.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118..947T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006MNRAS.369.1267D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of a binary or planetary system during encounters with a third inclined body</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 369, Issue 3, pp. 1267-1280.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006MNRAS.369.1267D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...646..505B</bibcode>
			<title>Catalog of Nearby Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Butler, R. P.; Wright, J. T.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Vogt, S. S.; Tinney, C. G.; Jones, H. R. A.; Carter, B. D.; Johnson, J. A.; McCarthy, C.; Penny, A. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 646, Issue 1, pp. 505-522.</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...646..505B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...453L..21G</bibcode>
			<title>A correlation between the heavy element content of transiting extrasolar planets and the metallicity of their parent stars</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Iro, N.; Melo, C.; Ribas, I.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 453, Issue 2, July II 2006, pp.L21-L24</journal>
			<date>7/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...453L..21G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644.1237O</bibcode>
			<title>Rejecting Astrophysical False Positives from the TrES Transiting Planet Survey: The Example of GSC 03885-00829</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Torres, Guillermo; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Latham, David W.; Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Creevey, Orlagh L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 2, pp. 1237-1245.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644.1237O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...644..560D</bibcode>
			<title>Strong Infrared Emission from the Extrasolar Planet HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Harrington, Joseph; Seager, Sara; Richardson, L. Jeremy</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 644, Issue 1, pp. 560-564.</journal>
			<date>6/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...644..560D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006NewA...11..490I</bibcode>
			<title>Are we far from testing general relativity with the transitting extrasolar planet HD 209458b `Osiris'?</title>
			<authors>Iorio, L.</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 11, Issue 7, p. 490-494.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006NewA...11..490I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...642..495F</bibcode>
			<title>Atmosphere, Interior, and Evolution of the Metal-rich Transiting Planet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Saumon, D.; Marley, M. S.; Lodders, K.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 642, Issue 1, pp. 495-504.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...642..495F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...642..488S</bibcode>
			<title>Search for Planetary Candidates within the OGLE Stars</title>
			<authors>Silva, Adriana V. R.; Cruz, Patricia C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 642, Issue 1, pp. 488-494.</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...642..488S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006A&amp;A...450..825S</bibcode>
			<title>High resolution spectroscopy of stars with transiting planets. The cases of OGLE-TR-10, 56, 111, 113, and TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Pont, F.; Melo, C.; Israelian, G.; Bouchy, F.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Guillot, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 450, Issue 2, May I 2006, pp.825-831</journal>
			<date>5/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006A%26A...450..825S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...641..565S</bibcode>
			<title>The Effect of the Transit of Venus on ACRIM's Total Solar Irradiance Measurements: Implications for Transit Studies of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Schneider, G.; Pasachoff, J. M.; Willson, Richard C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 641, Issue 1, pp. 565-571.</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...641..565S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006AJ....131.2274S</bibcode>
			<title>Chemical Composition of the Planet-harboring Star TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Yong, David; Carney, Bruce W.; Laird, John B.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 131, Issue 4, pp. 2274-2289.</journal>
			<date>4/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006AJ....131.2274S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...638..488B</bibcode>
			<title>High-Contrast Imaging from Space: Speckle Nulling in a Low-Aberration Regime</title>
			<authors>Bord, Pascal J.; Traub, Wesley A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 638, Issue 1, pp. 488-498.</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...638..488B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...637.1102R</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. V. Identifying Very Metal-rich Stars with Low-Resolution Spectra: Finding Planet-Search Targets</title>
			<authors>Robinson, Sarah E.; Strader, Jay; Ammons, S. Mark; Laughlin, Gregory; Fischer, Debra</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 637, Issue 2, pp. 1102-1112.</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...637.1102R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...637.1094F</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. III. Short-Period Planets Orbiting HD 149143 and HD 109749</title>
			<authors>Fischer, Debra A.; Laughlin, Gregory; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Johnson, John A.; Henry, Gregory W.; McCarthy, Chris; Ammons, Mark; Robinson, Sarah; Strader, Jay; Valenti, Jeff A.; McCullough, P. R.; Charbonneau, David; Haislip, Joshua; Knutson, Heather A.; Reichart, Daniel E.; McGee, Padric; Monard, Berto; Wright, Jason T.; Ida, Shigeru; Sato, Bun'ei; Minniti, Dante</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 637, Issue 2, pp. 1094-1101.</journal>
			<date>2/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...637.1094F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006RPPh...69..119P</bibcode>
			<title>Planet formation and migration</title>
			<authors>Papaloizou, John C. B.; Terquem, Caroline</authors>
			<journal>Reports on Progress in Physics, Volume 69, Issue 1, pp. 119-180 (2006).</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006RPPh...69..119P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...636..445C</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Photometry of the Core-dominated Planet HD 149026b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; Bakos, Gspr; Falco, Emilio E.; Holman, Matthew J.; Noyes, Robert W.; Csk, Balzs; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 636, Issue 1, pp. 445-452.</journal>
			<date>1/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...636..445C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.364.1091K</bibcode>
			<title>Results from the Wide Angle Search for Planets Prototype (WASP0) - III. Planet hunting in the Draco field</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Collier Cameron, Andrew; Horne, Keith; James, David; Lister, T. A.; Pollacco, Don L.; Street, Rachel A.; Tsapras, Yiannis</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 364, Issue 3, pp. 1091-1103.</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.364.1091K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.364..649F</bibcode>
			<title>The effect of condensates on the characterization of transiting planet atmospheres with transmission spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 364, Issue 2, pp. 649-653.</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.364..649F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...634.1385M</bibcode>
			<title>A Moving Cluster Distance to the Exoplanet 2M1207b in the TW Hydrae Association</title>
			<authors>Mamajek, Eric E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 634, Issue 2, pp. 1385-1394.</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...634.1385M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...444L..15B</bibcode>
			<title>ELODIE metallicity-biased search for transiting Hot Jupiters. II. A very hot Jupiter transiting the bright K star HD 189733</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Udry, S.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pont, F.; Iribarne, N.; da Silva, R.; Ilovaisky, S.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 444, Issue 1, December II 2005, pp.L15-L19</journal>
			<date>12/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...444L..15B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.364L..96S</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the transit times of TrES-1b</title>
			<authors>Steffen, Jason H.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 364, Issue 1, pp. L96-L100.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.364L..96S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.364..325A</bibcode>
			<title>Candidate extrasolar planet transits discovered in the Microlensing Observations in Astrophysics-I Galactic bulge data</title>
			<authors>Abe, F.; Bond, I. A.; Furuta, Y.; Hearnshaw, J. B.; Kilmartin, P. M.; Kurata, Y.; Masuda, K.; Matsubara, Y.; Muraki, Y.; Noda, S.; Okajima, K.; Rattenbury, N. J.; Sako, T.; Sullivan, D. J.; Sumi, T.; Tristram, P.; Wood, J. N.; Yanagisawa, T.; Yock, P. C. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 364, Issue 1, pp. 325-334.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.364..325A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...633..465S</bibcode>
			<title>The N2K Consortium. II. A Transiting Hot Saturn around HD 149026 with a Large Dense Core</title>
			<authors>Sato, Bun'ei; Fischer, Debra A.; Henry, Gregory W.; Laughlin, Greg; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Vogt, Steven S.; Bodenheimer, Peter; Ida, Shigeru; Toyota, Eri; Wolf, Aaron; Valenti, Jeff A.; Boyd, Louis J.; Johnson, John A.; Wright, Jason T.; Ammons, Mark; Robinson, Sarah; Strader, Jay; McCarthy, Chris; Tah, K. L.; Minniti, Dante</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 633, Issue 1, pp. 465-473.</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...633..465S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...443..609S</bibcode>
			<title>On the ages of exoplanet host stars</title>
			<authors>Saffe, C.; Gmez, M.; Chavero, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 443, Issue 2, November IV 2005, pp.609-626</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...443..609S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...442..731G</bibcode>
			<title>On the potential of extrasolar planet transit surveys</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Courbin, F.; Magain, P.; Borguet, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 442, Issue 2, November I 2005, pp.731-744</journal>
			<date>11/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...442..731G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Sci...310..251S</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Planets: Constraints for Planet Formation Models</title>
			<authors>Santos, Nuno C.; Benz, Willy; Mayor, Michel</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 310, Issue 5746, pp. 251-255 (2005).</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Sci...310..251S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005PASP..117.1021S</bibcode>
			<title>Astrometric Methods and Instrumentation to Identify and Characterize Extrasolar Planets: A Review</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 117, Issue 836, pp. 1021-1048.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005PASP..117.1021S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.363..211S</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision K-band photometry of the secondary eclipse of HD 209458</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 363, Issue 1, pp. 211-215.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.363..211S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...632.1132B</bibcode>
			<title>Phase-Dependent Properties of Extrasolar Planet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Barman, Travis S.; Hauschildt, Peter H.; Allard, France</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 632, Issue 2, pp. 1132-1139.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...632.1132B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...632.1122S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Dayside Thermal Emission of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Seager, S.; Richardson, L. J.; Hansen, B. M. S.; Menou, K.; Cho, J. Y.-K.; Deming, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 632, Issue 2, pp. 1122-1131.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...632.1122S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...631.1215W</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of Spin-Orbit Alignment in an Extrasolar Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Noyes, Robert W.; Holman, Matthew J.; Charbonneau, David; Ohta, Yasuhiro; Taruya, Atsushi; Suto, Yasushi; Narita, Norio; Turner, Edwin L.; Johnson, John A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 631, Issue 2, pp. 1215-1226.</journal>
			<date>10/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...631.1215W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.362..460P</bibcode>
			<title>Fast identification of transits from light-curves</title>
			<authors>Protopapas, Pavlos; Jimenez, Raul; Alcock, Charles</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 362, Issue 2, pp. 460-468.</journal>
			<date>9/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.362..460P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005IBVS.5648....1S</bibcode>
			<title>Erratum: ``A High-Resolution Spectrum of the TrES-1 Parent Star''</title>
			<authors>Strassmeier, Klaus G.; Rice, John B.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 5648, 1.</journal>
			<date>9/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005IBVS.5648....1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005PASP..117..783M</bibcode>
			<title>The XO Project: Searching for Transiting Extrasolar Planet Candidates</title>
			<authors>McCullough, P. R.; Stys, J. E.; Valenti, J. A.; Fleming, S. W.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 117, Issue 834, pp. 783-795.</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005PASP..117..783M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005JAVSO..34...17P</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary Transits of the Trans-Atlantic Exoplanet Survey Candidate TrES-1b</title>
			<authors>Price, A.; Bissinger, R.; Laughlin, G. P.; Gary, B. L.; Vanmunster, T.; Henden, A. A.; Starkey, D. R.; Kaiser, D. H.; Holtzman, J. A.; Marschall, L. A.; Michalik, T.; Wellington, T.; Paakkonen, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Journal of the American Association of Variable Star Observers, Vol 34, No. 1, p. 17-22</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005JAVSO..34...17P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...629L.121L</bibcode>
			<title>On the Eccentricity of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Vogt, Steven S.; Fischer, Debra A.; Butler, R. Paul</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 629, Issue 2, pp. L121-L124.</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...629L.121L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...629L..45C</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamic Meteorology at the Photosphere of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Cooper, Curtis S.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 629, Issue 1, pp. L45-L48.</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...629L..45C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...439..771J</bibcode>
			<title>Roche lobe effects on expanded upper atmospheres of short-periodic giant exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jaritz, G. F.; Endler, S.; Langmayr, D.; Lammer, H.; Griemeier, J.-M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Biernat, H. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 439, Issue 2, August IV 2005, pp.771-775</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...439..771J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...438.1123P</bibcode>
			<title>Doppler follow-up of OGLE planetary transit candidates in Carina</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Bouchy, F.; Melo, C.; Santos, N. C.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 438, Issue 3, August II 2005, pp.1123-1140</journal>
			<date>8/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...438.1123P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...628L..73G</bibcode>
			<title>On the Size Distribution of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 628, Issue 1, pp. L73-L76.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...628L..73G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...627L..69F</bibcode>
			<title>Comparative Planetary Atmospheres: Models of TrES-1 and HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Marley, M. S.; Lodders, K.; Saumon, D.; Freedman, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 627, Issue 1, pp. L69-L72.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...627L..69F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...627.1011T</bibcode>
			<title>A Photometric Diagnostic to Aid in the Identification of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Tingley, Brandon; Sackett, Penny D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 627, Issue 2, pp. 1011-1018.</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...627.1011T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...437.1127S</bibcode>
			<title>Spectroscopic metallicities for planet-host stars: Extending the samples</title>
			<authors>Santos, N. C.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Bento, J. P.; Almeida, P. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Ecuvillon, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 437, Issue 3, July III 2005, pp.1127-1133</journal>
			<date>7/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...437.1127S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Msngr.120...19P</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting Extra-solar Planets, follow the FLAMES ...</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frederic; Bouchy, Francois; Queloz, Didier; Melo, Claudio; Santos, Nuno; Udry, Stephane; Mayor, Michel; Moutou, Claire</authors>
			<journal>The Messenger (ISSN0722-6691), No.120, p. 19-21 (June 2005)</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Msngr.120...19P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...626..523C</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission from an Extrasolar Planet</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Megeath, S. Thomas; Torres, Guillermo; Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Latham, David W.; Mandushev, Georgi; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Sozzetti, Alessandro</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 626, Issue 1, pp. 523-529.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...626..523C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...625L.135B</bibcode>
			<title>A Theoretical Interpretation of the Measurements of the Secondary Eclipses of TrES-1 and HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Sudarsky, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 625, Issue 2, pp. L135-L138.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...625L.135B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...625.1004M</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Hot Massive Extrasolar Planets around Nearby Young Stars with the Adaptive Optics System NACO</title>
			<authors>Masciadri, E.; Mundt, R.; Henning, Th.; Alvarez, C.; Barrado y Navascus, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 625, Issue 2, pp. 1004-1018.</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...625.1004M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005A&amp;A...436L..47B</bibcode>
			<title>Hot-Jupiters and hot-Neptunes: A common origin?</title>
			<authors>Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T. S.; Selsis, F.; Allard, F.; Hauschildt, P. H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 436, Issue 3, June IV 2005, pp.L47-L51</journal>
			<date>6/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005A%26A...436L..47B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.359.1096B</bibcode>
			<title>A survey for planetary transits in the field of NGC 7789</title>
			<authors>Bramich, D. M.; Horne, Keith; Bond, I. A.; Street, R. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hood, B.; Cooke, J.; James, D.; Lister, T. A.; Mitchell, D.; Pearson, K.; Penny, A.; Quirrenbach, A.; Safizadeh, N.; Tsapras, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 359, Issue 3, pp. 1096-1116.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.359.1096B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...624..463G</bibcode>
			<title>A Map of the Universe</title>
			<authors>Gott, J. Richard, III; Juric, Mario; Schlegel, David; Hoyle, Fiona; Vogeley, Michael; Tegmark, Max; Bahcall, Neta; Brinkmann, Jon</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 624, Issue 2, pp. 463-484.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...624..463G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...624..372K</bibcode>
			<title>A Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planet around the Star OGLE-TR-10</title>
			<authors>Konacki, Maciej; Torres, Guillermo; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Jha, Saurabh</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 624, Issue 1, pp. 372-377.</journal>
			<date>5/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...624..372K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...623L..45L</bibcode>
			<title>A Dynamical Method for Measuring the Masses of Stars with Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Loeb, Abraham</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 623, Issue 1, pp. L45-L48.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...623L..45L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...623..472G</bibcode>
			<title>On the Period Distribution of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. Scott; Seager, S.; Mallen-Ornelas, Gabriela</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 623, Issue 1, pp. 472-481.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...623..472G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622.1118O</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect and Analytic Radial Velocity Curves for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Ohta, Yasuhiro; Taruya, Atsushi; Suto, Yasushi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 2, pp. 1118-1135.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622.1118O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...622.1091J</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for Habitable ``Earths'' in Known Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Underwood, David R.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 622, Issue 2, pp. 1091-1101.</journal>
			<date>4/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...622.1091J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005Natur.434..707S</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary science : A planet that blinks</title>
			<authors>Stapelfeldt, Karl</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 434, Issue 7034, pp. 707-708 (2005).</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005Natur.434..707S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...621.1072L</bibcode>
			<title>A Comparison of Observationally Determined Radii with Theoretical Radius Predictions for Short-Period Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Wolf, Aaron; Vanmunster, Tonny; Bodenheimer, Peter; Fischer, Debra; Marcy, Geoff; Butler, Paul; Vogt, Steve</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 621, Issue 2, pp. 1072-1078.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...621.1072L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...621.1061M</bibcode>
			<title>The Challenge of Wide-Field Transit Surveys: The Case of GSC 01944-02289</title>
			<authors>Mandushev, Georgi; Torres, Guillermo; Latham, David W.; Charbonneau, David; Alonso, Roi; White, Russel J.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Dunham, Edward W.; Brown, Timothy M.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 621, Issue 2, pp. 1061-1071.</journal>
			<date>3/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...621.1061M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...620.1043W</bibcode>
			<title>An Absence of Hot Jupiter Planets in 47 Tucanae: Results of a Wide-Field Transit Search</title>
			<authors>Weldrake, David T. F.; Sackett, Penny D.; Bridges, Terry J.; Freeman, Kenneth C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 620, Issue 2, pp. 1043-1051.</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...620.1043W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005MNRAS.356..955M</bibcode>
			<title>An intriguing correlation between the masses and periods of the transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, Tsevi; Zucker, Shay; Pont, Frdric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 356, Issue 3, pp. 955-957.</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005MNRAS.356..955M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005ApJ...619..558T</bibcode>
			<title>Testing Blend Scenarios for Extrasolar Transiting Planet Candidates. II. OGLE-TR-56</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Konacki, Maciej; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Jha, Saurabh</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 619, Issue 1, pp. 558-569.</journal>
			<date>1/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005ApJ...619..558T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005IBVS.5599....1D</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of variables.</title>
			<authors>The Editors</authors>
			<journal>IAU Inform. Bull. Var. Stars, 5599, 1-1 (2005)</journal>
			<date>2/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005IBVS.5599....1D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2005BAVSR..54...39G</bibcode>
			<title>Aus den IBVS.</title>
			<authors>Grimm, W.</authors>
			<journal>BAV Rundbrief, 54, 39-41 (2005)</journal>
			<date>0/2005</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2005BAVSR..54...39G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...616L.167S</bibcode>
			<title>High-Resolution Spectroscopy of the Transiting Planet Host Star TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Yong, David; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Latham, David W.; Allende Prieto, Carlos; Brown, Timothy M.; Carney, Bruce W.; Laird, John B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 616, Issue 2, pp. L167-L170.</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...616L.167S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AcA....54..313U</bibcode>
			<title>The Optical Gravitational Lensing Experiment. Planetary and Low-Luminosity Object Transits in the Fields of Galactic Disk. Results of the 2003 OGLE Observing Campaigns</title>
			<authors>Udalski, A.; Szymanski, M. K.; Kubiak, M.; Pietrzynski, G.; Soszynski, I.; Zebrun, K.; Szewczyk, O.; Wyrzykowski, L.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, v.54, pp. 313-345, (2004).</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AcA....54..313U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004AAS...20513513S</bibcode>
			<title>System Parameters of the Transiting Extrasolar Planet TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Serio, A. W.; Kim, J. A.; Reimer, T. W.; Rosenfield, P. A.; Vargas-Alvarez, C. A.; Orosz, J. A.; Welsh, W. F.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society Meeting 205, #135.13; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 36, p.1566</journal>
			<date>12/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004AAS...20513513S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004IBVS.5566....1S</bibcode>
			<title>A High-Resolution Spectrum of the TrES-1 Parent Star</title>
			<authors>Strassmeier, Klaus G.; Rice, John B.</authors>
			<journal>Information Bulletin on Variable Stars, 5566, 1.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004IBVS.5566....1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2004ApJ...613L.153A</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-1: The Transiting Planet of a Bright K0 V Star</title>
			<authors>Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Torres, Guillermo; Latham, David W.; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Mandushev, Georgi; Belmonte, Juan A.; Charbonneau, David; Deeg, Hans J.; Dunham, Edward W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Stefanik, Robert P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 613, Issue 2, pp. L153-L156.</journal>
			<date>10/2004</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2004ApJ...613L.153A</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
