<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63L..67N</bibcode>
			<title>XO-2b: a Prograde Planet with Negligible Eccentricity and an Additional Radial Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sato, Bun'ei; Harakawa, Hiroki; Fukui, Akihiko; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.6, pp.L67-L71</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63L..67N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....9F</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Atmospheric Characterization of Giant Planet Kepler-12b: An Inflated Radius Outlier</title>
			<authors>Fortney, Jonathan J.; Demory, Brice-Olivier; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Rowe, Jason; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Buchhave, Lars A.; Ciardi, David; Gautier, Thomas N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Nutzman, Philip; Jenkins, Jon M.; Howard, Andrew; Charbonneau, David; Knutson, Heather A.; Howell, Steve B.; Everett, Mark; Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Deming, Drake; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Latham, David W.; Miller, Neil; Seager, Sara; Fischer, Debra A.; Koch, David; Lissauer, Jack J.; Haas, Michael R.; Still, Martin; Lucas, Philip; Gillon, Michael; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 9 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....9F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...59H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-32b and HAT-P-33b: Two Highly Inflated Hot Jupiters Transiting High-jitter Stars</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; B&#233;ky, B.; Quinn, S. N.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; Szklen&#225;r, T.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...59H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...35N</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Secondary Eclipses of WASP-18b</title>
			<authors>Nymeyer, Sarah; Harrington, Joseph; Hardy, Ryan A.; Stevenson, Kevin B.; Campo, Christopher J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Collier-Cameron, Andrew; Loredo, Thomas J.; Blecic, Jasmina; Bowman, William C.; Britt, Christopher B. T.; Cubillos, Patricio; Hellier, Coel; Gillon, Michael; Maxted, Pierre F. L.; Hebb, Leslie; Wheatley, Peter J.; Pollacco, Don; Anderson, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. 35 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A.116D</bibcode>
			<title>Prospecting transit duration variations in extrasolar planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Damiani, C.; Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A116</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...535A.116D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534L...6T</bibcode>
			<title>The time dependence of hot Jupiters' orbital inclinations</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.L6</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534L...6T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...86E</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-35b, WASP-48b, and HAT-P-30b/WASP-51b: Two New Planets and an Independent Discovery of a Hat Planet</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Faedi, F.; Gillon, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lister, T. A.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bouchy, F.; Bento, J.; Butters, O.; Fossati, L.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Jehen, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Simpson, E.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 3, article id. 86 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142...86E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..60A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-31b: a low-density planet transiting a metal-poor, late-F-type dwarf star</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Gillon, M.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233; gransan, D.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A60</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..60A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..40F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-39b: a highly inflated Saturn-mass planet orbiting a late G-type star</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Anderson, D. R.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Boisse, I.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..40F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..179C</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light-curve Project. XIV. Confirmation of Anomalous Radii for the Exoplanets TrES-4b, HAT-P-3b, and WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Chan, Tucker; Ingemyr, Mikael; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Esquerdo, Gil; Everett, Mark</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 6, article id. 179 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..179C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..63S</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. II. KOI-428b: a hot Jupiter transiting a subgiant F-star</title>
			<authors>Santerne, A.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Moutou, C.; H&#233;brard, G.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A63</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..63S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729L...7L</bibcode>
			<title>On the Anomalous Radii of the Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Crismani, Matteo; Adams, Fred C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. L7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729L...7L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..152T</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiter Magnetospheres</title>
			<authors>Trammell, George B.; Arras, Phil; Li, Zhi-Yun</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 152 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..152T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..138H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-26b: A Low-density Neptune-mass Planet Transiting a K Star</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Kipping, D. M.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Quinn, S. N.; Buchhave, L. A.; B&#233;ky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Perumpilly, G.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 138 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...75I</bibcode>
			<title>Explorations into the Viability of Coupled Radius-orbit Evolutionary Models for Inflated Planets</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...75I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...23B</bibcode>
			<title>Secondary Eclipse Photometry of WASP-4b with Warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Beerer, Ingrid M.; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Agol, Eric; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Deming, Drake; Desert, Jean-Michel; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 23 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62L..61N</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect of the Transiting Exoplanet XO-4b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.6, pp.L61--L65</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62L..61N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.2017K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-24b: An Inflated Hot Jupiter on a 3.36 Day Period Transiting a Hot, Metal-poor Star</title>
			<authors>Kipping, D. M.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; B&#233;ky, B.; Perumpilly, G.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 2017-2028 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.2017K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725..261M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Inference of Thermal Inversions in Hot Jupiter Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 1, pp. 261-274 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725..261M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.2007M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-22 b: A Transiting "Hot Jupiter" Planet in a Hierarchical Triple System</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Cegla, H.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 2007-2012 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.2007M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.1929L</bibcode>
			<title>Radio Observations of HD 80606 Near Planetary Periastron</title>
			<authors>Lazio, T. Joseph W.; Shankland, P. D.; Farrell, W. M.; Blank, D. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 1929-1933 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.1929L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407..507C</bibcode>
			<title>Line-profile tomography of exoplanet transits - II. A gas-giant planet transiting a rapidly rotating A5 star</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Guenther, E.; Smalley, B.; McDonald, I.; Hebb, L.; Andersen, J.; Augusteijn, Th.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Cochran, W. D.; Endl, M.; Fossey, S. J.; Hartmann, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Telting, J.; Waldmann, I. P.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 1, pp. 507-514.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407..507C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..97G</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XII. CoRoT-12b: a short-period low-density planet transiting a solar analog star</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Hatzes, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Fridlund, M.; Deleuil, M.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Barnes, S. I.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J. C.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H&#233; brard, G.; Jorda, L.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A97</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..97G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..653N</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-Orbit Alignment of the TrES-4 Transiting Planetary System and Possible Additional Radial-Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Winn, Joshua N.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.3, pp.653--660</journal>
			<date>6/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..653N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..64L</bibcode>
			<title>Is tidal heating sufficient to explain bloated exoplanets? Consistent calculations accounting for finite initial eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Chabrier, G.; Baraffe, I.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A64</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..64L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714L.238B</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating Hot Jupiters with Ohmic Dissipation</title>
			<authors>Batygin, Konstantin; Stevenson, David J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 714, Issue 2, pp. L238-L243 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714L.238B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712...38E</bibcode>
			<title>An a Priori Investigation of Astrophysical False Positives in Ground-Based Transiting Planet Surveys</title>
			<authors>Evans, Tom M.; Sackett, Penny D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 38-51 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712...38E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..374F</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Mandushev, Georgi; Spiegel, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 374-379 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..374F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1551O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Planetary Emission from the Exoplanet Tres-2 Using Spitzer/IRAC</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Harrington, Joseph; Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1551-1556 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1551O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710...97C</bibcode>
			<title>Studying the Atmosphere of the Exoplanet HAT-P-7b Via Secondary Eclipse Measurements with EPOXI, Spitzer, and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Holman, Matthew J.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Deming, Drake; A'Hearn, Michael F.; the EPOXI Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 97-104 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710...97C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...511A...3G</bibcode>
			<title>The thermal emission of the young and massive planet CoRoT-2b at 4.5 and 8 mum</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Lanotte, A. A.; Barman, T.; Miller, N.; Demory, B.-O.; Deleuil, M.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Bouchy, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Deeg, H. J.; Fortney, J. J.; Fridlund, M.; Harrington, J.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 511, id.A3</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...511A...3G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..458H</bibcode>
			<title>Analytic Description of the Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect for Transiting Exoplanets: Cross-Correlation Method and Comparison with Simulated Data</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Suto, Yasushi; Taruya, Atsushi; Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 458-469 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..458H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..149S</bibcode>
			<title>Models of Neptune-Mass Exoplanets: Emergent Fluxes and Albedos</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent; Hubeny, Ivan; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 149-158 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..149S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PABei..28...53J</bibcode>
			<title>Proper motions and the frontier of studies on the Galaxy.</title>
			<authors>Jin, W.-J.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 28, 53-71 (2010)</journal>
			<date>0/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PABei..28...53J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..785H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-12b: A Low-Density Sub-Saturn Mass Planet Transiting a Metal-Poor K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; P&#225;l, A.; Latham, D. W.; Sipocz, B.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 785-796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..785H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASJ...61L..35N</bibcode>
			<title>First Evidence of a Retrograde Orbit of a Transiting Exoplanet HAT-P-7b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.61, No.5, pp.L35-L40</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASJ...61L..35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..385L</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and evolution of the first CoRoT exoplanets: probing the brown dwarf/planet overlapping mass regime</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.385-389</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..385L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..752L</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-16b: A New Jupiter-Like Planet Transiting a Southern Solar Analog</title>
			<authors>Lister, T. A.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Smalley, B. S.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Wilson, D. M.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, R.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Kane, S. R.; Mayor, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 752-756 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..752L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1237B</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Orbits of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Brown, Robert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1237-1249 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1237B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.397.1591A</bibcode>
			<title>An iterative filter to reconstruct planetary transit signals in the presence of stellar variability</title>
			<authors>Alapini, A.; Aigrain, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 397, Issue 3, pp. 1591-1598.</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.397.1591A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701L..20Z</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Sulfur Photochemistry on Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Zahnle, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.; Lodders, K.; Fortney, J. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. L20-L24 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701L..20Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..514M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission of XO-2b: Evidence for a Weak Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 514-520 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..514M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700.1921I</bibcode>
			<title>Coupled Evolution with Tides of the Radius and Orbit of Transiting Giant Planets: General Results</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 1921-1932 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700.1921I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..965R</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Proper Motion and the Timing of Planetary Transits</title>
			<authors>Rafikov, Roman R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 965-970 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..965R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699.1487S</bibcode>
			<title>Can TiO Explain Thermal Inversions in the Upper Atmospheres of Irradiated Giant Planets?</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Silverio, Katie; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 2, pp. 1487-1500 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699.1487S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..564S</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Circulation of Hot Jupiters: Coupled Radiative-Dynamical General Circulation Model Simulations of HD 189733b and HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Showman, Adam P.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Lian, Yuan; Marley, Mark S.; Freedman, Richard S.; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 564-584 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..564S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...697.1256H</bibcode>
			<title>Heavy-element Enrichment of a Jupiter-mass Protoplanet as a Function of Orbital Location</title>
			<authors>Helled, R.; Schubert, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 697, Issue 2, pp. 1256-1262 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...697.1256H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AJ....137.4834W</bibcode>
			<title>The Low Density Transiting Exoplanet WASP-15b</title>
			<authors>West, R. G.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Spano, M.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 137, Issue 6, pp. 4834-4836 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AJ....137.4834W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...500L..45M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of orbital parameter changes in the TrES-2 exoplanet?</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 500, Issue 3, 2009, pp.L45-L49</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...500L..45M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Natur.459..543S</bibcode>
			<title>The changing phases of extrasolar planet CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Snellen, Ignas A. G.; de Mooij, Ernst J. W.; Albrecht, Simon</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 459, Issue 7246, pp. 543-545 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Natur.459..543S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..567D</bibcode>
			<title>Binarity of transit host stars. Implications for planetary parameters</title>
			<authors>Daemgen, S.; Hormuth, F.; Brandner, W.; Bergfors, C.; Janson, M.; Hippler, S.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 2, 2009, pp.567-574</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..567D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...497..545S</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE2-TR-L9b: an exoplanet transiting a rapidly rotating F3 star</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.; Koppenhoefer, J.; van der Burg, R. F. J.; Dreizler, S.; Greiner, J.; de Hoon, M. D. J.; Husser, T. O.; Kr&#252;hler, T.; Saglia, R. P.; Vuijsje, F. N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 497, Issue 2, 2009, pp.545-550</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...497..545S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691.1145S</bibcode>
			<title>A New Spectroscopic and Photometric Analysis of the Transiting Planet Systems TrES-3 and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Korzennik, Sylvain G.; Holman, Matthew J.; Latham, David W.; Laird, John B.; Fernandez, Jos&#233;; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward; Everett, Mark E.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Belmonte, Juan A.; Deeg, Hans J.; Brown, Timothy N.; Hidas, M&#225;rton G.; Baliber, Nairn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 2, pp. 1145-1158 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691.1145S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691..866K</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of A Temperature Inversion in the Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Burrows, Adam; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 1, pp. 866-874 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690L..89H</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-7: A Bright Transiting-Exoplanet System in the Southern Hemisphere</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Alsubai, K.; Bentley, S. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, R.; Haswell, C. A.; Joshi, Y. C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Ryans, R.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 690, Issue 1, pp. L89-L91 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690L..89H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MmSAI..80..318S</bibcode>
			<title>Probing structural and evolutionary properties of exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Latham, D. W.; Torres, G.; Carney, B. W.; Laird, J. B.; Stefanik, R. P.; Boss, A. P.; Charbonneau, D.; O'Donovan, F. T.; Holman, M. J.; Winn, J. N.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ&#224; Astronomica Italiana, v.80, p.318 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MmSAI..80..318S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689..492K</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Orbital Parameters through Planetary Transit Monitoring</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 1, pp. 492-498.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689..492K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1191L</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Radii of Extrasolar Giant Planets: the Cases of TrES-4, XO-3b, and HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>Liu, Xin; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1191-1200.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1191L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1341C</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Knutson, Heather A.; Barman, Travis; Allen, Lori E.; Mayor, Michel; Megeath, S. Thomas; Queloz, Didier; Udry, St&#233;phane</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1341-1348.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1341C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1302B</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting the Yields of Photometric Surveys for Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1302-1330.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1302B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...683.1076W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. IX. Evidence for a Smaller Radius of the Exoplanet XO-3b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Torres, Guillermo; McCullough, Peter; Johns-Krull, Christopher; Latham, David W.; Shporer, Avi; Mazeh, Tsevi; Garcia-Melendo, Enrique; Foote, Cindy; Esquerdo, Gil; Everett, Mark</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 683, Issue 2, pp. 1076-1084.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...683.1076W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1277B</bibcode>
			<title>Optical Albedo Theory of Strongly Irradiated Giant Planets: The Case of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Ibgui, L.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1277-1282.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1277B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681.1631J</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 2, pp. 1631-1638.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681.1631J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681..636I</bibcode>
			<title>Parameters and Predictions for the Long-Period Transiting Planet HD 17156b</title>
			<authors>Irwin, Jonathan; Charbonneau, David; Nutzman, Philip; Welsh, William F.; Rajan, Abhijith; Hidas, Marton; Brown, Timothy M.; Lister, Timothy A.; Davies, Donald; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 1, pp. 636-643.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681..636I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.387L...4A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-5b: a dense, very hot Jupiter transiting a 12th-mag Southern-hemisphere star</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Wilson, D. M.; Collier Cameron, A.; Smalley, B.; Lister, T. A.; Bentley, S. J.; Blecha, A.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Kane, S. R.; Marmier, M.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pollacco, D. L.; Pont, F.; Ryans, R.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 387, Issue 1, pp. L4-L7.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.387L...4A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1419F</bibcode>
			<title>A Unified Theory for the Atmospheres of the Hot and Very Hot Jupiters: Two Classes of Irradiated Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Lodders, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1419-1435.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1419F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677L.117F</bibcode>
			<title>Radiative Thrusters on Close-in Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. L117-L120.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677L.117F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677..657J</bibcode>
			<title>XO-3b: A Massive Planet in an Eccentric Orbit Transiting an F5 V Star</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Prato, L.; Bissinger, R.; Fleenor, M.; Foote, C. N.; Garcia-Melendo, E.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Mallia, F.; Masi, G.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. 657-670.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677..657J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482..299U</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE-TR-211 - a new transiting inflated hot Jupiter from the OGLE survey and ESO LP666 spectroscopic follow-up program</title>
			<authors>Udalski, A.; Pont, F.; Naef, D.; Melo, C.; Bouchy, F.; Santos, N. C.; Moutou, C.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Gieren, W.; Gillon, M.; Hoyer, S.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Minniti, D.; Pietrzynski, G.; Queloz, D.; Ramirez, S.; Ruiz, M. T.; Shporer, A.; Tamuz, O.; Udry, S.; Zoccali, M.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Soszyn ski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 1, 2008, pp.299-304</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482..299U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.384.1097K</bibcode>
			<title>SuperWASP-N extrasolar planet candidates from fields 06h &lt; RA &lt; 16h</title>
			<authors>Kane, S. R.; Clarkson, W. I.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Christian, D. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Lister, T. A.; Street, R. A.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Keenan, F. P.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J.; Parley, N. R.; Pollacco, D. L.; Ryans, R.; Skillen, I.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 384, Issue 3, pp. 1097-1108.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.384.1097K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...675L.113W</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-4b: A 12th Magnitude Transiting Hot Jupiter in the Southern Hemisphere</title>
			<authors>Wilson, D. M.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Smalley, B.; Lister, T. A.; Bentley, S. J.; Blecha, A.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Kane, S. R.; Marmier, M.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pollacco, D.; Pont, F.; Ryans, R.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 675, Issue 2, pp. L113-L116.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...675L.113W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673L..79N</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-6b: A Hot Jupiter Transiting a Bright F Star</title>
			<authors>Noyes, R. W.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; P&#225;l, A.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Latham, D. W.; Fern&#225;ndez, J. M.; Fischer, D. A.; Butler, R. P.; Marcy, G. W.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Sasselov, D. D.; Sato, B.; Stefanik, R.; Holman, M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. L79-L82.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673L..79N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671L.173B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-5b: A Jupiter-like Hot Jupiter Transiting a Bright Star</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Shporer, A.; P&#225;l, A.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Latham, D. W.; Mazeh, T.; Ofir, A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Esquerdo, G.; Sipocz, B.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 2, pp. L173-L176.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671L.173B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671..861H</bibcode>
			<title>Two Classes of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. 861-871.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671..861H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...670L..41K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-4b: A Metal-rich Low-Density Transiting Hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Kov&#225;cs, G.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Sozzetti, A.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Butler, R. P.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Fern&#225;ndez, J. M.; Esquerdo, G.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; P&#225;l, A.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 670, Issue 1, pp. L41-L44.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...670L..41K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667L.195M</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-4: A Transiting Hot Jupiter of Very Low Density</title>
			<authors>Mandushev, Georgi; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Torres, Guillermo; Latham, David W.; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Dunham, Edward W.; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Fern&#225;ndez, Jos&#233; M.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Brown, Timothy M.; Rabus, Markus; Belmonte, Juan A.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 2, pp. L195-L198.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667L.195M</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63L..67N</bibcode>
			<title>XO-2b: a Prograde Planet with Negligible Eccentricity and an Additional Radial Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sato, Bun'ei; Harakawa, Hiroki; Fukui, Akihiko; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.6, pp.L67-L71</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63L..67N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....9F</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Atmospheric Characterization of Giant Planet Kepler-12b: An Inflated Radius Outlier</title>
			<authors>Fortney, Jonathan J.; Demory, Brice-Olivier; D&#233;sert, Jean-Michel; Rowe, Jason; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Buchhave, Lars A.; Ciardi, David; Gautier, Thomas N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Nutzman, Philip; Jenkins, Jon M.; Howard, Andrew; Charbonneau, David; Knutson, Heather A.; Howell, Steve B.; Everett, Mark; Fressin, Fran&#231;ois; Deming, Drake; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Latham, David W.; Miller, Neil; Seager, Sara; Fischer, Debra A.; Koch, David; Lissauer, Jack J.; Haas, Michael R.; Still, Martin; Lucas, Philip; Gillon, Michael; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 9 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197....9F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...59H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-32b and HAT-P-33b: Two Highly Inflated Hot Jupiters Transiting High-jitter Stars</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; B&#233;ky, B.; Quinn, S. N.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; Szklen&#225;r, T.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...59H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...35N</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Secondary Eclipses of WASP-18b</title>
			<authors>Nymeyer, Sarah; Harrington, Joseph; Hardy, Ryan A.; Stevenson, Kevin B.; Campo, Christopher J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Collier-Cameron, Andrew; Loredo, Thomas J.; Blecic, Jasmina; Bowman, William C.; Britt, Christopher B. T.; Cubillos, Patricio; Hellier, Coel; Gillon, Michael; Maxted, Pierre F. L.; Hebb, Leslie; Wheatley, Peter J.; Pollacco, Don; Anderson, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. 35 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A.116D</bibcode>
			<title>Prospecting transit duration variations in extrasolar planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Damiani, C.; Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A116</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...535A.116D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534L...6T</bibcode>
			<title>The time dependence of hot Jupiters' orbital inclinations</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.L6</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534L...6T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...86E</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-35b, WASP-48b, and HAT-P-30b/WASP-51b: Two New Planets and an Independent Discovery of a Hat Planet</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Faedi, F.; Gillon, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lister, T. A.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bouchy, F.; Bento, J.; Butters, O.; Fossati, L.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Jehen, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Simpson, E.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 3, article id. 86 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142...86E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..60A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-31b: a low-density planet transiting a metal-poor, late-F-type dwarf star</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Gillon, M.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233; gransan, D.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A60</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..60A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..40F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-39b: a highly inflated Saturn-mass planet orbiting a late G-type star</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Anderson, D. R.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Boisse, I.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..40F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..179C</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light-curve Project. XIV. Confirmation of Anomalous Radii for the Exoplanets TrES-4b, HAT-P-3b, and WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Chan, Tucker; Ingemyr, Mikael; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Esquerdo, Gil; Everett, Mark</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 6, article id. 179 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..179C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..63S</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. II. KOI-428b: a hot Jupiter transiting a subgiant F-star</title>
			<authors>Santerne, A.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Moutou, C.; H&#233;brard, G.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A63</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..63S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729L...7L</bibcode>
			<title>On the Anomalous Radii of the Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Crismani, Matteo; Adams, Fred C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. L7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729L...7L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..152T</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiter Magnetospheres</title>
			<authors>Trammell, George B.; Arras, Phil; Li, Zhi-Yun</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 152 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..152T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..138H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-26b: A Low-density Neptune-mass Planet Transiting a K Star</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Kipping, D. M.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Isaacson, H.; Quinn, S. N.; Buchhave, L. A.; B&#233;ky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Perumpilly, G.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 138 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...75I</bibcode>
			<title>Explorations into the Viability of Coupled Radius-orbit Evolutionary Models for Inflated Planets</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...75I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...23B</bibcode>
			<title>Secondary Eclipse Photometry of WASP-4b with Warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Beerer, Ingrid M.; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Agol, Eric; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Deming, Drake; Desert, Jean-Michel; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 23 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62L..61N</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect of the Transiting Exoplanet XO-4b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.6, pp.L61--L65</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62L..61N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.2017K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-24b: An Inflated Hot Jupiter on a 3.36 Day Period Transiting a Hot, Metal-poor Star</title>
			<authors>Kipping, D. M.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; B&#233;ky, B.; Perumpilly, G.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 2017-2028 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.2017K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725..261M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Inference of Thermal Inversions in Hot Jupiter Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 1, pp. 261-274 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725..261M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.2007M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-22 b: A Transiting "Hot Jupiter" Planet in a Hierarchical Triple System</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Cegla, H.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 2007-2012 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.2007M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.1929L</bibcode>
			<title>Radio Observations of HD 80606 Near Planetary Periastron</title>
			<authors>Lazio, T. Joseph W.; Shankland, P. D.; Farrell, W. M.; Blank, D. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 1929-1933 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.1929L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407..507C</bibcode>
			<title>Line-profile tomography of exoplanet transits - II. A gas-giant planet transiting a rapidly rotating A5 star</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Guenther, E.; Smalley, B.; McDonald, I.; Hebb, L.; Andersen, J.; Augusteijn, Th.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Cochran, W. D.; Endl, M.; Fossey, S. J.; Hartmann, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Telting, J.; Waldmann, I. P.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 1, pp. 507-514.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407..507C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..97G</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XII. CoRoT-12b: a short-period low-density planet transiting a solar analog star</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Hatzes, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Fridlund, M.; Deleuil, M.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Barnes, S. I.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J. C.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H&#233; brard, G.; Jorda, L.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A97</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..97G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..653N</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-Orbit Alignment of the TrES-4 Transiting Planetary System and Possible Additional Radial-Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Winn, Joshua N.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.3, pp.653--660</journal>
			<date>6/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..653N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..64L</bibcode>
			<title>Is tidal heating sufficient to explain bloated exoplanets? Consistent calculations accounting for finite initial eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Chabrier, G.; Baraffe, I.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A64</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..64L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714L.238B</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating Hot Jupiters with Ohmic Dissipation</title>
			<authors>Batygin, Konstantin; Stevenson, David J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 714, Issue 2, pp. L238-L243 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714L.238B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712...38E</bibcode>
			<title>An a Priori Investigation of Astrophysical False Positives in Ground-Based Transiting Planet Surveys</title>
			<authors>Evans, Tom M.; Sackett, Penny D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 38-51 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712...38E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..374F</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Mandushev, Georgi; Spiegel, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 374-379 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..374F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1551O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Planetary Emission from the Exoplanet Tres-2 Using Spitzer/IRAC</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Harrington, Joseph; Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1551-1556 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1551O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710...97C</bibcode>
			<title>Studying the Atmosphere of the Exoplanet HAT-P-7b Via Secondary Eclipse Measurements with EPOXI, Spitzer, and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Holman, Matthew J.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Deming, Drake; A'Hearn, Michael F.; the EPOXI Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 97-104 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710...97C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...511A...3G</bibcode>
			<title>The thermal emission of the young and massive planet CoRoT-2b at 4.5 and 8 mum</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Lanotte, A. A.; Barman, T.; Miller, N.; Demory, B.-O.; Deleuil, M.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Bouchy, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Deeg, H. J.; Fortney, J. J.; Fridlund, M.; Harrington, J.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 511, id.A3</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...511A...3G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..458H</bibcode>
			<title>Analytic Description of the Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect for Transiting Exoplanets: Cross-Correlation Method and Comparison with Simulated Data</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Suto, Yasushi; Taruya, Atsushi; Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 458-469 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..458H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..149S</bibcode>
			<title>Models of Neptune-Mass Exoplanets: Emergent Fluxes and Albedos</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent; Hubeny, Ivan; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 149-158 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..149S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PABei..28...53J</bibcode>
			<title>Proper motions and the frontier of studies on the Galaxy.</title>
			<authors>Jin, W.-J.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 28, 53-71 (2010)</journal>
			<date>0/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PABei..28...53J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..785H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-12b: A Low-Density Sub-Saturn Mass Planet Transiting a Metal-Poor K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; P&#225;l, A.; Latham, D. W.; Sipocz, B.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 785-796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..785H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASJ...61L..35N</bibcode>
			<title>First Evidence of a Retrograde Orbit of a Transiting Exoplanet HAT-P-7b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.61, No.5, pp.L35-L40</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASJ...61L..35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..385L</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and evolution of the first CoRoT exoplanets: probing the brown dwarf/planet overlapping mass regime</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.385-389</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..385L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703..752L</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-16b: A New Jupiter-Like Planet Transiting a Southern Solar Analog</title>
			<authors>Lister, T. A.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Smalley, B. S.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Wilson, D. M.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, R.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Kane, S. R.; Mayor, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 1, pp. 752-756 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703..752L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1237B</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Orbits of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Brown, Robert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1237-1249 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1237B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.397.1591A</bibcode>
			<title>An iterative filter to reconstruct planetary transit signals in the presence of stellar variability</title>
			<authors>Alapini, A.; Aigrain, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 397, Issue 3, pp. 1591-1598.</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.397.1591A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701L..20Z</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Sulfur Photochemistry on Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Zahnle, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.; Lodders, K.; Fortney, J. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. L20-L24 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701L..20Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..514M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission of XO-2b: Evidence for a Weak Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 514-520 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..514M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700.1921I</bibcode>
			<title>Coupled Evolution with Tides of the Radius and Orbit of Transiting Giant Planets: General Results</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 1921-1932 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700.1921I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..965R</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Proper Motion and the Timing of Planetary Transits</title>
			<authors>Rafikov, Roman R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 965-970 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..965R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699.1487S</bibcode>
			<title>Can TiO Explain Thermal Inversions in the Upper Atmospheres of Irradiated Giant Planets?</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Silverio, Katie; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 2, pp. 1487-1500 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699.1487S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699..564S</bibcode>
			<title>Atmospheric Circulation of Hot Jupiters: Coupled Radiative-Dynamical General Circulation Model Simulations of HD 189733b and HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Showman, Adam P.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Lian, Yuan; Marley, Mark S.; Freedman, Richard S.; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 1, pp. 564-584 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...699..564S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...697.1256H</bibcode>
			<title>Heavy-element Enrichment of a Jupiter-mass Protoplanet as a Function of Orbital Location</title>
			<authors>Helled, R.; Schubert, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 697, Issue 2, pp. 1256-1262 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...697.1256H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AJ....137.4834W</bibcode>
			<title>The Low Density Transiting Exoplanet WASP-15b</title>
			<authors>West, R. G.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Spano, M.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 137, Issue 6, pp. 4834-4836 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AJ....137.4834W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...500L..45M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of orbital parameter changes in the TrES-2 exoplanet?</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 500, Issue 3, 2009, pp.L45-L49</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...500L..45M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Natur.459..543S</bibcode>
			<title>The changing phases of extrasolar planet CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Snellen, Ignas A. G.; de Mooij, Ernst J. W.; Albrecht, Simon</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 459, Issue 7246, pp. 543-545 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Natur.459..543S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..567D</bibcode>
			<title>Binarity of transit host stars. Implications for planetary parameters</title>
			<authors>Daemgen, S.; Hormuth, F.; Brandner, W.; Bergfors, C.; Janson, M.; Hippler, S.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 2, 2009, pp.567-574</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..567D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...497..545S</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE2-TR-L9b: an exoplanet transiting a rapidly rotating F3 star</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.; Koppenhoefer, J.; van der Burg, R. F. J.; Dreizler, S.; Greiner, J.; de Hoon, M. D. J.; Husser, T. O.; Kr&#252;hler, T.; Saglia, R. P.; Vuijsje, F. N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 497, Issue 2, 2009, pp.545-550</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...497..545S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691.1145S</bibcode>
			<title>A New Spectroscopic and Photometric Analysis of the Transiting Planet Systems TrES-3 and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Korzennik, Sylvain G.; Holman, Matthew J.; Latham, David W.; Laird, John B.; Fernandez, Jos&#233;; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward; Everett, Mark E.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Belmonte, Juan A.; Deeg, Hans J.; Brown, Timothy N.; Hidas, M&#225;rton G.; Baliber, Nairn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 2, pp. 1145-1158 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691.1145S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691..866K</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of A Temperature Inversion in the Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Burrows, Adam; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 1, pp. 866-874 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690L..89H</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-7: A Bright Transiting-Exoplanet System in the Southern Hemisphere</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Alsubai, K.; Bentley, S. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, R.; Haswell, C. A.; Joshi, Y. C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Ryans, R.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 690, Issue 1, pp. L89-L91 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690L..89H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MmSAI..80..318S</bibcode>
			<title>Probing structural and evolutionary properties of exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Latham, D. W.; Torres, G.; Carney, B. W.; Laird, J. B.; Stefanik, R. P.; Boss, A. P.; Charbonneau, D.; O'Donovan, F. T.; Holman, M. J.; Winn, J. N.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ&#224; Astronomica Italiana, v.80, p.318 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MmSAI..80..318S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689..492K</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Orbital Parameters through Planetary Transit Monitoring</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 1, pp. 492-498.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689..492K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1191L</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Radii of Extrasolar Giant Planets: the Cases of TrES-4, XO-3b, and HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>Liu, Xin; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1191-1200.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1191L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1341C</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Knutson, Heather A.; Barman, Travis; Allen, Lori E.; Mayor, Michel; Megeath, S. Thomas; Queloz, Didier; Udry, St&#233;phane</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1341-1348.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1341C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1302B</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting the Yields of Photometric Surveys for Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1302-1330.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1302B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...683.1076W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. IX. Evidence for a Smaller Radius of the Exoplanet XO-3b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Torres, Guillermo; McCullough, Peter; Johns-Krull, Christopher; Latham, David W.; Shporer, Avi; Mazeh, Tsevi; Garcia-Melendo, Enrique; Foote, Cindy; Esquerdo, Gil; Everett, Mark</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 683, Issue 2, pp. 1076-1084.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...683.1076W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1277B</bibcode>
			<title>Optical Albedo Theory of Strongly Irradiated Giant Planets: The Case of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Ibgui, L.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1277-1282.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1277B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681.1631J</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 2, pp. 1631-1638.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681.1631J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681..636I</bibcode>
			<title>Parameters and Predictions for the Long-Period Transiting Planet HD 17156b</title>
			<authors>Irwin, Jonathan; Charbonneau, David; Nutzman, Philip; Welsh, William F.; Rajan, Abhijith; Hidas, Marton; Brown, Timothy M.; Lister, Timothy A.; Davies, Donald; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 1, pp. 636-643.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681..636I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.387L...4A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-5b: a dense, very hot Jupiter transiting a 12th-mag Southern-hemisphere star</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Wilson, D. M.; Collier Cameron, A.; Smalley, B.; Lister, T. A.; Bentley, S. J.; Blecha, A.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Kane, S. R.; Marmier, M.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pollacco, D. L.; Pont, F.; Ryans, R.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 387, Issue 1, pp. L4-L7.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.387L...4A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1419F</bibcode>
			<title>A Unified Theory for the Atmospheres of the Hot and Very Hot Jupiters: Two Classes of Irradiated Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Lodders, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1419-1435.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1419F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677L.117F</bibcode>
			<title>Radiative Thrusters on Close-in Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. L117-L120.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677L.117F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677..657J</bibcode>
			<title>XO-3b: A Massive Planet in an Eccentric Orbit Transiting an F5 V Star</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Prato, L.; Bissinger, R.; Fleenor, M.; Foote, C. N.; Garcia-Melendo, E.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Mallia, F.; Masi, G.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. 657-670.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677..657J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...482..299U</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE-TR-211 - a new transiting inflated hot Jupiter from the OGLE survey and ESO LP666 spectroscopic follow-up program</title>
			<authors>Udalski, A.; Pont, F.; Naef, D.; Melo, C.; Bouchy, F.; Santos, N. C.; Moutou, C.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Gieren, W.; Gillon, M.; Hoyer, S.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Minniti, D.; Pietrzynski, G.; Queloz, D.; Ramirez, S.; Ruiz, M. T.; Shporer, A.; Tamuz, O.; Udry, S.; Zoccali, M.; Kubiak, M.; Szymanski, M. K.; Soszyn ski, I.; Szewczyk, O.; Ulaczyk, K.; Wyrzykowski, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 482, Issue 1, 2008, pp.299-304</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...482..299U</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.384.1097K</bibcode>
			<title>SuperWASP-N extrasolar planet candidates from fields 06h &lt; RA &lt; 16h</title>
			<authors>Kane, S. R.; Clarkson, W. I.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Christian, D. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Lister, T. A.; Street, R. A.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Keenan, F. P.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J.; Parley, N. R.; Pollacco, D. L.; Ryans, R.; Skillen, I.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 384, Issue 3, pp. 1097-1108.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.384.1097K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...675L.113W</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-4b: A 12th Magnitude Transiting Hot Jupiter in the Southern Hemisphere</title>
			<authors>Wilson, D. M.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Smalley, B.; Lister, T. A.; Bentley, S. J.; Blecha, A.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Kane, S. R.; Marmier, M.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pollacco, D.; Pont, F.; Ryans, R.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 675, Issue 2, pp. L113-L116.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...675L.113W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673L..79N</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-6b: A Hot Jupiter Transiting a Bright F Star</title>
			<authors>Noyes, R. W.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; P&#225;l, A.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Latham, D. W.; Fern&#225;ndez, J. M.; Fischer, D. A.; Butler, R. P.; Marcy, G. W.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Sasselov, D. D.; Sato, B.; Stefanik, R.; Holman, M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. L79-L82.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673L..79N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671L.173B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-5b: A Jupiter-like Hot Jupiter Transiting a Bright Star</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Shporer, A.; P&#225;l, A.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Latham, D. W.; Mazeh, T.; Ofir, A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Esquerdo, G.; Sipocz, B.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 2, pp. L173-L176.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671L.173B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671..861H</bibcode>
			<title>Two Classes of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. 861-871.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671..861H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...670L..41K</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-4b: A Metal-rich Low-Density Transiting Hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Kov&#225;cs, G.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Sozzetti, A.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Butler, R. P.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Fern&#225;ndez, J. M.; Esquerdo, G.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; P&#225;l, A.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 670, Issue 1, pp. L41-L44.</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...670L..41K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667L.195M</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-4: A Transiting Hot Jupiter of Very Low Density</title>
			<authors>Mandushev, Georgi; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Torres, Guillermo; Latham, David W.; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Dunham, Edward W.; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Fern&#225;ndez, Jos&#233; M.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Brown, Timothy M.; Rabus, Markus; Belmonte, Juan A.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 2, pp. L195-L198.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667L.195M</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
