<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...756..122D</bibcode>
			<title>The Photoeccentric Effect and Proto-hot Jupiters. I. Measuring Photometric Eccentricities of Individual Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Dawson, Rebekah I.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 756, Issue 2, article id. 122 (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...756..122D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJS..201...15H</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Occurrence within 0.25 AU of Solar-type Stars from Kepler</title>
			<authors>Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Cochran, William D.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Torres, Guillermo; Brown, Timothy M.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Ciardi, David; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael R.; Howell, Steve B.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Seager, Sara; Rogers, Leslie; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Steffen, Jason H.; Basri, Gibor S.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie; Clarke, Bruce; Dupree, Andrea; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fischer, Debra A.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Tarter, Jill; Girouard, Forrest R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Johnson, John Asher; Klaus, Todd C.; Machalek, Pavel; Moorhead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Twicken, Joseph D.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Lucas, Philip W.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Welsh, William F.; Boss, Alan; Devore, Edna; Gould, Alan; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Morris, Robert L.; Prsa, Andrej; Morton, Timothy D.; Still, Martin; Thompson, Susan E.; Mullally, Fergal; Endl, Michael; MacQueen, Phillip J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 201, Issue 2, article id. 15 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJS..201...15H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754..129S</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Hunters: Assessing the Kepler Inventory of Short-period Planets</title>
			<authors>Schwamb, Megan E.; Lintott, Chris J.; Fischer, Debra A.; Giguere, Matthew J.; Lynn, Stuart; Smith, Arfon M.; Brewer, John M.; Parrish, Michael; Schawinski, Kevin; Simpson, Robert J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 754, Issue 2, article id. 129 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754..129S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...543A..96E</bibcode>
			<title>Precise modeling of the exoplanet host star and CoRoT main target HD 52265</title>
			<authors>Escobar, M. E.; Thado, S.; Vauclair, S.; Ballot, J.; Charpinet, S.; Dolez, N.; Hui-Bon-Hoa, A.; Vauclair, G.; Gizon, L.; Mathur, S.; Quirion, P. O.; Stahn, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 543, id.A96</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...543A..96E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...72D</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation between the Eclipse Depths of Kepler Gas Giant Candidates and the Metallicities of Their Parent Stars</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 72 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...72D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751...96P</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Tidal Dissipation in Stars from the Destruction Rates of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Penev, Kaloyan; Jackson, Brian; Spada, Federico; Thom, Nicole</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. 96 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...751...96P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...542A..92R</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planets in stellar multiple systems</title>
			<authors>Roell, T.; Neuhuser, R.; Seifahrt, A.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 542, id.A92</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...542A..92R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.1512M</bibcode>
			<title>A massive exoplanet candidate around KOI-13: independent confirmation by ellipsoidal variations</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Hodgkin, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 2, pp. 1512-1517.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.1512M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..115K</bibcode>
			<title>The Hunt for Exomoons with Kepler (HEK). I. Description of a New Observational project</title>
			<authors>Kipping, D. M.; Bakos, G. .; Buchhave, L.; Nesvorn, D.; Schmitt, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 115 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750..115K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..56M</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler KOI-13.01 - Detection of beaming and ellipsoidal modulations pointing to a massive hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Nachmani, G.; Sokol, G.; Faigler, S.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A56</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..56M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..38R</bibcode>
			<title>Warm debris disks candidates in transiting planets systems</title>
			<authors>Ribas, .; Mern, B.; Ardila, D. R.; Bouy, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A38</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..38R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.421.1166K</bibcode>
			<title>A novel method to photometrically constrain orbital eccentricities: Multibody Asterodensity Profiling</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.; Dunn, William R.; Jasinski, Jamie M.; Manthri, Varun P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 421, Issue 2, pp. 1166-1188.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.421.1166K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..82K</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for enhanced chromospheric Ca II H and K emission in stars with close-in extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A82</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..82K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..62O</bibcode>
			<title>Transit-timing measurements with the model-independent barycenter method: application to the LHS 6343 system</title>
			<authors>Oshagh, M.; Bou, G.; Haghighipour, N.; Montalto, M.; Figueira, P.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A62</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..62O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...747...82C</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Phase Variations of WASP-12b: Defying Predictions</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Machalek, Pavel; Croll, Bryce; Shekhtman, Louis M.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Greene, Tom; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 747, Issue 1, article id. 82 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...747...82C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..97S</bibcode>
			<title>A consistent analysis of three years of ground- and space-based photometry of TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Schrter, S.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Mller, H. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A97</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..97S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746..111T</bibcode>
			<title>Warm Spitzer Observations of Three Hot Exoplanets: XO-4b, HAT-P-6b, and HAT-P-8b</title>
			<authors>Todorov, Kamen O.; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Sada, Pedro V.; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric; Desert, Jean-Michel; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Charbonneau, David; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan; Showman, Adam P.; Lewis, Nikole K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 1, article id. 111 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...746..111T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...39C</bibcode>
			<title>A Uniform Search for Secondary Eclipses of Hot Jupiters in Kepler Q2 Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Coughlin, J. L.; Lpez-Morales, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 2, article id. 39 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143...39C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A.147H</bibcode>
			<title>Optimizing exoplanet transit searches around low-mass stars with inclination constraints</title>
			<authors>Herrero, E.; Ribas, I.; Jordi, C.; Guinan, E. F.; Engle, S. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 537, id.A147</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...537A.147H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418.1165H</bibcode>
			<title>On stellar limb darkening and exoplanetary transits</title>
			<authors>Howarth, Ian D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 418, Issue 2, pp. 1165-1175.</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.418.1165H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418L..15K</bibcode>
			<title>Debris disc candidates in systems with transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Krivov, A. V.; Reidemeister, M.; Fiedler, S.; Lhne, T.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 418, Issue 1, pp. L15-L19.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.418L..15K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...35N</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Secondary Eclipses of WASP-18b</title>
			<authors>Nymeyer, Sarah; Harrington, Joseph; Hardy, Ryan A.; Stevenson, Kevin B.; Campo, Christopher J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Collier-Cameron, Andrew; Loredo, Thomas J.; Blecic, Jasmina; Bowman, William C.; Britt, Christopher B. T.; Cubillos, Patricio; Hellier, Coel; Gillon, Michael; Maxted, Pierre F. L.; Hebb, Leslie; Wheatley, Peter J.; Pollacco, Don; Anderson, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. 35 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417L..88K</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of visible light from the darkest world</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 417, Issue 1, pp. L88-L92.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417L..88K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740...33D</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler and Ground-based Transits of the Exo-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Sada, Pedro V.; Jackson, Brian; Peterson, Steven W.; Agol, Eric; Knutson, Heather A.; Jennings, Donald E.; Haase, Flynn; Bays, Kevin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 740, Issue 1, article id. 33 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740...33D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..112B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Input Catalog: Photometric Calibration and Stellar Classification</title>
			<authors>Brown, Timothy M.; Latham, David W.; Everett, Mark E.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 4, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142..112B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416..689K</bibcode>
			<title>LUNA: an algorithm for generating dynamic planet-moon transits</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 416, Issue 1, pp. 689-709.</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.416..689K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738...50A</bibcode>
			<title>Two Upper Limits on the Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect, with Differing Implications: WASP-1 has a High Obliquity and WASP-2 is Indeterminate</title>
			<authors>Albrecht, Simon; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Butler, R. Paul; Crane, Jeffrey D.; Shectman, Stephen A.; Thompson, Ian B.; Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Enya, Keigo; Fischer, Debra</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 50 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738...50A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Broadband Transmission Spectroscopy of the Super-Earth GJ 1214b Suggests a Low Mean Molecular Weight Atmosphere</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Miller-Ricci Kempton, Eliza; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman; Neilson, Hilding</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. 78 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, Sren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AN....332..547N</bibcode>
			<title>The Young Exoplanet Transit Initiative (YETI)</title>
			<authors>Neuhuser, R.; Errmann, R.; Berndt, A.; Maciejewski, G.; Takahashi, H.; Chen, W. P.; Dimitrov, D. P.; Pribulla, T.; Nikogossian, E. H.; Jensen, E. L. N.; Marschall, L.; Wu, Z.-Y.; Kellerer, A.; Walter, F. M.; Briceo, C.; Chini, R.; Fernandez, M.; Raetz, St.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Quinn, S. N.; Niedzielski, A.; Bukowiecki, L.; Nowak, G.; Tomov, T.; Tachihara, K.; Hu, S. C.-L.; Hung, L. W.; Kjurkchieva, D. P.; Radeva, V. S.; Mihov, B. M.; Slavcheva-Mihova, L.; Bozhinova, I. N.; Budaj, J.; Vanko, M.; Kundra, E.; Hamblek, L.; Krushevska, V.; Movsessian, T.; Harutyunyan, H.; Downes, J. J.; Hernandez, J.; Hoffmeister, V. H.; Cohen, D. H.; Abel, I.; Ahmad, R.; Chapman, S.; Eckert, S.; Goodman, J.; Guerard, A.; Kim, H. M.; Koontharana, A.; Sokol, J.; Trinh, J.; Wang, Y.; Zhou, X.; Redmer, R.; Kramm, U.; Nettelmann, N.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, J.; Moualla, M.; Ginski, C.; Marka, C.; Adam, C.; Seeliger, M.; Baar, S.; Roell, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Trepl, L.; Eisenbei, T.; Fiedler, S.; Tetzlaff, N.; Schmidt, E.; Hohle, M. M.; Kitze, M.; Chakrova, N.; Grfe, C.; Schreyer, K.; Hambaryan, V. V.; Broeg, C. H.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Pandey, A. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.332, Issue 6, p.547</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AN....332..547N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...530A..97B</bibcode>
			<title>Accurate p-mode measurements of the G0V metal-rich CoRoT target HD 52265</title>
			<authors>Ballot, J.; Gizon, L.; Samadi, R.; Vauclair, G.; Benomar, O.; Bruntt, H.; Mosser, B.; Stahn, T.; Verner, G. A.; Campante, T. L.; Garca, R. A.; Mathur, S.; Salabert, D.; Gaulme, P.; Rgulo, C.; Roxburgh, I. W.; Appourchaux, T.; Baudin, F.; Catala, C.; Chaplin, W. J.; Deheuvels, S.; Michel, E.; Bazot, M.; Creevey, O.; Dolez, N.; Elsworth, Y.; Sato, K. H.; Vauclair, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 530, id.A97</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...530A..97B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...36K</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of Kepler's Short-cadence Photometry for TrES-2b</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David; Bakos, Gspr</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 36 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...36K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...41B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in Five of the Exoplanetary Systems Studied by the NASA EPOXI Mission</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...41B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.412.1181E</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision automated follow-up transit photometry with a 50-cm robotic telescope</title>
			<authors>Eibe, M. T.; Cuesta, L.; Ulln, A.; Prez-Verde, A.; Navas, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 412, Issue 2, pp. 1181-1186.</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.412.1181E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..108C</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the Variability of Stars with Early-release Kepler Data</title>
			<authors>Ciardi, David R.; von Braun, Kaspar; Bryden, Geoff; van Eyken, Julian; Howell, Steve B.; Kane, Stephen R.; Plavchan, Peter; Ramrez, Solange V.; Stauffer, John R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 4, article id. 108 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..108C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Low-mass Eclipsing Binaries in the Initial Kepler Data Release</title>
			<authors>Coughlin, J. L.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Harrison, T. E.; Ule, N.; Hoffman, D. I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 3, article id. 78 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..73S</bibcode>
			<title>Gran Telescopio Canarias OSIRIS transiting exoplanet atmospheric survey: detection of potassium in XO-2b from narrowband spectrophotometry</title>
			<authors>Sing, D. K.; Dsert, J.-M.; Fortney, J. J.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Ballester, G. E.; Cepa, J.; Ehrenreich, D.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Pont, F.; Shabram, M.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A73</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..73S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...30C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from WASP-12b: Detections of the Secondary Eclipse in Ks, H, and J</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Lafreniere, David; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...30C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A.130S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-34b: a near-grazing transiting sub-Jupiter-mass exoplanet in a hierarchical triple system</title>
			<authors>Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Gillon, M.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wood, P. L.; Bento, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A130</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A.130S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...23B</bibcode>
			<title>Secondary Eclipse Photometry of WASP-4b with Warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Beerer, Ingrid M.; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Agol, Eric; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Deming, Drake; Desert, Jean-Michel; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 23 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...94C</bibcode>
			<title>System Parameters, Transit Times, and Secondary Eclipse Constraints of the Exoplanet Systems HAT-P-4, TrES-2, TrES-3, and WASP-3 from the NASA EPOXI Mission of Opportunity</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; A'Hearn, Michael F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 94 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...94C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726....2G</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of the Transiting Exoplanet Host HD 17156 with Hubble Space Telescope Fine Guidance Sensor</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; McCullough, Peter R.; Nelan, Edmund P.; Brown, Timothy M.; Charbonneau, David; Nutzman, Philip; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Kjeldsen, Hans</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id.2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726....2G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, Vol. 29, p. 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011BAVSR..60..261R</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplaneten f?r amateure.</title>
			<authors>Raetz, M.</authors>
			<journal>BAV Rundbrief, 60, 261 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011BAVSR..60..261R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725..261M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Inference of Thermal Inversions in Hot Jupiter Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 1, pp. 261-274 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725..261M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724.1108J</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect of Exoplanet Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Cochran, William D.; Welsh, William F.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John Asher; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Howard, Andrew W.; MacQueen, Phillip; Orosz, Jerome A.; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Allen, Christopher; Tenenbaum, Peter; Wu, Hayley; Meibom, Sren; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Cote, Miles T.; McCauliff, Sean; Girouard, Forrest R.; Gunter, Jay P.; Wohler, Bill; Hall, Jennifer R.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Kamal Uddin, AKM; Wu, Michael S.; Bhavsar, Paresh A.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Pletcher, David L.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, article id. 1108-1119 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724.1108J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1758K</bibcode>
			<title>Binning is sinning: morphological light-curve distortions due to finite integration time</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1758-1769.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1758K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1606W</bibcode>
			<title>Estimating the masses of extra-solar planets</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Littlefair, S. P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Dhillon, V. S.; Simpson, E. K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1606-1622.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1606W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1494C</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing transiting extrasolar planets with narrow-band photometry and GTC/OSIRIS</title>
			<authors>Coln, Knicole D.; Ford, Eric B.; Lee, Brian; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Blake, Cullen H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1494-1501.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1494C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2625M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation in exoplanet WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuhuser, R.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Ginski, Ch.; Adam, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2625-2631.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2625M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722..871S</bibcode>
			<title>Atmosphere and Spectral Models of the Kepler-field Planets HAT-P-7b and TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. 871-879 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722..871S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..920C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from TrES-3b: A Ks-band Detection and an H-band Upper Limit on the Depth of the Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Lafrenire, David; Albert, Loic</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 920-927 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..920C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717.1084C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Thermal Emission from the Hot Jupiter TrES-2b: Ground-based Detection of the Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Lafreniere, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. 1084-1091 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717.1084C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1336K</bibcode>
			<title>Stability Analysis of Single-planet Systems and Their Habitable Zones</title>
			<authors>Kopparapu, Ravi Kumar; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1336-1344 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1336K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Dsert, J.-M.; Daz, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..458T</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-14b: A 2.2 M J Exoplanet Transiting a Bright F Star</title>
			<authors>Torres, G.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kipping, D.; Sipocz, B.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M. E.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 458-467 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..458T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714..462S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Apparent Orbital Inclination Change of the Extrasolar Transiting Planet TrES-2b</title>
			<authors>Scuderi, Louis J.; Dittmann, Jason A.; Males, Jared R.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Close, Laird M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 462-468 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714..462S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714...13A</bibcode>
			<title>Lack of Transit Timing Variations of OGLE-TR-111b: A Re-Analysis with Six New Epochs</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Elliot, J. L.; Seager, S.; Osip, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 13-24 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714...13A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.164C</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismic Investigation of Known Planet Hosts in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Kjeldsen, H.; Brown, T. M.; Gilliland, R. L.; Arentoft, T.; Frandsen, S.; Quirion, P.-O.; Borucki, W. J.; Koch, D.; Jenkins, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L164-L168 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.164C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.160G</bibcode>
			<title>Initial Characteristics of Kepler Short Cadence Data</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer; Klaus, Todd; Koch, David; McCauliff, Sean; Quintana, Elisa V.; Twicken, Joseph D.; van Cleve, Jeffrey E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L160-L163 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.160G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.131K</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of the Transiting Planet Kepler-5b</title>
			<authors>Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Caldwell, John; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ron L.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoff W.; Morrison, David; Tarter, Jill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, article id. L131-L135 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.131K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..374F</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Mandushev, Georgi; Spiegel, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 374-379 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..374F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..111M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission and Tidal Heating of the Heavy and Eccentric Planet XO-3b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; Greene, Tom; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Deming, Drake L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 111-118 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..111M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...327..977B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Planet-Detection Mission: Introduction and First Results</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy; Caldwell, Douglas; Caldwell, John; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kondo, Yoji; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Meibom, Sren; Kjeldsen, Hans; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Morrison, David; Sasselov, Dimitar; Tarter, Jill; Boss, Alan; Brownlee, Don; Owen, Toby; Buzasi, Derek; Charbonneau, David; Doyle, Laurance; Fortney, Jonathan; Ford, Eric B.; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Rowe, Jason; Anderson, Howard; Buchhave, Lars; Ciardi, David; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Sherry, William; Horch, Elliott; Isaacson, Howard; Everett, Mark E.; Fischer, Debra; Torres, Guillermo; Johnson, John Asher; Endl, Michael; MacQueen, Phillip; Bryson, Stephen T.; Dotson, Jessie; Haas, Michael; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Allen, Christopher; Li, Jie; Wu, Haley; Tenenbaum, Peter; Verner, Ekaterina; Bruhweiler, Frederick; Barnes, Jason; Prsa, Andrej</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 327, Issue 5968, pp. 977- (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...327..977B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; Hbrard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1724B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-11b: A Super-Neptune Planet Transiting a Bright K Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Pl, A.; Hartman, J.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Isaacson, H.; Howard, A.; Vogt, S.; Kovcs, Gbor; Fernandez, J.; Mor, A.; Stefanik, R. P.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1724-1745 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1551O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Planetary Emission from the Exoplanet Tres-2 Using Spitzer/IRAC</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Harrington, Joseph; Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1551-1556 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1551O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710...97C</bibcode>
			<title>Studying the Atmosphere of the Exoplanet HAT-P-7b Via Secondary Eclipse Measurements with EPOXI, Spitzer, and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Holman, Matthew J.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Deming, Drake; A'Hearn, Michael F.; EPOXI Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 97-104 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710...97C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...511A...3G</bibcode>
			<title>The thermal emission of the young and massive planet CoRoT-2b at 4.5 and 8 mum</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Lanotte, A. A.; Barman, T.; Miller, N.; Demory, B.-O.; Deleuil, M.; Montalbn, J.; Bouchy, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Deeg, H. J.; Fortney, J. J.; Fridlund, M.; Harrington, J.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 511, id.A3</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...511A...3G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...510A.107M</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-band transit observations of the TrES-2b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Schrter, S.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Cordes, O.; Reif, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 510, id.A107</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...510A.107M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..458H</bibcode>
			<title>Analytic Description of the Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect for Transiting Exoplanets: Cross-Correlation Method and Comparison with Simulated Data</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Suto, Yasushi; Taruya, Atsushi; Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 458-469 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..458H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508.1011R</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing analysis of the exoplanets TrES-1 and TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Rabus, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Alonso, R.; Belmonte, J. A.; Almenara, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 2, 2009, pp.1011-1020</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508.1011R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.2091W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Ingress and the Tilted Orbit of the Extraordinarily Eccentric Exoplanet HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Gazak, J. Zachary; Starkey, Donn; Ford, Eric B.; Coln, Knicole D.; Reyes, Francisco; Nortmann, Lisa; Dreizler, Stefan; Odewahn, Stephen; Welsh, William F.; Kadakia, Shimonee; Vanderbei, Robert J.; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Lockhart, Matthew; Crossfield, Ian J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Dantowitz, Ronald; Carter, Joshua A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. 2091-2100 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.2091W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..455S</bibcode>
			<title>The LAEX and NASA portals for CoRoT public data</title>
			<authors>Solano, E.; von Braun, K.; Velasco, A.; Ciardi, D. R.; Gutirrez, R.; McElroy, D. L.; Lpez, M.; Abajian, M.; Garca, M.; Ali, B.; Sarro, L. M.; Berriman, G. B.; Bryden, G.; Chan, B.; Good, J.; Kane, S. R.; Laity, A. C.; Lau, C.; Payne, A. N.; Plavchan, P.; Ramirez, S.; Schmitz, M.; Stauffer, J. R.; Wyatt, P. L.; Zhang, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.455-463</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..455S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009OEJV..109...28K</bibcode>
			<title>Photometry of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Krejcova, T.</authors>
			<journal>Open European Journal on Variable stars, 109, 28 (2009)</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009OEJV..109...28K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..514M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission of XO-2b: Evidence for a Weak Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 514-520 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..514M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...500L..45M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of orbital parameter changes in the TrES-2 exoplanet?</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 500, Issue 3, 2009, pp.L45-L49</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...500L..45M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1230F</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Spin-Orbit Alignment: Results from the Ensemble of Rossiter-McLaughlin Observations</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1230-1240 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1230F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AN....330..469F</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamics of the TrES-2 system</title>
			<authors>Freistetter, F.; Sli, .; Funk, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.330, Issue 5, p.469-474</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AN....330..469F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AN....330..459R</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit observations at the University Observatory Jena: TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Raetz, St.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Roell, T.; Eisenbeiss, T.; Hohle, M. M.; Koeltzsch, A.; Vanko, M.; Ginski, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Tetzlaff, N.; Seifahrt, A.; Broeg, Ch.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Raetz, M.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.330, Issue 5, p.459</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AN....330..459R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..567D</bibcode>
			<title>Binarity of transit host stars. Implications for planetary parameters</title>
			<authors>Daemgen, S.; Hormuth, F.; Brandner, W.; Bergfors, C.; Janson, M.; Hippler, S.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 2, 2009, pp.567-574</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..567D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691..866K</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of A Temperature Inversion in the Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Burrows, Adam; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 1, pp. 866-874 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origins of Eccentric Close-In Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Takeda, Genya; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. L29-L32.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1302B</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting the Yields of Photometric Surveys for Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1302-1330.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1302B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..649J</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Angle of Exoplanet HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.; Narita, Norio; Enya, Keigo; Williams, Peter K. G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Sato, Bun'ei; Ohta, Yasuhiro; Taruya, Atsushi; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Bakos, Gaspar; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide; Yamada, Toru; Yoshii, Yuzuru; Hidas, Marton</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 649-657.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..649J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684.1427M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission of Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Burrows, Adam; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 2, pp. 1427-1432.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684.1427M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488..763H</bibcode>
			<title>Misaligned spin-orbit in the XO-3 planetary system?</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Loeillet, B.; Rabus, M.; Bonfils, X.; Moutou, C.; Boisse, I.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488..763H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1283W</bibcode>
			<title>The Prograde Orbit of Exoplanet TrES-2b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Narita, Norio; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Fischer, Debra A.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1283-1288.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1283W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681.1631J</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 2, pp. 1631-1638.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681.1631J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...680.1450P</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-7b: An Extremely Hot Massive Planet Transiting a Bright Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Pl, A.; Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, Gza; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Kovcs, Gbor; Stefanik, R.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 680, Issue 2, pp. 1450-1456.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...680.1450P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1419F</bibcode>
			<title>A Unified Theory for the Atmospheres of the Hot and Very Hot Jupiters: Two Classes of Irradiated Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Lodders, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1419-1435.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1419F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1407F</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the Orbital Eccentricities of Transiting Extrasolar Planets with Photometric Observations</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Veras, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1407-1418.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1407F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...477..309P</bibcode>
			<title>Influence of the evolving stellar X-ray luminosity distribution on exoplanetary mass loss</title>
			<authors>Penz, T.; Micela, G.; Lammer, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 477, Issue 1, January I 2008, pp.309-314</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...477..309P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671L.173B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-5b: A Jupiter-like Hot Jupiter Transiting a Bright Star</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Shporer, A.; Pl, A.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Mazeh, T.; Ofir, A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Esquerdo, G.; Sipocz, B.; Kovcs, Gbor; Stefanik, R.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 2, pp. L173-L176.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671L.173B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671..861H</bibcode>
			<title>Two Classes of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. 861-871.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671..861H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..729F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting and predicting the yield of transit surveys: giant planets in the OGLE fields</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Morello, V.; Pont, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 2, November IV 2007, pp.729-746</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..729F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...668L.171B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectral Models of the Planet HD 209458b with a Thermal Inversion and Water Emission Bands</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Knutson, H. A.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 668, Issue 2, pp. L171-L174.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...668L.171B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667L.191L</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission from Transiting Very Hot Jupiters: Prospects for Ground-based Detection at Optical Wavelengths</title>
			<authors>Lpez-Morales, Mercedes; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 2, pp. L191-L194.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667L.191L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...474..301B</bibcode>
			<title>A method to detect H{2} in the atmosphere of transiting extrasolar planets using the EUV spectrum</title>
			<authors>Barthlmy, M.; Lilensten, J.; Parkinson, C. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 474, Issue 1, October IV 2007, pp.301-306</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...474..301B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASJ...59..763N</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Rossiter-Laughlin Effect in the Transiting Exoplanetary System TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Narita, N.; Enya, K.; Sato, B.; Ohta, Y.; Winn, J. N.; Suto, Y.; Taruya, A.; Turner, E. L.; Aoki, W.; Yoshii, M.; Yamada, T.; Tamura, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.59, No.4, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASJ...59..763N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664.1190S</bibcode>
			<title>Improving Stellar and Planetary Parameters of Transiting Planet Systems: The Case of TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Latham, David W.; Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Laird, John B.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 2, pp. 1190-1198.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664.1190S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664.1185H</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve (TLC) Project. VI. Three Transits of the Exoplanet TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Fernandez, Jose; Everett, Mark E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 2, pp. 1185-1189.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664.1185H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379L..11S</bibcode>
			<title>A method for the direct determination of the surface gravities of transiting extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Wheatley, Peter J.; Sams, Giles</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 379, Issue 1, pp. L11-L15.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379L..11S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...663L..37O</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-3: A Nearby, Massive, Transiting Hot Jupiter in a 31 Hour Orbit</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Bakos, Gspr .; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Brown, Timothy M.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Kovcs, Gza; Everett, Mark E.; Baliber, Nairn; Hidas, Mrton G.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Deeg, Hans J.; Belmonte, Juan A.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Stefanik, Robert P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 663, Issue 1, pp. L37-L40.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...663L..37O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662..658O</bibcode>
			<title>Outcome of Six Candidate Transiting Planets from a TrES Field in Andromeda</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Latham, David W.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Torres, Guillermo; Everett, Mark E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 1, pp. 658-668.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662..658O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...661L..81C</bibcode>
			<title>Heat Transport in Giant (Exo)planets: A New Perspective</title>
			<authors>Chabrier, Gilles; Baraffe, Isabelle</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 661, Issue 1, pp. L81-L84.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...661L..81C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...661..502B</bibcode>
			<title>Possible Solutions to the Radius Anomalies of Transiting Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Hubbard, W. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 661, Issue 1, pp. 502-514.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...661..502B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..850D</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude Photometry for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Candidates. II. Transits of OGLE-TR-113-b in the Optical and Near-IR</title>
			<authors>Daz, Rodrigo F.; Ramrez, Sebastin; Fernndez, Jos Miguel; Gallardo, Jos; Gieren, Wolfgang; Ivanov, Valentin D.; Mauas, Pablo; Minniti, Dante; Pietrzynski, Grzegorz; Prez, Felipe; Ruz, Mara Teresa; Udalski, Andrzej; Zoccali, Manuela</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 850-857.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..850D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1328C</bibcode>
			<title>Looking for Giant Earths in the HD 209458 System: A Search for Transits in MOST Space-based Photometry</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Kuschnig, Rainer; Walker, Andrew; Gladman, Brett; Sasselov, Dimitar; Cameron, Chris; Walker, Gordon A. H.; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rucinski, Slavek M.; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1328-1339.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1328C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1322C</bibcode>
			<title>Precise Radius Estimates for the Exoplanets WASP-1b and WASP-2b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Everett, Mark E.; Latham, David W.; Holman, Matthew J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1322-1327.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1322C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...656..552B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-1b: A Large-Radius, Low-Density Exoplanet Transiting One Member of a Stellar Binary</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Noyes, R. W.; Kovcs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Torres, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sato, B.; Johnson, J. A.; P l, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Stanek, K. Z.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.; Sipocz, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 656, Issue 1, pp. 552-559.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...656..552B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...462L...5L</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal dissipation within hot Jupiters: a new appraisal</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Correia, A. C. M.; Chabrier, G.; Baraffe, I.; Selsis, F.; Laskar, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 462, Issue 1, January IV 2007, pp.L5-L8</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...462L...5L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007BAVSR..56..163B</bibcode>
			<title>Uebersicht zum BAV Veraenderlichen-Treffen 2007 in Hartha.</title>
			<authors>Braune, W.; Flechsig, G.-U.</authors>
			<journal>BAV Rundbrief, 56, 163 (2007)</journal>
			<date>0/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007BAVSR..56..163B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1621P</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy with Small Telescopes</title>
			<authors>Paczynski, Bohdan</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 850, pp. 1621-1625.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1621P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652L.137F</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Constraints on Trojans of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. L137-L140.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652L.137F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...651L..61O</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-2: The First Transiting Planet in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Brown, Timothy M.; Trauger, John T.; Belmonte, Juan A.; Rabus, Markus; Almenara, Jos M.; Alonso, Roi; Deeg, Hans J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Falco, Emilio E.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Roussanova, Anna; Stefanik, Robert P.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 651, Issue 1, pp. L61-L64.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...651L..61O</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...756..122D</bibcode>
			<title>The Photoeccentric Effect and Proto-hot Jupiters. I. Measuring Photometric Eccentricities of Individual Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Dawson, Rebekah I.; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 756, Issue 2, article id. 122 (2012).</journal>
			<date>9/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...756..122D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJS..201...15H</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Occurrence within 0.25 AU of Solar-type Stars from Kepler</title>
			<authors>Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Cochran, William D.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Torres, Guillermo; Brown, Timothy M.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Ciardi, David; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael R.; Howell, Steve B.; Kjeldsen, Hans; Seager, Sara; Rogers, Leslie; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Steffen, Jason H.; Basri, Gibor S.; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie; Clarke, Bruce; Dupree, Andrea; Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Fischer, Debra A.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Tarter, Jill; Girouard, Forrest R.; Holman, Matthew J.; Johnson, John Asher; Klaus, Todd C.; Machalek, Pavel; Moorhead, Althea V.; Morehead, Robert C.; Ragozzine, Darin; Tenenbaum, Peter; Twicken, Joseph D.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Isaacson, Howard; Shporer, Avi; Lucas, Philip W.; Walkowicz, Lucianne M.; Welsh, William F.; Boss, Alan; Devore, Edna; Gould, Alan; Smith, Jeffrey C.; Morris, Robert L.; Prsa, Andrej; Morton, Timothy D.; Still, Martin; Thompson, Susan E.; Mullally, Fergal; Endl, Michael; MacQueen, Phillip J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 201, Issue 2, article id. 15 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJS..201...15H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...754..129S</bibcode>
			<title>Planet Hunters: Assessing the Kepler Inventory of Short-period Planets</title>
			<authors>Schwamb, Megan E.; Lintott, Chris J.; Fischer, Debra A.; Giguere, Matthew J.; Lynn, Stuart; Smith, Arfon M.; Brewer, John M.; Parrish, Michael; Schawinski, Kevin; Simpson, Robert J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 754, Issue 2, article id. 129 (2012).</journal>
			<date>8/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...754..129S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...543A..96E</bibcode>
			<title>Precise modeling of the exoplanet host star and CoRoT main target HD 52265</title>
			<authors>Escobar, M. E.; Thado, S.; Vauclair, S.; Ballot, J.; Charpinet, S.; Dolez, N.; Hui-Bon-Hoa, A.; Vauclair, G.; Gizon, L.; Mathur, S.; Quirion, P. O.; Stahn, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 543, id.A96</journal>
			<date>7/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...543A..96E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...752...72D</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation between the Eclipse Depths of Kepler Gas Giant Candidates and the Metallicities of Their Parent Stars</title>
			<authors>Dodson-Robinson, Sarah E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 752, Issue 1, article id. 72 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...752...72D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751...96P</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Tidal Dissipation in Stars from the Destruction Rates of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Penev, Kaloyan; Jackson, Brian; Spada, Federico; Thom, Nicole</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. 96 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...751...96P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...542A..92R</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar planets in stellar multiple systems</title>
			<authors>Roell, T.; Neuhuser, R.; Seifahrt, A.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 542, id.A92</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...542A..92R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.1512M</bibcode>
			<title>A massive exoplanet candidate around KOI-13: independent confirmation by ellipsoidal variations</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Hodgkin, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 2, pp. 1512-1517.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.1512M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..115K</bibcode>
			<title>The Hunt for Exomoons with Kepler (HEK). I. Description of a New Observational project</title>
			<authors>Kipping, D. M.; Bakos, G. .; Buchhave, L.; Nesvorn, D.; Schmitt, A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 115 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...750..115K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..56M</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler KOI-13.01 - Detection of beaming and ellipsoidal modulations pointing to a massive hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Mazeh, T.; Nachmani, G.; Sokol, G.; Faigler, S.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A56</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..56M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...541A..38R</bibcode>
			<title>Warm debris disks candidates in transiting planets systems</title>
			<authors>Ribas, .; Mern, B.; Ardila, D. R.; Bouy, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 541, id.A38</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...541A..38R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.421.1166K</bibcode>
			<title>A novel method to photometrically constrain orbital eccentricities: Multibody Asterodensity Profiling</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.; Dunn, William R.; Jasinski, Jamie M.; Manthri, Varun P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 421, Issue 2, pp. 1166-1188.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.421.1166K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..82K</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for enhanced chromospheric Ca II H and K emission in stars with close-in extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A82</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..82K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..62O</bibcode>
			<title>Transit-timing measurements with the model-independent barycenter method: application to the LHS 6343 system</title>
			<authors>Oshagh, M.; Bou, G.; Haghighipour, N.; Montalto, M.; Figueira, P.; Santos, N. C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A62</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..62O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...747...82C</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Phase Variations of WASP-12b: Defying Predictions</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Machalek, Pavel; Croll, Bryce; Shekhtman, Louis M.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Greene, Tom; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 747, Issue 1, article id. 82 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...747...82C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...539A..97S</bibcode>
			<title>A consistent analysis of three years of ground- and space-based photometry of TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Schrter, S.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Mller, H. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 539, id.A97</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...539A..97S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746..111T</bibcode>
			<title>Warm Spitzer Observations of Three Hot Exoplanets: XO-4b, HAT-P-6b, and HAT-P-8b</title>
			<authors>Todorov, Kamen O.; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Sada, Pedro V.; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric; Desert, Jean-Michel; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Charbonneau, David; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan; Showman, Adam P.; Lewis, Nikole K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 1, article id. 111 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...746..111T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...39C</bibcode>
			<title>A Uniform Search for Secondary Eclipses of Hot Jupiters in Kepler Q2 Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Coughlin, J. L.; Lpez-Morales, M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 2, article id. 39 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143...39C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A.147H</bibcode>
			<title>Optimizing exoplanet transit searches around low-mass stars with inclination constraints</title>
			<authors>Herrero, E.; Ribas, I.; Jordi, C.; Guinan, E. F.; Engle, S. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 537, id.A147</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...537A.147H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418.1165H</bibcode>
			<title>On stellar limb darkening and exoplanetary transits</title>
			<authors>Howarth, Ian D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 418, Issue 2, pp. 1165-1175.</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.418.1165H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418L..15K</bibcode>
			<title>Debris disc candidates in systems with transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Krivov, A. V.; Reidemeister, M.; Fiedler, S.; Lhne, T.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 418, Issue 1, pp. L15-L19.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.418L..15K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...35N</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Secondary Eclipses of WASP-18b</title>
			<authors>Nymeyer, Sarah; Harrington, Joseph; Hardy, Ryan A.; Stevenson, Kevin B.; Campo, Christopher J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Collier-Cameron, Andrew; Loredo, Thomas J.; Blecic, Jasmina; Bowman, William C.; Britt, Christopher B. T.; Cubillos, Patricio; Hellier, Coel; Gillon, Michael; Maxted, Pierre F. L.; Hebb, Leslie; Wheatley, Peter J.; Pollacco, Don; Anderson, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. 35 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417L..88K</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of visible light from the darkest world</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 417, Issue 1, pp. L88-L92.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417L..88K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...740...33D</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler and Ground-based Transits of the Exo-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Sada, Pedro V.; Jackson, Brian; Peterson, Steven W.; Agol, Eric; Knutson, Heather A.; Jennings, Donald E.; Haase, Flynn; Bays, Kevin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 740, Issue 1, article id. 33 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...740...33D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..112B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Input Catalog: Photometric Calibration and Stellar Classification</title>
			<authors>Brown, Timothy M.; Latham, David W.; Everett, Mark E.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 4, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142..112B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416..689K</bibcode>
			<title>LUNA: an algorithm for generating dynamic planet-moon transits</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 416, Issue 1, pp. 689-709.</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.416..689K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738...50A</bibcode>
			<title>Two Upper Limits on the Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect, with Differing Implications: WASP-1 has a High Obliquity and WASP-2 is Indeterminate</title>
			<authors>Albrecht, Simon; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Butler, R. Paul; Crane, Jeffrey D.; Shectman, Stephen A.; Thompson, Ian B.; Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Enya, Keigo; Fischer, Debra</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 50 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...738...50A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Broadband Transmission Spectroscopy of the Super-Earth GJ 1214b Suggests a Low Mean Molecular Weight Atmosphere</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Miller-Ricci Kempton, Eliza; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman; Neilson, Hilding</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. 78 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...19B</bibcode>
			<title>Characteristics of Planetary Candidates Observed by Kepler. II. Analysis of the First Four Months of Data</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy M.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Rowe, Jason; Sasselov, Dimitar; Boss, Alan; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David; Doyle, Laurance; Dupree, Andrea K.; Ford, Eric B.; Fortney, Jonathan; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Tarter, Jill; Welsh, William F.; Allen, Christopher; Buchhave, Lars A.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Das, Santanu; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Endl, Michael; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Haas, Michael; Horch, Elliott; Howard, Andrew; Isaacson, Howard; Kjeldsen, Hans; Kolodziejczak, Jeffery; Kulesa, Craig; Li, Jie; Lucas, Philip W.; Machalek, Pavel; McCarthy, Donald; MacQueen, Phillip; Meibom, Sren; Miquel, Thibaut; Prsa, Andrej; Quinn, Samuel N.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Ragozzine, Darin; Sherry, William; Shporer, Avi; Tenenbaum, Peter; Torres, Guillermo; Twicken, Joseph D.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Witteborn, Fred C.; Still, Martin</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 1, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...19B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AN....332..547N</bibcode>
			<title>The Young Exoplanet Transit Initiative (YETI)</title>
			<authors>Neuhuser, R.; Errmann, R.; Berndt, A.; Maciejewski, G.; Takahashi, H.; Chen, W. P.; Dimitrov, D. P.; Pribulla, T.; Nikogossian, E. H.; Jensen, E. L. N.; Marschall, L.; Wu, Z.-Y.; Kellerer, A.; Walter, F. M.; Briceo, C.; Chini, R.; Fernandez, M.; Raetz, St.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Quinn, S. N.; Niedzielski, A.; Bukowiecki, L.; Nowak, G.; Tomov, T.; Tachihara, K.; Hu, S. C.-L.; Hung, L. W.; Kjurkchieva, D. P.; Radeva, V. S.; Mihov, B. M.; Slavcheva-Mihova, L.; Bozhinova, I. N.; Budaj, J.; Vanko, M.; Kundra, E.; Hamblek, L.; Krushevska, V.; Movsessian, T.; Harutyunyan, H.; Downes, J. J.; Hernandez, J.; Hoffmeister, V. H.; Cohen, D. H.; Abel, I.; Ahmad, R.; Chapman, S.; Eckert, S.; Goodman, J.; Guerard, A.; Kim, H. M.; Koontharana, A.; Sokol, J.; Trinh, J.; Wang, Y.; Zhou, X.; Redmer, R.; Kramm, U.; Nettelmann, N.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, J.; Moualla, M.; Ginski, C.; Marka, C.; Adam, C.; Seeliger, M.; Baar, S.; Roell, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Trepl, L.; Eisenbei, T.; Fiedler, S.; Tetzlaff, N.; Schmidt, E.; Hohle, M. M.; Kitze, M.; Chakrova, N.; Grfe, C.; Schreyer, K.; Hambaryan, V. V.; Broeg, C. H.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Pandey, A. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.332, Issue 6, p.547</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AN....332..547N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...530A..97B</bibcode>
			<title>Accurate p-mode measurements of the G0V metal-rich CoRoT target HD 52265</title>
			<authors>Ballot, J.; Gizon, L.; Samadi, R.; Vauclair, G.; Benomar, O.; Bruntt, H.; Mosser, B.; Stahn, T.; Verner, G. A.; Campante, T. L.; Garca, R. A.; Mathur, S.; Salabert, D.; Gaulme, P.; Rgulo, C.; Roxburgh, I. W.; Appourchaux, T.; Baudin, F.; Catala, C.; Chaplin, W. J.; Deheuvels, S.; Michel, E.; Bazot, M.; Creevey, O.; Dolez, N.; Elsworth, Y.; Sato, K. H.; Vauclair, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 530, id.A97</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...530A..97B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...733...36K</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of Kepler's Short-cadence Photometry for TrES-2b</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David; Bakos, Gspr</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 733, Issue 1, article id. 36 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...733...36K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...41B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in Five of the Exoplanetary Systems Studied by the NASA EPOXI Mission</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...41B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.412.1181E</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision automated follow-up transit photometry with a 50-cm robotic telescope</title>
			<authors>Eibe, M. T.; Cuesta, L.; Ulln, A.; Prez-Verde, A.; Navas, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 412, Issue 2, pp. 1181-1186.</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.412.1181E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..108C</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the Variability of Stars with Early-release Kepler Data</title>
			<authors>Ciardi, David R.; von Braun, Kaspar; Bryden, Geoff; van Eyken, Julian; Howell, Steve B.; Kane, Stephen R.; Plavchan, Peter; Ramrez, Solange V.; Stauffer, John R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 4, article id. 108 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..108C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Low-mass Eclipsing Binaries in the Initial Kepler Data Release</title>
			<authors>Coughlin, J. L.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Harrison, T. E.; Ule, N.; Hoffman, D. I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 3, article id. 78 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..73S</bibcode>
			<title>Gran Telescopio Canarias OSIRIS transiting exoplanet atmospheric survey: detection of potassium in XO-2b from narrowband spectrophotometry</title>
			<authors>Sing, D. K.; Dsert, J.-M.; Fortney, J. J.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Ballester, G. E.; Cepa, J.; Ehrenreich, D.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Pont, F.; Shabram, M.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A73</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..73S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...30C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from WASP-12b: Detections of the Secondary Eclipse in Ks, H, and J</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Lafreniere, David; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...30C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A.130S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-34b: a near-grazing transiting sub-Jupiter-mass exoplanet in a hierarchical triple system</title>
			<authors>Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Gillon, M.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wood, P. L.; Bento, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A130</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A.130S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...23B</bibcode>
			<title>Secondary Eclipse Photometry of WASP-4b with Warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Beerer, Ingrid M.; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Agol, Eric; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Deming, Drake; Desert, Jean-Michel; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 23 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...94C</bibcode>
			<title>System Parameters, Transit Times, and Secondary Eclipse Constraints of the Exoplanet Systems HAT-P-4, TrES-2, TrES-3, and WASP-3 from the NASA EPOXI Mission of Opportunity</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; A'Hearn, Michael F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 94 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...94C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726....2G</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismology of the Transiting Exoplanet Host HD 17156 with Hubble Space Telescope Fine Guidance Sensor</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; McCullough, Peter R.; Nelan, Edmund P.; Brown, Timothy M.; Charbonneau, David; Nutzman, Philip; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Kjeldsen, Hans</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id.2 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726....2G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, Vol. 29, p. 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011BAVSR..60..261R</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplaneten f?r amateure.</title>
			<authors>Raetz, M.</authors>
			<journal>BAV Rundbrief, 60, 261 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011BAVSR..60..261R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725..261M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Inference of Thermal Inversions in Hot Jupiter Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 1, pp. 261-274 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725..261M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724.1108J</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect of Exoplanet Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Cochran, William D.; Welsh, William F.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John Asher; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Howard, Andrew W.; MacQueen, Phillip; Orosz, Jerome A.; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Allen, Christopher; Tenenbaum, Peter; Wu, Hayley; Meibom, Sren; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Cote, Miles T.; McCauliff, Sean; Girouard, Forrest R.; Gunter, Jay P.; Wohler, Bill; Hall, Jennifer R.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Kamal Uddin, AKM; Wu, Michael S.; Bhavsar, Paresh A.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Pletcher, David L.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, article id. 1108-1119 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724.1108J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1758K</bibcode>
			<title>Binning is sinning: morphological light-curve distortions due to finite integration time</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1758-1769.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1758K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1606W</bibcode>
			<title>Estimating the masses of extra-solar planets</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Littlefair, S. P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Dhillon, V. S.; Simpson, E. K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1606-1622.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1606W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1494C</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing transiting extrasolar planets with narrow-band photometry and GTC/OSIRIS</title>
			<authors>Coln, Knicole D.; Ford, Eric B.; Lee, Brian; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Blake, Cullen H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1494-1501.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1494C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2625M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation in exoplanet WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuhuser, R.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Ginski, Ch.; Adam, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2625-2631.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2625M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722..871S</bibcode>
			<title>Atmosphere and Spectral Models of the Kepler-field Planets HAT-P-7b and TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 722, Issue 1, pp. 871-879 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722..871S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..920C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from TrES-3b: A Ks-band Detection and an H-band Upper Limit on the Depth of the Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Lafrenire, David; Albert, Loic</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 920-927 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..920C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717.1084C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Thermal Emission from the Hot Jupiter TrES-2b: Ground-based Detection of the Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Lafreniere, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. 1084-1091 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717.1084C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1336K</bibcode>
			<title>Stability Analysis of Single-planet Systems and Their Habitable Zones</title>
			<authors>Kopparapu, Ravi Kumar; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1336-1344 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1336K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Dsert, J.-M.; Daz, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..458T</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-14b: A 2.2 M J Exoplanet Transiting a Bright F Star</title>
			<authors>Torres, G.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kipping, D.; Sipocz, B.; Stefanik, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M. E.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 458-467 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..458T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714..462S</bibcode>
			<title>On the Apparent Orbital Inclination Change of the Extrasolar Transiting Planet TrES-2b</title>
			<authors>Scuderi, Louis J.; Dittmann, Jason A.; Males, Jared R.; Green, Elizabeth M.; Close, Laird M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 462-468 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714..462S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714...13A</bibcode>
			<title>Lack of Transit Timing Variations of OGLE-TR-111b: A Re-Analysis with Six New Epochs</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Elliot, J. L.; Seager, S.; Osip, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 13-24 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714...13A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.164C</bibcode>
			<title>Asteroseismic Investigation of Known Planet Hosts in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Christensen-Dalsgaard, J.; Kjeldsen, H.; Brown, T. M.; Gilliland, R. L.; Arentoft, T.; Frandsen, S.; Quirion, P.-O.; Borucki, W. J.; Koch, D.; Jenkins, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L164-L168 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.164C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.160G</bibcode>
			<title>Initial Characteristics of Kepler Short Cadence Data</title>
			<authors>Gilliland, Ronald L.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.; Hall, Jennifer; Klaus, Todd; Koch, David; McCauliff, Sean; Quintana, Elisa V.; Twicken, Joseph D.; van Cleve, Jeffrey E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L160-L163 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.160G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.131K</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of the Transiting Planet Kepler-5b</title>
			<authors>Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.; Rowe, Jason F.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Caldwell, John; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Gautier, Thomas N., III; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ron L.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoff W.; Morrison, David; Tarter, Jill</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, article id. L131-L135 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.131K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..374F</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Mandushev, Georgi; Spiegel, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 374-379 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..374F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..111M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission and Tidal Heating of the Heavy and Eccentric Planet XO-3b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; Greene, Tom; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Deming, Drake L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 111-118 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..111M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Sci...327..977B</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler Planet-Detection Mission: Introduction and First Results</title>
			<authors>Borucki, William J.; Koch, David; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie; Brown, Timothy; Caldwell, Douglas; Caldwell, John; Christensen-Dalsgaard, Jrgen; Cochran, William D.; DeVore, Edna; Dunham, Edward W.; Dupree, Andrea K.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald; Gould, Alan; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kondo, Yoji; Latham, David W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Meibom, Sren; Kjeldsen, Hans; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Morrison, David; Sasselov, Dimitar; Tarter, Jill; Boss, Alan; Brownlee, Don; Owen, Toby; Buzasi, Derek; Charbonneau, David; Doyle, Laurance; Fortney, Jonathan; Ford, Eric B.; Holman, Matthew J.; Seager, Sara; Steffen, Jason H.; Welsh, William F.; Rowe, Jason; Anderson, Howard; Buchhave, Lars; Ciardi, David; Walkowicz, Lucianne; Sherry, William; Horch, Elliott; Isaacson, Howard; Everett, Mark E.; Fischer, Debra; Torres, Guillermo; Johnson, John Asher; Endl, Michael; MacQueen, Phillip; Bryson, Stephen T.; Dotson, Jessie; Haas, Michael; Kolodziejczak, Jeffrey; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Allen, Christopher; Li, Jie; Wu, Haley; Tenenbaum, Peter; Verner, Ekaterina; Bruhweiler, Frederick; Barnes, Jason; Prsa, Andrej</authors>
			<journal>Science, Volume 327, Issue 5968, pp. 977- (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010Sci...327..977B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; Hbrard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1724B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-11b: A Super-Neptune Planet Transiting a Bright K Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Pl, A.; Hartman, J.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Isaacson, H.; Howard, A.; Vogt, S.; Kovcs, Gbor; Fernandez, J.; Mor, A.; Stefanik, R. P.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1724-1745 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1724B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1551O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Planetary Emission from the Exoplanet Tres-2 Using Spitzer/IRAC</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Harrington, Joseph; Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1551-1556 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1551O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710...97C</bibcode>
			<title>Studying the Atmosphere of the Exoplanet HAT-P-7b Via Secondary Eclipse Measurements with EPOXI, Spitzer, and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Holman, Matthew J.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Deming, Drake; A'Hearn, Michael F.; EPOXI Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 97-104 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710...97C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...511A...3G</bibcode>
			<title>The thermal emission of the young and massive planet CoRoT-2b at 4.5 and 8 mum</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Lanotte, A. A.; Barman, T.; Miller, N.; Demory, B.-O.; Deleuil, M.; Montalbn, J.; Bouchy, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Deeg, H. J.; Fortney, J. J.; Fridlund, M.; Harrington, J.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 511, id.A3</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...511A...3G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...510A.107M</bibcode>
			<title>Multi-band transit observations of the TrES-2b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Schrter, S.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.; Cordes, O.; Reif, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 510, id.A107</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...510A.107M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..458H</bibcode>
			<title>Analytic Description of the Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect for Transiting Exoplanets: Cross-Correlation Method and Comparison with Simulated Data</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Suto, Yasushi; Taruya, Atsushi; Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 458-469 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..458H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...508.1011R</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing analysis of the exoplanets TrES-1 and TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Rabus, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Alonso, R.; Belmonte, J. A.; Almenara, J. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 508, Issue 2, 2009, pp.1011-1020</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...508.1011R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.2091W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Ingress and the Tilted Orbit of the Extraordinarily Eccentric Exoplanet HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Gazak, J. Zachary; Starkey, Donn; Ford, Eric B.; Coln, Knicole D.; Reyes, Francisco; Nortmann, Lisa; Dreizler, Stefan; Odewahn, Stephen; Welsh, William F.; Kadakia, Shimonee; Vanderbei, Robert J.; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Lockhart, Matthew; Crossfield, Ian J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Dantowitz, Ronald; Carter, Joshua A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. 2091-2100 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.2091W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..455S</bibcode>
			<title>The LAEX and NASA portals for CoRoT public data</title>
			<authors>Solano, E.; von Braun, K.; Velasco, A.; Ciardi, D. R.; Gutirrez, R.; McElroy, D. L.; Lpez, M.; Abajian, M.; Garca, M.; Ali, B.; Sarro, L. M.; Berriman, G. B.; Bryden, G.; Chan, B.; Good, J.; Kane, S. R.; Laity, A. C.; Lau, C.; Payne, A. N.; Plavchan, P.; Ramirez, S.; Schmitz, M.; Stauffer, J. R.; Wyatt, P. L.; Zhang, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.455-463</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..455S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009OEJV..109...28K</bibcode>
			<title>Photometry of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Krejcova, T.</authors>
			<journal>Open European Journal on Variable stars, 109, 28 (2009)</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009OEJV..109...28K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..514M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission of XO-2b: Evidence for a Weak Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 514-520 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..514M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...500L..45M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of orbital parameter changes in the TrES-2 exoplanet?</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 500, Issue 3, 2009, pp.L45-L49</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...500L..45M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1230F</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Spin-Orbit Alignment: Results from the Ensemble of Rossiter-McLaughlin Observations</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1230-1240 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1230F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AN....330..469F</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamics of the TrES-2 system</title>
			<authors>Freistetter, F.; Sli, .; Funk, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.330, Issue 5, p.469-474</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AN....330..469F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AN....330..459R</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit observations at the University Observatory Jena: TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Raetz, St.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Roell, T.; Eisenbeiss, T.; Hohle, M. M.; Koeltzsch, A.; Vanko, M.; Ginski, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Tetzlaff, N.; Seifahrt, A.; Broeg, Ch.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Raetz, M.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.330, Issue 5, p.459</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AN....330..459R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..567D</bibcode>
			<title>Binarity of transit host stars. Implications for planetary parameters</title>
			<authors>Daemgen, S.; Hormuth, F.; Brandner, W.; Bergfors, C.; Janson, M.; Hippler, S.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 2, 2009, pp.567-574</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..567D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691..866K</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of A Temperature Inversion in the Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Burrows, Adam; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 1, pp. 866-874 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691..866K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origins of Eccentric Close-In Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Takeda, Genya; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. L29-L32.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686L..29M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1302B</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting the Yields of Photometric Surveys for Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1302-1330.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1302B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..649J</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Angle of Exoplanet HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.; Narita, Norio; Enya, Keigo; Williams, Peter K. G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Sato, Bun'ei; Ohta, Yasuhiro; Taruya, Atsushi; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Bakos, Gaspar; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide; Yamada, Toru; Yoshii, Yuzuru; Hidas, Marton</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 649-657.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..649J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684.1427M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission of Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Burrows, Adam; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 2, pp. 1427-1432.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684.1427M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488..763H</bibcode>
			<title>Misaligned spin-orbit in the XO-3 planetary system?</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Loeillet, B.; Rabus, M.; Bonfils, X.; Moutou, C.; Boisse, I.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488..763H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1283W</bibcode>
			<title>The Prograde Orbit of Exoplanet TrES-2b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Narita, Norio; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Fischer, Debra A.; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1283-1288.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1283W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681.1631J</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Greenberg, Richard; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 2, pp. 1631-1638.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681.1631J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...680.1450P</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-7b: An Extremely Hot Massive Planet Transiting a Bright Star in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>Pl, A.; Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, Gza; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Sipocz, B.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Kovcs, Gbor; Stefanik, R.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 680, Issue 2, pp. 1450-1456.</journal>
			<date>6/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...680.1450P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1419F</bibcode>
			<title>A Unified Theory for the Atmospheres of the Hot and Very Hot Jupiters: Two Classes of Irradiated Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Lodders, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1419-1435.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1419F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1407F</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing the Orbital Eccentricities of Transiting Extrasolar Planets with Photometric Observations</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Veras, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1407-1418.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1407F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...477..309P</bibcode>
			<title>Influence of the evolving stellar X-ray luminosity distribution on exoplanetary mass loss</title>
			<authors>Penz, T.; Micela, G.; Lammer, H.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 477, Issue 1, January I 2008, pp.309-314</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...477..309P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671L.173B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-5b: A Jupiter-like Hot Jupiter Transiting a Bright Star</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Shporer, A.; Pl, A.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Mazeh, T.; Ofir, A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; Esquerdo, G.; Sipocz, B.; Kovcs, Gbor; Stefanik, R.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 2, pp. L173-L176.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671L.173B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671..861H</bibcode>
			<title>Two Classes of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. 861-871.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671..861H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..729F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting and predicting the yield of transit surveys: giant planets in the OGLE fields</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Morello, V.; Pont, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 2, November IV 2007, pp.729-746</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..729F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...668L.171B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectral Models of the Planet HD 209458b with a Thermal Inversion and Water Emission Bands</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Knutson, H. A.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 668, Issue 2, pp. L171-L174.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...668L.171B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667L.191L</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission from Transiting Very Hot Jupiters: Prospects for Ground-based Detection at Optical Wavelengths</title>
			<authors>Lpez-Morales, Mercedes; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 2, pp. L191-L194.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667L.191L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...474..301B</bibcode>
			<title>A method to detect H{2} in the atmosphere of transiting extrasolar planets using the EUV spectrum</title>
			<authors>Barthlmy, M.; Lilensten, J.; Parkinson, C. D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 474, Issue 1, October IV 2007, pp.301-306</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...474..301B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASJ...59..763N</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Rossiter-Laughlin Effect in the Transiting Exoplanetary System TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Narita, N.; Enya, K.; Sato, B.; Ohta, Y.; Winn, J. N.; Suto, Y.; Taruya, A.; Turner, E. L.; Aoki, W.; Yoshii, M.; Yamada, T.; Tamura, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.59, No.4, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASJ...59..763N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664.1190S</bibcode>
			<title>Improving Stellar and Planetary Parameters of Transiting Planet Systems: The Case of TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Latham, David W.; Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Laird, John B.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 2, pp. 1190-1198.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664.1190S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...664.1185H</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve (TLC) Project. VI. Three Transits of the Exoplanet TrES-2</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Fernandez, Jose; Everett, Mark E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 664, Issue 2, pp. 1185-1189.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...664.1185H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379L..11S</bibcode>
			<title>A method for the direct determination of the surface gravities of transiting extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Wheatley, Peter J.; Sams, Giles</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 379, Issue 1, pp. L11-L15.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379L..11S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...663L..37O</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-3: A Nearby, Massive, Transiting Hot Jupiter in a 31 Hour Orbit</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Bakos, Gspr .; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Brown, Timothy M.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Kovcs, Gza; Everett, Mark E.; Baliber, Nairn; Hidas, Mrton G.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Deeg, Hans J.; Belmonte, Juan A.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Stefanik, Robert P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 663, Issue 1, pp. L37-L40.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...663L..37O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...662..658O</bibcode>
			<title>Outcome of Six Candidate Transiting Planets from a TrES Field in Andromeda</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Alonso, Roi; Brown, Timothy M.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Latham, David W.; Stefanik, Robert P.; Torres, Guillermo; Everett, Mark E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 662, Issue 1, pp. 658-668.</journal>
			<date>6/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...662..658O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...661L..81C</bibcode>
			<title>Heat Transport in Giant (Exo)planets: A New Perspective</title>
			<authors>Chabrier, Gilles; Baraffe, Isabelle</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 661, Issue 1, pp. L81-L84.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...661L..81C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...661..502B</bibcode>
			<title>Possible Solutions to the Radius Anomalies of Transiting Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Hubbard, W. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 661, Issue 1, pp. 502-514.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...661..502B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..850D</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude Photometry for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Candidates. II. Transits of OGLE-TR-113-b in the Optical and Near-IR</title>
			<authors>Daz, Rodrigo F.; Ramrez, Sebastin; Fernndez, Jos Miguel; Gallardo, Jos; Gieren, Wolfgang; Ivanov, Valentin D.; Mauas, Pablo; Minniti, Dante; Pietrzynski, Grzegorz; Prez, Felipe; Ruz, Mara Teresa; Udalski, Andrzej; Zoccali, Manuela</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 850-857.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..850D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1328C</bibcode>
			<title>Looking for Giant Earths in the HD 209458 System: A Search for Transits in MOST Space-based Photometry</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Matthews, Jaymie M.; Rowe, Jason F.; Kuschnig, Rainer; Walker, Andrew; Gladman, Brett; Sasselov, Dimitar; Cameron, Chris; Walker, Gordon A. H.; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Guenther, David B.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Rucinski, Slavek M.; Weiss, Werner W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1328-1339.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1328C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...658.1322C</bibcode>
			<title>Precise Radius Estimates for the Exoplanets WASP-1b and WASP-2b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Everett, Mark E.; Latham, David W.; Holman, Matthew J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; O'Donovan, Francis T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 658, Issue 2, pp. 1322-1327.</journal>
			<date>4/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...658.1322C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...656..552B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-1b: A Large-Radius, Low-Density Exoplanet Transiting One Member of a Stellar Binary</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Noyes, R. W.; Kovcs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Torres, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sato, B.; Johnson, J. A.; P l, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Stanek, K. Z.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.; Sipocz, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 656, Issue 1, pp. 552-559.</journal>
			<date>2/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...656..552B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...462L...5L</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal dissipation within hot Jupiters: a new appraisal</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Correia, A. C. M.; Chabrier, G.; Baraffe, I.; Selsis, F.; Laskar, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 462, Issue 1, January IV 2007, pp.L5-L8</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...462L...5L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007BAVSR..56..163B</bibcode>
			<title>Uebersicht zum BAV Veraenderlichen-Treffen 2007 in Hartha.</title>
			<authors>Braune, W.; Flechsig, G.-U.</authors>
			<journal>BAV Rundbrief, 56, 163 (2007)</journal>
			<date>0/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007BAVSR..56..163B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1621P</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy with Small Telescopes</title>
			<authors>Paczynski, Bohdan</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 850, pp. 1621-1625.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1621P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652L.137F</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Constraints on Trojans of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. L137-L140.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652L.137F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...651L..61O</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-2: The First Transiting Planet in the Kepler Field</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Brown, Timothy M.; Trauger, John T.; Belmonte, Juan A.; Rabus, Markus; Almenara, Jos M.; Alonso, Roi; Deeg, Hans J.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Falco, Emilio E.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Roussanova, Anna; Stefanik, Robert P.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 651, Issue 1, pp. L61-L64.</journal>
			<date>11/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...651L..61O</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
