<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742..116B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-20b-HAT-P-23b: Four Massive Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Kipping, D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Shporer, A.; B&#233;ky, B.; Buchhave, L. A.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ChA&amp;A..35..409Z</bibcode>
			<title>Observation and Research of the Transits of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Zhang, Ji-Cheng; Cao, Chen; Song, Nan; Wang, Fei-Ge; Zhang, Xiao-Tong</authors>
			<journal>Chinese Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 35, Issue 4, p. 409-420.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ChA%26A..35..409Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Broadband Transmission Spectroscopy of the Super-Earth GJ 1214b Suggests a Low Mean Molecular Weight Atmosphere</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Miller-Ricci Kempton, Eliza; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman; Neilson, Hilding</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. 78 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735L..12D</bibcode>
			<title>The High Albedo of the Hot Jupiter Kepler-7 b</title>
			<authors>Demory, Brice-Olivier; Seager, Sara; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Kjeldsen, Hans; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Gillon, Micha&#235;l; Rowe, Jason F.; Welsh, William F.; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Dupree, Andrea; McCarthy, Don; Kulesa, Craig; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 735, Issue 1, article id. L12 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735L..12D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414..108B</bibcode>
			<title>On the use of the Virtual Observatory to select calibrators for phase-referenced astrometry of exoplanet-host stars</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonneau, D.; Mourard, D.; Lafrasse, S.; Mella, G.; Duvert, G.; Chelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. 108-115.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414..108B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...74G</bibcode>
			<title>Consequences of the Ejection and Disruption of Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Guillochon, James; Ramirez-Ruiz, Enrico; Lin, Douglas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...74G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...41B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in Five of the Exoplanetary Systems Studied by the NASA EPOXI Mission</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...41B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.412.1181E</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision automated follow-up transit photometry with a 50-cm robotic telescope</title>
			<authors>Eibe, M. T.; Cuesta, L.; Ull&#225;n, A.; P&#233;rez-Verde, A.; Navas, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 412, Issue 2, pp. 1181-1186.</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.412.1181E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..49D</bibcode>
			<title>The GROUSE project. II. Detection of the Ks-band secondary eclipse of exoplanet HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>de Mooij, E. J. W.; de Kok, R. J.; Nefs, S. V.; Snellen, I. A. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A49</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..49D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..41L</bibcode>
			<title>Distorted, nonspherical transiting planets: impact on the transit depth and on the radius determination</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Lai, D.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A41</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..41L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..85N</bibcode>
			<title>TASTE: The Asiago Search for Transit timing variations of Exoplanets. I. Overview and improved parameters for HAT-P-3b and HAT-P-14b</title>
			<authors>Nascimbeni, V.; Piotto, G.; Bedin, L. R.; Damasso, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A85</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..85N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63..301L</bibcode>
			<title>Physical Properties of the Transiting Planetary System TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Lee, Jae Woo; Youn, Jae-Hyuck; Kim, Seung-Lee; Lee, Chung-Uk; Koo, Jae-Rim</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.1, pp.301--307</journal>
			<date>2/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63..301L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411L..46V</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for detection of exoplanet magnetic fields through bow-shock observations during transits</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. L46-L50.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411L..46V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...30C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from WASP-12b: Detections of the Secondary Eclipse in Ks, H, and J</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Lafreniere, David; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...30C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...23B</bibcode>
			<title>Secondary Eclipse Photometry of WASP-4b with Warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Beerer, Ingrid M.; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Agol, Eric; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Deming, Drake; Desert, Jean-Michel; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 23 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...94C</bibcode>
			<title>System Parameters, Transit Times, and Secondary Eclipse Constraints of the Exoplanet Systems HAT-P-4, TrES-2, TrES-3, and WASP-3 from the NASA EPOXI Mission of Opportunity</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; A'Hearn, Michael F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 94 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...94C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 29, 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1494C</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing transiting extrasolar planets with narrow-band photometry and GTC/OSIRIS</title>
			<authors>Col&#243;n, Knicole D.; Ford, Eric B.; Lee, Brian; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Blake, Cullen H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1494-1501.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1494C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723.1436C</bibcode>
			<title>A New 24 mum Phase Curve for upsilo Andromedae b</title>
			<authors>Crossfield, Ian J. M.; Hansen, Brad M. S.; Harrington, Joseph; Cho, James Y.-K.; Deming, Drake; Menou, Kristen; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1446 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723.1436C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2625M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation in exoplanet WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Ginski, Ch.; Adam, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2625-2631.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2625M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..920C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from TrES-3b: A Ks-band Detection and an H-band Upper Limit on the Depth of the Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Lafreni&#232;re, David; Albert, Loic</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 920-927 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..920C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717.1084C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Thermal Emission from the Hot Jupiter TrES-2b: Ground-based Detection of the Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Lafreniere, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. 1084-1091 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717.1084C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.404L.114G</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based detection of thermal emission from the exoplanet WASP-19b</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Aigrain, S.; Pollacco, D. L.; Barros, S. C. C.; Hebb, L.; Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; West, R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 404, Issue 1, pp. L114-L118.</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.404L.114G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714...13A</bibcode>
			<title>Lack of Transit Timing Variations of OGLE-TR-111b: A Re-Analysis with Six New Epochs</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; L&#243;pez-Morales, M.; Elliot, J. L.; Seager, S.; Osip, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 13-24 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714...13A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.2111H</bibcode>
			<title>Tight constraints on the existence of additional planets around HD 189733&amp;dagger</title>
			<authors>Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Skillen, I.; Benn, C. R.; Gibson, N. P.; Pollacco, D.; Nesvorn&#253;, D.; Augusteijn, T.; Tulloch, S. M.; Joshi, Y. C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 4, pp. 2111-2119.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.2111H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...513L...3A</bibcode>
			<title>H-band thermal emission from the 19-h period planet WASP-19b</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Barman, T. S.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 513, id.L3</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...513L...3A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..374F</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Mandushev, Georgi; Spiegel, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 374-379 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..374F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..111M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission and Tidal Heating of the Heavy and Eccentric Planet XO-3b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; Greene, Tom; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Deming, Drake L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 111-118 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..111M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1551O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Planetary Emission from the Exoplanet Tres-2 Using Spitzer/IRAC</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Harrington, Joseph; Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1551-1556 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1551O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710...97C</bibcode>
			<title>Studying the Atmosphere of the Exoplanet HAT-P-7b Via Secondary Eclipse Measurements with EPOXI, Spitzer, and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Holman, Matthew J.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Deming, Drake; A'Hearn, Michael F.; the EPOXI Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 97-104 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710...97C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...511A...3G</bibcode>
			<title>The thermal emission of the young and massive planet CoRoT-2b at 4.5 and 8 mum</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Lanotte, A. A.; Barman, T.; Miller, N.; Demory, B.-O.; Deleuil, M.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Bouchy, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Deeg, H. J.; Fortney, J. J.; Fridlund, M.; Harrington, J.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 511, id.A3</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...511A...3G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401.1917G</bibcode>
			<title>A transit timing analysis of seven RISE light curves of the exoplanet system HAT-P-3</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Pollacco, D. L.; Barros, S.; Benn, C.; Christian, D.; Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Joshi, Y. C.; Keenan, F. P.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Steele, I. A.; Todd, I.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 3, pp. 1917-1923.</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401.1917G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707.1707R</bibcode>
			<title>Ks-Band Detection of Thermal Emission and Color Constraints to CoRoT-1b: A Low-Albedo Planet with Inefficient Atmospheric Energy Redistribution and a Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Rogers, Justin C.; Apai, D&#225;niel; L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Sing, David K.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 2, article id. 1707-1716 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707.1707R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.399..287S</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision photometry by telescope defocussing - II. The transiting planetary system WASP-4</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Dominik, M.; Hornstrup, A.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Ricci, D.; Th&#246;ne, C. C.; Anguita, T.; Bozza, V.; Novati, S. Calchi; Harps&#248;e, K.; Mancini, L.; Masi, G.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Scarpetta, G.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.; Zub, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 399, Issue 1, pp. 287-294.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.399..287S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704.1107L</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Transiting Planet and Eight Eclipsing Binaries in HATNet Field G205</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Torres, Guillermo; Stefanik, Robert P.; Noyes, Robert W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Butler, R. Paul; Sipocz, Brigitta; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Vogt, Steven S.; Hartman, Joel D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; L&#225;z&#225;r, J&#243;zsef; Papp, Istv&#225;n; S&#225;ri, P&#225;l</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 2, pp. 1107-1119 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704.1107L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..359G</bibcode>
			<title>VLT transit and occultation photometry for the bloated planet CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Demory, B.-O.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Barman, T.; Hebb, L.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Deleuil, M.; Magain, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.359-367</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..359G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700.1078G</bibcode>
			<title>A Transit Timing Analysis of Nine Rise Light Curves of the Exoplanet System TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Barros, S.; Joshi, Y. C.; Todd, I.; Keenan, F. P.; Skillen, I.; Benn, C.; Christian, D.; Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Steele, I. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 1078-1085 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700.1078G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698..558G</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Detection of a Transit of HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Garcia-Melendo, E.; McCullough, P. R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 1, pp. 558-561 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698..558G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...500L..45M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of orbital parameter changes in the TrES-2 exoplanet?</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 500, Issue 3, 2009, pp.L45-L49</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...500L..45M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1116W</bibcode>
			<title>Nondetection of Polarized, Scattered Light from the HD 189733b Hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Wiktorowicz, Sloane J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1116-1124 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1116W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..567D</bibcode>
			<title>Binarity of transit host stars. Implications for planetary parameters</title>
			<authors>Daemgen, S.; Hormuth, F.; Brandner, W.; Bergfors, C.; Janson, M.; Hippler, S.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 2, 2009, pp.567-574</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..567D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691.1145S</bibcode>
			<title>A New Spectroscopic and Photometric Analysis of the Transiting Planet Systems TrES-3 and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Korzennik, Sylvain G.; Holman, Matthew J.; Latham, David W.; Laird, John B.; Fernandez, Jos&#233;; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward; Everett, Mark E.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Belmonte, Juan A.; Deeg, Hans J.; Brown, Timothy N.; Hidas, M&#225;rton G.; Baliber, Nairn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 2, pp. 1145-1158 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691.1145S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493L..35D</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based K-band detection of thermal emission from the exoplanet TrES-3b</title>
			<authors>de Mooij, E. J. W.; Snellen, I. A. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 2, 2009, pp.L35-L38</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493L..35D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PABei..27...14Z</bibcode>
			<title>The detection methods and statistical characteristics of exoplanet.</title>
			<authors>Zhang, N.; Ji, J.-H.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 27, 14-28 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PABei..27...14Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MmSAI..80..318S</bibcode>
			<title>Probing structural and evolutionary properties of exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Latham, D. W.; Torres, G.; Carney, B. W.; Laird, J. B.; Stefanik, R. P.; Boss, A. P.; Charbonneau, D.; O'Donovan, F. T.; Holman, M. J.; Winn, J. N.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ&#224; Astronomica Italiana, v.80, p.318 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MmSAI..80..318S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689..492K</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Orbital Parameters through Planetary Transit Monitoring</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 1, pp. 492-498.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689..492K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1341C</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Knutson, Heather A.; Barman, Travis; Allen, Lori E.; Mayor, Michel; Megeath, S. Thomas; Queloz, Didier; Udry, St&#233;phane</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1341-1348.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1341C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1302B</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting the Yields of Photometric Surveys for Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1302-1330.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1302B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...683L.195S</bibcode>
			<title>Cloudy Atmosphere of the Extrasolar Planet HD 189733b: A Possible Explanation of the Detected B-Band Polarization</title>
			<authors>Sengupta, Sujan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 683, Issue 2, pp. L195-L198.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...683L.195S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AJ....136..267W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. VIII. Six Occultations of the Exoplanet TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Shporer, Avi; Fern&#225;ndez, Jos&#233;; Mazeh, Tsevi; Latham, David W.; Charbonneau, David; Everett, Mark E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 136, Issue 1, pp. 267-271 (2008).</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AJ....136..267W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1419F</bibcode>
			<title>A Unified Theory for the Atmospheres of the Hot and Very Hot Jupiters: Two Classes of Irradiated Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Lodders, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1419-1435.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1419F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.384.1097K</bibcode>
			<title>SuperWASP-N extrasolar planet candidates from fields 06h &lt; RA &lt; 16h</title>
			<authors>Kane, S. R.; Clarkson, W. I.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Christian, D. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Lister, T. A.; Street, R. A.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Keenan, F. P.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J.; Parley, N. R.; Pollacco, D. L.; Ryans, R.; Skillen, I.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 384, Issue 3, pp. 1097-1108.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.384.1097K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...675L.113W</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-4b: A 12th Magnitude Transiting Hot Jupiter in the Southern Hemisphere</title>
			<authors>Wilson, D. M.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Smalley, B.; Lister, T. A.; Bentley, S. J.; Blecha, A.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Kane, S. R.; Marmier, M.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pollacco, D.; Pont, F.; Ryans, R.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 675, Issue 2, pp. L113-L116.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...675L.113W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671..861H</bibcode>
			<title>Two Classes of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. 861-871.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671..861H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...668L.171B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectral Models of the Planet HD 209458b with a Thermal Inversion and Water Emission Bands</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Knutson, H. A.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 668, Issue 2, pp. L171-L174.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...668L.171B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667L.191L</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission from Transiting Very Hot Jupiters: Prospects for Ground-based Detection at Optical Wavelengths</title>
			<authors>L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 2, pp. L191-L194.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667L.191L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.380.1230C</bibcode>
			<title>Efficient identification of exoplanetary transit candidates from SuperWASP light curves</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Wilson, D. M.; West, R. G.; Hebb, L.; Wang, X.-B.; Aigrain, S.; Bouchy, F.; Christian, D. J.; Clarkson, W. I.; Enoch, B.; Esposito, M.; Guenther, E.; Haswell, C. A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Loeillet, B.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Parley, N.; Pollacco, D.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 380, Issue 3, pp. 1230-1244.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.380.1230C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379..647L</bibcode>
			<title>SuperWASP-North extrasolar planet candidates: candidates from fields 17h&lt;RA&lt;18h</title>
			<authors>Lister, T. A.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Collier Cameron, A.; Clarkson, W. I.; Street, R. A.; Enoch, B.; Parley, N. R.; Christian, D. J.; Kane, S. R.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, Keith; Irwin, J.; Keenan, F. P.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J.; Pollacco, D. L.; Ryans, R.; Skillen, I.; Wheatley, P. J.; Barnes, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 379, Issue 2, pp. 647-662.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379..647L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...663L..37O</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-3: A Nearby, Massive, Transiting Hot Jupiter in a 31 Hour Orbit</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Brown, Timothy M.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Everett, Mark E.; Baliber, Nairn; Hidas, M&#225;rton G.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Deeg, Hans J.; Belmonte, Juan A.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Stefanik, Robert P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 663, Issue 1, pp. L37-L40.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...663L..37O</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742..116B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-20b-HAT-P-23b: Four Massive Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Kipping, D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Shporer, A.; B&#233;ky, B.; Buchhave, L. A.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ChA&amp;A..35..409Z</bibcode>
			<title>Observation and Research of the Transits of Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Zhang, Ji-Cheng; Cao, Chen; Song, Nan; Wang, Fei-Ge; Zhang, Xiao-Tong</authors>
			<journal>Chinese Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 35, Issue 4, p. 409-420.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ChA%26A..35..409Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Broadband Transmission Spectroscopy of the Super-Earth GJ 1214b Suggests a Low Mean Molecular Weight Atmosphere</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Miller-Ricci Kempton, Eliza; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman; Neilson, Hilding</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. 78 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...736...78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735L..12D</bibcode>
			<title>The High Albedo of the Hot Jupiter Kepler-7 b</title>
			<authors>Demory, Brice-Olivier; Seager, Sara; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Kjeldsen, Hans; Christensen-Dalsgaard, J&#248;rgen; Gillon, Micha&#235;l; Rowe, Jason F.; Welsh, William F.; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Dupree, Andrea; McCarthy, Don; Kulesa, Craig; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 735, Issue 1, article id. L12 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...735L..12D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414..108B</bibcode>
			<title>On the use of the Virtual Observatory to select calibrators for phase-referenced astrometry of exoplanet-host stars</title>
			<authors>Beust, H.; Bonneau, D.; Mourard, D.; Lafrasse, S.; Mella, G.; Duvert, G.; Chelli, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 1, pp. 108-115.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414..108B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...74G</bibcode>
			<title>Consequences of the Ejection and Disruption of Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Guillochon, James; Ramirez-Ruiz, Enrico; Lin, Douglas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...74G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...41B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in Five of the Exoplanetary Systems Studied by the NASA EPOXI Mission</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732...41B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.412.1181E</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision automated follow-up transit photometry with a 50-cm robotic telescope</title>
			<authors>Eibe, M. T.; Cuesta, L.; Ull&#225;n, A.; P&#233;rez-Verde, A.; Navas, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 412, Issue 2, pp. 1181-1186.</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.412.1181E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..49D</bibcode>
			<title>The GROUSE project. II. Detection of the Ks-band secondary eclipse of exoplanet HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>de Mooij, E. J. W.; de Kok, R. J.; Nefs, S. V.; Snellen, I. A. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A49</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..49D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..41L</bibcode>
			<title>Distorted, nonspherical transiting planets: impact on the transit depth and on the radius determination</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Lai, D.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A41</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...528A..41L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..85N</bibcode>
			<title>TASTE: The Asiago Search for Transit timing variations of Exoplanets. I. Overview and improved parameters for HAT-P-3b and HAT-P-14b</title>
			<authors>Nascimbeni, V.; Piotto, G.; Bedin, L. R.; Damasso, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A85</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..85N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63..301L</bibcode>
			<title>Physical Properties of the Transiting Planetary System TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Lee, Jae Woo; Youn, Jae-Hyuck; Kim, Seung-Lee; Lee, Chung-Uk; Koo, Jae-Rim</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.1, pp.301--307</journal>
			<date>2/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63..301L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411L..46V</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for detection of exoplanet magnetic fields through bow-shock observations during transits</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. L46-L50.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411L..46V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...30C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from WASP-12b: Detections of the Secondary Eclipse in Ks, H, and J</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Lafreniere, David; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...30C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...23B</bibcode>
			<title>Secondary Eclipse Photometry of WASP-4b with Warm Spitzer</title>
			<authors>Beerer, Ingrid M.; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Agol, Eric; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Deming, Drake; Desert, Jean-Michel; Langton, Jonathan; Laughlin, Gregory; Lewis, Nikole K.; Showman, Adam P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 23 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727...23B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...94C</bibcode>
			<title>System Parameters, Transit Times, and Secondary Eclipse Constraints of the Exoplanet Systems HAT-P-4, TrES-2, TrES-3, and WASP-3 from the NASA EPOXI Mission of Opportunity</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; A'Hearn, Michael F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 94 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726...94C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 29, 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1494C</bibcode>
			<title>Characterizing transiting extrasolar planets with narrow-band photometry and GTC/OSIRIS</title>
			<authors>Col&#243;n, Knicole D.; Ford, Eric B.; Lee, Brian; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Blake, Cullen H.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1494-1501.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1494C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723.1436C</bibcode>
			<title>A New 24 mum Phase Curve for upsilo Andromedae b</title>
			<authors>Crossfield, Ian J. M.; Hansen, Brad M. S.; Harrington, Joseph; Cho, James Y.-K.; Deming, Drake; Menou, Kristen; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1446 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723.1436C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2625M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation in exoplanet WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Ginski, Ch.; Adam, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2625-2631.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2625M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..920C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from TrES-3b: A Ks-band Detection and an H-band Upper Limit on the Depth of the Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Lafreni&#232;re, David; Albert, Loic</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 920-927 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718..920C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717.1084C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-Infrared Thermal Emission from the Hot Jupiter TrES-2b: Ground-based Detection of the Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Lafreniere, David; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. 1084-1091 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717.1084C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1047B</bibcode>
			<title>A Search for Additional Planets in the NASA EPOXI Observations of the Exoplanet System GJ 436</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Charbonneau, David; Deming, Drake; Holman, Matthew J.; Fabrycky, Daniel; A'Hearn, Michael F.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Barry, Richard K.; Kuchner, Marc J.; Livengood, Timothy A.; Hewagama, Tilak; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Hampton, Don L.; Lisse, Carey M.; Seager, Sara; Veverka, Joseph F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1047-1059 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...716.1047B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.404L.114G</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based detection of thermal emission from the exoplanet WASP-19b</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Aigrain, S.; Pollacco, D. L.; Barros, S. C. C.; Hebb, L.; Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; West, R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 404, Issue 1, pp. L114-L118.</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.404L.114G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714...13A</bibcode>
			<title>Lack of Transit Timing Variations of OGLE-TR-111b: A Re-Analysis with Six New Epochs</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; L&#243;pez-Morales, M.; Elliot, J. L.; Seager, S.; Osip, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 714, Issue 1, pp. 13-24 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...714...13A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403.2111H</bibcode>
			<title>Tight constraints on the existence of additional planets around HD 189733&amp;dagger</title>
			<authors>Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Skillen, I.; Benn, C. R.; Gibson, N. P.; Pollacco, D.; Nesvorn&#253;, D.; Augusteijn, T.; Tulloch, S. M.; Joshi, Y. C.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 4, pp. 2111-2119.</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403.2111H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...513L...3A</bibcode>
			<title>H-band thermal emission from the 19-h period planet WASP-19b</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Barman, T. S.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 513, id.L3</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...513L...3A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..374F</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Fressin, Francois; Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Mandushev, Georgi; Spiegel, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 374-379 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..374F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..111M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission and Tidal Heating of the Heavy and Eccentric Planet XO-3b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; Greene, Tom; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Deming, Drake L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 111-118 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..111M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710.1551O</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Planetary Emission from the Exoplanet Tres-2 Using Spitzer/IRAC</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Harrington, Joseph; Madhusudhan, N.; Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 2, pp. 1551-1556 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710.1551O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...710...97C</bibcode>
			<title>Studying the Atmosphere of the Exoplanet HAT-P-7b Via Secondary Eclipse Measurements with EPOXI, Spitzer, and Kepler</title>
			<authors>Christiansen, Jessie L.; Ballard, Sarah; Charbonneau, David; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Seager, Sara; Holman, Matthew J.; Wellnitz, Dennis D.; Deming, Drake; A'Hearn, Michael F.; the EPOXI Team</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 710, Issue 1, pp. 97-104 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...710...97C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...511A...3G</bibcode>
			<title>The thermal emission of the young and massive planet CoRoT-2b at 4.5 and 8 mum</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Lanotte, A. A.; Barman, T.; Miller, N.; Demory, B.-O.; Deleuil, M.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Bouchy, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Deeg, H. J.; Fortney, J. J.; Fridlund, M.; Harrington, J.; Magain, P.; Moutou, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 511, id.A3</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...511A...3G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401.1917G</bibcode>
			<title>A transit timing analysis of seven RISE light curves of the exoplanet system HAT-P-3</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Pollacco, D. L.; Barros, S.; Benn, C.; Christian, D.; Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Joshi, Y. C.; Keenan, F. P.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Steele, I. A.; Todd, I.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 3, pp. 1917-1923.</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401.1917G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707.1707R</bibcode>
			<title>Ks-Band Detection of Thermal Emission and Color Constraints to CoRoT-1b: A Low-Albedo Planet with Inefficient Atmospheric Energy Redistribution and a Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Rogers, Justin C.; Apai, D&#225;niel; L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Sing, David K.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 2, article id. 1707-1716 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707.1707R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.399..287S</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision photometry by telescope defocussing - II. The transiting planetary system WASP-4</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Dominik, M.; Hornstrup, A.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Ricci, D.; Th&#246;ne, C. C.; Anguita, T.; Bozza, V.; Novati, S. Calchi; Harps&#248;e, K.; Mancini, L.; Masi, G.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Scarpetta, G.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.; Zub, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 399, Issue 1, pp. 287-294.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.399..287S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704.1107L</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Transiting Planet and Eight Eclipsing Binaries in HATNet Field G205</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Torres, Guillermo; Stefanik, Robert P.; Noyes, Robert W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Butler, R. Paul; Sipocz, Brigitta; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Vogt, Steven S.; Hartman, Joel D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; L&#225;z&#225;r, J&#243;zsef; Papp, Istv&#225;n; S&#225;ri, P&#225;l</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 2, pp. 1107-1119 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704.1107L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..359G</bibcode>
			<title>VLT transit and occultation photometry for the bloated planet CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Demory, B.-O.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Barman, T.; Hebb, L.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Deleuil, M.; Magain, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.359-367</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..359G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700.1078G</bibcode>
			<title>A Transit Timing Analysis of Nine Rise Light Curves of the Exoplanet System TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Barros, S.; Joshi, Y. C.; Todd, I.; Keenan, F. P.; Skillen, I.; Benn, C.; Christian, D.; Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Steele, I. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 1078-1085 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700.1078G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698..558G</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric Detection of a Transit of HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Garcia-Melendo, E.; McCullough, P. R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 1, pp. 558-561 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698..558G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...500L..45M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of orbital parameter changes in the TrES-2 exoplanet?</title>
			<authors>Mislis, D.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 500, Issue 3, 2009, pp.L45-L49</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...500L..45M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1116W</bibcode>
			<title>Nondetection of Polarized, Scattered Light from the HD 189733b Hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Wiktorowicz, Sloane J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1116-1124 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1116W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498..567D</bibcode>
			<title>Binarity of transit host stars. Implications for planetary parameters</title>
			<authors>Daemgen, S.; Hormuth, F.; Brandner, W.; Bergfors, C.; Janson, M.; Hippler, S.; Henning, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 2, 2009, pp.567-574</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498..567D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...691.1145S</bibcode>
			<title>A New Spectroscopic and Photometric Analysis of the Transiting Planet Systems TrES-3 and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, Alessandro; Torres, Guillermo; Charbonneau, David; Winn, Joshua N.; Korzennik, Sylvain G.; Holman, Matthew J.; Latham, David W.; Laird, John B.; Fernandez, Jos&#233;; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward; Everett, Mark E.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Belmonte, Juan A.; Deeg, Hans J.; Brown, Timothy N.; Hidas, M&#225;rton G.; Baliber, Nairn</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 691, Issue 2, pp. 1145-1158 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...691.1145S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...493L..35D</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based K-band detection of thermal emission from the exoplanet TrES-3b</title>
			<authors>de Mooij, E. J. W.; Snellen, I. A. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 493, Issue 2, 2009, pp.L35-L38</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...493L..35D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PABei..27...14Z</bibcode>
			<title>The detection methods and statistical characteristics of exoplanet.</title>
			<authors>Zhang, N.; Ji, J.-H.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 27, 14-28 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PABei..27...14Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MmSAI..80..318S</bibcode>
			<title>Probing structural and evolutionary properties of exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Latham, D. W.; Torres, G.; Carney, B. W.; Laird, J. B.; Stefanik, R. P.; Boss, A. P.; Charbonneau, D.; O'Donovan, F. T.; Holman, M. J.; Winn, J. N.</authors>
			<journal>Memorie della Societ&#224; Astronomica Italiana, v.80, p.318 (2009)</journal>
			<date>0/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MmSAI..80..318S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...689..492K</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Orbital Parameters through Planetary Transit Monitoring</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; von Braun, Kaspar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 689, Issue 1, pp. 492-498.</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...689..492K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1341C</bibcode>
			<title>The Broadband Infrared Emission Spectrum of the Exoplanet HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Charbonneau, David; Knutson, Heather A.; Barman, Travis; Allen, Lori E.; Mayor, Michel; Megeath, S. Thomas; Queloz, Didier; Udry, St&#233;phane</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1341-1348.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1341C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1302B</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting the Yields of Photometric Surveys for Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1302-1330.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1302B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...683L.195S</bibcode>
			<title>Cloudy Atmosphere of the Extrasolar Planet HD 189733b: A Possible Explanation of the Detected B-Band Polarization</title>
			<authors>Sengupta, Sujan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 683, Issue 2, pp. L195-L198.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...683L.195S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008AJ....136..267W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. VIII. Six Occultations of the Exoplanet TrES-3</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Shporer, Avi; Fern&#225;ndez, Jos&#233;; Mazeh, Tsevi; Latham, David W.; Charbonneau, David; Everett, Mark E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 136, Issue 1, pp. 267-271 (2008).</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008AJ....136..267W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1419F</bibcode>
			<title>A Unified Theory for the Atmospheres of the Hot and Very Hot Jupiters: Two Classes of Irradiated Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Fortney, J. J.; Lodders, K.; Marley, M. S.; Freedman, R. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1419-1435.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1419F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.384.1097K</bibcode>
			<title>SuperWASP-N extrasolar planet candidates from fields 06h &lt; RA &lt; 16h</title>
			<authors>Kane, S. R.; Clarkson, W. I.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Christian, D. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Lister, T. A.; Street, R. A.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Keenan, F. P.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J.; Parley, N. R.; Pollacco, D. L.; Ryans, R.; Skillen, I.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 384, Issue 3, pp. 1097-1108.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.384.1097K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...675L.113W</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-4b: A 12th Magnitude Transiting Hot Jupiter in the Southern Hemisphere</title>
			<authors>Wilson, D. M.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Smalley, B.; Lister, T. A.; Bentley, S. J.; Blecha, A.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Kane, S. R.; Marmier, M.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pollacco, D.; Pont, F.; Ryans, R.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 675, Issue 2, pp. L113-L116.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...675L.113W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...671..861H</bibcode>
			<title>Two Classes of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 671, Issue 1, pp. 861-871.</journal>
			<date>12/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...671..861H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...668L.171B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectral Models of the Planet HD 209458b with a Thermal Inversion and Water Emission Bands</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Knutson, H. A.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 668, Issue 2, pp. L171-L174.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...668L.171B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...667L.191L</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission from Transiting Very Hot Jupiters: Prospects for Ground-based Detection at Optical Wavelengths</title>
			<authors>L&#243;pez-Morales, Mercedes; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 667, Issue 2, pp. L191-L194.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...667L.191L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.380.1230C</bibcode>
			<title>Efficient identification of exoplanetary transit candidates from SuperWASP light curves</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Wilson, D. M.; West, R. G.; Hebb, L.; Wang, X.-B.; Aigrain, S.; Bouchy, F.; Christian, D. J.; Clarkson, W. I.; Enoch, B.; Esposito, M.; Guenther, E.; Haswell, C. A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Loeillet, B.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Parley, N.; Pollacco, D.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 380, Issue 3, pp. 1230-1244.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.380.1230C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379..647L</bibcode>
			<title>SuperWASP-North extrasolar planet candidates: candidates from fields 17h&lt;RA&lt;18h</title>
			<authors>Lister, T. A.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Collier Cameron, A.; Clarkson, W. I.; Street, R. A.; Enoch, B.; Parley, N. R.; Christian, D. J.; Kane, S. R.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, Keith; Irwin, J.; Keenan, F. P.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J.; Pollacco, D. L.; Ryans, R.; Skillen, I.; Wheatley, P. J.; Barnes, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 379, Issue 2, pp. 647-662.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379..647L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...663L..37O</bibcode>
			<title>TrES-3: A Nearby, Massive, Transiting Hot Jupiter in a 31 Hour Orbit</title>
			<authors>O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Mandushev, Georgi; Dunham, Edward W.; Brown, Timothy M.; Latham, David W.; Torres, Guillermo; Sozzetti, Alessandro; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Everett, Mark E.; Baliber, Nairn; Hidas, M&#225;rton G.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Rabus, Markus; Deeg, Hans J.; Belmonte, Juan A.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Stefanik, Robert P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 663, Issue 1, pp. L37-L40.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...663L..37O</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
