<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141....8S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-37b: A 1.8 M J Exoplanet Transiting a Metal-poor Star</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hebb, L.; Pollacco, D.; Smalley, B.; Todd, I.; Butters, O. W.; H&#233;brard, G.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Santerne, A.; Street, R. A.; Skillen, I.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Anderson, D. R.; Bento, J.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Horne, K.; Keenan, F. P.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Segransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Stempels, H. C.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 1, article id. 8 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141....8S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724.1108J</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect of Exoplanet Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Cochran, William D.; Welsh, William F.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John Asher; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Howard, Andrew W.; MacQueen, Phillip; Orosz, Jerome A.; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Allen, Christopher; Tenenbaum, Peter; Wu, Hayley; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Cote, Miles T.; McCauliff, Sean; Girouard, Forrest R.; Gunter, Jay P.; Wohler, Bill; Hall, Jennifer R.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Kamal Uddin, AKM; Wu, Michael S.; Bhavsar, Paresh A.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Pletcher, David L.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, pp. 1108-1119 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724.1108J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.2007M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-22 b: A Transiting "Hot Jupiter" Planet in a Hierarchical Triple System</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Cegla, H.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 2007-2012 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.2007M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.2625M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation in exoplanet WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuh&#228;user, R.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Ginski, Ch.; Adam, Ch.; Marka, C.; Moualla, M.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 4, pp. 2625-2631.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.2625M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722L.224B</bibcode>
			<title>Confirmation of a Retrograde Orbit for Exoplanet WASP-17b</title>
			<authors>Bayliss, Daniel D. R.; Winn, Joshua N.; Mardling, Rosemary A.; Sackett, Penny D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 722, Issue 2, pp. L224-L227 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722L.224B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407..507C</bibcode>
			<title>Line-profile tomography of exoplanet transits - II. A gas-giant planet transiting a rapidly rotating A5 star</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Guenther, E.; Smalley, B.; McDonald, I.; Hebb, L.; Andersen, J.; Augusteijn, Th.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Cochran, W. D.; Endl, M.; Fossey, S. J.; Hartmann, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Telting, J.; Waldmann, I. P.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 1, pp. 507-514.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407..507C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720..337S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-24 b: A New Transiting Close-in Hot Jupiter Orbiting a Late F-star</title>
			<authors>Street, R. A.; Simpson, E.; Barros, S. C. C.; Pollacco, D.; Joshi, Y.; Todd, I.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Parley, N.; Stempels, E.; Hebb, L.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Queloz, D.; Segransan, D.; Pepe, F.; Udry, S.; Lister, T. A.; Depagne, &#201;.; West, R. G.; Norton, A. J.; Smalley, B.; Hellier, C.; Anderson, D. R.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Bentley, S. J.; Skillen, I.; Gillon, M.; Wheatley, P.; Bento, J.; Cathaway-Kjontvedt, P.; Christian, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 1, pp. 337-343 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720..337S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..97G</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XII. CoRoT-12b: a short-period low-density planet transiting a solar analog star</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Hatzes, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Fridlund, M.; Deleuil, M.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Barnes, S. I.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J. C.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H&#233; brard, G.; Jorda, L.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Montalb&#225;n, J.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A97</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..97G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A..10C</bibcode>
			<title>Dynamical stability analysis of the HD 202206 system and constraints to the planetary orbits</title>
			<authors>Couetdic, J.; Laskar, J.; Correia, A. C. M.; Mayor, M.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A10</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...519A..10C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..653N</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-Orbit Alignment of the TrES-4 Transiting Planetary System and Possible Additional Radial-Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Winn, Joshua N.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.3, pp.653--660</journal>
			<date>6/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..653N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713L.140L</bibcode>
			<title>Kepler-7b: A Transiting Planet with Unusually Low Density</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Brown, Timothy M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Cochran, William D.; Dunham, Edward W.; Fur&#233;sz, Gabor; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Monet, David G.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. L140-L144 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713L.140L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...513L...3A</bibcode>
			<title>H-band thermal emission from the 19-h period planet WASP-19b</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Barman, T. S.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 513, id.L3</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...513L...3A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403..151C</bibcode>
			<title>Line-profile tomography of exoplanet transits - I. The Doppler shadow of HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Bruce, V. A.; Miller, G. R. M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 1, pp. 151-158.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403..151C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712L..86P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Variations for Inclined and Retrograde Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.; Veras, Dimitri</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. L86-L92 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712L..86P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722L.224B</bibcode>
			<title>Confirmation of a Retrograde Orbit for Exoplanet WASP-17b</title>
			<authors>Bayliss, Daniel D. R.; Winn, Joshua N.; Mardling, Rosemary A.; Sackett, Penny D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 722, Issue 2, pp. L224-L227 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...722L.224B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1048M</bibcode>
			<title>The determination of planetary structure in tidally relaxed inclined systems</title>
			<authors>Mardling, Rosemary A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1048-1069.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1048M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.1867S</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit alignment of the transiting exoplanet WASP-3b from Rossiter-McLaughlin observations</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Pollacco, D.; H&#233;brard, G.; Gibson, N. P.; Barros, S. C. C.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Miller, G. R. M.; Watson, C. A.; Keenan, F. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 1867-1872.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.1867S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..33E</bibcode>
			<title>An improved method for estimating the masses of stars with transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Parley, N. R.; Hebb, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A33</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..33E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..421T</bibcode>
			<title>A Prograde, Low-inclination Orbit for the Very Hot Jupiter WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Tripathi, Anjali; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Halverson, Sam; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Holman, Matthew J.; de Kleer, Katherine R.; Carter, Joshua A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Cabrera, Nicole E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 421-428 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..421T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A.103S</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos preliminary astrometric masses for the two close-in companions to HD 131664 and HD 43848. A brown dwarf and a low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Desidera, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A103</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A.103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
