<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746..111T</bibcode>
			<title>Warm Spitzer Observations of Three Hot Exoplanets: XO-4b, HAT-P-6b, and HAT-P-8b</title>
			<authors>Todorov, Kamen O.; Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather A.; Burrows, Adam; Sada, Pedro V.; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric; Desert, Jean-Michel; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Charbonneau, David; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan; Showman, Adam P.; Lewis, Nikole K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 1, article id. 111 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...746..111T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012Natur.481..448S</bibcode>
			<title>Astronomy: A new class of planet</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 481, Issue 7382, pp. 448-449 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012Natur.481..448S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..203J</bibcode>
			<title>A Survey of Alkali Line Absorption in Exoplanetary Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Jensen, Adam G.; Redfield, Seth; Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Koesterke, Lars; Barman, Travis S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 203 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..203J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...72N</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Distributions of Close-in Planets and Distant Planets Formed by Scattering and Dynamical Tides</title>
			<authors>Nagasawa, M.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 72 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...72N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...10B</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Misalignment of KOI-13.01 from Its Gravity-darkened Kepler Transit Lightcurve</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.; Linscott, Ethan; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 10 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...10B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....9F</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Atmospheric Characterization of Giant Planet Kepler-12b: An Inflated Radius Outlier</title>
			<authors>