<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...35N</bibcode>
			<title>Spitzer Secondary Eclipses of WASP-18b</title>
			<authors>Nymeyer, Sarah; Harrington, Joseph; Hardy, Ryan A.; Stevenson, Kevin B.; Campo, Christopher J.; Madhusudhan, Nikku; Collier-Cameron, Andrew; Loredo, Thomas J.; Blecic, Jasmina; Bowman, William C.; Britt, Christopher B. T.; Cubillos, Patricio; Hellier, Coel; Gillon, Michael; Maxted, Pierre F. L.; Hebb, Leslie; Wheatley, Peter J.; Pollacco, Don; Anderson, David R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. 35 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742...35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534L...6T</bibcode>
			<title>The time dependence of hot Jupiters' orbital inclinations</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.L6</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...534L...6T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..83B</bibcode>
			<title>SOPHIE velocimetry of Kepler transit candidates. III. KOI-423b: an 18 MJup transiting companion around an F7IV star</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Moutou, C.; Deleuil, M.; D&#237; az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Gry, C.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H&#233; brard, G.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A83</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...533A..83B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A...3S</bibcode>
			<title>The corona and companion of CoRoT-2a. Insights from X-rays and optical spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Schr&#246;ter, S.; Czesla, S.; Wolter, U.; M&#252;ller, H. M.; Huber, K. F.; Schmitt, J. H. M. M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A3</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A...3S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A..50L</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining tidal dissipation in F-type main-sequence stars: the case of CoRoT-11</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Damiani, C.; Gandolfi, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A50</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A..50L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...731....1S</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Brown Dwarf Like Objects in the Core of NGC 3603</title>
			<authors>Spezzi, Loredana; Beccari, Giacomo; De Marchi, Guido; Young, Erick T.; Paresce, Francesco; Dopita, Michael A.; Andersen, Morten; Panagia, Nino; Balick, Bruce; Bond, Howard E.; Calzetti, Daniela; Carollo, C. Marcella; Disney, Michael J.; Frogel, Jay A.; Hall, Donald N. B.; Holtzman, Jon A.; Kimble, Randy A.; McCarthy, Patrick J.; O'Connell, Robert W.; Ryan, Russell E., Jr.; Saha, Abhijit; Silk, Joseph I.; Trauger, John T.; Walker, Alistair R.; Whitmore, Bradley C.; Windhorst, Rogier A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 731, Issue 1, article id. 1 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...731....1S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527L..11H</bibcode>
			<title>The retrograde orbit of the HAT-P-6b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Ehrenreich, D.; Bouchy, F.; Delfosse, X.; Moutou, C.; Arnold, L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.L11</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527L..11H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1680S</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision photometry by telescope defocusing - III. The transiting planetary system WASP-2</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Mancini, L.; Novati, S. Calchi; Dominik, M.; Glitrup, M.; Hinse, T. C.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Mathiasen, M.; Ricci, D.; Maier, G.; Zimmer, F.; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Bruni, I.; Burgdorf, M.; Dall'Ora, M.; Finet, F.; Harps&#248;e, K.; Hundertmark, M.; Liebig, C.; Rahvar, S.; Scarpetta, G.; Skottfelt, J.; Smalley, B.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1680-1688.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1680S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.404.1849B</bibcode>
			<title>On internal wave breaking and tidal dissipation near the centre of a solar-type star</title>
			<authors>Barker, Adrian J.; Ogilvie, Gordon I.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 404, Issue 4, pp. 1849-1868.</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.404.1849B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..33E</bibcode>
			<title>An improved method for estimating the masses of stars with transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Parley, N. R.; Hebb, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A33</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..33E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708..224H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-19b: The Shortest Period Transiting Exoplanet Yet Discovered</title>
			<authors>Hebb, L.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Hellier, C.; Anderson, D. R.; Pollacco, D.; Gillon, M.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Horne, K.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 1, pp. 224-231 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...708..224H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707..167S</bibcode>
			<title>Physical Properties of the 0.94-Day Period Transiting Planetary System WASP-18</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Dominik, M.; Glitrup, M.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Mathiasen, M.; Anderson, D. R.; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Burgdorf, M.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Harps&#248;e, K.; Hessman, F.; Hundertmark, M.; Maier, G.; Mancini, L.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Skottfelt, J.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.; Zimmer, F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, article id. 167-172 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707..167S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009Natur.460.1098H</bibcode>
			<title>An orbital period of 0.94days for the hot-Jupiter planet WASP-18b</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 460, Issue 7259, pp. 1098-1100 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009Natur.460.1098H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>1962RGOB...49....3C</bibcode>
			<title>Standard magnitudes in the E regions.</title>
			<authors>Cousins, A. W. J.; Stoy, R. H.</authors>
			<journal>Royal Observatory Bulletin, 49 (1962)</journal>
			<date>0/1962</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/1962RGOB...49....3C</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
