<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A.130S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-34b: a near-grazing transiting sub-Jupiter-mass exoplanet in a hierarchical triple system</title>
			<authors>Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Gillon, M.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wood, P. L.; Bento, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A130</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...526A.130S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.410.1631E</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-25b: a 0.6 MJ planet in the Southern hemisphere</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Cameron, A. Collier; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Lendl, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Simpson, E.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 410, Issue 3, pp. 1631-1636.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.410.1631E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.2007M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-22 b: A Transiting "Hot Jupiter" Planet in a Hierarchical Triple System</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Cegla, H.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 2007-2012 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010AJ....140.2007M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.410.1631E</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-25b: a 0.6 MJ planet in the Southern hemisphere</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Cameron, A. Collier; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Lendl, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Simpson, E.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 410, Issue 3, pp. 1631-1636.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.410.1631E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
