<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751...96P</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Tidal Dissipation in Stars from the Destruction Rates of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Penev, Kaloyan; Jackson, Brian; Spada, Federico; Thom, Nicole</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. 96 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...751...96P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...95L</bibcode>
			<title>The Sub-Saturn Mass Transiting Planet HAT-P-12b</title>
			<authors>Lee, Jae Woo; Youn, Jae-Hyuck; Kim, Seung-Lee; Lee, Chung-Uk; Hinse, Tobias Cornelius</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 4, article id. 95 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012AJ....143...95L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.419.1248B</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision transit observations of the exoplanet WASP-13b with the RISE instrument</title>
			<authors>Barros, S. C. C.; Pollacco, D. L.; Gibson, N. P.; Keenan, F. P.; Skillen, I.; Steele, I. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 419, Issue 2, pp. 1248-1253.</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012MNRAS.419.1248B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416.2593B</bibcode>
			<title>A lower mass for the exoplanet WASP-21b</title>
			<authors>Barros, S. C. C.; Pollacco, D. L.; Gibson, N. P.; Howarth, I. D.; Keenan, F. P.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Steele, I. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 416, Issue 4, pp. 2593-2599.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.416.2593B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734..109B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-27b: A Hot Jupiter Transiting a G Star on a 3 Day Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bky, B.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Jordn, A.; Arriagada, P.; Bayliss, D.; Kiss, L. L.; Kovcs, Gza; Quinn, S. N.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 2, article id. 109 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...734..109B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.410.1631E</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-25b: a 0.6 MJ planet in the Southern hemisphere</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Cameron, A. Collier; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Lendl, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Simpson, E.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 410, Issue 3, pp. 1631-1636.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.410.1631E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...52H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-18b and HAT-P-19b: Two Low-density Saturn-mass Planets Transiting Metal-rich K Stars</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Sato, B.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Howard, A. W.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Fresz, G.; Perumpilly, G.; Bky, B.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Csubry, Z.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id. 52 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...726...52H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723L..60H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-29b: A Saturn-sized Transiting Exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Enoch, B.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S gransan, D.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. L60-L63 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...723L..60H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A..98B</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-21b: a hot-Saturn exoplanet transiting a thick disc star</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Hebb, L.; Skillen, I.; Collier Cameron, A.; Smalley, B.; Udry, S.; Anderson, D. R.; Boisse, I.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hbrard, G.; Hellier, C.; Joshi, Y.; Kane, S. R.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Smith, A. M. S.; Stempels, H. C.; Street, R.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A98</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...519A..98B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...95L</bibcode>
			<title>The Sub-Saturn Mass Transiting Planet HAT-P-12b</title>
			<authors>Lee, Jae Woo; Youn, Jae-Hyuck; Kim, Seung-Lee; Lee, Chung-Uk; Hinse, Tobias Cornelius</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 4, article id. 95 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012AJ....143...95L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...81S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-36b: A New Transiting Planet around a Metal-poor G-dwarf, and an Investigation into Analyses Based on a Single Transit Light Curve</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Barros, S. C. C.; Jehin, E.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Southworth, J.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 4, article id. 81 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012AJ....143...81S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416.2593B</bibcode>
			<title>A lower mass for the exoplanet WASP-21b</title>
			<authors>Barros, S. C. C.; Pollacco, D. L.; Gibson, N. P.; Howarth, I. D.; Keenan, F. P.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Steele, I. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 416, Issue 4, pp. 2593-2599.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.416.2593B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..40F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-39b: a highly inflated Saturn-mass planet orbiting a late G-type star</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Anderson, D. R.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Boisse, I.; Hbrard, G.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...531A..40F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...52H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-18b and HAT-P-19b: Two Low-density Saturn-mass Planets Transiting Metal-rich K Stars</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Sato, B.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Howard, A. W.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Fresz, G.; Perumpilly, G.; Bky, B.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Csubry, Z.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id. 52 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...726...52H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141....8S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-37b: A 1.8 M J Exoplanet Transiting a Metal-poor Star</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hebb, L.; Pollacco, D.; Smalley, B.; Todd, I.; Butters, O. W.; Hbrard, G.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Santerne, A.; Street, R. A.; Skillen, I.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Anderson, D. R.; Bento, J.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Horne, K.; Keenan, F. P.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Segransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Stempels, H. C.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 1, article id. 8 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....141....8S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; Sgransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...519A..98B</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-21b: a hot-Saturn exoplanet transiting a thick disc star</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; Hebb, L.; Skillen, I.; Collier Cameron, A.; Smalley, B.; Udry, S.; Anderson, D. R.; Boisse, I.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hbrard, G.; Hellier, C.; Joshi, Y.; Kane, S. R.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Smith, A. M. S.; Stempels, H. C.; Street, R.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 519, id.A98</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...519A..98B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
