<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..115D</bibcode>
			<title>TERMS Photometry of Known Transiting Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Dragomir, Diana; Kane, Stephen R.; Pilyavsky, Genady; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Ciardi, David R.; Gazak, J. Zachary; Gelino, Dawn M.; Payne, Alan; Rabus, Markus; Ramirez, Solange V.; von Braun, Kaspar; Wright, Jason T.; Wyatt, Pamela</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 4, article id. 115 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142..115D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..60A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-31b: a low-density planet transiting a metal-poor, late-F-type dwarf star</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Gillon, M.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S gransan, D.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A60</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..60A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..40F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-39b: a highly inflated Saturn-mass planet orbiting a late G-type star</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Anderson, D. R.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Boisse, I.; Hbrard, G.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..40F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734..109B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-27b: A Hot Jupiter Transiting a G Star on a 3 Day Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bky, B.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Jordn, A.; Arriagada, P.; Bayliss, D.; Kiss, L. L.; Kovcs, Gza; Quinn, S. N.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 2, article id. 109 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...734..109B</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.423.1503B</bibcode>
			<title>Rossiter-McLaughlin effect measurements for WASP-16, WASP-25 and WASP-31</title>
			<authors>Brown, D. J. A.; Cameron, A. Collier; Anderson, D. R.; Enoch, B.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Miller, G. R. M.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Simpson, E.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Gillon, M.; Hbrard, G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 423, Issue 2, pp. 1503-1520.</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.423.1503B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418.1039M</bibcode>
			<title>UBV(RI)C photometry of transiting planet hosting stars</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Koen, C.; Smalley, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 418, Issue 2, pp. 1039-1042.</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.418.1039M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142..115D</bibcode>
			<title>TERMS Photometry of Known Transiting Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Dragomir, Diana; Kane, Stephen R.; Pilyavsky, Genady; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Ciardi, David R.; Gazak, J. Zachary; Gelino, Dawn M.; Payne, Alan; Rabus, Markus; Ramirez, Solange V.; von Braun, Kaspar; Wright, Jason T.; Wyatt, Pamela</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 4, article id. 115 (2011).</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142..115D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..60A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-31b: a low-density planet transiting a metal-poor, late-F-type dwarf star</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Gillon, M.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S gransan, D.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A60</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..60A</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
