<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..684B</bibcode>
			<title>The NIRSPEC Ultracool Dwarf Radial Velocity Survey</title>
			<authors>Blake, Cullen H.; Charbonneau, David; White, Russel J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 684-706 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..684B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..653N</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-Orbit Alignment of the TrES-4 Transiting Planetary System and Possible Additional Radial-Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Winn, Joshua N.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.3, pp.653--660</journal>
			<date>6/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..653N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403..151C</bibcode>
			<title>Line-profile tomography of exoplanet transits - I. The Doppler shadow of HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Bruce, V. A.; Miller, G. R. M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 1, pp. 151-158.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403..151C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A.103S</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos preliminary astrometric masses for the two close-in companions to HD 131664 and HD 43848. A brown dwarf and a low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Desidera, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A103</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A.103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1104J</bibcode>
			<title>A Third Exoplanetary System with Misaligned Orbital and Stellar Spin Axes</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.; Albrecht, Simon; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Gazak, J. Zachary</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 884, pp.1104-1111</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1104J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASJ...61L..35N</bibcode>
			<title>First Evidence of a Retrograde Orbit of a Transiting Exoplanet HAT-P-7b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.61, No.5, pp.L35-L40</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASJ...61L..35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703L..99W</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-7: A Retrograde or Polar Orbit, and a Third Body</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Albrecht, Simon; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Crossfield, Ian J.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. L99-L103 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703L..99W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.2091W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Ingress and the Tilted Orbit of the Extraordinarily Eccentric Exoplanet HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Gazak, J. Zachary; Starkey, Donn; Ford, Eric B.; Col&#243;n, Knicole D.; Reyes, Francisco; Nortmann, Lisa; Dreizler, Stefan; Odewahn, Stephen; Welsh, William F.; Kadakia, Shimonee; Vanderbei, Robert J.; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Lockhart, Matthew; Crossfield, Ian J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Dantowitz, Ronald; Carter, Joshua A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. 2091-2100 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.2091W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1230F</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Spin-Orbit Alignment: Results from the Ensemble of Rossiter-McLaughlin Observations</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1230-1240 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1230F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394L..93M</bibcode>
			<title>On the various origins of close-in extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.; Ortolani, S.; Nagasawa, M.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. L93-L96.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394L..93M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392.1585C</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-10b: a 3MJ, gas-giant planet transiting a late-type K star</title>
			<authors>Christian, D. J.; Gibson, N. P.; Simpson, E. K.; Street, R. A.; Skillen, I.; Pollacco, D.; Collier Cameron, A.; Joshi, Y. C.; Keenan, F. P.; Stempels, H. C.; Haswell, C. A.; Horne, K.; Anderson, D. R.; Bentley, S.; Bouchy, F.; Clarkson, W. I.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hellier, C.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Lister, T. A.; Loeillet, B.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; McDonald, I.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Todd, I.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 4, pp. 1585-1590.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392.1585C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392.1532J</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-14b: 7.3 MJ transiting planet in an eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Joshi, Y. C.; Pollacco, D.; Cameron, A. Collier; Skillen, I.; Simpson, E.; Steele, I.; Street, R. A.; Stempels, H. C.; Christian, D. J.; Hebb, L.; Bouchy, F.; Gibson, N. P.; H&#233;brard, G.; Keenan, F. P.; Loeillet, B.; Meaburn, J.; Moutou, C.; Smalley, B.; Todd, I.; West, R. G.; Anderson, D. R.; Bentley, S.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; McDonald, I.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 4, pp. 1532-1538.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392.1532J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...492..603G</bibcode>
			<title>Updated parameters for the transiting exoplanet WASP-3b using RISE, a new fast camera for the Liverpool Telescope</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Pollacco, D.; Simpson, E. K.; Joshi, Y. C.; Todd, I.; Benn, C.; Christian, D.; Hrudkov&#225;, M.; Keenan, F. P.; Meaburn, J.; Skillen, I.; Steele, I. A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 492, Issue 2, 2008, pp.603-607</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...492..603G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...491..889D</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission . VI. CoRoT-Exo-3b: the first secure inhabitant of the brown-dwarf desert</title>
			<authors>Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Alonso, R.; Bouchy, F.; Rouan, D.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bruntt, H.; Bord&#233;, P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 491, Issue 3, 2008, pp.889-897</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...491..889D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origins of Eccentric Close-In Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Takeda, Genya; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. L29-L32.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686L..29M</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.1867S</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit alignment of the transiting exoplanet WASP-3b from Rossiter-McLaughlin observations</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Pollacco, D.; H&#233;brard, G.; Gibson, N. P.; Barros, S. C. C.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Cameron, A. Collier; Miller, G. R. M.; Watson, C. A.; Keenan, F. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 1867-1872.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.1867S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..33E</bibcode>
			<title>An improved method for estimating the masses of stars with transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Parley, N. R.; Hebb, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A33</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..33E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..421T</bibcode>
			<title>A Prograde, Low-inclination Orbit for the Very Hot Jupiter WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Tripathi, Anjali; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Halverson, Sam; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Holman, Matthew J.; de Kleer, Katherine R.; Carter, Joshua A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Cabrera, Nicole E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 421-428 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..421T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A.103S</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos preliminary astrometric masses for the two close-in companions to HD 131664 and HD 43848. A brown dwarf and a low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Desidera, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A103</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A.103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707..167S</bibcode>
			<title>Physical Properties of the 0.94-Day Period Transiting Planetary System WASP-18</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Dominik, M.; Glitrup, M.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Mathiasen, M.; Anderson, D. R.; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Burgdorf, M.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Harps&#248;e, K.; Hessman, F.; Hundertmark, M.; Maier, G.; Mancini, L.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Skottfelt, J.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.; Zimmer, F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, article id. 167-172 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707..167S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1104J</bibcode>
			<title>A Third Exoplanetary System with Misaligned Orbital and Stellar Spin Axes</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.; Albrecht, Simon; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Gazak, J. Zachary</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 884, pp.1104-1111</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1104J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392.1532J</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-14b: 7.3 MJ transiting planet in an eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Joshi, Y. C.; Pollacco, D.; Cameron, A. Collier; Skillen, I.; Simpson, E.; Steele, I.; Street, R. A.; Stempels, H. C.; Christian, D. J.; Hebb, L.; Bouchy, F.; Gibson, N. P.; H&#233;brard, G.; Keenan, F. P.; Loeillet, B.; Meaburn, J.; Moutou, C.; Smalley, B.; Todd, I.; West, R. G.; Anderson, D. R.; Bentley, S.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; McDonald, I.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 4, pp. 1532-1538.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392.1532J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...491..889D</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission . VI. CoRoT-Exo-3b: the first secure inhabitant of the brown-dwarf desert</title>
			<authors>Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Alonso, R.; Bouchy, F.; Rouan, D.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bruntt, H.; Bord&#233;, P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 491, Issue 3, 2008, pp.889-897</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...491..889D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origins of Eccentric Close-In Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Takeda, Genya; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. L29-L32.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686L..29M</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
