<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751...96P</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining Tidal Dissipation in Stars from the Destruction Rates of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Penev, Kaloyan; Jackson, Brian; Spada, Federico; Thom, Nicole</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. 96 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...751...96P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..100C</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling Multi-wavelength Stellar Astrometry. III. Determination of the Absolute Masses of Exoplanets and Their Host Stars</title>
			<authors>Coughlin, J. L.; Lpez-Morales, Mercedes</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 100 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...750..100C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...80Q</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-25b: A Hot-Jupiter Transiting a Moderately Faint G Star</title>
			<authors>Quinn, S. N.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Szentgyorgyi, A.; Fursz, G.; Buchhave, L. A.; Bky, B.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 80 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...745...80Q</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734..109B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-27b: A Hot Jupiter Transiting a G Star on a 3 Day Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bky, B.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Jordn, A.; Arriagada, P.; Bayliss, D.; Kiss, L. L.; Kovcs, Gza; Quinn, S. N.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 2, article id. 109 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...734..109B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A.130S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-34b: a near-grazing transiting sub-Jupiter-mass exoplanet in a hierarchical triple system</title>
			<authors>Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Gillon, M.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wood, P. L.; Bento, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A130</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...526A.130S</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...81S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-36b: A New Transiting Planet around a Metal-poor G-dwarf, and an Investigation into Analyses Based on a Single Transit Light Curve</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Barros, S. C. C.; Jehin, E.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Southworth, J.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 4, article id. 81 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012AJ....143...81S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418.1039M</bibcode>
			<title>UBV(RI)C photometry of transiting planet hosting stars</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Koen, C.; Smalley, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 418, Issue 2, pp. 1039-1042.</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.418.1039M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417.2166S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - IV. Thirty systems with space-based light curves</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 417, Issue 3, pp. 2166-2196.</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.417.2166S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...526A.130S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-34b: a near-grazing transiting sub-Jupiter-mass exoplanet in a hierarchical triple system</title>
			<authors>Smalley, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Gillon, M.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wood, P. L.; Bento, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 526, id.A130</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...526A.130S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; Sgransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
