<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751..112J</bibcode>
			<title>The EVIL-MC Model for Ellipsoidal Variations of Planet-hosting Stars and Applications to the HAT-P-7 System</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian K.; Lewis, Nikole K.; Barnes, Jason W.; Drake Deming, L.; Showman, Adam P.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...751..112J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751...86J</bibcode>
			<title>A Detection of Halpha in an Exoplanetary Exosphere</title>
			<authors>Jensen, Adam G.; Redfield, Seth; Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Koesterke, Lars; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 2, article id. 86 (2012).</journal>
			<date>6/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...751...86J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751...59P</bibcode>
			<title>The Effects of Irradiation on Hot Jovian Atmospheres: Heat Redistribution and Energy Dissipation</title>
			<authors>Perna, Rosalba; Heng, Kevin; Pont, Frdric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...751...59P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..133H</bibcode>
			<title>Stellar Wind Influence on Planetary Dynamos</title>
			<authors>Heyner, Daniel; Glassmeier, Karl-Heinz; Schmitt, Dieter</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 133 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...750..133H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..100C</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling Multi-wavelength Stellar Astrometry. III. Determination of the Absolute Masses of Exoplanets and Their Host Stars</title>
			<authors>Coughlin, J. L.; Lpez-Morales, Mercedes</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 100 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...750..100C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750...52N</bibcode>
			<title>Jupiter Models with Improved Ab Initio Hydrogen Equation of State (H-REOS.2)</title>
			<authors>Nettelmann, N.; Becker, A.; Holst, B.; Redmer, R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 1, article id. 52 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...750...52N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012NewA...17..356I</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital effects of non-isotropic mass depletion of the atmospheres of evaporating hot Jupiters in extrasolar systems</title>
			<authors>Iorio, Lorenzo</authors>
			<journal>New Astronomy, Volume 17, Issue 3, p. 356-361.</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012NewA...17..356I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...749..134H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-17b,c: A Transiting, Eccentric, Hot Saturn and a Long-period, Cold Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Howard, A. W.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Shporer, A.; Mazeh, T.; Kovcs, Gza; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Bky, B.; Butler, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 749, Issue 2, article id. 134 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...749..134H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AstL...38..180S</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of extrasolar planet transits with the automated telescopes of the Pulkovo Astronomical Observatory</title>
			<authors>Sokov, E. N.; Vereshchagina, I. A.; Gnedin, Yu. N.; Devyatkin, A. V.; Gorshanov, D. L.; Slesarenko, V. Yu.; Ivanov, A. V.; Naumov, K. N.; Zinov'ev, S. V.; Bekhteva, A. S.; Romas, E. S.; Karashevich, S. V.; Kupriyanov, V. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Letters, Volume 38, Issue 3, pp.180-190</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012AstL...38..180S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...747L..27F</bibcode>
			<title>On the Carbon-to-oxygen Ratio Measurement in nearby Sun-like Stars: Implications for Planet Formation and the Determination of Stellar Abundances</title>
			<authors>Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 747, Issue 2, article id. L27 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...747L..27F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...747...82C</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Phase Variations of WASP-12b: Defying Predictions</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Machalek, Pavel; Croll, Bryce; Shekhtman, Louis M.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Greene, Tom; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 747, Issue 1, article id. 82 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...747...82C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746...46C</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based, Near-infrared Exospectroscopy. II. Tentative Detection of Emission from the Extremely Hot Jupiter WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Crossfield, Ian J. M.; Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 1, article id. 46 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...746...46C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...77K</bibcode>
			<title>A Photochemical Model for the Carbon-rich Planet WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Kopparapu, Ravi kumar; Kasting, James F.; Zahnle, Kevin J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 77 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...745...77K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..122Z</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based Detections of Thermal Emission from CoRoT-1b and WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Zhao, Ming; Monnier, John D.; Swain, Mark R.; Barman, Travis; Hinkley, Sasha</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 122 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...744..122Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...537A.115B</bibcode>
			<title>Day and night side core cooling of a strongly irradiated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.; Burrows, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 537, id.A115</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012A%26A...537A.115B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743L..16O</bibcode>
			<title>The Effects of Snowlines on C/O in Planetary Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>berg, Karin I.; Murray-Clay, Ruth; Bergin, Edwin A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. L16 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...743L..16O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..203J</bibcode>
			<title>A Survey of Alkali Line Absorption in Exoplanetary Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Jensen, Adam G.; Redfield, Seth; Endl, Michael; Cochran, William D.; Koesterke, Lars; Barman, Travis S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 203 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...743..203J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..191M</bibcode>
			<title>Carbon-rich Giant Planets: Atmospheric Chemistry, Thermal Inversions, Spectra, and Formation Conditions</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, Nikku; Mousis, Olivier; Johnson, Torrence V.; Lunine, Jonathan I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 191 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...743..191M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...536C...1L</bibcode>
			<title>Distorted, non-spherical transiting planets: impact on the transit depth and on the radius determination (Corrigendum)</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Lai, D.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 536, id.C1</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...536C...1L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197....9F</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Atmospheric Characterization of Giant Planet Kepler-12b: An Inflated Radius Outlier</title>
			<authors>Fortney, Jonathan J.; Demory, Brice-Olivier; Dsert, Jean-Michel; Rowe, Jason; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Isaacson, Howard; Buchhave, Lars A.; Ciardi, David; Gautier, Thomas N.; Batalha, Natalie M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Nutzman, Philip; Jenkins, Jon M.; Howard, Andrew; Charbonneau, David; Knutson, Heather A.; Howell, Steve B.; Everett, Mark; Fressin, Franois; Deming, Drake; Borucki, William J.; Brown, Timothy M.; Ford, Eric B.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Latham, David W.; Miller, Neil; Seager, Sara; Fischer, Debra A.; Koch, David; Lissauer, Jack J.; Haas, Michael R.; Still, Martin; Lucas, Philip; Gillon, Michael; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Geary, John C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 1, article id. 9 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJS..197....9F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...59H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-32b and HAT-P-33b: Two Highly Inflated Hot Jupiters Transiting High-jitter Stars</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, Gza; Bky, B.; Quinn, S. N.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; Szklenr, T.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...742...59H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A..50M</bibcode>
			<title>A binary merger origin for inflated hot Jupiter planets</title>
			<authors>Martin, E. L.; Spruit, H. C.; Tata, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A50</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...535A..50M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416L..41L</bibcode>
			<title>The shocking transit of WASP-12b: modelling the observed early ingress in the near-ultraviolet</title>
			<authors>Llama, J.; Wood, K.; Jardine, M.; Vidotto, A. A.; Helling, Ch.; Fossati, L.; Haswell, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 416, Issue 1, pp. L41-L44.</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.416L..41L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416.2096S</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal emission from WASP-33b, the hottest known planet</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Anderson, D. R.; Skillen, I.; Collier Cameron, A.; Smalley, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 416, Issue 3, pp. 2096-2101.</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.416.2096S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...738....1B</bibcode>
			<title>Evolution of Ohmically Heated Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Batygin, Konstantin; Stevenson, David J.; Bodenheimer, Peter H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 738, Issue 1, article id. 1 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...738....1B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...533A..88G</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-50 b: a hot Jupiter transiting a moderately active solar-type star</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Doyle, A. P.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Anderson, D. R.; Barros, S. C. C.; Bento, J.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Faedi, F.; Hellier, C.; Jehin, E.; Magain, P.; Montalbn, J.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Segransan, D.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 533, id.A88</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...533A..88G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...736...78C</bibcode>
			<title>Broadband Transmission Spectroscopy of the Super-Earth GJ 1214b Suggests a Low Mean Molecular Weight Atmosphere</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Miller-Ricci Kempton, Eliza; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman; Neilson, Hilding</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 736, Issue 2, article id. 78 (2011).</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...736...78C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...41P</bibcode>
			<title>Carbon and Oxygen in Nearby Stars: Keys to Protoplanetary Disk Chemistry</title>
			<authors>Petigura, Erik A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...735...41P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..60A</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-31b: a low-density planet transiting a metal-poor, late-F-type dwarf star</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Gillon, M.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S gransan, D.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A60</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...531A..60A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..40F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-39b: a highly inflated Saturn-mass planet orbiting a late G-type star</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Anderson, D. R.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Boisse, I.; Hbrard, G.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...531A..40F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1573V</bibcode>
			<title>Transit variability in bow shock-hosting planets</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1573-1582.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1573V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.413.2500H</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital eccentricity of WASP-12 and WASP-14 from new radial velocity monitoring with SOPHIE</title>
			<authors>Husnoo, Nawal; Pont, Frdric; Hbrard, Guillaume; Simpson, Elaine; Mazeh, Tsevi; Bouchy, Franois; Moutou, Claire; Arnold, Luc; Boisse, Isabelle; Daz, Rodrigo F.; Eggenberger, Anne; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 413, Issue 4, pp. 2500-2508.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.413.2500H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..179C</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light-curve Project. XIV. Confirmation of Anomalous Radii for the Exoplanets TrES-4b, HAT-P-3b, and WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Chan, Tucker; Ingemyr, Mikael; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Esquerdo, Gil; Everett, Mark</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 6, article id. 179 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....141..179C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732...74G</bibcode>
			<title>Consequences of the Ejection and Disruption of Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Guillochon, James; Ramirez-Ruiz, Enrico; Lin, Douglas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. 74 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...732...74G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...731...67P</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Extrasolar Planets: High Stellar Q from New Theoretical Models</title>
			<authors>Penev, Kaloyan; Sasselov, Dimitar</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 731, Issue 1, article id. 67 (2011).</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...731...67P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..65M</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision photometry of WASP-12 b transits</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Errmann, R.; Raetz, St.; Seeliger, M.; Spaleniak, I.; Neuh user, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A65</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...528A..65M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..53B</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variations in eccentric hierarchical triple exoplanetary systems. I. Perturbations on the time scale of the orbital period of the perturber</title>
			<authors>Borkovits, T.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Forgcs-Dajka, E.; Hegeds, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A53</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...528A..53B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..41L</bibcode>
			<title>Distorted, nonspherical transiting planets: impact on the transit depth and on the radius determination</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Lai, D.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A41</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...528A..41L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729L...7L</bibcode>
			<title>On the Anomalous Radii of the Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Laughlin, Gregory; Crismani, Matteo; Adams, Fred C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. L7 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...729L...7L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...54C</bibcode>
			<title>The Statistics of Albedo and Heat Recirculation on Hot Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Agol, Eric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 1, article id. 54 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...729...54C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..85N</bibcode>
			<title>TASTE: The Asiago Search for Transit timing variations of Exoplanets. I. Overview and improved parameters for HAT-P-3b and HAT-P-14b</title>
			<authors>Nascimbeni, V.; Piotto, G.; Bedin, L. R.; Damasso, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A85</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...527A..85N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411L..46V</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for detection of exoplanet magnetic fields through bow-shock observations during transits</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. L46-L50.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.411L..46V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..152T</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiter Magnetospheres</title>
			<authors>Trammell, George B.; Arras, Phil; Li, Zhi-Yun</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 152 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...728..152T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727L..44S</bibcode>
			<title>A Short-period Censor of Sub-Jupiter Mass Exoplanets with Low Density</title>
			<authors>Szab, Gy. M.; Kiss, L. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. L44 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...727L..44S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727..125C</bibcode>
			<title>On the Orbit of Exoplanet WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Campo, Christopher J.; Harrington, Joseph; Hardy, Ryan A.; Stevenson, Kevin B.; Nymeyer, Sarah; Ragozzine, Darin; Lust, Nate B.; Anderson, David R.; Collier-Cameron, Andrew; Blecic, Jasmina; Britt, Christopher B. T.; Bowman, William C.; Wheatley, Peter J.; Loredo, Thomas J.; Deming, Drake; Hebb, Leslie; Hellier, Coel; Maxted, Pierre F. L.; Pollaco, Don; West, Richard G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 125 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...727..125C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...75I</bibcode>
			<title>Explorations into the Viability of Coupled Radius-orbit Evolutionary Models for Inflated Planets</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...727...75I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...30C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from WASP-12b: Detections of the Secondary Eclipse in Ks, H, and J</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Lafreniere, David; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....141...30C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011Natur.469...64M</bibcode>
			<title>A high C/O ratio and weak thermal inversion in the atmosphere of exoplanet WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, Nikku; Harrington, Joseph; Stevenson, Kevin B.; Nymeyer, Sarah; Campo, Christopher J.; Wheatley, Peter J.; Deming, Drake; Blecic, Jasmina; Hardy, Ryan A.; Lust, Nate B.; Anderson, David R.; Collier-Cameron, Andrew; Britt, Christopher B. T.; Bowman, William C.; Hebb, Leslie; Hellier, Coel; Maxted, Pierre F. L.; Pollacco, Don; West, Richard G.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 469, Issue 7328, pp. 64-67 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011Natur.469...64M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727....4H</bibcode>
			<title>Ionization in Atmospheres of Brown Dwarfs and Extrasolar Planets. I. The Role of Electron Avalanche</title>
			<authors>Helling, Ch.; Jardine, M.; Witte, S.; Diver, D. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 4 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...727....4H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...95D</bibcode>
			<title>Warm Spitzer Photometry of the Transiting Exoplanets CoRoT-1 and CoRoT-2 at Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather; Agol, Eric; Desert, Jean-Michel; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan; Showman, Adam P.; Lewis, Nikole K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 95 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...726...95D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...52H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-18b and HAT-P-19b: Two Low-density Saturn-mass Planets Transiting Metal-rich K Stars</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Sato, B.; Torres, G.; Noyes, R. W.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, G.; Fischer, D. A.; Howard, A. W.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Fresz, G.; Perumpilly, G.; Bky, B.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sasselov, D. D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Csubry, Z.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 1, article id. 52 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...726...52H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010BASI...38..137L</bibcode>
			<title>Evaporation of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.</authors>
			<journal>Bulletin of the Astronomical Soceity of India, Vol. 38, p. 137-145, 2010</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010BASI...38..137L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.2007M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-22 b: A Transiting "Hot Jupiter" Planet in a Hierarchical Triple System</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Cegla, H.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 2007-2012 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010AJ....140.2007M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010AJ....140.1929L</bibcode>
			<title>Radio Observations of HD 80606 Near Planetary Periastron</title>
			<authors>Lazio, T. Joseph W.; Shankland, P. D.; Farrell, W. M.; Blank, D. L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 140, Issue 6, pp. 1929-1933 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010AJ....140.1929L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723.1703D</bibcode>
			<title>Too Little, Too Late: How the Tidal Evolution of Hot Jupiters Affects Transit Surveys of Clusters</title>
			<authors>Debes, John H.; Jackson, Brian</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 2, pp. 1703-1710 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...723.1703D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722L.168V</bibcode>
			<title>Early UV Ingress in WASP-12b: Measuring Planetary Magnetic Fields</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 722, Issue 2, pp. L168-L172 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...722L.168V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721.1113Y</bibcode>
			<title>The Mechanical Greenhouse: Burial of Heat by Turbulence in Hot Jupiter Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Youdin, Andrew N.; Mitchell, Jonathan L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. 1113-1126 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...721.1113Y</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721..923L</bibcode>
			<title>Mass Transfer, Transiting Stream, and Magnetopause in Close-in Exoplanetary Systems with Applications to WASP-12</title>
			<authors>Lai, Dong; Helling, Ch.; van den Heuvel, E. P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. 923-928 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...721..923L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407..507C</bibcode>
			<title>Line-profile tomography of exoplanet transits - II. A gas-giant planet transiting a rapidly rotating A5 star</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Guenther, E.; Smalley, B.; McDonald, I.; Hebb, L.; Andersen, J.; Augusteijn, Th.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Cochran, W. D.; Endl, M.; Fossey, S. J.; Hartmann, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Telting, J.; Waldmann, I. P.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 1, pp. 507-514.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.407..507C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720..872F</bibcode>
			<title>A Detailed Spectropolarimetric Analysis of the Planet-hosting Star WASP-12</title>
			<authors>Fossati, L.; Bagnulo, S.; Elmasli, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Holmes, S.; Kochukhov, O.; Shkolnik, E. L.; Shulyak, D. V.; Bohlender, D.; Albayrak, B.; Froning, C.; Hebb, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 1, pp. 872-886 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...720..872F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..97G</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. XII. CoRoT-12b: a short-period low-density planet transiting a solar analog star</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Hatzes, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Fridlund, M.; Deleuil, M.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Barnes, S. I.; Bonomo, A. S.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Cochran, W. D.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Endl, M.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Gandolfi, D.; Gazzano, J. C.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Havel, M.; H brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Lammer, H.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Montalbn, J.; Moutou, C.; Ofir, A.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Santerne, A.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Weingrill, J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A97</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...520A..97G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718..920C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from TrES-3b: A Ks-band Detection and an H-band Upper Limit on the Depth of the Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Lafrenire, David; Albert, Loic</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. 920-927 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...718..920C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716L..36L</bibcode>
			<title>Day-side z'-band Emission and Eccentricity of WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Lpez-Morales, Mercedes; Coughlin, Jeffrey L.; Sing, David K.; Burrows, Adam; Apai, Dniel; Rogers, Justin C.; Spiegel, David S.; Adams, Elisabeth R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 716, Issue 1, pp. L36-L40 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...716L..36L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1336K</bibcode>
			<title>Stability Analysis of Single-planet Systems and Their Habitable Zones</title>
			<authors>Kopparapu, Ravi Kumar; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1336-1344 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...716.1336K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..64L</bibcode>
			<title>Is tidal heating sufficient to explain bloated exoplanets? Consistent calculations accounting for finite initial eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Chabrier, G.; Baraffe, I.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A64</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...516A..64L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714L.238B</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating Hot Jupiters with Ohmic Dissipation</title>
			<authors>Batygin, Konstantin; Stevenson, David J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 714, Issue 2, pp. L238-L243 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...714L.238B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714L.222F</bibcode>
			<title>Metals in the Exosphere of the Highly Irradiated Planet WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Fossati, L.; Haswell, C. A.; Froning, C. S.; Hebb, L.; Holmes, S.; Kolb, U.; Helling, Ch.; Carter, A.; Wheatley, P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Loeillet, B.; Pollacco, D.; Street, R.; Stempels, H. C.; Simpson, E.; Udry, S.; Joshi, Y. C.; West, R. G.; Skillen, I.; Wilson, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 714, Issue 2, pp. L222-L227 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...714L.222F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010JRASC.104...75S</bibcode>
			<title>Second Light: A Plethora of Planets</title>
			<authors>Sage, Leslie J.</authors>
			<journal>Journal of the Royal Society of Canada, Vol. 104, No. 2, p.75</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010JRASC.104...75S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.463.1054L</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-12b as a prolate, inflated and disrupting planet from tidal dissipation</title>
			<authors>Li, Shu-Lin; Miller, N.; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 463, Issue 7284, pp. 1054-1056 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010Natur.463.1054L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..168A</bibcode>
			<title>How Eccentric Orbital Solutions Can Hide Planetary Systems in 2:1 Resonant Orbits</title>
			<authors>Anglada-Escud, Guillem; Lpez-Morales, Mercedes; Chambers, John E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 168-178 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...709..168A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708..224H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-19b: The Shortest Period Transiting Exoplanet Yet Discovered</title>
			<authors>Hebb, L.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Hellier, C.; Anderson, D. R.; Pollacco, D.; Gillon, M.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Horne, K.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 1, pp. 224-231 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...708..224H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..281R</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. VII. The ``hot-Jupiter''-type planet CoRoT-5b</title>
			<authors>Rauer, H.; Queloz, D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; de La Reza, R.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Guenther, E.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Kabath, P.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pont, F.; Rabus, M.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Shporer, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.281-286</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009A%26A...506..281R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700.1921I</bibcode>
			<title>Coupled Evolution with Tides of the Radius and Orbit of Transiting Giant Planets: General Results</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 1921-1932 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...700.1921I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...699.1487S</bibcode>
			<title>Can TiO Explain Thermal Inversions in the Upper Atmospheres of Irradiated Giant Planets?</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Silverio, Katie; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 699, Issue 2, pp. 1487-1500 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...699.1487S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.395.2268B</bibcode>
			<title>On the tidal evolution of Hot Jupiters on inclined orbits</title>
			<authors>Barker, Adrian J.; Ogilvie, Gordon I.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 395, Issue 4, pp. 2268-2287.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009MNRAS.395.2268B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...497..545S</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE2-TR-L9b: an exoplanet transiting a rapidly rotating F3 star</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.; Koppenhoefer, J.; van der Burg, R. F. J.; Dreizler, S.; Greiner, J.; de Hoon, M. D. J.; Husser, T. O.; Krhler, T.; Saglia, R. P.; Vuijsje, F. N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 497, Issue 2, 2009, pp.545-550</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009A%26A...497..545S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693.1920H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-12b: The Hottest Transiting Extrasolar Planet Yet Discovered</title>
			<authors>Hebb, L.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Loeillet, B.; Pollacco, D.; Hbrard, G.; Street, R. A.; Bouchy, F.; Stempels, H. C.; Moutou, C.; Simpson, E.; Udry, S.; Joshi, Y. C.; West, R. G.; Skillen, I.; Wilson, D. M.; McDonald, I.; Gibson, N. P.; Aigrain, S.; Anderson, D. R.; Benn, C. R.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 2, pp. 1920-1928 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...693.1920H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392.1532J</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-14b: 7.3 MJ transiting planet in an eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Joshi, Y. C.; Pollacco, D.; Collier Cameron, A.; Skillen, I.; Simpson, E.; Steele, I.; Street, R. A.; Stempels, H. C.; Christian, D. J.; Hebb, L.; Bouchy, F.; Gibson, N. P.; Hbrard, G.; Keenan, F. P.; Loeillet, B.; Meaburn, J.; Moutou, C.; Smalley, B.; Todd, I.; West, R. G.; Anderson, D. R.; Bentley, S.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; McDonald, I.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 4, pp. 1532-1538.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009MNRAS.392.1532J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690L..89H</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-7: A Bright Transiting-Exoplanet System in the Southern Hemisphere</title>
			<authors>Hellier, Coel; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Alsubai, K.; Bentley, S. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, R.; Haswell, C. A.; Joshi, Y. C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Ryans, R.; Street, R. A.; Todd, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 690, Issue 1, pp. L89-L91 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...690L..89H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...751...59P</bibcode>
			<title>The Effects of Irradiation on Hot Jovian Atmospheres: Heat Redistribution and Energy Dissipation</title>
			<authors>Perna, Rosalba; Heng, Kevin; Pont, Frdric</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 751, Issue 1, article id. 59 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...751...59P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...750..100C</bibcode>
			<title>Modeling Multi-wavelength Stellar Astrometry. III. Determination of the Absolute Masses of Exoplanets and Their Host Stars</title>
			<authors>Coughlin, J. L.; Lpez-Morales, Mercedes</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 750, Issue 2, article id. 100 (2012).</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...750..100C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...747...82C</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Phase Variations of WASP-12b: Defying Predictions</title>
			<authors>Cowan, Nicolas B.; Machalek, Pavel; Croll, Bryce; Shekhtman, Louis M.; Burrows, Adam; Deming, Drake; Greene, Tom; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 747, Issue 1, article id. 82 (2012).</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...747...82C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...746...46C</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based, Near-infrared Exospectroscopy. II. Tentative Detection of Emission from the Extremely Hot Jupiter WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Crossfield, Ian J. M.; Hansen, Brad M. S.; Barman, Travis</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 746, Issue 1, article id. 46 (2012).</journal>
			<date>2/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...746...46C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...77K</bibcode>
			<title>A Photochemical Model for the Carbon-rich Planet WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Kopparapu, Ravi kumar; Kasting, James F.; Zahnle, Kevin J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 77 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...745...77K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..122Z</bibcode>
			<title>Ground-based Detections of Thermal Emission from CoRoT-1b and WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Zhao, Ming; Monnier, John D.; Swain, Mark R.; Barman, Travis; Hinkley, Sasha</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 122 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2012ApJ...744..122Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743L..16O</bibcode>
			<title>The Effects of Snowlines on C/O in Planetary Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>berg, Karin I.; Murray-Clay, Ruth; Bergin, Edwin A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. L16 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...743L..16O</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..191M</bibcode>
			<title>Carbon-rich Giant Planets: Atmospheric Chemistry, Thermal Inversions, Spectra, and Formation Conditions</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, Nikku; Mousis, Olivier; Johnson, Torrence V.; Lunine, Jonathan I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 191 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...743..191M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535L...7H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-43b: the closest-orbiting hot Jupiter</title>
			<authors>Hellier, C.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Sgransan, D.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Southworth, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.L7</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...535L...7H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A.116D</bibcode>
			<title>Prospecting transit duration variations in extrasolar planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Damiani, C.; Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A116</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...535A.116D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...534L...6T</bibcode>
			<title>The time dependence of hot Jupiters' orbital inclinations</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 534, id.L6</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...534L...6T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416L..41L</bibcode>
			<title>The shocking transit of WASP-12b: modelling the observed early ingress in the near-ultraviolet</title>
			<authors>Llama, J.; Wood, K.; Jardine, M.; Vidotto, A. A.; Helling, Ch.; Fossati, L.; Haswell, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 416, Issue 1, pp. L41-L44.</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.416L..41L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...735...41P</bibcode>
			<title>Carbon and Oxygen in Nearby Stars: Keys to Protoplanetary Disk Chemistry</title>
			<authors>Petigura, Erik A.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 735, Issue 1, article id. 41 (2011).</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...735...41P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.413.2500H</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital eccentricity of WASP-12 and WASP-14 from new radial velocity monitoring with SOPHIE</title>
			<authors>Husnoo, Nawal; Pont, Frdric; Hbrard, Guillaume; Simpson, Elaine; Mazeh, Tsevi; Bouchy, Franois; Moutou, Claire; Arnold, Luc; Boisse, Isabelle; Daz, Rodrigo F.; Eggenberger, Anne; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 413, Issue 4, pp. 2500-2508.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.413.2500H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..179C</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light-curve Project. XIV. Confirmation of Anomalous Radii for the Exoplanets TrES-4b, HAT-P-3b, and WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Chan, Tucker; Ingemyr, Mikael; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Esquerdo, Gil; Everett, Mark</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 6, article id. 179 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....141..179C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..161S</bibcode>
			<title>Independent Discovery of the Transiting Exoplanet HAT-P-14b</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Stempels, H. C.; Boisse, I.; Faedi, F.; Hbrard, G.; McCormac, J.; Sorensen, P.; Street, R. A.; Anderson, D.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hebb, L.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Horne, K.; Keenan, F. P.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Santerne, A.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Todd, I.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 5, article id. 161 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....141..161S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A..80E</bibcode>
			<title>HST/STIS Lyman-alpha observations of the quiet M dwarf GJ 436. Predictions for the exospheric transit signature of the hot Neptune GJ 436b</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Delfosse, X.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A80</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...529A..80E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A..50L</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining tidal dissipation in F-type main-sequence stars: the case of CoRoT-11</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Damiani, C.; Gandolfi, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A50</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...529A..50L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A..65M</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision photometry of WASP-12 b transits</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Errmann, R.; Raetz, St.; Seeliger, M.; Spaleniak, I.; Neuh user, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A65</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...528A..65M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..85N</bibcode>
			<title>TASTE: The Asiago Search for Transit timing variations of Exoplanets. I. Overview and improved parameters for HAT-P-3b and HAT-P-14b</title>
			<authors>Nascimbeni, V.; Piotto, G.; Bedin, L. R.; Damasso, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A85</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...527A..85N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..73S</bibcode>
			<title>Gran Telescopio Canarias OSIRIS transiting exoplanet atmospheric survey: detection of potassium in XO-2b from narrowband spectrophotometry</title>
			<authors>Sing, D. K.; Dsert, J.-M.; Fortney, J. J.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Ballester, G. E.; Cepa, J.; Ehrenreich, D.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Pont, F.; Shabram, M.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A73</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...527A..73S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411L..46V</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for detection of exoplanet magnetic fields through bow-shock observations during transits</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. L46-L50.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.411L..46V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727..125C</bibcode>
			<title>On the Orbit of Exoplanet WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Campo, Christopher J.; Harrington, Joseph; Hardy, Ryan A.; Stevenson, Kevin B.; Nymeyer, Sarah; Ragozzine, Darin; Lust, Nate B.; Anderson, David R.; Collier-Cameron, Andrew; Blecic, Jasmina; Britt, Christopher B. T.; Bowman, William C.; Wheatley, Peter J.; Loredo, Thomas J.; Deming, Drake; Hebb, Leslie; Hellier, Coel; Maxted, Pierre F. L.; Pollaco, Don; West, Richard G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 125 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...727..125C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...75I</bibcode>
			<title>Explorations into the Viability of Coupled Radius-orbit Evolutionary Models for Inflated Planets</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...727...75I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...30C</bibcode>
			<title>Near-infrared Thermal Emission from WASP-12b: Detections of the Secondary Eclipse in Ks, H, and J</title>
			<authors>Croll, Bryce; Lafreniere, David; Albert, Loic; Jayawardhana, Ray; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Murray, Norman</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 30 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....141...30C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726...95D</bibcode>
			<title>Warm Spitzer Photometry of the Transiting Exoplanets CoRoT-1 and CoRoT-2 at Secondary Eclipse</title>
			<authors>Deming, Drake; Knutson, Heather; Agol, Eric; Desert, Jean-Michel; Burrows, Adam; Fortney, Jonathan J.; Charbonneau, David; Cowan, Nicolas B.; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan; Showman, Adam P.; Lewis, Nikole K.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 95 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...726...95D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; Sgransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...722L.168V</bibcode>
			<title>Early UV Ingress in WASP-12b: Measuring Planetary Magnetic Fields</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Jardine, M.; Helling, Ch.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 722, Issue 2, pp. L168-L172 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...722L.168V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...721..923L</bibcode>
			<title>Mass Transfer, Transiting Stream, and Magnetopause in Close-in Exoplanetary Systems with Applications to WASP-12</title>
			<authors>Lai, Dong; Helling, Ch.; van den Heuvel, E. P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 721, Issue 2, pp. 923-928 (2010).</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...721..923L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720..872F</bibcode>
			<title>A Detailed Spectropolarimetric Analysis of the Planet-hosting Star WASP-12</title>
			<authors>Fossati, L.; Bagnulo, S.; Elmasli, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Holmes, S.; Kochukhov, O.; Shkolnik, E. L.; Shulyak, D. V.; Bohlender, D.; Albayrak, B.; Froning, C.; Hebb, L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 1, pp. 872-886 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...720..872F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.404.1849B</bibcode>
			<title>On internal wave breaking and tidal dissipation near the centre of a solar-type star</title>
			<authors>Barker, Adrian J.; Ogilvie, Gordon I.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 404, Issue 4, pp. 1849-1868.</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.404.1849B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716L..36L</bibcode>
			<title>Day-side z'-band Emission and Eccentricity of WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Lpez-Morales, Mercedes; Coughlin, Jeffrey L.; Sing, David K.; Burrows, Adam; Apai, Dniel; Rogers, Justin C.; Spiegel, David S.; Adams, Elisabeth R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 716, Issue 1, pp. L36-L40 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...716L..36L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..64L</bibcode>
			<title>Is tidal heating sufficient to explain bloated exoplanets? Consistent calculations accounting for finite initial eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Chabrier, G.; Baraffe, I.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A64</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...516A..64L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..33E</bibcode>
			<title>An improved method for estimating the masses of stars with transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Parley, N. R.; Hebb, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A33</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...516A..33E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...714L.222F</bibcode>
			<title>Metals in the Exosphere of the Highly Irradiated Planet WASP-12b</title>
			<authors>Fossati, L.; Haswell, C. A.; Froning, C. S.; Hebb, L.; Holmes, S.; Kolb, U.; Helling, Ch.; Carter, A.; Wheatley, P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Loeillet, B.; Pollacco, D.; Street, R.; Stempels, H. C.; Simpson, E.; Udry, S.; Joshi, Y. C.; West, R. G.; Skillen, I.; Wilson, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 714, Issue 2, pp. L222-L227 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...714L.222F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010Natur.463.1054L</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-12b as a prolate, inflated and disrupting planet from tidal dissipation</title>
			<authors>Li, Shu-Lin; Miller, N.; Lin, Douglas N. C.; Fortney, Jonathan J.</authors>
			<journal>Nature, Volume 463, Issue 7284, pp. 1054-1056 (2010).</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010Natur.463.1054L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...708..224H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-19b: The Shortest Period Transiting Exoplanet Yet Discovered</title>
			<authors>Hebb, L.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Hellier, C.; Anderson, D. R.; Pollacco, D.; Gillon, M.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Horne, K.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Segransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 708, Issue 1, pp. 224-231 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...708..224H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..385L</bibcode>
			<title>Structure and evolution of the first CoRoT exoplanets: probing the brown dwarf/planet overlapping mass regime</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Baraffe, I.; Chabrier, G.; Barman, T.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.385-389</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009A%26A...506..385L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.395.2268B</bibcode>
			<title>On the tidal evolution of Hot Jupiters on inclined orbits</title>
			<authors>Barker, Adrian J.; Ogilvie, Gordon I.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 395, Issue 4, pp. 2268-2287.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009MNRAS.395.2268B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693.1920H</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-12b: The Hottest Transiting Extrasolar Planet Yet Discovered</title>
			<authors>Hebb, L.; Collier-Cameron, A.; Loeillet, B.; Pollacco, D.; Hbrard, G.; Street, R. A.; Bouchy, F.; Stempels, H. C.; Moutou, C.; Simpson, E.; Udry, S.; Joshi, Y. C.; West, R. G.; Skillen, I.; Wilson, D. M.; McDonald, I.; Gibson, N. P.; Aigrain, S.; Anderson, D. R.; Benn, C. R.; Christian, D. J.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 2, pp. 1920-1928 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...693.1920H</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
