<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...95L</bibcode>
			<title>The Sub-Saturn Mass Transiting Planet HAT-P-12b</title>
			<authors>Lee, Jae Woo; Youn, Jae-Hyuck; Kim, Seung-Lee; Lee, Chung-Uk; Hinse, Tobias Cornelius</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 4, article id. 95 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143...95L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AstL...38..180S</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of extrasolar planet transits with the automated telescopes of the Pulkovo Astronomical Observatory</title>
			<authors>Sokov, E. N.; Vereshchagina, I. A.; Gnedin, Yu. N.; Devyatkin, A. V.; Gorshanov, D. L.; Slesarenko, V. Yu.; Ivanov, A. V.; Naumov, K. N.; Zinov'ev, S. V.; Bekhteva, A. S.; Romas, E. S.; Karashevich, S. V.; Kupriyanov, V. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Letters, Volume 38, Issue 3, pp.180-190</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AstL...38..180S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...86E</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-35b, WASP-48b, and HAT-P-30b/WASP-51b: Two New Planets and an Independent Discovery of a Hat Planet</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Faedi, F.; Gillon, M.; Hbrard, G.; Lister, T. A.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bouchy, F.; Bento, J.; Butters, O.; Fossati, L.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Simpson, E.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 3, article id. 86 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142...86E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..40F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-39b: a highly inflated Saturn-mass planet orbiting a late G-type star</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Anderson, D. R.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Boisse, I.; Hbrard, G.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..40F</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...95L</bibcode>
			<title>The Sub-Saturn Mass Transiting Planet HAT-P-12b</title>
			<authors>Lee, Jae Woo; Youn, Jae-Hyuck; Kim, Seung-Lee; Lee, Chung-Uk; Hinse, Tobias Cornelius</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 4, article id. 95 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143...95L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.416.2593B</bibcode>
			<title>A lower mass for the exoplanet WASP-21b</title>
			<authors>Barros, S. C. C.; Pollacco, D. L.; Gibson, N. P.; Howarth, I. D.; Keenan, F. P.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Steele, I. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 416, Issue 4, pp. 2593-2599.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.416.2593B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...531A..40F</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-39b: a highly inflated Saturn-mass planet orbiting a late G-type star</title>
			<authors>Faedi, F.; Barros, S. C. C.; Anderson, D. R.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Boisse, I.; Hbrard, G.; Lendl, M.; Lister, T. A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Keenan, F. P.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Simpson, E. K.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 531, id.A40</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...531A..40F</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
