<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AJ....143...81S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-36b: A New Transiting Planet around a Metal-poor G-dwarf, and an Investigation into Analyses Based on a Single Transit Light Curve</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Barros, S. C. C.; Jehin, E.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Southworth, J.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 143, Issue 4, article id. 81 (2012).</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AJ....143...81S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AstL...38..180S</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of extrasolar planet transits with the automated telescopes of the Pulkovo Astronomical Observatory</title>
			<authors>Sokov, E. N.; Vereshchagina, I. A.; Gnedin, Yu. N.; Devyatkin, A. V.; Gorshanov, D. L.; Slesarenko, V. Yu.; Ivanov, A. V.; Naumov, K. N.; Zinov'ev, S. V.; Bekhteva, A. S.; Romas, E. S.; Karashevich, S. V.; Kupriyanov, V. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Letters, Volume 38, Issue 3, pp.180-190</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AstL...38..180S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743..200B</bibcode>
			<title>The Kepler-19 System: A Transiting 2.2 R &amp;oplus; Planet and a Second Planet Detected via Transit Timing Variations</title>
			<authors>Ballard, Sarah; Fabrycky, Daniel; Fressin, Francois; Charbonneau, David; Desert, Jean-Michel; Torres, Guillermo; Marcy, Geoffrey; Burke, Christopher J.; Isaacson, Howard; Henze, Christopher; Steffen, Jason H.; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steven B.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Bryson, Stephen T.; Rowe, Jason F.; Holman, Matthew J.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Still, Martin; Ford, Eric B.; Christiansen, Jessie L.; Middour, Christopher K.; Haas, Michael R.; Li, Jie; Hall, Jennifer R.; McCauliff, Sean; Batalha, Natalie M.; Koch, David G.; Borucki, William J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 2, article id. 200 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743..200B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742..116B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-20b-HAT-P-23b: Four Massive Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Kipping, D.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Shporer, A.; Bky, B.; Buchhave, L. A.; Perumpilly, G.; Everett, M.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 116 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...742..116B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A...7M</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of new high-precision transit light curves of WASP-10 b: starspot occultations, small planetary radius, and high metallicity</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Raetz, St.; Nettelmann, N.; Seeliger, M.; Adam, C.; Nowak, G.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A7</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...535A...7M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.417L..16G</bibcode>
			<title>Potential biases in the detection of planetary systems with large transit timing variations</title>
			<authors>Garca-Melendo, E.; Lpez-Morales, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 417, Issue 1, pp. L16-L20.</journal>
			<date>10/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.417L..16G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532A..24N</bibcode>
			<title>TASTE II. A new observational study of transit time variations in HAT-P-13b</title>
			<authors>Nascimbeni, V.; Piotto, G.; Bedin, L. R.; Damasso, M.; Malavolta, L.; Borsato, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.A24</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532A..24N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415..605B</bibcode>
			<title>Are falling planets spinning up their host stars?</title>
			<authors>Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hall, C.; Hebb, L.; Smalley, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 1, pp. 605-618.</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415..605B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AN....332..547N</bibcode>
			<title>The Young Exoplanet Transit Initiative (YETI)</title>
			<authors>Neuhuser, R.; Errmann, R.; Berndt, A.; Maciejewski, G.; Takahashi, H.; Chen, W. P.; Dimitrov, D. P.; Pribulla, T.; Nikogossian, E. H.; Jensen, E. L. N.; Marschall, L.; Wu, Z.-Y.; Kellerer, A.; Walter, F. M.; Briceo, C.; Chini, R.; Fernandez, M.; Raetz, St.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Quinn, S. N.; Niedzielski, A.; Bukowiecki, L.; Nowak, G.; Tomov, T.; Tachihara, K.; Hu, S. C.-L.; Hung, L. W.; Kjurkchieva, D. P.; Radeva, V. S.; Mihov, B. M.; Slavcheva-Mihova, L.; Bozhinova, I. N.; Budaj, J.; Vanko, M.; Kundra, E.; Hamblek, L.; Krushevska, V.; Movsessian, T.; Harutyunyan, H.; Downes, J. J.; Hernandez, J.; Hoffmeister, V. H.; Cohen, D. H.; Abel, I.; Ahmad, R.; Chapman, S.; Eckert, S.; Goodman, J.; Guerard, A.; Kim, H. M.; Koontharana, A.; Sokol, J.; Trinh, J.; Wang, Y.; Zhou, X.; Redmer, R.; Kramm, U.; Nettelmann, N.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, J.; Moualla, M.; Ginski, C.; Marka, C.; Adam, C.; Seeliger, M.; Baar, S.; Roell, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Trepl, L.; Eisenbei, T.; Fiedler, S.; Tetzlaff, N.; Schmidt, E.; Hohle, M. M.; Kitze, M.; Chakrova, N.; Grfe, C.; Schreyer, K.; Hambaryan, V. V.; Broeg, C. H.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Pandey, A. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.332, Issue 6, p.547</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AN....332..547N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.413L..43P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variations in the HAT-P-13 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Pl, Andrs; Srneczky, Krisztin; Szab, Gyula M.; Szing, Attila; Kiss, Lszl L.; Mezo, Gyrgy; Regly, Zsolt</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 413, Issue 1, pp. L43-L46.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.413L..43P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AcA....61...25M</bibcode>
			<title>Refining Parameters of the XO-5 Planetary System with High-Precision Transit Photometry</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Seeliger, M.; Adam, Ch.; Raetz, St.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Acta Astronomica, vol 61, no 1, p. 25-35</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AcA....61...25M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1204M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation and activity in the WASP-10 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuhuser, R.; Tetzlaff, N.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Chen, W. P.; Walter, F.; Marka, C.; Baar, S.; Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.; Krushevska, V.; Tachihara, K.; Takahashi, H.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 2, pp. 1204-1212.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1204M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...728..125A</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Variation Analysis of OGLE-TR-132b with Seven New Transits</title>
			<authors>Adams, E. R.; Lpez-Morales, M.; Elliot, J. L.; Seager, S.; Osip, D. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 728, Issue 2, article id. 125 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...728..125A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727....4H</bibcode>
			<title>Ionization in Atmospheres of Brown Dwarfs and Extrasolar Planets. I. The Role of Electron Avalanche</title>
			<authors>Helling, Ch.; Jardine, M.; Witte, S.; Diver, D. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 4 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...727....4H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 29, 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010CoSka..40...77K</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric observations of transiting extrasolar planet WASP-10b</title>
			<authors>Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.; Krushevska, V.</authors>
			<journal>Contributions of the Astronomical Observatory Skalnat Pleso, vol. 40, no. 2, p. 77-82.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010CoSka..40...77K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1118B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-16b: A 4 M J Planet Transiting a Bright Star on an Eccentric Orbit</title>
			<authors>Buchhave, L. A.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J. D.; Torres, G.; Kovcs, G.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Everett, M.; Howard, A. W.; Marcy, G. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Andersen, J.; Fursz, G.; Perumpilly, G.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Bky, B.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1118-1125 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1118B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717..235D</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Observations of the WASP-10 System</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, J. A.; Close, L. M.; Scuderi, L. J.; Morris, M. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 1, pp. 235-238 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717..235D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..168A</bibcode>
			<title>How Eccentric Orbital Solutions Can Hide Planetary Systems in 2:1 Resonant Orbits</title>
			<authors>Anglada-Escud, Guillem; Lpez-Morales, Mercedes; Chambers, John E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 168-178 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..168A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...502..695P</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-orbit misalignment in the HD 80606 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Hbrard, G.; Irwin, J. M.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Guillot, T.; Aigrain, S.; Bonfils, X.; Berta, Z.; Boisse, I.; Burke, C.; Charbonneau, D.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Nutzman, P.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 502, Issue 2, 2009, pp.695-703</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...502..695P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1357J</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Evidence for Tidal Destruction of Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Brian; Barnes, Rory; Greenberg, Richard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1357-1366 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1357J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392.1585C</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-10b: a 3MJ, gas-giant planet transiting a late-type K star</title>
			<authors>Christian, D. J.; Gibson, N. P.; Simpson, E. K.; Street, R. A.; Skillen, I.; Pollacco, D.; Collier Cameron, A.; Joshi, Y. C.; Keenan, F. P.; Stempels, H. C.; Haswell, C. A.; Horne, K.; Anderson, D. R.; Bentley, S.; Bouchy, F.; Clarkson, W. I.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Hbrard, G.; Hellier, C.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Lister, T. A.; Loeillet, B.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; McDonald, I.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Todd, I.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 4, pp. 1585-1590.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392.1585C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392.1532J</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-14b: 7.3 MJ transiting planet in an eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Joshi, Y. C.; Pollacco, D.; Collier Cameron, A.; Skillen, I.; Simpson, E.; Steele, I.; Street, R. A.; Stempels, H. C.; Christian, D. J.; Hebb, L.; Bouchy, F.; Gibson, N. P.; Hbrard, G.; Keenan, F. P.; Loeillet, B.; Meaburn, J.; Moutou, C.; Smalley, B.; Todd, I.; West, R. G.; Anderson, D. R.; Bentley, S.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; McDonald, I.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 4, pp. 1532-1538.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392.1532J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L.100J</bibcode>
			<title>A Smaller Radius for the Transiting Exoplanet WASP-10b</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.; Cabrera, Nicole E.; Carter, Joshua A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 2, pp. L100-L104 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L.100J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686L..29M</bibcode>
			<title>On the Origins of Eccentric Close-In Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Takeda, Genya; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. L29-L32.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686L..29M</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...535A...7M</bibcode>
			<title>Analysis of new high-precision transit light curves of WASP-10 b: starspot occultations, small planetary radius, and high metallicity</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Raetz, St.; Nettelmann, N.; Seeliger, M.; Adam, C.; Nowak, G.; Neuhuser, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 535, id.A7</journal>
			<date>11/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...535A...7M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.415..605B</bibcode>
			<title>Are falling planets spinning up their host stars?</title>
			<authors>Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hall, C.; Hebb, L.; Smalley, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 415, Issue 1, pp. 605-618.</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.415..605B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AN....332..547N</bibcode>
			<title>The Young Exoplanet Transit Initiative (YETI)</title>
			<authors>Neuhuser, R.; Errmann, R.; Berndt, A.; Maciejewski, G.; Takahashi, H.; Chen, W. P.; Dimitrov, D. P.; Pribulla, T.; Nikogossian, E. H.; Jensen, E. L. N.; Marschall, L.; Wu, Z.-Y.; Kellerer, A.; Walter, F. M.; Briceo, C.; Chini, R.; Fernandez, M.; Raetz, St.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Quinn, S. N.; Niedzielski, A.; Bukowiecki, L.; Nowak, G.; Tomov, T.; Tachihara, K.; Hu, S. C.-L.; Hung, L. W.; Kjurkchieva, D. P.; Radeva, V. S.; Mihov, B. M.; Slavcheva-Mihova, L.; Bozhinova, I. N.; Budaj, J.; Vanko, M.; Kundra, E.; Hamblek, L.; Krushevska, V.; Movsessian, T.; Harutyunyan, H.; Downes, J. J.; Hernandez, J.; Hoffmeister, V. H.; Cohen, D. H.; Abel, I.; Ahmad, R.; Chapman, S.; Eckert, S.; Goodman, J.; Guerard, A.; Kim, H. M.; Koontharana, A.; Sokol, J.; Trinh, J.; Wang, Y.; Zhou, X.; Redmer, R.; Kramm, U.; Nettelmann, N.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, J.; Moualla, M.; Ginski, C.; Marka, C.; Adam, C.; Seeliger, M.; Baar, S.; Roell, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Trepl, L.; Eisenbei, T.; Fiedler, S.; Tetzlaff, N.; Schmidt, E.; Hohle, M. M.; Kitze, M.; Chakrova, N.; Grfe, C.; Schreyer, K.; Hambaryan, V. V.; Broeg, C. H.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Pandey, A. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.332, Issue 6, p.547</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AN....332..547N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.413.2500H</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital eccentricity of WASP-12 and WASP-14 from new radial velocity monitoring with SOPHIE</title>
			<authors>Husnoo, Nawal; Pont, Frdric; Hbrard, Guillaume; Simpson, Elaine; Mazeh, Tsevi; Bouchy, Franois; Moutou, Claire; Arnold, Luc; Boisse, Isabelle; Daz, Rodrigo F.; Eggenberger, Anne; Shporer, Avi</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 413, Issue 4, pp. 2500-2508.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.413.2500H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.413L..43P</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variations in the HAT-P-13 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Pl, Andrs; Srneczky, Krisztin; Szab, Gyula M.; Szing, Attila; Kiss, Lszl L.; Mezo, Gyrgy; Regly, Zsolt</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 413, Issue 1, pp. L43-L46.</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.413L..43P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..161S</bibcode>
			<title>Independent Discovery of the Transiting Exoplanet HAT-P-14b</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Stempels, H. C.; Boisse, I.; Faedi, F.; Hbrard, G.; McCormac, J.; Sorensen, P.; Street, R. A.; Anderson, D.; Bento, J.; Bouchy, F.; Butters, O. W.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hebb, L.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Horne, K.; Keenan, F. P.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Santerne, A.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Todd, I.; Watson, C. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 5, article id. 161 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141..161S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...729...98P</bibcode>
			<title>An Analysis of Jitter and Transit Timing Variations in the HAT-P-13 System</title>
			<authors>Payne, Matthew J.; Ford, Eric B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 729, Issue 2, article id. 98 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...729...98P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63..287F</bibcode>
			<title>Measurements of Transit Timing Variations for WASP-5b</title>
			<authors>Fukui, Akihiko; Narita, Norio; Tristram, Paul J.; Sumi, Takahiro; Abe, Fumio; Itow, Yoshitaka; Sullivan, Denis J.; Bond, Ian A.; Hirano, Teruyuki; Tamura, Motohide; Bennett, David P.; Furusawa, Kei; Hayashi, Fumiya; Hearnshaw, John B.; Hosaka, Shun; Kamiya, Koki; Kobara, Shuhei; Korpela, Aarno; Kilmartin, Pam M.; Lin, Wei; Ling, Cho Hong; Makita, Shota; Masuda, Kimiaki; Matsubara, Yutaka; Miyake, Noriyuki; Muraki, Yasushi; Nagaya, Maiko; Nishimoto, Kenta; Ohnishi, Kouji; Omori, Kengo; Perrott, Yvette; Rattenbury, Nicholas; Saito, Toshiharu; Skuljan, Ljiljana; Suzuki, Daisuke; Sweatman, Winston L.; Wada, Kohei</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.1, pp.287--300</journal>
			<date>2/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PASJ...63..287F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.1204M</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing variation and activity in the WASP-10 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Maciejewski, G.; Dimitrov, D.; Neuhuser, R.; Tetzlaff, N.; Niedzielski, A.; Raetz, St.; Chen, W. P.; Walter, F.; Marka, C.; Baar, S.; Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.; Krushevska, V.; Tachihara, K.; Takahashi, H.; Mugrauer, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 2, pp. 1204-1212.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.1204M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PABei..29..371D</bibcode>
			<title>Research progress on the transit timing variations in extrasolar planets.</title>
			<authors>Dong, Y.; Ji, J.-H.; Sun, Z.</authors>
			<journal>Progress in Astronomy, 29, 371-386 (2011)</journal>
			<date>0/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011PABei..29..371D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010CoSka..40...77K</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric observations of transiting extrasolar planet WASP-10b</title>
			<authors>Krejcov, T.; Budaj, J.; Krushevska, V.</authors>
			<journal>Contributions of the Astronomical Observatory Skalnat Pleso, vol. 40, no. 2, p. 77-82.</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010CoSka..40...77K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717..235D</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Observations of the WASP-10 System</title>
			<authors>Dittmann, J. A.; Close, L. M.; Scuderi, L. J.; Morris, M. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 717, Issue 1, pp. 235-238 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717..235D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..33E</bibcode>
			<title>An improved method for estimating the masses of stars with transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Parley, N. R.; Hebb, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A33</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..33E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707..167S</bibcode>
			<title>Physical Properties of the 0.94-Day Period Transiting Planetary System WASP-18</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Dominik, M.; Glitrup, M.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Mathiasen, M.; Anderson, D. R.; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Burgdorf, M.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Harpse, K.; Hessman, F.; Hundertmark, M.; Maier, G.; Mancini, L.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Skottfelt, J.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.; Zimmer, F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, article id. 167-172 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707..167S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.399..287S</bibcode>
			<title>High-precision photometry by telescope defocussing - II. The transiting planetary system WASP-4</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Dominik, M.; Hornstrup, A.; Jrgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Ricci, D.; Thne, C. C.; Anguita, T.; Bozza, V.; Novati, S. Calchi; Harpse, K.; Mancini, L.; Masi, G.; Mathiasen, M.; Rahvar, S.; Scarpetta, G.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.; Zub, M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 399, Issue 1, pp. 287-294.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.399..287S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392.1585C</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-10b: a 3MJ, gas-giant planet transiting a late-type K star</title>
			<authors>Christian, D. J.; Gibson, N. P.; Simpson, E. K.; Street, R. A.; Skillen, I.; Pollacco, D.; Collier Cameron, A.; Joshi, Y. C.; Keenan, F. P.; Stempels, H. C.; Haswell, C. A.; Horne, K.; Anderson, D. R.; Bentley, S.; Bouchy, F.; Clarkson, W. I.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Hbrard, G.; Hellier, C.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Lister, T. A.; Loeillet, B.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; McDonald, I.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Smalley, B.; Smith, A. M. S.; Todd, I.; Udry, S.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 4, pp. 1585-1590.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392.1585C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L.100J</bibcode>
			<title>A Smaller Radius for the Transiting Exoplanet WASP-10b</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.; Cabrera, Nicole E.; Carter, Joshua A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 2, pp. L100-L104 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L.100J</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
