<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...742...72N</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital Distributions of Close-in Planets and Distant Planets Formed by Scattering and Dynamical Tides</title>
			<authors>Nagasawa, M.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 742, Issue 2, article id. 72 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...742...72N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.414.1278P</bibcode>
			<title>Determining eccentricities of transiting planets: a divide in the mass-period plane</title>
			<authors>Pont, Frdric; Husnoo, Nawal; Mazeh, Tsevi; Fabrycky, Daniel</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 414, Issue 2, pp. 1278-1284.</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.414.1278P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...734..109B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-27b: A Hot Jupiter Transiting a G Star on a 3 Day Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bky, B.; Bakos, G. .; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Jordn, A.; Arriagada, P.; Bayliss, D.; Kiss, L. L.; Kovcs, Gza; Quinn, S. N.; Marcy, G. W.; Howard, A. W.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Noyes, R. W.; Buchhave, L. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Perumpilly, G.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 734, Issue 2, article id. 109 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...734..109B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A.136E</bibcode>
			<title>Mass-loss rates for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Ehrenreich, D.; Dsert, J.-M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A136</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...529A.136E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...528A...2B</bibcode>
			<title>The mass-period distribution of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Bentez-Llambay, P.; Masset, F.; Beaug, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 528, id.A2</journal>
			<date>4/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...528A...2B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527L..11H</bibcode>
			<title>The retrograde orbit of the HAT-P-6b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Ehrenreich, D.; Bouchy, F.; Delfosse, X.; Moutou, C.; Arnold, L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; Daz, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.L11</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...527L..11H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411..167I</bibcode>
			<title>Classical and relativistic long-term time variations of some observables for transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iorio, L.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 1, pp. 167-183.</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.411..167I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...75I</bibcode>
			<title>Explorations into the Viability of Coupled Radius-orbit Evolutionary Models for Inflated Planets</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...727...75I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.410.1631E</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-25b: a 0.6 MJ planet in the Southern hemisphere</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Cameron, A. Collier; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Brown, D. J. A.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Lendl, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Simpson, E.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 410, Issue 3, pp. 1631-1636.</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.410.1631E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727....4H</bibcode>
			<title>Ionization in Atmospheres of Brown Dwarfs and Extrasolar Planets. I. The Role of Electron Avalanche</title>
			<authors>Helling, Ch.; Jardine, M.; Witte, S.; Diver, D. A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 1, article id. 4 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...727....4H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...726..112T</bibcode>
			<title>Using Stellar Densities to Evaluate Transiting Exoplanetary Candidates</title>
			<authors>Tingley, B.; Bonomo, A. S.; Deeg, H. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 726, Issue 2, article id. 112 (2011).</journal>
			<date>1/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...726..112T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62L..61N</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect of the Transiting Exoplanet XO-4b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sanchis-Ojeda, Roberto; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.6, pp.L61--L65</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010PASJ...62L..61N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1666S</bibcode>
			<title>Rotation periods of exoplanet host stars</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Baliunas, S. L.; Henry, G. W.; Watson, C. A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1666-1679.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1666S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1606W</bibcode>
			<title>Estimating the masses of extra-solar planets</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Littlefair, S. P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Dhillon, V. S.; Simpson, E. K.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1606-1622.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1606W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.2037W</bibcode>
			<title>Orbital period variations of hot Jupiters caused by the Applegate effect</title>
			<authors>Watson, C. A.; Marsh, T. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 2037-2043.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010MNRAS.405.2037W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...716.1336K</bibcode>
			<title>Stability Analysis of Single-planet Systems and Their Habitable Zones</title>
			<authors>Kopparapu, Ravi Kumar; Barnes, Rory</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 716, Issue 2, pp. 1336-1344 (2010).</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...716.1336K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..785H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-12b: A Low-Density Sub-Saturn Mass Planet Transiting a Metal-Poor K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. .; Torres, G.; Kovcs, Gza; Noyes, R. W.; Pl, A.; Latham, D. W.; Sipocz, B.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kovcs, Gbor; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; Lzr, J.; Papp, I.; Sri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 785-796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009ApJ...706..785H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..281R</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. VII. The ``hot-Jupiter''-type planet CoRoT-5b</title>
			<authors>Rauer, H.; Queloz, D.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Alonso, R.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barge, P.; Bord, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; de La Reza, R.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Guenther, E.; Hatzes, A.; Hbrard, G.; Kabath, P.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; Ptzold, M.; Pont, F.; Rabus, M.; Renner, S.; Rouan, D.; Shporer, A.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.281-286</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009A%26A...506..281R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AJ....137.4834W</bibcode>
			<title>The Low Density Transiting Exoplanet WASP-15b</title>
			<authors>West, R. G.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Spano, M.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 137, Issue 6, pp. 4834-4836 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009AJ....137.4834W</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.418.1039M</bibcode>
			<title>UBV(RI)C photometry of transiting planet hosting stars</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Koen, C.; Smalley, B.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 418, Issue 2, pp. 1039-1042.</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011MNRAS.418.1039M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141..187S</bibcode>
			<title>The RAdial Velocity Experiment (RAVE): Third Data Release</title>
			<authors>Siebert, A.; Williams, M. E. K.; Siviero, A.; Reid, W.; Boeche, C.; Steinmetz, M.; Fulbright, J.; Munari, U.; Zwitter, T.; Watson, F. G.; Wyse, R. F. G.; de Jong, R. S.; Enke, H.; Anguiano, B.; Burton, D.; Cass, C. J. P.; Fiegert, K.; Hartley, M.; Ritter, A.; Russel, K. S.; Stupar, M.; Bienaym, O.; Freeman, K. C.; Gilmore, G.; Grebel, E. K.; Helmi, A.; Navarro, J. F.; Binney, J.; Bland-Hawthorn, J.; Campbell, R.; Famaey, B.; Gerhard, O.; Gibson, B. K.; Matijevic, G.; Parker, Q. A.; Seabroke, G. M.; Sharma, S.; Smith, M. C.; Wylie-de Boer, E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 6, article id. 187 (2011).</journal>
			<date>6/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011AJ....141..187S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...529A..50L</bibcode>
			<title>Constraining tidal dissipation in F-type main-sequence stars: the case of CoRoT-11</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.; Damiani, C.; Gandolfi, D.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 529, id.A50</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...529A..50L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011PASJ...63S.531H</bibcode>
			<title>A Possible Tilted Orbit of the Super-Neptune HAT-P-11b</title>
			<authors>Hirano, Teruyuki; Narita, Norio; Shporer, Avi; Sato, Bun'ei; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.63, No.SP2, pp.531--536</journal>
			<date>3/2011 %L</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011PASJ...63S.531H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527L..11H</bibcode>
			<title>The retrograde orbit of the HAT-P-6b exoplanet</title>
			<authors>Hbrard, G.; Ehrenreich, D.; Bouchy, F.; Delfosse, X.; Moutou, C.; Arnold, L.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; Daz, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; Sgransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.L11</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011A%26A...527L..11H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...727...75I</bibcode>
			<title>Explorations into the Viability of Coupled Radius-orbit Evolutionary Models for Inflated Planets</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 727, Issue 2, article id. 75 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2011ApJ...727...75I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASP..122.1465M</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-32b: A Transiting Hot Jupiter Planet Orbiting a Lithium-Poor, Solar-Type Star</title>
			<authors>Maxted, P. F. L.; Anderson, D. R.; Collier Cameron, A.; Gillon, M.; Hellier, C.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Enoch, R.; Lister, T. A.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D. L.; Sgransan, D.; Skillen, I.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 122, issue 898, pp.1465-1470</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010PASP..122.1465M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...522A..54Z</bibcode>
			<title>Distance determination for RAVE stars using stellar models . II. Most likely values assuming a standard stellar evolution scenario</title>
			<authors>Zwitter, T.; Matijevic, G.; Breddels, M. A.; Smith, M. C.; Helmi, A.; Munari, U.; Bienaym, O.; Binney, J.; Bland-Hawthorn, J.; Boeche, C.; Brown, A. G. A.; Campbell, R.; Freeman, K. C.; Fulbright, J.; Gibson, B.; Gilmore, G.; Grebel, E. K.; Navarro, J. F.; Parker, Q. A.; Seabroke, G. M.; Siebert, A.; Siviero, A.; Steinmetz, M.; Watson, F. G.; Williams, M.; Wyse, R. F. G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 522, id.A54</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...522A..54Z</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..33E</bibcode>
			<title>An improved method for estimating the masses of stars with transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Parley, N. R.; Hebb, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A33</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...516A..33E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...511A..90B</bibcode>
			<title>Distance determination for RAVE stars using stellar models</title>
			<authors>Breddels, M. A.; Smith, M. C.; Helmi, A.; Bienaym, O.; Binney, J.; Bland-Hawthorn, J.; Boeche, C.; Burnett, B. C. M.; Campbell, R.; Freeman, K. C.; Gibson, B.; Gilmore, G.; Grebel, E. K.; Munari, U.; Navarro, J. F.; Parker, Q. A.; Seabroke, G. M.; Siebert, A.; Siviero, A.; Steinmetz, M.; Watson, F. G.; Williams, M.; Wyse, R. F. G.; Zwitter, T.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 511, id.A90</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2010A%26A...511A..90B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.398.1827S</bibcode>
			<title>A SuperWASP search for additional transiting planets in 24 known systems</title>
			<authors>Smith, A. M. S.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Anderson, D. R.; Lister, T. A.; Hellier, C.; Pollacco, D.; Queloz, D.; Skillen, I.; West, R. G.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 398, Issue 4, pp. 1827-1834.</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009MNRAS.398.1827S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AJ....137.4834W</bibcode>
			<title>The Low Density Transiting Exoplanet WASP-15b</title>
			<authors>West, R. G.; Anderson, D. R.; Gillon, M.; Hebb, L.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Spano, M.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 137, Issue 6, pp. 4834-4836 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://cdsads.u-strasbg.fr/abs/2009AJ....137.4834W</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
