<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012MNRAS.422.2024J</bibcode>
			<title>The coronal X-ray-age relation and its implications for the evaporation of exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jackson, Alan P.; Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 422, Issue 3, pp. 2024-2043.</journal>
			<date>5/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012MNRAS.422.2024J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012A&amp;A...540A..99E</bibcode>
			<title>Factors affecting the radii of close-in transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Collier Cameron, A.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 540, id.A99</journal>
			<date>4/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012A%26A...540A..99E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012AstL...38..180S</bibcode>
			<title>Observations of extrasolar planet transits with the automated telescopes of the Pulkovo Astronomical Observatory</title>
			<authors>Sokov, E. N.; Vereshchagina, I. A.; Gnedin, Yu. N.; Devyatkin, A. V.; Gorshanov, D. L.; Slesarenko, V. Yu.; Ivanov, A. V.; Naumov, K. N.; Zinov'ev, S. V.; Bekhteva, A. S.; Romas, E. S.; Karashevich, S. V.; Kupriyanov, V. V.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy Letters, Volume 38, Issue 3, pp.180-190</journal>
			<date>3/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012AstL...38..180S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...86E</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-35b, WASP-48b, and HAT-P-30b/WASP-51b: Two New Planets and an Independent Discovery of a Hat Planet</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Faedi, F.; Gillon, M.; Hbrard, G.; Lister, T. A.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bouchy, F.; Bento, J.; Butters, O.; Fossati, L.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Simpson, E.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 3, article id. 86 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142...86E</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....142...86E</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-35b, WASP-48b, and HAT-P-30b/WASP-51b: Two New Planets and an Independent Discovery of a Hat Planet</title>
			<authors>Enoch, B.; Anderson, D. R.; Barros, S. C. C.; Brown, D. J. A.; Collier Cameron, A.; Faedi, F.; Gillon, M.; Hbrard, G.; Lister, T. A.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Smalley, B.; Street, R. A.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; West, R. G.; Bouchy, F.; Bento, J.; Butters, O.; Fossati, L.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Holmes, S.; Jehin, E.; Lendl, M.; Maxted, P. F. L.; McCormac, J.; Miller, G. R. M.; Moulds, V.; Moutou, C.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; Segransan, D.; Simpson, E.; Skillen, I.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 142, Issue 3, article id. 86 (2011).</journal>
			<date>9/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....142...86E</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
