<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...745...26B</bibcode>
			<title>Resolved Spectroscopy of a Brown Dwarf Binary at the T Dwarf/Y Dwarf Transition</title>
			<authors>Burgasser, Adam J.; Gelino, Christopher R.; Cushing, Michael C.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 745, Issue 1, article id. 26 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...745...26B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2012ApJ...744..135L</bibcode>
			<title>Confirmation of One of the Coldest Known Brown Dwarfs</title>
			<authors>Luhman, K. L.; Burgasser, A. J.; Labb, I.; Saumon, D.; Marley, M. S.; Bochanski, J. J.; Monson, A. J.; Persson, S. E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 744, Issue 2, article id. 135 (2012).</journal>
			<date>1/2012</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2012ApJ...744..135L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJS..197...19K</bibcode>
			<title>The First Hundred Brown Dwarfs Discovered by the Wide-field Infrared Survey Explorer (WISE)</title>
			<authors>Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Cushing, Michael C.; Gelino, Christopher R.; Griffith, Roger L.; Skrutskie, Michael F.; Marsh, Kenneth A.; Wright, Edward L.; Mainzer, A.; Eisenhardt, Peter R.; McLean, Ian S.; Thompson, Maggie A.; Bauer, James M.; Benford, Dominic J.; Bridge, Carrie R.; Lake, Sean E.; Petty, Sara M.; Stanford, S. A.; Tsai, Chao-Wei; Bailey, Vanessa; Beichman, Charles A.; Bloom, Joshua S.; Bochanski, John J.; Burgasser, Adam J.; Capak, Peter L.; Cruz, Kelle L.; Hinz, Philip M.; Kartaltepe, Jeyhan S.; Knox, Russell P.; Manohar, Swarnima; Masters, Daniel; Morales-Caldern, Maria; Prato, Lisa A.; Rodigas, Timothy J.; Salvato, Mara; Schurr, Steven D.; Scoville, Nicholas Z.; Simcoe, Robert A.; Stapelfeldt, Karl R.; Stern, Daniel; Stock, Nathan D.; Vacca, William D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement, Volume 197, Issue 2, article id. 19 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJS..197...19K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...743...50C</bibcode>
			<title>The Discovery of Y Dwarfs using Data from the Wide-field Infrared Survey Explorer (WISE)</title>
			<authors>Cushing, Michael C.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Gelino, Christopher R.; Griffith, Roger L.; Skrutskie, Michael F.; Mainzer, A.; Marsh, Kenneth A.; Beichman, Charles A.; Burgasser, Adam J.; Prato, Lisa A.; Simcoe, Robert A.; Marley, Mark S.; Saumon, D.; Freedman, Richard S.; Eisenhardt, Peter R.; Wright, Edward L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 743, Issue 1, article id. 50 (2011).</journal>
			<date>12/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...743...50C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...532L...5S</bibcode>
			<title>Two very nearby (d ~ 5 pc) ultracool brown dwarfs detected by their large proper motions from WISE, 2MASS, and SDSS data</title>
			<authors>Scholz, R.-D.; Bihain, G.; Schnurr, O.; Storm, J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 532, id.L5</journal>
			<date>8/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...532L...5S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...732L..29R</bibcode>
			<title>The Ultra Cool Brown Dwarf Companion of WD 0806-661B: Age, Mass, and Formation Mechanism</title>
			<authors>Rodriguez, David R.; Zuckerman, B.; Melis, Carl; Song, Inseok</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 732, Issue 2, article id. L29 (2011).</journal>
			<date>5/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...732L..29R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011ApJ...730L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Candidate for the Coolest Known Brown Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Luhman, K. L.; Burgasser, A. J.; Bochanski, J. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 730, Issue 1, article id. L9 (2011).</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011ApJ...730L...9L</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
