<planet>
	<bibliography />
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AN....332..547N</bibcode>
			<title>The Young Exoplanet Transit Initiative (YETI)</title>
			<authors>Neuh&#228;user, R.; Errmann, R.; Berndt, A.; Maciejewski, G.; Takahashi, H.; Chen, W. P.; Dimitrov, D. P.; Pribulla, T.; Nikogossian, E. H.; Jensen, E. L. N.; Marschall, L.; Wu, Z.-Y.; Kellerer, A.; Walter, F. M.; Brice&#241;o, C.; Chini, R.; Fernandez, M.; Raetz, St.; Torres, G.; Latham, D. W.; Quinn, S. N.; Niedzielski, A.; Bukowiecki, L.; Nowak, G.; Tomov, T.; Tachihara, K.; Hu, S. C.-L.; Hung, L. W.; Kjurkchieva, D. P.; Radeva, V. S.; Mihov, B. M.; Slavcheva-Mihova, L.; Bozhinova, I. N.; Budaj, J.; Vanko, M.; Kundra, E.; Hamb&#225;lek, L.; Krushevska, V.; Movsessian, T.; Harutyunyan, H.; Downes, J. J.; Hernandez, J.; Hoffmeister, V. H.; Cohen, D. H.; Abel, I.; Ahmad, R.; Chapman, S.; Eckert, S.; Goodman, J.; Guerard, A.; Kim, H. M.; Koontharana, A.; Sokol, J.; Trinh, J.; Wang, Y.; Zhou, X.; Redmer, R.; Kramm, U.; Nettelmann, N.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, J.; Moualla, M.; Ginski, C.; Marka, C.; Adam, C.; Seeliger, M.; Baar, S.; Roell, T.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Trepl, L.; Eisenbei&#223;, T.; Fiedler, S.; Tetzlaff, N.; Schmidt, E.; Hohle, M. M.; Kitze, M.; Chakrova, N.; Gr&#228;fe, C.; Schreyer, K.; Hambaryan, V. V.; Broeg, C. H.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Pandey, A. K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.332, Issue 6, p.547</journal>
			<date>7/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AN....332..547N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011MNRAS.411.2199G</bibcode>
			<title>A new look at NICMOS transmission spectroscopy of HD 189733, GJ-436 and XO-1: no conclusive evidence for molecular features</title>
			<authors>Gibson, N. P.; Pont, F.; Aigrain, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 411, Issue 4, pp. 2199-2213.</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011MNRAS.411.2199G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011A&amp;A...527A..20G</bibcode>
			<title>An analysis of the CoRoT-2 system: a young spotted star and its inflated giant planet</title>
			<authors>Guillot, T.; Havel, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy &amp; Astrophysics, Volume 527, id.A20</journal>
			<date>3/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011A%26A...527A..20G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.408.1689S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - III. Additional planets and stellar models</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 408, Issue 3, pp. 1689-1713.</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.408.1689S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ARA&amp;A..48..631S</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanet Atmospheres</title>
			<authors>Seager, Sara; Deming, Drake</authors>
			<journal>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, vol. 48, p.631-672</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ARA%26A..48..631S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719.1796B</bibcode>
			<title>NICMOS Observations of the Transiting Hot Jupiter XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Burke, Christopher J.; McCullough, P. R.; Bergeron, L. E.; Long, Douglas; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Nelan, Edmund P.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Janes, Kenneth A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 2, pp. 1796-1806 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719.1796B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712L.139T</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Terminator Region Atmosphere of the Hot-Jupiter XO-1b with Transmission Spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>Tinetti, G.; Deroo, P.; Swain, M. R.; Griffith, C. A.; Vasisht, G.; Brown, L. R.; Burke, C.; McCullough, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 712, Issue 2, pp. L139-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712L.139T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..455S</bibcode>
			<title>The LAEX and NASA portals for CoRoT public data</title>
			<authors>Solano, E.; von Braun, K.; Velasco, A.; Ciardi, D. R.; Guti&#233;rrez, R.; McElroy, D. L.; L&#243;pez, M.; Abajian, M.; Garc&#237;a, M.; Ali, B.; Sarro, L. M.; Berriman, G. B.; Bryden, G.; Chan, B.; Good, J.; Kane, S. R.; Laity, A. C.; Lau, C.; Payne, A. N.; Plavchan, P.; Ramirez, S.; Schmitz, M.; Stauffer, J. R.; Wyatt, P. L.; Zhang, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.455-463</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..455S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..514M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission of XO-2b: Evidence for a Weak Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 514-520 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..514M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009AN....330..475R</bibcode>
			<title>Planetary transit observations at the University Observatory Jena: XO-1b and TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Raetz, St.; Mugrauer, M.; Schmidt, T. O. B.; Roell, T.; Eisenbeiss, T.; Hohle, M. M.; Tetzlaff, N.; Vanko, M.; Seifahrt, A.; Broeg, Ch.; Koppenhoefer, J.; Neuh&#228;user, R.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomische Nachrichten, Vol.330, Issue 5, p.475</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009AN....330..475R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692L...9L</bibcode>
			<title>Falling Transiting Extrasolar Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Levrard, B.; Winisdoerffer, C.; Chabrier, G.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. L9-L13 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692L...9L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1302B</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting the Yields of Photometric Surveys for Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1302-1330.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1302B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686..649J</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Spin-Orbit Angle of Exoplanet HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.; Narita, Norio; Enya, Keigo; Williams, Peter K. G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Sato, Bun'ei; Ohta, Yasuhiro; Taruya, Atsushi; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Bakos, Gaspar; Butler, R. Paul; Vogt, Steven S.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide; Yamada, Toru; Yoshii, Yuzuru; Hidas, Marton</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 1, pp. 649-657.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686..649J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684.1427M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission of Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Burrows, Adam; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 2, pp. 1427-1432.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684.1427M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677.1324T</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Parameters for Extrasolar Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Torres, Guillermo; Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 2, pp. 1324-1342.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677.1324T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677..657J</bibcode>
			<title>XO-3b: A Massive Planet in an Eccentric Orbit Transiting an F5 V Star</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Prato, L.; Bissinger, R.; Fleenor, M.; Foote, C. N.; Garcia-Melendo, E.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Mallia, F.; Masi, G.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. 657-670.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677..657J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.384.1097K</bibcode>
			<title>SuperWASP-N extrasolar planet candidates from fields 06h &lt; RA &lt; 16h</title>
			<authors>Kane, S. R.; Clarkson, W. I.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Christian, D. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Lister, T. A.; Street, R. A.; Evans, A.; Fitzsimmons, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Keenan, F. P.; Norton, A. J.; Osborne, J.; Parley, N. R.; Pollacco, D. L.; Ryans, R.; Skillen, I.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 384, Issue 3, pp. 1097-1108.</journal>
			<date>3/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.384.1097K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007A&amp;A...475..729F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting and predicting the yield of transit surveys: giant planets in the OGLE fields</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Morello, V.; Pont, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 475, Issue 2, November IV 2007, pp.729-746</journal>
			<date>11/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007A%26A...475..729F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.380.1230C</bibcode>
			<title>Efficient identification of exoplanetary transit candidates from SuperWASP light curves</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Wilson, D. M.; West, R. G.; Hebb, L.; Wang, X.-B.; Aigrain, S.; Bouchy, F.; Christian, D. J.; Clarkson, W. I.; Enoch, B.; Esposito, M.; Guenther, E.; Haswell, C. A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Loeillet, B.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; Moutou, C.; Parley, N.; Pollacco, D.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 380, Issue 3, pp. 1230-1244.</journal>
			<date>9/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.380.1230C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007PASJ...59..763N</bibcode>
			<title>Measurement of the Rossiter-Laughlin Effect in the Transiting Exoplanetary System TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Narita, N.; Enya, K.; Sato, B.; Ohta, Y.; Winn, J. N.; Suto, Y.; Taruya, A.; Turner, E. L.; Aoki, W.; Yoshii, M.; Yamada, T.; Tamura, Y.</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.59, No.4, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007PASJ...59..763N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379..773S</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-1: a lithium- and metal-rich star with an oversized planet</title>
			<authors>Stempels, H. C.; Collier Cameron, A.; Hebb, L.; Smalley, B.; Frandsen, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 379, Issue 2, pp. 773-778.</journal>
			<date>8/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379..773S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007MNRAS.379L..11S</bibcode>
			<title>A method for the direct determination of the surface gravities of transiting extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Wheatley, Peter J.; Sams, Giles</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 379, Issue 1, pp. L11-L15.</journal>
			<date>7/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007MNRAS.379L..11S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...661..502B</bibcode>
			<title>Possible Solutions to the Radius Anomalies of Transiting Giant Planets</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Hubbard, W. B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 661, Issue 1, pp. 502-514.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...661..502B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...660..850D</bibcode>
			<title>Millimagnitude Photometry for Transiting Extrasolar Planetary Candidates. II. Transits of OGLE-TR-113-b in the Optical and Near-IR</title>
			<authors>D&#237;az, Rodrigo F.; Ram&#237;rez, Sebasti&#225;n; Fern&#225;ndez, Jos&#233; Miguel; Gallardo, Jos&#233;; Gieren, Wolfgang; Ivanov, Valentin D.; Mauas, Pablo; Minniti, Dante; Pietrzynski, Grzegorz; P&#233;rez, Felipe; Ru&#237;z, Mar&#237;a Teresa; Udalski, Andrzej; Zoccali, Manuela</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 660, Issue 1, pp. 850-857.</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...660..850D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...657.1098W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. III. Tres Transits of TrES-1</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Roussanova, Anna</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 657, Issue 2, pp. 1098-1106.</journal>
			<date>3/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...657.1098W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...655..550G</bibcode>
			<title>Prospects for the Characterization and Confirmation of Transiting Exoplanets via the Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect</title>
			<authors>Gaudi, B. Scott; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 655, Issue 1, pp. 550-563.</journal>
			<date>1/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...655..550G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007BAVSR..56..163B</bibcode>
			<title>Uebersicht zum BAV Veraenderlichen-Treffen 2007 in Hartha.</title>
			<authors>Braune, W.; Flechsig, G.-U.</authors>
			<journal>BAV Rundbrief, 56, 163 (2007)</journal>
			<date>0/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007BAVSR..56..163B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652L.137F</bibcode>
			<title>Observational Constraints on Trojans of Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Ford, Eric B.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. L137-L140.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652L.137F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...652.1715H</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. I. Four Consecutive Transits of the Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Holman, Matthew J.; Winn, Joshua N.; Latham, David W.; O'Donovan, Francis T.; Charbonneau, David; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Hergenrother, Carl; Everett, Mark E.; P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 652, Issue 2, pp. 1715-1723.</journal>
			<date>12/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...652.1715H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006PASP..118.1245W</bibcode>
			<title>SuperWASP Observations of the Transiting Extrasolar Planet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Wilson, D. M.; Enoch, B.; Christian, D. J.; Clarkson, W. I.; Collier Cameron, A.; Deeg, H. J.; Evans, A.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Kane, S. R.; Lister, T. A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Norton, A. J.; Pollacco, D.; Skillen, I.; Street, R. A.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>The Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 118, Issue 847, pp. 1245-1251.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006PASP..118.1245W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2006ApJ...648.1228M</bibcode>
			<title>A Transiting Planet of a Sun-like Star</title>
			<authors>McCullough, P. R.; Stys, J. E.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Johns-Krull, C. M.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Bye, B. A.; Dodd, C.; Fleming, S. W.; Pinnick, A.; Bissinger, R.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 648, Issue 2, pp. 1228-1238.</journal>
			<date>9/2006</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2006ApJ...648.1228M</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
