<planet>
	<bibliography>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2011AJ....141...59B</bibcode>
			<title>The Reflection Effect in Interacting Binaries or in Planet-Star Systems</title>
			<authors>Budaj, J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 141, Issue 2, article id. 59 (2011).</journal>
			<date>2/2011</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2011AJ....141...59B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...724.1108J</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and Rossiter-Mclaughlin Effect of Exoplanet Kepler-8b</title>
			<authors>Jenkins, Jon M.; Borucki, William J.; Koch, David G.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Cochran, William D.; Welsh, William F.; Basri, Gibor; Batalha, Natalie M.; Buchhave, Lars A.; Brown, Timothy M.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Dunham, Edward W.; Endl, Michael; Fischer, Debra A.; Gautier, Thomas N.; Geary, John C.; Gilliland, Ronald L.; Howell, Steve B.; Isaacson, Howard; Johnson, John Asher; Latham, David W.; Lissauer, Jack J.; Monet, David G.; Rowe, Jason F.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Howard, Andrew W.; MacQueen, Phillip; Orosz, Jerome A.; Chandrasekaran, Hema; Twicken, Joseph D.; Bryson, Stephen T.; Quintana, Elisa V.; Clarke, Bruce D.; Li, Jie; Allen, Christopher; Tenenbaum, Peter; Wu, Hayley; Meibom, S&#248;ren; Klaus, Todd C.; Middour, Christopher K.; Cote, Miles T.; McCauliff, Sean; Girouard, Forrest R.; Gunter, Jay P.; Wohler, Bill; Hall, Jennifer R.; Ibrahim, Khadeejah; Kamal Uddin, AKM; Wu, Michael S.; Bhavsar, Paresh A.; Van Cleve, Jeffrey; Pletcher, David L.; Dotson, Jessie L.; Haas, Michael R.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 724, Issue 2, pp. 1108-1119 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...724.1108J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...521A..76W</bibcode>
			<title>Limits on the orbits and masses of moons around currently-known transiting exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Weidner, C.; Horne, K.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 521, id.A76</journal>
			<date>10/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...521A..76W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.407.1259J</bibcode>
			<title>Habitability of exoplanetary systems with planets observed in transit</title>
			<authors>Jones, Barrie W.; Sleep, P. Nick</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 407, Issue 2, pp. 1259-1267.</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.407.1259J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1644K</bibcode>
			<title>On the Transit Potential of the Planet Orbiting Iota Draconis</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Reffert, Sabine; Henry, Gregory W.; Fischer, Debra; Schwab, Christian; Clubb, Kelsey I.; Bergmann, Christoph</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1644-1649 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1644K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...520A..65B</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. X. CoRoT-10b: a giant planet in a 13.24 day eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Bonomo, A. S.; Santerne, A.; Alonso, R.; Gazzano, J.-C.; Havel, M.; Aigrain, S.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Bruntt, H.; Cabrera, J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Carone, L.; Carpano, S.; Csizmadia, Sz.; Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Ferraz-Mello, S.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Samuel, B.; Schneider, J.; Tingley, B.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 520, id.A65</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...520A..65B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.406.1918D</bibcode>
			<title>The Hill stability of the possible moons of extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Donnison, J. R.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 406, Issue 3, pp. 1918-1934.</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.406.1918D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...717L.138H</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and the Surface Gravity of Hot Jupiters</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 717, Issue 2, pp. L138-L142 (2010).</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...717L.138H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010PASJ...62..653N</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-Orbit Alignment of the TrES-4 Transiting Planetary System and Possible Additional Radial-Velocity Variation</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Winn, Joshua N.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.62, No.3, pp.653--660</journal>
			<date>6/2010 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010PASJ...62..653N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...713..751I</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Heating Models for the Radii of the Inflated Transiting Giant Planets WASP-4b, WASP-6b, WASP-12b, WASP-15b, and TrES-4</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam; Spiegel, David S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 713, Issue 2, pp. 751-763 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...713..751I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712.1433B</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Probabilities for Stars with Stellar Inclination Constraints</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 2, pp. 1433-1442 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712.1433B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...513A..69H</bibcode>
			<title>The SOPHIE search for northern extrasolar planets. II. A multiple planet system around HD 9446</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Bonfils, X.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Moutou, C.; Delfosse, X.; Bouchy, F.; Boisse, I.; Arnold, L.; Desort, M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 513, id.A69</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...513A..69H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.403..151C</bibcode>
			<title>Line-profile tomography of exoplanet transits - I. The Doppler shadow of HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Collier Cameron, A.; Bruce, V. A.; Miller, G. R. M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Queloz, D.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 403, Issue 1, pp. 151-158.</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.403..151C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712...38E</bibcode>
			<title>An a Priori Investigation of Astrophysical False Positives in Ground-Based Transiting Planet Surveys</title>
			<authors>Evans, Tom M.; Sackett, Penny D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 38-51 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712...38E</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..111M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission and Tidal Heating of the Heavy and Eccentric Planet XO-3b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; Greene, Tom; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Deming, Drake L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 111-118 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..111M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.401.2665P</bibcode>
			<title>Refined stellar, orbital and planetary parameters of the eccentric HAT-P-2 planetary system</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Torres, Guillermo; Noyes, Robert W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Johnson, John A.; Henry, Gregory W.; Butler, R. Paul; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Howard, Andrew W.; Sipocz, Brigitta; Latham, David W.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 401, Issue 4, pp. 2665-2674.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.401.2665P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..159A</bibcode>
			<title>Wasp-17b: An Ultra-Low Density Planet in a Probable Retrograde Orbit</title>
			<authors>Anderson, D. R.; Hellier, C.; Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Smalley, B.; Hebb, L.; Collier Cameron, A.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Queloz, D.; West, R. G.; Bentley, S. J.; Enoch, B.; Horne, K.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Parley, N. R.; Pepe, F.; Pollacco, D.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 159-167 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..159A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...709..149S</bibcode>
			<title>Models of Neptune-Mass Exoplanets: Emergent Fluxes and Albedos</title>
			<authors>Spiegel, David S.; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent; Hubeny, Ivan; Milsom, John A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 709, Issue 1, pp. 149-158 (2010).</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...709..149S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A.103S</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos preliminary astrometric masses for the two close-in companions to HD 131664 and HD 43848. A brown dwarf and a low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Desidera, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A103</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A.103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707..446B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-13b,c: A Transiting Hot Jupiter with a Massive Outer Companion on an Eccentric Orbit</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; Howard, A. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Hartman, J.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225; cs, G&#233;za; Fischer, D. A.; Latham, D. W.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Stefanik, R. P.; Sipocz, B.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Esquerdo, G. A.; P&#225;l, A.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, pp. 446-456 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707..446B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...706..785H</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-12b: A Low-Density Sub-Saturn Mass Planet Transiting a Metal-Poor K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Hartman, J. D.; Bakos, G. &#193;.; Torres, G.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Noyes, R. W.; P&#225;l, A.; Latham, D. W.; Sipocz, B.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; Fernandez, J. M.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 706, Issue 1, pp. 785-796 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...706..785H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASJ...61L..35N</bibcode>
			<title>First Evidence of a Retrograde Orbit of a Transiting Exoplanet HAT-P-7b</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Sato, Bun'ei; Hirano, Teruyuki; Tamura, Motohide</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.61, No.5, pp.L35-L40</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASJ...61L..35N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASJ...61..991N</bibcode>
			<title>Improved Measurement of the Rossiter-McLaughlin Effect in the Exoplanetary System HD 17156</title>
			<authors>Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Sato, Bun'ei; Winn, Joshua N.; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Aoki, Wako; Tamura, Motohide; Yamada, Toru</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Vol.61, No.5, pp.991--997</journal>
			<date>10/2009 %L</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASJ...61..991N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...704.1107L</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Transiting Planet and Eight Eclipsing Binaries in HATNet Field G205</title>
			<authors>Latham, David W.; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.; Torres, Guillermo; Stefanik, Robert P.; Noyes, Robert W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Fischer, Debra A.; Butler, R. Paul; Sipocz, Brigitta; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Vogt, Steven S.; Hartman, Joel D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; L&#225;z&#225;r, J&#243;zsef; Papp, Istv&#225;n; S&#225;ri, P&#225;l</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 704, Issue 2, pp. 1107-1119 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...704.1107L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703L..99W</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-7: A Retrograde or Polar Orbit, and a Third Body</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Albrecht, Simon; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Crossfield, Ian J.; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. L99-L103 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703L..99W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.2091W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Ingress and the Tilted Orbit of the Extraordinarily Eccentric Exoplanet HD 80606b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Howard, Andrew W.; Johnson, John Asher; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Gazak, J. Zachary; Starkey, Donn; Ford, Eric B.; Col&#243;n, Knicole D.; Reyes, Francisco; Nortmann, Lisa; Dreizler, Stefan; Odewahn, Stephen; Welsh, William F.; Kadakia, Shimonee; Vanderbei, Robert J.; Adams, Elisabeth R.; Lockhart, Matthew; Crossfield, Ian J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Dantowitz, Ronald; Carter, Joshua A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. 2091-2100 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.2091W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...703.1734V</bibcode>
			<title>Simulations of Winds of Weak-Lined T Tauri Stars: The Magnetic Field Geometry and the Influence of the Wind on Giant Planet Migration</title>
			<authors>Vidotto, A. A.; Opher, M.; Jatenco-Pereira, V.; Gombosi, T. I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 703, Issue 2, pp. 1734-1742 (2009).</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...703.1734V</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..399L</bibcode>
			<title>Determining the mass loss limit for close-in exoplanets: what can we learn from transit observations?</title>
			<authors>Lammer, H.; Odert, P.; Leitzinger, M.; Khodachenko, M. L.; Panchenko, M.; Kulikov, Yu. N.; Zhang, T. L.; Lichtenegger, H. I. M.; Erkaev, N. V.; Wuchterl, G.; Micela, G.; Penz, T.; Biernat, H. K.; Weingrill, J.; Steller, M.; Ottacher, H.; Hasiba, J.; Hanslmeier, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.399-410</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..399L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..377T</bibcode>
			<title>The Rossiter-McLaughlin effect of CoRoT-3b and HD 189733b</title>
			<authors>Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Queloz, D.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Collier Cameron, A.; Claret, A.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Deleuil, M.; Guillot, T.; H&#233;brard, G.; Lecavelier Des &#201;tangs, A.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Udry, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.377-384</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..377T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...505..853B</bibcode>
			<title>The SOPHIE search for northern extrasolar planets . I. A companion around HD 16760 with mass close to the planet/brown-dwarf transition</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; H&#233;brard, G.; Udry, S.; Delfosse, X.; Boisse, I.; Desort, M.; Bonfils, X.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A. M.; Le Coroller, H.; Lovis, C.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 505, Issue 2, 2009, pp.853-858</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...505..853B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701..514M</bibcode>
			<title>Detection of Thermal Emission of XO-2b: Evidence for a Weak Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 1, pp. 514-520 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701..514M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700.1921I</bibcode>
			<title>Coupled Evolution with Tides of the Radius and Orbit of Transiting Giant Planets: General Results</title>
			<authors>Ibgui, Laurent; Burrows, Adam</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 2, pp. 1921-1932 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700.1921I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...503..601B</bibcode>
			<title>Characterization of the HD 17156 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Barbieri, M.; Alonso, R.; Desidera, S.; Sozzetti, A.; Martinez Fiorenzano, A. F.; Almenara, J. M.; Cecconi, M.; Claudi, R. U.; Charbonneau, D.; Endl, M.; Granata, V.; Gratton, R.; Laughlin, G.; Loeillet, B.; Amateur Consortium, Exoplanet</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 503, Issue 2, 2009, pp.601-612</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...503..601B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1797K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon - II</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1797-1804.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1797K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..302W</bibcode>
			<title>On the Spin-Orbit Misalignment of the XO-3 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Fabrycky, Daniel; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Narita, Norio; Crossfield, Ian J.; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Esquerdo, Gil; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 302-308 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..302W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.395.2268B</bibcode>
			<title>On the tidal evolution of Hot Jupiters on inclined orbits</title>
			<authors>Barker, Adrian J.; Ogilvie, Gordon I.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 395, Issue 4, pp. 2268-2287.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.395.2268B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...698.1778R</bibcode>
			<title>Probing the Interiors of very Hot Jupiters Using Transit Light Curves</title>
			<authors>Ragozzine, Darin; Wolf, Aaron S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 698, Issue 2, pp. 1778-1794 (2009).</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...698.1778R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1950B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-10b: A Light and Moderately Hot Jupiter Transiting A K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; P&#225;l, A.; Torres, G.; Sipocz, B.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Hartman, J.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1950-1955 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1950B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1230F</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Spin-Orbit Alignment: Results from the Ensemble of Rossiter-McLaughlin Observations</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1230-1240 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1230F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...499..615D</bibcode>
			<title>On the possibility of detecting extrasolar planets' atmospheres with the Rossiter-McLaughlin effect</title>
			<authors>Dreizler, S.; Reiners, A.; Homeier, D.; Noll, M.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 499, Issue 2, 2009, pp.615-621</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...499..615D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498L..41L</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit alignment of the Fomalhaut planetary system probed by optical long baseline interferometry</title>
			<authors>Le Bouquin, J.-B.; Absil, O.; Benisty, M.; Massi, F.; M&#233;rand, A.; Stefl, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 3, 2009, pp.L41-L44</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498L..41L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121..309J</bibcode>
			<title>International Year of Astronomy Invited Review on Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 878, pp.309-315</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121..309J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694.1566S</bibcode>
			<title>The Stability and Dynamics of Planets in Tight Binary Systems</title>
			<authors>Saleh, Lamya A.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 2, pp. 1566-1576 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694.1566S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...497..545S</bibcode>
			<title>OGLE2-TR-L9b: an exoplanet transiting a rapidly rotating F3 star</title>
			<authors>Snellen, I. A. G.; Koppenhoefer, J.; van der Burg, R. F. J.; Dreizler, S.; Greiner, J.; de Hoon, M. D. J.; Husser, T. O.; Kr&#252;hler, T.; Saglia, R. P.; Vuijsje, F. N.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 497, Issue 2, 2009, pp.545-550</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...497..545S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394L..93M</bibcode>
			<title>On the various origins of close-in extrasolar planets</title>
			<authors>Marchi, S.; Ortolani, S.; Nagasawa, M.; Ida, S.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. L93-L96.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394L..93M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694..183F</bibcode>
			<title>Protostellar Cloud Fragmentation and Inward Migration by Disk Capture as the Origin of Massive Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Font-Ribera, Andreu; Miralda Escud&#233;, Jordi; Ribas, Ignasi</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 1, pp. 183-191 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694..183F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392.1532J</bibcode>
			<title>WASP-14b: 7.3 MJ transiting planet in an eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Joshi, Y. C.; Pollacco, D.; Collier Cameron, A.; Skillen, I.; Simpson, E.; Steele, I.; Street, R. A.; Stempels, H. C.; Christian, D. J.; Hebb, L.; Bouchy, F.; Gibson, N. P.; H&#233;brard, G.; Keenan, F. P.; Loeillet, B.; Meaburn, J.; Moutou, C.; Smalley, B.; Todd, I.; West, R. G.; Anderson, D. R.; Bentley, S.; Enoch, B.; Haswell, C. A.; Hellier, C.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Lister, T. A.; McDonald, I.; Maxted, P.; Mayor, M.; Norton, A. J.; Parley, N.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Ryans, R.; Smith, A. M. S.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.; Wilson, D. M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 4, pp. 1532-1538.</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392.1532J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...692..290K</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery of a Low-Mass Companion to the Solar-Type Star TYC 2534-698-1</title>
			<authors>Kane, Stephen R.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Cochran, William D.; Street, Rachel A.; Sivarani, Thirupathi; Henry, Gregory W.; Williamson, Michael H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 692, Issue 1, pp. 290-297 (2009).</journal>
			<date>2/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...692..290K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.392..181K</bibcode>
			<title>Transit timing effects due to an exomoon</title>
			<authors>Kipping, David M.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 392, Issue 1, pp. 181-189.</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.392..181K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...690.1393S</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-9b: A Low-Density Planet Transiting a Moderately Faint F Star</title>
			<authors>Shporer, Avi; Bakos, G&#193;sp&#193;r &#193;.; Bouchy, Francois; Pont, Frederic; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Latham, Dave W.; Sip&#246;cz, Brigitta; Torres, Guillermo; Mazeh, Tsevi; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Noyes, Robert W.; Sasselov, Dimitar D.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J&#243;zsef; Papp, Istv&#225;n; S&#225;ri, P&#225;l; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 690, Issue 2, pp. 1393-1400 (2009).</journal>
			<date>1/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...690.1393S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...491..889D</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission . VI. CoRoT-Exo-3b: the first secure inhabitant of the brown-dwarf desert</title>
			<authors>Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Alonso, R.; Bouchy, F.; Rouan, D.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bruntt, H.; Bord&#233;, P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 491, Issue 3, 2008, pp.889-897</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...491..889D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1191L</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Radii of Extrasolar Giant Planets: the Cases of TrES-4, XO-3b, and HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>Liu, Xin; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1191-1200.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1191L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1331B</bibcode>
			<title>XO-5b: A Transiting Jupiter-sized Planet with a 4 day Period</title>
			<authors>Burke, Christopher J.; McCullough, P. R.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Long, Doug; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Machalek, P.; Janes, Kenneth A.; Taylor, B.; Fleenor, Michael L.; Foote, C. N.; Gary, Bruce L.; Garc&#237;a-Melendo, Enrique; Gregorio, J.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1331-1340.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1331B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...686.1302B</bibcode>
			<title>Predicting the Yields of Photometric Surveys for Transiting Extrasolar Planets</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Gaudi, B. Scott</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 686, Issue 2, pp. 1302-1330.</journal>
			<date>10/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...686.1302B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389..191P</bibcode>
			<title>Periastron precession measurements in transiting extrasolar planetary systems at the level of general relativity</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Kocsis, Bence</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 1, pp. 191-198.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389..191P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...685..543J</bibcode>
			<title>Observability of the General Relativistic Precession of Periastra in Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jord&#225;n, Andr&#233;s; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 685, Issue 1, pp. 543-552.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...685..543J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684.1427M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission of Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Burrows, Adam; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 2, pp. 1427-1432.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684.1427M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488L..47M</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. V. CoRoT-Exo-4b: stellar and planetary parameters</title>
			<authors>Moutou, C.; Bruntt, H.; Guillot, T.; Shporer, A.; Guenther, E.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Benz, W.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deeg, H. J.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gillon, M.; Gondoin, P.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Kabath, P.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Magain, P.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pepe, F.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rabus, M.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Udry, S.; Wuchterl, G.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.L47-L50</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488L..47M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488..763H</bibcode>
			<title>Misaligned spin-orbit in the XO-3 planetary system?</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Loeillet, B.; Rabus, M.; Bonfils, X.; Moutou, C.; Boisse, I.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488..763H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...683L..59C</bibcode>
			<title>The Spin-Orbit Alignment of the HD 17156 Transiting Eccentric Planetary System</title>
			<authors>Cochran, William D.; Redfield, Seth; Endl, Michael; Cochran, Anita L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 683, Issue 1, pp. L59-L62.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...683L..59C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...683.1076W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. IX. Evidence for a Smaller Radius of the Exoplanet XO-3b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Torres, Guillermo; McCullough, Peter; Johns-Krull, Christopher; Latham, David W.; Shporer, Avi; Mazeh, Tsevi; Garcia-Melendo, Enrique; Foote, Cindy; Esquerdo, Gil; Everett, Mark</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 683, Issue 2, pp. 1076-1084.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...683.1076W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...682.1277B</bibcode>
			<title>Optical Albedo Theory of Strongly Irradiated Giant Planets: The Case of HD 209458b</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Ibgui, L.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 682, Issue 2, pp. 1277-1282.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...682.1277B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...681..636I</bibcode>
			<title>Parameters and Predictions for the Long-Period Transiting Planet HD 17156b</title>
			<authors>Irwin, Jonathan; Charbonneau, David; Nutzman, Philip; Welsh, William F.; Rajan, Abhijith; Hidas, Marton; Brown, Timothy M.; Lister, Timothy A.; Davies, Donald; Laughlin, Gregory; Langton, Jonathan</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 681, Issue 1, pp. 636-643.</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...681..636I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...485..871G</bibcode>
			<title>Improved parameters for the transiting planet HD 17156b: a high-density giant planet with a very eccentric orbit</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Mayor, M.; Queloz, D.; Udry, S.; North, P.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 485, Issue 3, 2008, pp.871-875</journal>
			<date>7/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...485..871G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677..657J</bibcode>
			<title>XO-3b: A Massive Planet in an Eccentric Orbit Transiting an F5 V Star</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Prato, L.; Bissinger, R.; Fleenor, M.; Foote, C. N.; Garcia-Melendo, E.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Mallia, F.; Masi, G.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. 657-670.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677..657J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...668L.171B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectral Models of the Planet HD 209458b with a Thermal Inversion and Water Emission Bands</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Knutson, H. A.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 668, Issue 2, pp. L171-L174.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...668L.171B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AAS...210.9605J</bibcode>
			<title>The Unusual Transiting Extra-Solar Planet Orbiting XO-3</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; McCullough, P. M.; Burke, C. J.; Valenti, J. A.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Bissinger, R.; Fleenor, M.; Foote, C. N.; Garcia-Melendo, E.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Mallia, F.; Masi, G.; Prato, L. A.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society Meeting 210, #96.05; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 38, p.225; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 38, p.225</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AAS...210.9605J</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliography>
	<bibliographystar>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...725.1995M</bibcode>
			<title>Tidal Evolution of Close-in Planets</title>
			<authors>Matsumura, Soko; Peale, Stanton J.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 725, Issue 2, pp. 1995-2016 (2010).</journal>
			<date>12/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...725.1995M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...723..285H</bibcode>
			<title>Calibration of Equilibrium Tide Theory for Extrasolar Planet Systems</title>
			<authors>Hansen, Brad M. S.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 723, Issue 1, pp. 285-299 (2010).</journal>
			<date>11/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...723..285H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...720.1569K</bibcode>
			<title>A Correlation Between Stellar Activity and Hot Jupiter Emission Spectra</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 720, Issue 2, pp. 1569-1576 (2010).</journal>
			<date>9/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...720.1569K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...719..602S</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence of Possible Spin-orbit Misalignment Along the Line of Sight in Transiting Exoplanet Systems</title>
			<authors>Schlaufman, Kevin C.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 719, Issue 1, pp. 602-611 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...719..602S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...718L.145W</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Stars with Hot Jupiters Have High Obliquities</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Fabrycky, Daniel; Albrecht, Simon; Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 718, Issue 2, pp. L145-L149 (2010).</journal>
			<date>8/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...718L.145W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.405.1867S</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit alignment of the transiting exoplanet WASP-3b from Rossiter-McLaughlin observations</title>
			<authors>Simpson, E. K.; Pollacco, D.; H&#233;brard, G.; Gibson, N. P.; Barros, S. C. C.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Collier Cameron, A.; Miller, G. R. M.; Watson, C. A.; Keenan, F. P.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 405, Issue 3, pp. 1867-1872.</journal>
			<date>7/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.405.1867S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..95H</bibcode>
			<title>Observation of the full 12-hour-long transit of the exoplanet HD 80606b. Warm-Spitzer photometry and SOPHIE spectroscopy</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; D&#233;sert, J.-M.; D&#237;az, R. F.; Boisse, I.; Bouchy, F.; Lecavelier Des Etangs, A.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Arnold, L.; Bonfils, X.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Gregorio, J.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santerne, A.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Sing, D. K.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A95</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..95H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...516A..64L</bibcode>
			<title>Is tidal heating sufficient to explain bloated exoplanets? Consistent calculations accounting for finite initial eccentricity</title>
			<authors>Leconte, J.; Chabrier, G.; Baraffe, I.; Levrard, B.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 516, id.A64</journal>
			<date>6/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...516A..64L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...715..421T</bibcode>
			<title>A Prograde, Low-inclination Orbit for the Very Hot Jupiter WASP-3b</title>
			<authors>Tripathi, Anjali; Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Howard, Andrew W.; Halverson, Sam; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Holman, Matthew J.; de Kleer, Katherine R.; Carter, Joshua A.; Esquerdo, Gilbert A.; Everett, Mark E.; Cabrera, Nicole E.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 715, Issue 1, pp. 421-428 (2010).</journal>
			<date>5/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...715..421T</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712.1433B</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Probabilities for Stars with Stellar Inclination Constraints</title>
			<authors>Beatty, Thomas G.; Seager, Sara</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 2, pp. 1433-1442 (2010).</journal>
			<date>4/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712.1433B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...712..218I</bibcode>
			<title>A Time-Dependent Radiative Model for the Atmosphere of the Eccentric Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Iro, N.; Deming, L. D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 712, Issue 1, pp. 218-225 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...712..218I</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..772R</bibcode>
			<title>Planet-Planet Scattering in Planetesimal Disks. II. Predictions for Outer Extrasolar Planetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Raymond, Sean N.; Armitage, Philip J.; Gorelick, Noel</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 2, pp. 772-795 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..772R</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010ApJ...711..111M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission and Tidal Heating of the Heavy and Eccentric Planet XO-3b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; Greene, Tom; McCullough, Peter R.; Burrows, Adam; Burke, Christopher J.; Hora, Joseph L.; Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; Deming, Drake L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 711, Issue 1, pp. 111-118 (2010).</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010ApJ...711..111M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...512A..77L</bibcode>
			<title>Hot Jupiters and the evolution of stellar angular momentum</title>
			<authors>Lanza, A. F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 512, id.A77</journal>
			<date>3/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...512A..77L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010MNRAS.402L...1P</bibcode>
			<title>The spin-orbit angle of the transiting hot Jupiter CoRoT-1b</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; Endl, M.; Cochran, W. D.; Barnes, S. I.; Sneden, C.; MacQueen, P. J.; Moutou, C.; Aigrain, S.; Alonso, R.; Baglin, A.; Bouchy, F.; Deleuil, M.; Fridlund, M.; H&#233;brard, G.; Hatzes, A.; Mazeh, T.; Shporer, A.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 402, Issue 1, pp. L1-L5.</journal>
			<date>2/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010MNRAS.402L...1P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2010A&amp;A...509A.103S</bibcode>
			<title>Hipparcos preliminary astrometric masses for the two close-in companions to HD 131664 and HD 43848. A brown dwarf and a low-mass star</title>
			<authors>Sozzetti, A.; Desidera, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 509, id.A103</journal>
			<date>1/2010</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2010A%26A...509A.103S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...707..167S</bibcode>
			<title>Physical Properties of the 0.94-Day Period Transiting Planetary System WASP-18</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John; Hinse, T. C.; Dominik, M.; Glitrup, M.; J&#248;rgensen, U. G.; Liebig, C.; Mathiasen, M.; Anderson, D. R.; Bozza, V.; Browne, P.; Burgdorf, M.; Calchi Novati, S.; Dreizler, S.; Finet, F.; Harps&#248;e, K.; Hessman, F.; Hundertmark, M.; Maier, G.; Mancini, L.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Rahvar, S.; Ricci, D.; Scarpetta, G.; Skottfelt, J.; Snodgrass, C.; Surdej, J.; Zimmer, F.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 707, Issue 1, article id. 167-172 (2009).</journal>
			<date>12/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...707..167S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...705..683B</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Lightcurves of Extrasolar Planets Orbiting Rapidly Rotating Stars</title>
			<authors>Barnes, Jason W.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 705, Issue 1, pp. 683-692 (2009).</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...705..683B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...507..523A</bibcode>
			<title>A homogeneous spectroscopic analysis of host stars of transiting planets</title>
			<authors>Ammler-von Eiff, M.; Santos, N. C.; Sousa, S. G.; Fernandes, J.; Guillot, T.; Israelian, G.; Mayor, M.; Melo, C.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 507, Issue 1, 2009, pp.523-530</journal>
			<date>11/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...507..523A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121.1104J</bibcode>
			<title>A Third Exoplanetary System with Misaligned Orbital and Stellar Spin Axes</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher; Winn, Joshua N.; Albrecht, Simon; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Gazak, J. Zachary</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 884, pp.1104-1111</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121.1104J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...506..153M</bibcode>
			<title>Accuracy of stellar parameters of exoplanet-host stars determined from asteroseismology</title>
			<authors>Mulet-Marquis, C.; Baraffe, I.; Aigrain, S.; Pont, F.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 506, Issue 1, 2009, pp.153-158</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...506..153M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...505..853B</bibcode>
			<title>The SOPHIE search for northern extrasolar planets . I. A companion around HD 16760 with mass close to the planet/brown-dwarf transition</title>
			<authors>Bouchy, F.; H&#233;brard, G.; Udry, S.; Delfosse, X.; Boisse, I.; Desort, M.; Bonfils, X.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A. M.; Le Coroller, H.; Lovis, C.; Moutou, C.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 505, Issue 2, 2009, pp.853-858</journal>
			<date>10/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...505..853B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...702.1413M</bibcode>
			<title>Inflating and Deflating Hot Jupiters: Coupled Tidal and Thermal Evolution of Known Transiting Planets</title>
			<authors>Miller, N.; Fortney, J. J.; Jackson, B.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 702, Issue 2, pp. 1413-1427 (2009).</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...702.1413M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...504..605F</bibcode>
			<title>Interpreting the yield of transit surveys: are there groups in the known transiting planets population?</title>
			<authors>Fressin, F.; Guillot, T.; Nesta, L.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 504, Issue 2, 2009, pp.605-615</journal>
			<date>9/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...504..605F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...701.1116N</bibcode>
			<title>Transit Timing Variations for Eccentric and Inclined Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Nesvorn&#253;, David</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 701, Issue 2, pp. 1116-1122 (2009).</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...701.1116N</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...502..695P</bibcode>
			<title>Spin-orbit misalignment in the HD 80606 planetary system</title>
			<authors>Pont, F.; H&#233;brard, G.; Irwin, J. M.; Bouchy, F.; Moutou, C.; Ehrenreich, D.; Guillot, T.; Aigrain, S.; Bonfils, X.; Berta, Z.; Boisse, I.; Burke, C.; Charbonneau, D.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Nutzman, P.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 502, Issue 2, 2009, pp.695-703</journal>
			<date>8/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...502..695P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1789P</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical evidence for tidal evolution in transiting planetary systems</title>
			<authors>Pont, Fr&#233;d&#233;ric</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 3, pp. 1789-1796.</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1789P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..832C</bibcode>
			<title>The Role of Planet Accretion in Creating the Next Generation of Red Giant Rapid Rotators</title>
			<authors>Carlberg, Joleen K.; Majewski, Steven R.; Arras, Phil</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 832-843 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..832C</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...700..302W</bibcode>
			<title>On the Spin-Orbit Misalignment of the XO-3 Exoplanetary System</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Johnson, John Asher; Fabrycky, Daniel; Howard, Andrew W.; Marcy, Geoffrey W.; Narita, Norio; Crossfield, Ian J.; Suto, Yasushi; Turner, Edwin L.; Esquerdo, Gil; Holman, Matthew J.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 700, Issue 1, pp. 302-308 (2009).</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...700..302W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...501..785G</bibcode>
			<title>Discovery and characterization of WASP-6b, an inflated sub-Jupiter mass planet transiting a solar-type star</title>
			<authors>Gillon, M.; Anderson, D. R.; Triaud, A. H. M. J.; Hellier, C.; Maxted, P. F. L.; Pollaco, D.; Queloz, D.; Smalley, B.; West, R. G.; Wilson, D. M.; Bentley, S. J.; Collier Cameron, A.; Enoch, B.; Hebb, L.; Horne, K.; Irwin, J.; Joshi, Y. C.; Lister, T. A.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Parley, N.; Segransan, D.; Udry, S.; Wheatley, P. J.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 501, Issue 2, 2009, pp.785-792</journal>
			<date>7/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...501..785G</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.396.1012D</bibcode>
			<title>Evidence for a lost population of close-in exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Davis, Timothy A.; Wheatley, Peter J.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 396, Issue 2, pp. 1012-1017.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.396.1012D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.395.2268B</bibcode>
			<title>On the tidal evolution of Hot Jupiters on inclined orbits</title>
			<authors>Barker, Adrian J.; Ogilvie, Gordon I.</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 395, Issue 4, pp. 2268-2287.</journal>
			<date>6/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.395.2268B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1950B</bibcode>
			<title>HAT-P-10b: A Light and Moderately Hot Jupiter Transiting A K Dwarf</title>
			<authors>Bakos, G. &#193;.; P&#225;l, A.; Torres, G.; Sipocz, B.; Latham, D. W.; Noyes, R. W.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#233;za; Hartman, J.; Esquerdo, G. A.; Fischer, D. A.; Johnson, J. A.; Marcy, G. W.; Butler, R. P.; Howard, A. W.; Sasselov, D. D.; Kov&#225;cs, G&#225;bor; Stefanik, R. P.; L&#225;z&#225;r, J.; Papp, I.; S&#225;ri, P.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1950-1955 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1950B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...696.1230F</bibcode>
			<title>Exoplanetary Spin-Orbit Alignment: Results from the Ensemble of Rossiter-McLaughlin Observations</title>
			<authors>Fabrycky, Daniel C.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 696, Issue 2, pp. 1230-1240 (2009).</journal>
			<date>5/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...696.1230F</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009PASP..121..309J</bibcode>
			<title>International Year of Astronomy Invited Review on Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Johnson, John Asher</authors>
			<journal>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 121, issue 878, pp.309-315</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009PASP..121..309J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...694.1566S</bibcode>
			<title>The Stability and Dynamics of Planets in Tight Binary Systems</title>
			<authors>Saleh, Lamya A.; Rasio, Frederic A.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 694, Issue 2, pp. 1566-1576 (2009).</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...694.1566S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009A&amp;A...498L...5M</bibcode>
			<title>Photometric and spectroscopic detection of the primary transit of the 111-day-period planet HD 80 606 b</title>
			<authors>Moutou, C.; H&#233;brard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Eggenberger, A.; Boisse, I.; Bonfils, X.; Gravallon, D.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 498, Issue 1, 2009, pp.L5-L8</journal>
			<date>4/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009A%26A...498L...5M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009MNRAS.394..272S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - II. Physical properties</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 394, Issue 1, pp. 272-294.</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009MNRAS.394..272S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2009ApJ...693..784M</bibcode>
			<title>Empirical Constraints on Trojan Companions and Orbital Eccentricities in 25 Transiting Exoplanetary Systems</title>
			<authors>Madhusudhan, N.; Winn, Joshua N.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 693, Issue 1, pp. 784-793 (2009).</journal>
			<date>3/2009</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2009ApJ...693..784M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...491..889D</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission . VI. CoRoT-Exo-3b: the first secure inhabitant of the brown-dwarf desert</title>
			<authors>Deleuil, M.; Deeg, H. J.; Alonso, R.; Bouchy, F.; Rouan, D.; Auvergne, M.; Baglin, A.; Aigrain, S.; Almenara, J. M.; Barbieri, M.; Barge, P.; Bruntt, H.; Bord&#233;, P.; Collier Cameron, A.; Csizmadia, Sz.; de La Reza, R.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gandolfi, D.; Gillon, M.; Guenther, E.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; H&#233;brard, G.; Jorda, L.; Lammer, H.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Loeillet, B.; Mayor, M.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Ollivier, M.; P&#228;tzold, M.; Pont, F.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Schneider, J.; Shporer, A.; Wuchterl, G.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 491, Issue 3, 2008, pp.889-897</journal>
			<date>12/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...491..889D</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1339K</bibcode>
			<title>Extrasolar Giant Planets and X-Ray Activity</title>
			<authors>Kashyap, Vinay L.; Drake, Jeremy J.; Saar, Steven H.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1339-1354.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1339K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...687.1191L</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Radii of Extrasolar Giant Planets: the Cases of TrES-4, XO-3b, and HAT-P-1b</title>
			<authors>Liu, Xin; Burrows, Adam; Ibgui, Laurent</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 687, Issue 2, pp. 1191-1200.</journal>
			<date>11/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...687.1191L</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.389..191P</bibcode>
			<title>Periastron precession measurements in transiting extrasolar planetary systems at the level of general relativity</title>
			<authors>P&#225;l, Andr&#225;s; Kocsis, Bence</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 389, Issue 1, pp. 191-198.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.389..191P</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...685..543J</bibcode>
			<title>Observability of the General Relativistic Precession of Periastra in Exoplanets</title>
			<authors>Jord&#225;n, Andr&#233;s; Bakos, G&#225;sp&#225;r &#193;.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 685, Issue 1, pp. 543-552.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...685..543J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...684.1427M</bibcode>
			<title>Thermal Emission of Exoplanet XO-1b</title>
			<authors>Machalek, Pavel; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Burrows, Adam; Hora, Joseph L.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 684, Issue 2, pp. 1427-1432.</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...684.1427M</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488L..43A</bibcode>
			<title>Transiting exoplanets from the CoRoT space mission. IV. CoRoT-Exo-4b: a transiting planet in a 9.2 day synchronous orbit</title>
			<authors>Aigrain, S.; Collier Cameron, A.; Ollivier, M.; Pont, F.; Jorda, L.; Almenara, J. M.; Alonso, R.; Barge, P.; Bord&#233;, P.; Bouchy, F.; Deeg, H.; de La Reza, R.; Deleuil, M.; Dvorak, R.; Erikson, A.; Fridlund, M.; Gondoin, P.; Gillon, M.; Guillot, T.; Hatzes, A.; Lammer, H.; Lanza, A. F.; L&#233;ger, A.; Llebaria, A.; Magain, P.; Mazeh, T.; Moutou, C.; Paetzold, M.; Pinte, C.; Queloz, D.; Rauer, H.; Rouan, D.; Schneider, J.; Wuchter, G.; Zucker, S.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.L43-L46</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488L..43A</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008A&amp;A...488..763H</bibcode>
			<title>Misaligned spin-orbit in the XO-3 planetary system?</title>
			<authors>H&#233;brard, G.; Bouchy, F.; Pont, F.; Loeillet, B.; Rabus, M.; Bonfils, X.; Moutou, C.; Boisse, I.; Delfosse, X.; Desort, M.; Eggenberger, A.; Ehrenreich, D.; Forveille, T.; Lagrange, A.-M.; Lovis, C.; Mayor, M.; Pepe, F.; Perrier, C.; Queloz, D.; Santos, N. C.; S&#233;gransan, D.; Udry, S.; Vidal-Madjar, A.</authors>
			<journal>Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 488, Issue 2, 2008, pp.763-770</journal>
			<date>9/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008A%26A...488..763H</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...683.1076W</bibcode>
			<title>The Transit Light Curve Project. IX. Evidence for a Smaller Radius of the Exoplanet XO-3b</title>
			<authors>Winn, Joshua N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Torres, Guillermo; McCullough, Peter; Johns-Krull, Christopher; Latham, David W.; Shporer, Avi; Mazeh, Tsevi; Garcia-Melendo, Enrique; Foote, Cindy; Esquerdo, Gil; Everett, Mark</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 683, Issue 2, pp. 1076-1084.</journal>
			<date>8/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...683.1076W</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008MNRAS.386.1644S</bibcode>
			<title>Homogeneous studies of transiting extrasolar planets - I. Light-curve analyses</title>
			<authors>Southworth, John</authors>
			<journal>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 386, Issue 3, pp. 1644-1666.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008MNRAS.386.1644S</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...678.1436B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectra and Light Curves of Close-in Extrasolar Giant Planets and Comparison with Data</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Budaj, J.; Hubeny, I.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 678, Issue 2, pp. 1436-1457.</journal>
			<date>5/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...678.1436B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...677..657J</bibcode>
			<title>XO-3b: A Massive Planet in an Eccentric Orbit Transiting an F5 V Star</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; McCullough, Peter R.; Burke, Christopher J.; Valenti, Jeff A.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Prato, L.; Bissinger, R.; Fleenor, M.; Foote, C. N.; Garcia-Melendo, E.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Mallia, F.; Masi, G.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 677, Issue 1, pp. 657-670.</journal>
			<date>4/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...677..657J</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2008ApJ...673..526K</bibcode>
			<title>The 3.6-8.0 mum Broadband Emission Spectrum of HD 209458b: Evidence for an Atmospheric Temperature Inversion</title>
			<authors>Knutson, Heather A.; Charbonneau, David; Allen, Lori E.; Burrows, Adam; Megeath, S. Thomas</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 673, Issue 1, pp. 526-531.</journal>
			<date>1/2008</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2008ApJ...673..526K</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007ApJ...668L.171B</bibcode>
			<title>Theoretical Spectral Models of the Planet HD 209458b with a Thermal Inversion and Water Emission Bands</title>
			<authors>Burrows, A.; Hubeny, I.; Budaj, J.; Knutson, H. A.; Charbonneau, D.</authors>
			<journal>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 668, Issue 2, pp. L171-L174.</journal>
			<date>10/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007ApJ...668L.171B</url>
		</paper>
		<paper>
			<bibcode>2007AAS...210.9605J</bibcode>
			<title>The Unusual Transiting Extra-Solar Planet Orbiting XO-3</title>
			<authors>Johns-Krull, Christopher M.; McCullough, P. M.; Burke, C. J.; Valenti, J. A.; Janes, K. A.; Heasley, J. N.; Bissinger, R.; Fleenor, M.; Foote, C. N.; Garcia-Melendo, E.; Gary, B. L.; Howell, P. J.; Mallia, F.; Masi, G.; Prato, L. A.; Vanmunster, T.</authors>
			<journal>American Astronomical Society Meeting 210, #96.05; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 38, p.225; Bulletin of the American Astronomical Society, Vol. 38, p.225</journal>
			<date>5/2007</date>
			<url>http://adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2007AAS...210.9605J</url>
		</paper>
	</bibliographystar>
</planet>
